<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 20:10:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[A heavily-mutated Covid variant emerges in Southern Africa

Fuck off]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464136788583329792</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464136788583329792</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:35:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Investing vs Trading: What is the easiest way to build wealth?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’ve been investing since February of this year with $26,000 deposited in the
stock market and I’m currently up to $33,014 so I made a 25% profit so far. My
portfolio currently consists of nine stocks. I’ve been looking into options
trading recently which involves high risk but can give high returns…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r24bqb/investing_vs_trading_what_is_the_easiest_way_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r24bqb/investing_vs_trading_what_is_the_easiest_way_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:34:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been investing since February of this year with $26,000 deposited in the stock market and I’m currently up to $33,014 so I made a 25% profit so far. My portfolio currently consists of nine stocks. I’ve been looking into options trading recently which involves high risk but can give high returns if I know what I’m doing. However, investing in established companies is obviously safer but takes longer to build wealth unless I have at least $200,000 in the market, and I can’t afford to deposit anywhere near that amount right now. Between investing in a diverse set of stocks, investing in two or three startup company stocks that may blow up one day, or doing options trading, which of these strategies do you think would be the easiest for building significant wealth within ten years?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thanks for the insurance money]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2pexn/thanks_for_the_insurance_money/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2pexn/thanks_for_the_insurance_money/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:34:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anyone DCA-ing into Disney?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Disney is official well below my average cost of $154. It was at $200 at one
point and now has crashed down to $148. I’ve been steadily buying more shares
but don’t want to fall into the falling knife thing.

Anyone else buying more of Disney? Anything I should be aware of or is this just
a covid…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2qwft/anyone_dcaing_into_disney/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2qwft/anyone_dcaing_into_disney/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 18:49:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disney is official well below my average cost of $154. It was at $200 at one point and now has crashed down to $148. I’ve been steadily buying more shares but don’t want to fall into the falling knife thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone else buying more of Disney? Anything I should be aware of or is this just a covid scare?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Happy BlackFriday from a Vietnamese retard! Should I sell or hold my MRNA calls?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2orio/happy_blackfriday_from_a_vietnamese_retard_should/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2orio/happy_blackfriday_from_a_vietnamese_retard_should/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 18:49:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ima just post this in hopes of the market turning green.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2oe7s/ima_just_post_this_in_hopes_of_the_market_turning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2oe7s/ima_just_post_this_in_hopes_of_the_market_turning/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 17:48:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is the impact of Intel returning to the GPU market on Nvidia being underestimated?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have noticed that most people on here are very bullish towards Nvidia even at
its current valuation but I haven't seen much talk about how Intel's return to
the GPU market will affect Nvidia's valuation and future growth.

Intel has the money and talent especially with Raja Koduri leading the…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2l9n8/is_the_impact_of_intel_returning_to_the_gpu/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2l9n8/is_the_impact_of_intel_returning_to_the_gpu/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 17:48:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have noticed that most people on here are very bullish towards Nvidia even at its current valuation but I haven&amp;#39;t seen much talk about how Intel&amp;#39;s return to the GPU market will affect Nvidia&amp;#39;s valuation and future growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intel has the money and talent especially with Raja Koduri leading the Graphics department to become highly competitive with Nvidia if not a leader in the market. Intel will also have the advantage of using their new fabs in the future to produce their GPU&amp;#39;s whereas Nvidia will be reliant on TSMC/Samsung.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With AMD also becoming more competitive and both Intel and AMD not being as limited to just the GPU market unlike Nvidia, should people be worried that Nvidia may have to lower profit margins and suffer from lower growth that could make their current price look extremely high?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For disclosure I do own some INTC and would be interested in NVDA if the valuation was more reasonable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NVDA calls are ready to F*ck me today]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2iqrz/nvda_calls_are_ready_to_fck_me_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2iqrz/nvda_calls_are_ready_to_fck_me_today/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 17:34:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is your view on UIPath right now?]]></title><description><![CDATA[The stock has dropped 34% since it IPO'd this year and the market cap has
dropped $10 billion. I have been considering picking up some shares recently and
after seeing their recent earnings I understand that they are not profitable
because they have been dramatically increasing their R&D plus…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r25k25/what_is_your_view_on_uipath_right_now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r25k25/what_is_your_view_on_uipath_right_now/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 17:05:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The stock has dropped 34% since it IPO&amp;#39;d this year and the market cap has dropped $10 billion. I have been considering picking up some shares recently and after seeing their recent earnings I understand that they are not profitable because they have been dramatically increasing their R&amp;amp;D plus Marketing Spend even though Revenues are increasing a good amount.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Research report on DraftKings ($DKNG)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey all, I’d appreciate it if someone could take a look at my equity research
report and provide some feedback or discussion. Thanks! -a college freshman
interested in Equity research

https://www.theancienteconomist.com/post/draftkings-dkng-equity-research-report

DraftKings is regarded as one of…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r28h7w/research_report_on_draftkings_dkng/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r28h7w/research_report_on_draftkings_dkng/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 15:47:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey all, I’d appreciate it if someone could take a look at my equity research report and provide some feedback or discussion.
Thanks! -a college freshman interested in Equity research&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theancienteconomist.com/post/draftkings-dkng-equity-research-report&quot;&gt;https://www.theancienteconomist.com/post/draftkings-dkng-equity-research-report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DraftKings is regarded as one of the current leaders of the sports gambling indus- try. The company, since its founding in 2012, has obtained lucrative partnering agree- ments with the biggest players in sports and entertainment, establishing contracts with MLB, NFL, NASCAR, UFC, ESPN, 21st Century Fox Sports, and Bleacher Report. DraftK- ings offers live daily fantasy contests for over 13 sports. The online sports gambling in- dustry has huge growth potential, which has yielded a large number of competitors to spring up, such as Penn National Gaming (NASDAQ: $PENN), fuboTV (NYSE: $FUBO), and Flutter Entertainment (OTCMKTS: $PDYPY). Despite the lure of the sports gambling industry, the bearish case for DraftKings lies in waiting for a further correction before in- vesting due to competitive pressure, limited growth, and their profitability track record.
The quality of services is critical in determining the long-term growth and customer retainment for a firm, especially within the gaming sector. DraftKings’ narrow yet compact focus on live online sports betting limits their presence in the overall gam- bling industry, as opposed to other firms such as Penn National Gaming, which employs a generalist approach to available services. Penn, in addition to sports and casino style bet- ting, is a large operator of casino and resort locations. This versatility in gambling ser- vices could provide greater growth in a post-COVID world less reliant on virtual gaming, which DraftKings does not offer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Be greedy when others are fearful. Be fearful when others are greedy.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Looks like all of the markets are going to take a shit on the news of the new
Covid variant. Funny thing about the news on that, it is simply the new strain
is heavily mutated and we don’t know if that’s bad. We should see this as an
opportunity to buy more stocks at a discount. This happened…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2lpz7/be_greedy_when_others_are_fearful_be_fearful_when/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2lpz7/be_greedy_when_others_are_fearful_be_fearful_when/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 15:27:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looks like all of the markets are going to take a shit on the news of the new Covid variant. Funny thing about the news on that, it is simply the new strain is heavily mutated and we don’t know if that’s bad. We should see this as an opportunity to buy more stocks at a discount. This happened earlier in the year and most stocks have recovered since then. Just like the Warren Buffett quote in the title. Sure everyone’s portfolio is red at the moment. Some people see the red and panic, I see a green opportunity on the horizon. Someone else once said, “scared money don’t make money”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dow futures plunge 400 points amid fears of new Covid variant found in South Africa]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2e6ss/dow_futures_plunge_400_points_amid_fears_of_new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2e6ss/dow_futures_plunge_400_points_amid_fears_of_new/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 13:31:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gotta print them all 💵]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2jd98/gotta_print_them_all/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2jd98/gotta_print_them_all/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 13:31:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What are you buying when the market opens??]]></title><description><![CDATA[As everyone knows, futures are bloody red right now on fears of a new variant.
There are really two things you should do when things open and that is nothing,
or buy. Do not sell in these conditions because I guarantee you will regret it.

With that being said…if you are in the buy group, what are…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2ivb9/what_are_you_buying_when_the_market_opens/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2ivb9/what_are_you_buying_when_the_market_opens/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 13:05:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As everyone knows, futures are bloody red right now on fears of a new variant. There are really two things you should do when things open and that is nothing, or buy. Do not sell in these conditions because I guarantee you will regret it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said…if you are in the buy group, what are you looking at when the markets open?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m looking at tech: APPLE, AMAZON and MSFT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dow futures plunge 800 points amid fears of new Covid variant found in South Africa]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/26/stock-futures-open-to-close-market-news.html

> U.S. stock futures dropped in early morning trading on Friday as investors
> geared up for a shortened trading day amid renewed Covid fears over a new
> variant found in South Africa.
> 
> Futures for the Dow Jones…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2ko1v/dow_futures_plunge_800_points_amid_fears_of_new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2ko1v/dow_futures_plunge_800_points_amid_fears_of_new/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 12:39:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/26/stock-futures-open-to-close-market-news.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/26/stock-futures-open-to-close-market-news.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;U.S. stock futures dropped in early morning trading on Friday as investors geared up for a shortened trading day amid renewed Covid fears over a new variant found in South Africa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Futures for the Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 800 points, while those for the S&amp;amp;P 500 and Nasdaq 100 were also in in negative territory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The downward moves came after WHO officials on Thursday warned of a new Covid-19 variant that&amp;#39;s been detected in South Africa. The United Kingdom temporarily suspended flights from six African countries due to the variant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bond yields tumbled amid the flight to safety. The yield on the benchmark U.S. 10-year Treasury note fell to 1.5380%, a sharp reversal after surging above 1.65% earlier this week. Bond yields move inversely to prices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oil prices also tumbled, with U.S. crude futures down 6.2% to $73.57 per barrel, while the South African rand weakened 1.7% against the greenback to 16.231 per dollar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Asia markets were hit hard in Friday trade, with Japan&amp;#39;s Nikkei 225 and Hong Kong&amp;#39;s Hang Seng index both falling more than 2% each.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Asian markets sink as investors weigh latest global virus concerns]]></title><description><![CDATA[Asian stock markets sank Friday after some European countries tightened curbs on
travel and business following a surge in coronavirus infections and South Africa
reported a new variant. Shanghai, Tokyo, Hong Kong and Sydney declined. U.S.
markets were closed Thursday for the Thanksgiving holiday.…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2g92r/asian_markets_sink_as_investors_weigh_latest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2g92r/asian_markets_sink_as_investors_weigh_latest/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 11:35:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asian stock markets sank Friday after some European countries tightened curbs on travel and business following a surge in coronavirus infections and South Africa reported a new variant. Shanghai, Tokyo, Hong Kong and Sydney declined. U.S. markets were closed Thursday for the Thanksgiving holiday. Austria imposed a nationwide 10-day lockdown after its daily virus deaths tripled, while Italy imposed curbs on activity by unvaccinated people. The U.S. government advised Americans to avoid travel to Germany and Denmark. Scientists in South Africa said a new variant was spreading among young people in its most populous province.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Investors are likely to shoot first and ask questions later until more is known,” Jeffrey Halley of Oanda said in a report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Shanghai Composite Index CN:SHCOMP lost 0.6% to 3,560.15 and the Nikkei 225 JP:NIK NIY00 in Tokyo plunged by an unusually wide 2.8% margin to 28,656.17. The Hang Seng HK:HSI in Hong Kong tumbled 2.3% to 24,161.55. The Kospi KR:180721 in Seoul lost 1.4% to 2,938.09 and Sydney’s S&amp;amp;P-ASX 200 AU:XJO fell 1.7% to 7,279. New Zealand and Southeast Asian markets also declined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wall Street’s benchmark S&amp;amp;P 500 SPX closed up 0.2% on Wednesday. U.S. markets are due to reopen Friday for a shortened post-Thanksgiving trading session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/asian-markets-sink-as-investors-weigh-latest-global-virus-concerns-01637900804?mod=mw_quote_news&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/asian-markets-sink-as-investors-weigh-latest-global-virus-concerns-01637900804?mod=mw_quote_news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What are my options since China is pushing Didi to delist from the US?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I own a small amount of Didi shares. China has asked Didi to delist from the US
over security fears. What are my options?

I use ME by BofA to trade stocks. They don't allow trading of securities that
trade over-the-counter.

Should I take a wait and see approach or offload immediately?

I've read…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2dmfx/what_are_my_options_since_china_is_pushing_didi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2dmfx/what_are_my_options_since_china_is_pushing_didi/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 10:11:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I own a small amount of Didi shares.  China has asked Didi to delist from the US over security fears.  What are my options?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use ME by BofA to trade stocks.  They don&amp;#39;t allow trading of securities that trade over-the-counter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should I take a wait and see approach or offload immediately?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve read that if privatization were to occur, it would be at the $14 IPO price.  The stock closed at $8.11 on Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If they were to delist, how would I go about trading the stock?  Or is it just considered a total loss?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How will Nu covid variant affect the markets compared to the Delta variant?]]></title><description><![CDATA[First issues with the Nu variant -

 * B.1.1.529, to be named Nu
 * 32 mutations in spike protein
 * Earliest known case: South Africa, Nov. 12
 * Fears it could be more transmissible, evade immunity
 * UK & Israel impose travel bans
 * SA reports 2,465 new cases, up 321% from last week

According…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2e5iy/how_will_nu_covid_variant_affect_the_markets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2e5iy/how_will_nu_covid_variant_affect_the_markets/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 06:52:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;First issues with the Nu variant -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.1.1.529, to be named Nu&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;32 mutations in spike protein&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earliest known case: South Africa, Nov. 12&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fears it could be more transmissible, evade immunity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UK &amp;amp; Israel impose travel bans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SA reports 2,465 new cases, up 321% from last week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According here &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/drericding/status/1463998740340121601?s=21&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/drericding/status/1463998740340121601?s=21&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost double the mutations as delta&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Was vaccine resistant as people tested were double vaccinated with Pfizer (but did not have 3rd booster) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WHO already emergency meeting and UK and Israel have shut down flights coming from 6 nations. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biggest issue is that the new variant is VACCINE RESISTANT which seems awful long term unless people are really going to attempt to get us to take brand new vaccine shots in 3-4 months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[South African scientists detect new coronavirus variant amid spike in cases. Futures down bad at the moment…]]></title><description><![CDATA[What are your thoughts? I couldn’t link any articles due to mods and rules, but
do a quick search online.

Will retails lose their cold blood? I think a lot of people on margin will eat
their socks in the next days…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2eo5e/south_african_scientists_detect_new_coronavirus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2eo5e/south_african_scientists_detect_new_coronavirus/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 06:30:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What are your thoughts? I couldn’t link any articles due to mods and rules, but do a quick search online. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will retails lose their cold blood? I think a lot of people on margin will eat their socks in the next days…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can I fund a Roth IRA with money that I had previously put into a regular brokerage?]]></title><description><![CDATA[If this has been addressed, please let me know. I have googled and searched
through this sub and can’t seem to find an answer to my question.

I didn’t contribute enough to my Roth this year and want to reach the $6000
maximum. The problem is that my income went into my brokerage and I’m…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2ddl7/can_i_fund_a_roth_ira_with_money_that_i_had/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2ddl7/can_i_fund_a_roth_ira_with_money_that_i_had/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 05:22:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If this has been addressed, please let me know. I have googled and searched through this sub and can’t seem to find an answer to my question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t contribute enough to my Roth this year and want to reach the $6000 maximum. The problem is that my income went into my brokerage and I’m concerned about how it may look to the IRS if I withdraw money from my brokerage and deposit into my Roth. This money would not be in surplus to what I deposited into my brokerage. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The IRS website just says that the money used to fund it has to be earned wages, but doesn’t go into further depth. Is it still “earned” if I’m just withdrawing money that I had earned and churned through some day trades? Am I over thinking this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any answer is appreciated and thank you for your time&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[China Asks Didi to Delist From U.S. On Security Fears]]></title><description><![CDATA[(Bloomberg) -- Chinese regulators have asked Didi Global Inc.’s top executives
to devise a plan to delist from U.S. bourses, people familiar with the matter
said, an unprecedented request that’s likely to revive fears about Beijing’s
intentions for its giant tech industry.

The country’s tech…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2d32w/china_asks_didi_to_delist_from_us_on_security/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2d32w/china_asks_didi_to_delist_from_us_on_security/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 04:43:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Chinese regulators have asked Didi Global Inc.’s top executives to devise a plan to delist from U.S. bourses, people familiar with the matter said, an unprecedented request that’s likely to revive fears about Beijing’s intentions for its giant tech industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The country’s tech watchdog wants management to take the company off the New York Stock Exchange because of concerns about leakage of sensitive data, the people said, asking not to be identified discussing a sensitive matter. The Cyberspace Administration of China, the agency responsible for data security in the country, has directed Didi to work out precise details, subject to government approval, they said. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proposals under consideration include a straight-up privatization or a share float in Hong Kong followed by a delisting from the U.S., the people added. If the privatization proceeds, the proposal will likely be at least the $14 IPO price since a lower offer so soon after the June initial public offering could prompt lawsuits or shareholder resistance, the people said. If there is a secondary listing in Hong Kong, the IPO price would probably be a discount to the share price in the U.S., $8.11 as of Wednesday’s close. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shares in SoftBank Group Corp., Didi’s biggest minority shareholder, slid more than 5% in Tokyo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deliberations continue and it’s possible regulators will backtrack on their request, the people said. Either option would deal a severe blow to a ride-hailing giant that pulled off the largest U.S. IPO by a Chinese firm since Alibaba Group Holding Ltd.’s in 2014. Representatives for Didi and the CAC didn’t respond to requests for comment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi sparked the ire of Beijing when it proceeded with its New York stock offering this summer, despite regulatory requests that it ensure the security of its data before the IPO. Chinese regulators quickly launched multiple investigations into the company and have considered a range of unprecedented penalties, Bloomberg News reported in July. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s possible that the delisting would be part of a package of punishments for Didi. Beijing’s municipal government has proposed an investment in the company that would give state-run firms effective control, Bloomberg News reported in September. Such an investment could help Didi finance the repurchase of its U.S.-traded shares. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi is currently controlled by the management team of co-founder Cheng Wei and President Jean Liu, which received aggregate voting power of 58% after the company’s U.S. initial public offering. SoftBank and Uber Technologies Inc. are Didi’s biggest minority shareholders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if Didi shifts its listing to Hong Kong, it will have to address the data security concerns that have drawn regulatory scrutiny. The company may have to give up control of its data to a third-party -- again undercutting its price tag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regulators have weighed a delisting for Didi since the summer, after the world’s largest ride-hailing company infuriated officials by ploughing ahead with its U.S. IPO, Bloomberg News has reported. A withdrawal from U.S. bourses could stoke fears of an exodus of Chinese firms as Washington and Beijing quarrel about access to listed firms’ books. On Thursday, a senior Chinese regulatory official said such delistings would be a setback for relations with the U.S., while offering broad support for Hong Kong as an alternative venue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi -- once feted for defeating Uber in China -- has now become a test case for a broader Chinese government effort to curb the power of internet titans. Xi Jinping’s administration, keen to promote his vision of sharing the wealth or “common prosperity,” has targeted an internet sector that’s accumulated vast wealth by operating on the periphery of the law, minted an unprecedented number of billionaires and enriched local and foreign investors in the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A state-directed privatization would be unprecedented for a private firm of Didi’s stature, affirming that the Chinese government remains bent on curtailing the power of the country’s internet firms and unlocking the data and wealth hoarded during a decade of heady expansion. It would send a chilling signal to American investors, long accustomed to investing freely in China’s largest corporations from Alibaba to Baidu Inc. and JD.com Inc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beijing’s moves against Didi have been particularly harsh, even after a crackdown that has penalized giants like Alibaba and Tencent Holdings Ltd. The Cyberspace Administration of China saw Didi’s IPO decision as a challenge to the central government’s authority, which led to the CAC, the Ministry of Public Security, the Ministry of State Security and several other agencies initiating on-site inspections at Didi’s offices in July.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s since been ensnared by probes into data security and the way it treats its millions of drivers. Many of the options Beijing is weighing involve re-asserting state control over a company that’s traditionally operated in a legal gray zone, Bloomberg News has reported.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/china-asks-didi-to-delist-from-u-s-on-security-fears-1.1687281&quot;&gt;https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/china-asks-didi-to-delist-from-u-s-on-security-fears-1.1687281&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Costco (COST) - Why does it just keep running?]]></title><description><![CDATA[COST has gone on a ridiculous run this year, breaking out of the 300s and
leaping now well into the 500s. I grabbed 10 shares when I started investing in
April because I knew it was a profitable company that’s well-run with a solid
loyal customer base, but never in my wildest dreams did I expect it…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2advu/costco_cost_why_does_it_just_keep_running/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2advu/costco_cost_why_does_it_just_keep_running/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 03:37:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;COST has gone on a ridiculous run this year, breaking out of the 300s and leaping now well into the 500s. I grabbed 10 shares when I started investing in April because I knew it was a profitable company that’s well-run with a solid loyal customer base, but never in my wildest dreams did I expect it to go on this kind of run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone find any reasons that COST is climbing like this? Seemingly not even the September correction could slow it down (unlike in March).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[About to be 18 next year, need some advices…]]></title><description><![CDATA[My goal is to learn to develop a good perception of money/investing/common
social systems (banks, etc which are country dependent) and apply my knowledge
to achieve financial independence and maybe develop businesses or just be aware
of these things at an early age (any suggested topics which might…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2367p/about_to_be_18_next_year_need_some_advices/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2367p/about_to_be_18_next_year_need_some_advices/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 02:38:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My goal is to learn to develop a good perception of money/investing/common social systems (banks, etc which are country dependent) and apply my knowledge to achieve financial independence and maybe develop businesses or  just be aware of these things at an early age (any suggested topics which might be useful to know at 18/19 are welcome)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m willing to read any novels/books regarding this… though I have 0 idea of commercial studies etc since I picked sciences as subjects at 16…so I don’t know basic stuff about accounting/economics (though I can read about it if required)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-with all these currency, stocks etc which I currently have no idea about, which one should I approach and what mentality should I keep before approaching these things? What books/sources do you recommend to gain knowledge about these things?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Please recommend any books which can help me develop my perception of money, maybe learn about investing/stocks, or which can help me develop my understanding of basic social systems like banks etc (if required) 
[ive only read basic books like rich dad, poor dad  etc but I don’t have formal knowledge regarding these in any way…]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-ANY general advice, maybe mistakes you made in early stage, any miscellaneous books or knowledge about the topics (like budgeting etc) you think are beneficial for me are welcome… go all out…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks in advance&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit- thank you all for the advices… I’ll take a ss and will review each advice and try my best to follow the suggestions the moment my entrance exams are done (assuming I go to a good uni, seems likely)
Thank you all again for the lists, I will save them 100%%%&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anyone Boglehead through the dot com bubble? That would be over 7 years of staying the course. I'm not sure I would be able to hang in there]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2a7be/anyone_boglehead_through_the_dot_com_bubble_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2a7be/anyone_boglehead_through_the_dot_com_bubble_that/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 02:01:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Took a line of credit to YOLO, suggestions anyone?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r23rx6/took_a_line_of_credit_to_yolo_suggestions_anyone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r23rx6/took_a_line_of_credit_to_yolo_suggestions_anyone/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 00:58:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[About sums it up]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r280jm/about_sums_it_up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r280jm/about_sums_it_up/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 23:54:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is your most speculative stock?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Give me them pre-revenue SPACs, the unprofitable pennies, and the sleeping
giants at their 52 week lows. I'm looking for those 100x opportunities with the
0x possibility. Shill me your heaviest bag that you are still adding too and
believe in. Make me feel fomo for not investing in your moonshot…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r260wh/what_is_your_most_speculative_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r260wh/what_is_your_most_speculative_stock/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 23:54:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Give me them pre-revenue SPACs, the unprofitable pennies, and the sleeping giants at their 52 week lows. I&amp;#39;m looking for those 100x opportunities with the 0x possibility. Shill me your heaviest bag that you are still adding too and believe in. Make me feel fomo for not investing in your moonshot tech stock. I&amp;#39;ll go first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$BLGO&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BioLargo OTC $.20&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These guys are basically pre-revenue, but they have spent the last few years making a water filtration system for PFAS&amp;#39;s. If the stars align just right with the EPA declaring PFAS a hazardous material and their tech works as advertised they are looking to lead a $180B industry. They also have a consumer product releasing soon called Pooph. It&amp;#39;s an anti smell cleaning product which could bring in a good amount of steady revenue in 2022. Management seems to have their head on straight and be focused on the right things. All in all definitely worth the ~2% of my portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bogleheads in Europe]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello dear Bogleheads friends, specially the European ones.

I really want to get into the 3-way portfolio, but the book looks really like
it´s for US folks. A few questions:

- Do you invest in sp500 or SPY? or Similar funds/ETFs in EU? Do you consider EU
80% or US as 80% of stocks?

- Which…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r26hx5/bogleheads_in_europe/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r26hx5/bogleheads_in_europe/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 23:42:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello dear  Bogleheads friends, specially the European ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really want to get into the 3-way portfolio, but the book looks really like it´s for US  folks. A few questions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Do you invest in sp500 or SPY? or Similar funds/ETFs in EU? Do you consider EU 80% or US as 80% of stocks?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Which brokers you use in Europe for low commissions?  Any idea how taxes works? I´m in Portugal&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Overall indexes funds are better here or ETFs?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any literature or anything else would be much appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hey at least we're cool]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r25vz2/hey_at_least_were_cool/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r25vz2/hey_at_least_were_cool/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 23:27:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Price targets are bullshit. like $ETSY.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Check out this bullshit.

> On November 4, Needham adjusted price target on etsy to $265 from $250, keeps
> buy rating.
> 
> On November 22, Needham raises price target on etsy to $325 from $265, keeps
> buy rating.



what the fuck has fundamentally changed in 18 days???

keep your original price…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r25dz0/price_targets_are_bullshit_like_etsy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r25dz0/price_targets_are_bullshit_like_etsy/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 23:05:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out this bullshit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On November 4, Needham adjusted price target on etsy to $265 from $250, keeps buy rating.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On November 22, Needham raises price target on etsy to $325 from $265, keeps buy rating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;what the fuck has fundamentally changed in 18 days???&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;keep your original price target, and stick to it. Stop raising the damn price target just because the stock price is being pumped up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is like a gamma squeeze. assholes are just pumping stocks for no reason, and people are gonna get burned when the whales pull the rug.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Billionaires are cashing out at these all time highs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I have no positions in etsy&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WSB DnD alignment chart]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r23ba1/wsb_dnd_alignment_chart/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r23ba1/wsb_dnd_alignment_chart/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 22:37:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Legality of managing an investment club with friends]]></title><description><![CDATA[A group of friends and I have been investing for awhile and each of us has their
own 'area' they focus on. In general for you own portion of capital in a sector
you will defer to the opinion of the 'specialist' on where to invest it, and
they to you for whatever you specialize in. There are also…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2043j/legality_of_managing_an_investment_club_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2043j/legality_of_managing_an_investment_club_with/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 22:19:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A group of friends and I have been investing for awhile and each of us has their own &amp;#39;area&amp;#39; they focus on. In general for you own portion of capital in a sector you will defer to the opinion of the &amp;#39;specialist&amp;#39; on where to invest it, and they to you for whatever you specialize in. There are also friends who follow along with us but do not have the time to research anything and so do not provide insights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This got us thinking, wouldn&amp;#39;t it be convenient to just pool our money in a club and let everyone handle their specialty independently but the effects would be felt collectively. John handles all the healthcare investments, Brian the banking, Steve the tech, etc. From what I have read on investment clubs its pretty clear that those who would actually manage investments can all form a club together and we wouldn&amp;#39;t need any sort of licensing. The question comes in with the silent members who do not research or invest themselves. If we had 4 people making the decisions and 6 whose money was in the partnership but they made no input, would this mean the 4 &amp;#39;managers&amp;#39; need licensing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, if we were to divide the partnership in a way that the active members received more through ownership means, would this break the rules for an investment club? Ex: Brain and Steve form an investment club and both contribute $50,000. Brain manages and makes all investment decisions so he gets a 60% interest in the LLC while Steve gets 40%. From my own understanding and research it seems this should be allowed under &amp;#39;sweat equity&amp;#39; rules but I know investing is subject to special stipulations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And yes, I am aware of the old &amp;#39;never invest your friends money&amp;#39; saying but we are all adults&amp;#39; with experience and this represents a tiny fraction of each of our net worth&amp;#39;s. Appreciate any input!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Markets are closed today. Happy Thanksgiving! 🦃🍽🍁 https://t.co/gd1nJWKToH]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1463871698948829193</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1463871698948829193</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 21:42:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Next promising tech stock?!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey guys,

unfortunately I missed the promising tech stocks like $net $ttd $okta $crwd in
their early days and now the valuations seem a bit high for me regarding the
risk/return profile.

So I would like to ask if you are watching any promising tech stock right now?
Maybe one that is still a bit…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r21tcj/next_promising_tech_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r21tcj/next_promising_tech_stock/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 21:30:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey guys,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;unfortunately I missed the promising tech stocks like $net $ttd $okta $crwd in their early days and now the valuations seem a bit high for me regarding the risk/return profile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I would like to ask if you are watching any promising tech stock right now? Maybe one that is still a bit under the radar like the ones I mentioned where few years ago?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What tech/IT related sources you use to get information about these kind of stocks first?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wish blocked in France: 95% of products do not comply with EU legislation. Google must remove it from searches]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r1yabs/wish_blocked_in_france_95_of_products_do_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r1yabs/wish_blocked_in_france_95_of_products_do_not/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 21:13:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Looking back at R/Stock users predictions]]></title><description><![CDATA[Last year I made a post telling Reddit/stock users to predict the best
performing stock of 2021, and the answers were very interesting to say the
least. There was a lot of Tesla, Alibaba, Palantir, Cloudflare, Sea Limited,
etc.

It's always interesting to look back and see how hard it is to predict…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r21761/looking_back_at_rstock_users_predictions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r21761/looking_back_at_rstock_users_predictions/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 20:25:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year I made a post telling Reddit/stock users to predict the best performing stock of 2021, and the answers were very interesting to say the least. There was a lot of Tesla, Alibaba, Palantir, Cloudflare, Sea Limited, etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s always interesting to look back and see how hard it is to predict things in the stock market. Alot of mentioned stocks are still down for the year. Oh and btw the reward will be given out early next year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/kgtgh6/predict_the_best_performing_stock_of_2021_and/&quot;&gt;Predict the best performing stock of 2021 and receive a reward. : stocks (reddit.com)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Me looking at my portfolio this days.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r1y9y8/me_looking_at_my_portfolio_this_days/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r1y9y8/me_looking_at_my_portfolio_this_days/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 19:58:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A "Lost Decade" Case For Diversification]]></title><description><![CDATA[Death knells aplenty in the noise: Market's looking frothy, right? Big crash
around the corner? Everything could get slammed and stay there! You don't want
to baghold through a lost decade like 2000-2010, right?

Peter Mallouk's book "The Five Mistakes Every Investor Makes" examines how
different…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r1qgr1/a_lost_decade_case_for_diversification/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r1qgr1/a_lost_decade_case_for_diversification/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 19:20:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Death knells aplenty in the noise: Market&amp;#39;s looking frothy, right? Big crash around the corner? Everything could get slammed and stay there! You don&amp;#39;t want to baghold through a lost decade like 2000-2010, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Peter Mallouk&amp;#39;s book &amp;quot;The Five Mistakes Every Investor Makes&amp;quot; examines how different sectors performed during that period. To wit, between 2000 and 2010, the following sectors performed as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Large-Cap US: 0.00%*
Mid-Cap US: +64.73%
Small-Cap US: +78.76%
International: +134.39%
Emerging Markets: +437.36%
Real Estate: +228.19%
Bonds: +175.73%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reach for total market, world market, emerging markets, is what I see. Not sure which exact bonds and real estate markets are included in Mallouk&amp;#39;s analysis, but bonds in general are useful portfolio ballast, and real estate is included in diversified indexes by default.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*The book acknowledges that if an S&amp;amp;P 500 investor reinvested dividends, they actually came out of that crater a few percentage points ahead!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Difference between DCA and “catching a falling knife?”]]></title><description><![CDATA[Curious to get everyone’s take on this as it popped into my mind last night and
I realized I’m not totally sure of the distinction between the two.

It’s common advice or strategy to DCA a stock you believe in when its value
drops.

It’s also common advice to not try to catch a falling knife by…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r1vo9a/difference_between_dca_and_catching_a_falling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r1vo9a/difference_between_dca_and_catching_a_falling/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 18:48:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Curious to get everyone’s take on this as it popped into my mind last night and I realized I’m not totally sure of the distinction between the two. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s common advice or strategy to DCA a stock you believe in when its value drops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s also common advice to not try to catch a falling knife by buying into a stock on the way down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s the distinction between the two or how do you differentiate?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My Boglehead Retirement Makeover]]></title><description><![CDATA[So I just though I would share what I have put together based on the advice of
this forum and my own thinking. My retirement portfolio was portfolio was a mess
using all kinds of ETFs. I had my emergency fund invested and no Roth. Here's
where I'm at now.

Emergency Fund: 3 months cash 3 months I…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r1h1u2/my_boglehead_retirement_makeover/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r1h1u2/my_boglehead_retirement_makeover/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 18:48:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I just though I would share what I have put together based on the advice of this forum and my own thinking. My retirement portfolio was portfolio was a mess using all kinds of ETFs. I had my emergency fund invested and no Roth. Here&amp;#39;s where I&amp;#39;m at now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Emergency Fund: 3 months cash 3 months I-bonds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;401k: BlackRock LifePath Target Date Fund (+5 years to target date to be more aggressive).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roth: Fidelity Freedom Target Date Fund &amp;quot;Most Aggressive&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taxable: 4 Fund Portfolio (VTI/VXUS/BND/BNDX)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s it and I&amp;#39;m hoping this simple formula will get me through a long and happy life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: I will reevaluate my equity and bond holdings at my retirement date, as the TDFs get too bond heavy for what I&amp;#39;m looking for during retirement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy Holidays Fellow Bogleheads!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Inflation isn't real]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r1v4rc/inflation_isnt_real/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r1v4rc/inflation_isnt_real/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 18:28:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anti ARK ETF about to explode?]]></title><description><![CDATA[What is Anti ARK ETF? Ticker: $SARK

> The fund is an actively managed exchange traded fund that attempts to achieve
> the inverse (-1x) of the return of the ETF for a single day, not for any other
> period, by entering into a swap agreement on the ETF. The ARK Innovation ETF
> is an actively…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r1vjvr/anti_ark_etf_about_to_explode/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r1vjvr/anti_ark_etf_about_to_explode/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 16:59:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is Anti ARK ETF? Ticker: $SARK&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fund is an actively managed exchange traded fund that attempts to achieve the inverse (-1x) of the return of the ETF for a single day, not for any other period, by entering into a swap agreement on the ETF. The ARK Innovation ETF is an actively managed ETF that seeks long-term growth of capital by investing primarily in domestic and foreign equity securities of companies that are relevant to the fund&amp;#39;s investment theme of disruptive innovation. It is non-diversified.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s been a tough year to be a Cathie Wood  ARKK investor. It has been slowly but steadily losing ground throughout much of 2021, with ARK Innovation falling about 15% year to date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently Cathie Wood says her firm is testing a more aggressive strategy that would be ‘ARK on steroids’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would you see this this as an opportunity for Anti ARK?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Should I continue averaging down Alibaba (Ticker: BABA) if it's already a substantial holding and my largest position?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm still bullish on Alibaba long term relative to it's current valuation
inspite of the challenges it currently faces.

Unfortunately I didn't DCA and instead did a big lump sum investment at $230~
(statistically lump sum is better, except for when I invest xD). I manage to
average down to $200 but…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r1sl8l/should_i_continue_averaging_down_alibaba_ticker/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r1sl8l/should_i_continue_averaging_down_alibaba_ticker/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 16:59:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m still bullish on Alibaba long term relative to it&amp;#39;s current valuation inspite of the challenges it currently faces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately I didn&amp;#39;t DCA and instead did a big lump sum investment at $230~ (statistically lump sum is better, except for when I invest xD). I manage to average down to $200 but it&amp;#39;s still far away from the current price of $136~, I want to continue to average down since I think it&amp;#39;s still very attractive valuation for the risk vs reward but it&amp;#39;s already my biggest holding and makes up 21-24% of my portfolio alone, adding in JD, my China risk is already at 30-33% of my entire portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On one hand I want to continue to average down because I think it&amp;#39;s a bargain and it&amp;#39;s a big difference from my cost basis but on the other hand, it&amp;#39;s already a very substantial position in my portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you guys reckon I do?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[25 Chinese Stocks On the Brink of Automatic Delisting From the US]]></title><description><![CDATA[China’s attempts to prevent hundreds of its companies from being delisted from
US stock exchanges may come too late for 25 that have seen their share prices
plunge too close to or below $1 per share.

Both the New York Stock Exchange and Nasdaq begin an automatic delisting process
when a company’s…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r1wlt4/25_chinese_stocks_on_the_brink_of_automatic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r1wlt4/25_chinese_stocks_on_the_brink_of_automatic/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 15:38:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;China’s attempts to prevent hundreds of its companies from being delisted from US stock exchanges may come too late for 25 that have seen their share prices plunge too close to or below $1 per share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both the New York Stock Exchange and Nasdaq begin an automatic delisting process when a company’s share price falls below $1 for more than 30 business days. The companies are given six months to come back in line with exchange rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.asiafinancial.com/chinese-stocks-delisted&quot;&gt;https://www.asiafinancial.com/chinese-stocks-delisted&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[#TBT Dr. PP at it again.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r1v7jy/tbt_dr_pp_at_it_again/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r1v7jy/tbt_dr_pp_at_it_again/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 13:37:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The only way to do it baby]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r1b4e5/the_only_way_to_do_it_baby/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r1b4e5/the_only_way_to_do_it_baby/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 13:19:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[When you’ve been thinking about it all wrong …]]></title><description><![CDATA[I started following the Bogelhead approach a few years ago, so I’ve known for a
while to steer clear of actively managed funds and money managers that charge
AUM fees.

My parents have some friends that work in wealth management that are very well
off. When I was growing up, I thought these people…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r1qad1/when_youve_been_thinking_about_it_all_wrong/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r1qad1/when_youve_been_thinking_about_it_all_wrong/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 12:17:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I started following the Bogelhead approach a few years ago, so I’ve known for a while to steer clear of actively managed funds and money managers that charge AUM fees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My parents have some friends that work in wealth management that are very well off. When I was growing up, I thought these people must be great investors and that’d probably made some great investments for themselves that made them wealthy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It hit me today — decades later — that the most likely reason these people are so rich is because they’re literally just raking in fees from managing other people’s money. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pretty sketchy profession now that I actually think about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[6-figure loss achieved]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r1gtf1/6figure_loss_achieved/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r1gtf1/6figure_loss_achieved/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 09:26:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hit me $BB 🍇 one more time! (Papa Chen about to close BlackBerry's billion dollar patent sale and launch Amazon IVY connected car)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi Everyone,

BlackBerry is set to have a parabolic run over the next few weeks/months with
many upcoming catalysts! Below is my analysis of why I think the stock is going
higher.

Buying BlackBerry now is similar to buying $AMD at $2.00 in 2014 when SU BAE
stepped in as CEO and took the stock to…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r1hc4x/hit_me_bb_one_more_time_papa_chen_about_to_close/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r1hc4x/hit_me_bb_one_more_time_papa_chen_about_to_close/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 07:44:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BlackBerry is set to have a parabolic run over the next few weeks/months with many upcoming catalysts! Below is my analysis of why I think the stock is going higher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buying BlackBerry now is similar to buying $AMD at $2.00 in 2014 when SU BAE stepped in as CEO and took the stock to the moon! I believe this is a very similar opportunity right now! 🤫&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My fellow APES&lt;/strong&gt; 🐵 &lt;strong&gt;just remember that DIAMONDS&lt;/strong&gt; 💎 &lt;strong&gt;are made under PRESSURE&lt;/strong&gt; 🖐&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good Luck and let&amp;#39;s hope that PAPA CHEN makes it rain TENDIES!  🐔 💦&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-------------------------&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background - The turn around story of the SLEEPING GIANT&lt;/strong&gt;  💪&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under the leadership of CEO John Chen, BlackBerry has spent the past 8 years pivoting from hardware smartphones to the future: (1) IoT Internet of Things (2) Automotive/EV and (3) Cyber Security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All three of these areas are growth opportunities and BlackBerry has strategically partnered with many large tech companies including: Amazon, Microsoft and Qualcomm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The market value of &lt;strong&gt;BlackBerry is CRIMINALLY UNDERVALUED&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;at ~$6 Billion&lt;/strong&gt; compared to their competitors such as $CRWD at $53 Billion, $PANW at $54 Billion and $ZS at $48 Billion to name a few.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The transformation of the business can be summarized in the slide below. Mickensy Consulting has estimated that the pool of reoccurring revenue from the IoT and connected car will grow exponentially over the next 10 years, which is VERY GOOD for BlackBerry&amp;#39;s new business model!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/t037ypmu9m181.png?width=1706&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=977b898dae2d197779b042a40b56702310ae3ad9&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/t037ypmu9m181.png?width=1706&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=977b898dae2d197779b042a40b56702310ae3ad9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/n0ietxa1bm181.png?width=1246&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=01c9ae993ec8935af6e04c22163b46fd9dae1aae&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/n0ietxa1bm181.png?width=1246&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=01c9ae993ec8935af6e04c22163b46fd9dae1aae&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Patent Sale/Settlement/Partnership Announcement&lt;/strong&gt;  💰&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is been lots of speculation and rumors over the past few month from various sources, ranging from Facebook $FB being the sole purchaser for cash up front and/or a partnership deal, to a group of parties. The range of the deal is said to be worth $1 Billion to $2 Billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the last conference call, CEO John Chen said that there is about an &amp;quot;80% probability that the deal closes by Q4&amp;quot;. This date is November 2021, which is next week. However, they could also be waiting to release it during their next earnings call on December 21st, 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/8xyowycxdm181.png?width=936&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=40ff564570e406d24aba3aa07c6e2ab7fc688ede&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/8xyowycxdm181.png?width=936&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=40ff564570e406d24aba3aa07c6e2ab7fc688ede&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QNX, IoT (Internet of Things), Amazon IVY and the connected car ecosystem&lt;/strong&gt;  👍&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;QNX real-time OS is installed in 195M cars today, out of 1.4B cars in total on the road worldwide. QNX enables many different software pieces to run in a car, so acts as a kind of central control unit. QNX is becoming the predominant OS for connected cars, since it´s installed in so many cars. Whilst today $BB licenses QNX to OEMs on a per-unit royalty basis, QNX is effectively set up (through Blackberry Ivy, in partnership with $AMZN) to be the foundation of the data value chain for the auto industry, which McKinsey estimates will be quite big, specially for a company ($BB) with a market cap of $6 Billion today. I think this will extend to other verticals over the next decade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to the North American and Japanese automakers, BlackBerry QNX also have partnerships with Chinese EV&amp;#39;s such as $XPEV and $BIDU (who plans to make EV&amp;#39;s in the future).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/vbofc4ylcm181.png?width=1802&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=70c9e30b3355c64189e13e571d22b97ca3e491ac&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/vbofc4ylcm181.png?width=1802&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=70c9e30b3355c64189e13e571d22b97ca3e491ac&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/uylt6j3r9m181.png?width=1627&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=4f5604ecbd04b4dc0238c70d159b79db12dc1cba&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/zg0wqrep9m181.png?width=972&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=ce09018f2ca2e5ef565636a78b4e7d65ab5224dc&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/zg0wqrep9m181.png?width=972&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=ce09018f2ca2e5ef565636a78b4e7d65ab5224dc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/451j7o02am181.png?width=941&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=4826ae27694734e9984d64fbdbed2559d2ab4c0a&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/451j7o02am181.png?width=941&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=4826ae27694734e9984d64fbdbed2559d2ab4c0a&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CES 2022 BB will be demonstrating both cyber and IoT with key partners&lt;/strong&gt;  👏&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BlackBerry has started testing their BETA version of IVY with Amazon this fall and are looking to showcase more features and capabilities with key partners at the CES in early 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/mou8wkvvem181.png?width=970&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=19e8d506ece446890b7c2d1cc4c71ceb2eb9116d&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/mou8wkvvem181.png?width=970&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=19e8d506ece446890b7c2d1cc4c71ceb2eb9116d&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On the last conference call, BlackBerry announced that they hired John Giamatteo from McAfee to lead BlackBerry&amp;#39;s cyber security business unit&lt;/strong&gt;  👌&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;John&amp;#39;s executive experience and connections should be BlackBerry generate sales in their current vertices and new market opportunities down the road, for both enterprise and consumer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/bc6p1ukyrm181.png?width=1809&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=4086560904724b639c23d7e31c62ed2637ea0c88&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/bc6p1ukyrm181.png?width=1809&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=4086560904724b639c23d7e31c62ed2637ea0c88&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BlackBerry continues to win Awards and is issued/granted new patents every month&lt;/strong&gt;  😎&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most recently, SE Labs  independently-owned and run testing company that assesses security products and services ranked BlackBerry as #1 in New Endpoint system security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quote: ”2021 has been the first year we have tested this product with BlackBerry publicly. When judging for our annual awards it is hard to ignore when a new, significant vendor enters our tests and performs so well from the start,&amp;quot; said Simon Edwards, CEO SE Labs. Blackberry has demonstrated excellent performance in our &amp;#39;real-world&amp;#39; testing, and the product is well regarded by both our expert panel of judges and users of the product. We would like to congratulate BlackBerry on achieving the award for best new endpoint.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/3ex9n1e6dn181.png?width=1717&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=475bfe9f0915690869d597cba115e52a1d1aa758&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/3ex9n1e6dn181.png?width=1717&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=475bfe9f0915690869d597cba115e52a1d1aa758&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Institutional Funds are loading up BIGLY&lt;/strong&gt;  👀 🔍&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the past months, big institutions have been increasing their position. Today for example, Morgan Stanley&amp;#39;s 13F filing showed that they alone increased their $BB holdings by +51%!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do they have insider info about the patent sale and/or other news? Could a Price Target increase be coming soon now that they  have loaded up on shares?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/5awqbg901n181.png?width=1336&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=a840cfdc381ad91d898286a2f6fff969e6696b1d&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/5awqbg901n181.png?width=1336&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=a840cfdc381ad91d898286a2f6fff969e6696b1d&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Analysis&lt;/strong&gt;  📈  🚀 🍋&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The weekly chart is a tight equilibrium pattern looking to break out on the bullish catalyst(s). Price target $30+ by early next year. Some UOA (Unusual Options Activity) also showed up today too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/5w3u8nacam181.png?width=1999&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=cc7079f51e961a40bd03fe1110a1c0cd7ebbdd62&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/5w3u8nacam181.png?width=1999&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=cc7079f51e961a40bd03fe1110a1c0cd7ebbdd62&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/frrjw4m8qm181.png?width=1333&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=4a2eef2758ce80a031b44b140afa2a1d39c15cf1&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/frrjw4m8qm181.png?width=1333&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=4a2eef2758ce80a031b44b140afa2a1d39c15cf1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[“I thought Doge went to a dollar?” https://t.co/xcn1Ynk5oa]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1463538433477992457</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1463538433477992457</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 07:35:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>