<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 17:43:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[The S&amp;P 500 fell 2.3% on Friday, its 5th 2-3% decline of the year. This has been a relatively calm year for US equities. There has yet to be a daily decline of more than 3% - in 2020 we saw that 16 times. $SPX https://t.co/qwvNPnRnyO]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464984717208571916</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464984717208571916</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 16:54:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[US 10-Year Treasury Yield...
Nov 1980: 12.7%
Nov 1985: 9.7%
Nov 1990: 8.3%
Nov 1995: 5.9%
Nov 2000: 5.6%
Nov 2005: 4.4%
Nov 2010: 2.9%
Nov 2015: 2.2%
Nov 2020: 0.9%
Nov 2021: 1.5%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464971781916217355</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464971781916217355</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 16:54:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GBTC ETF is significantly underperforming Bitcoin. GBTC’s 2% expense ratio is generating $740 million in annualized fee income for its management!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ref:
https://www.barrons.com/articles/grayscale-bitcoin-trust-fund-etf-price-51637689328

With $37 billion in assets, the Grayscale trust GBTC is the world’s largest
Bitcoin fund. It towers over every other fund on the market. Investors have
flooded into the Grayscale trust because it owns Bitcoin…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r45pcn/gbtc_etf_is_significantly_underperforming_bitcoin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r45pcn/gbtc_etf_is_significantly_underperforming_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 16:18:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ref: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/grayscale-bitcoin-trust-fund-etf-price-51637689328&quot;&gt;https://www.barrons.com/articles/grayscale-bitcoin-trust-fund-etf-price-51637689328&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With $37 billion in assets, the Grayscale trust GBTC is the world’s largest Bitcoin fund. It towers over every other fund on the market. Investors have flooded into the Grayscale trust because it owns Bitcoin directly. Its largest holder is Ark Invest, the fund shop run by Cathie Wood, which has invested $375 million in the trust, including assets held in its Ark Next Generation ETF (ARKW). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shares of the trust, which trade over the counter, are up 42% this year versus a 95% gain for Bitcoin, through Oct. 29.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Investors that crowded into GBTC, buying at a premium, really got burned,” says Morningstar analyst Bobby Blue. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, GBTC management made a killing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Big Drop in Black Friday Retails Store Traffic]]></title><description><![CDATA[Preliminary data shows a drop of 28.3% in foot traffic at U.S. retails stores on
Black Friday as compared to 2019 levels.

Sensormatic Solutions found that the drop was even bigger for Thanksgiving Day,
visits to brick-and-mortar stores plummeted by 90.4% compared to 2019. Retailers
including Target…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r44f75/big_drop_in_black_friday_retails_store_traffic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r44f75/big_drop_in_black_friday_retails_store_traffic/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 15:52:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preliminary data shows a drop of 28.3% in foot traffic at U.S. retails stores on Black Friday as compared to 2019 levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sensormatic Solutions found that the drop was even bigger for Thanksgiving Day, visits to brick-and-mortar stores plummeted by 90.4% compared to 2019. Retailers including Target Walmart and Best Buy chose to remain closed on the holiday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a positive note, in-person shopper traffic on Black Friday was up 47.5% compared with 2020, when many shoppers stayed home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Traffic was closest to returning to 2019 levels in the South, followed by the Midwest and then the Western U.S., according to a report from CNBC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.benzinga.com/node/24317896?utm_referrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.benzinga.com%2F&amp;amp;utm_source=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.benzinga.com%2F&quot;&gt;https://www.benzinga.com/node/24317896?utm_referrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.benzinga.com%2F&amp;amp;utm_source=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.benzinga.com%2F&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I hate weekends]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3mbjf/i_hate_weekends/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3mbjf/i_hate_weekends/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 15:20:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ew]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3x0bn/ew/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3x0bn/ew/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 11:29:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[If the first $100,000 is the hardest, shouldn't I try to consolidate most investments into one account? If so, what type of account would it be?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I started investing in Robinhood (taxable) before learning about retirement
accounts and Bogleheads. Learning about index funds and compound interest was
exciting, and now I want to shovel a lot of money into an optimized place as
fast as possible.

Roth IRA has stood out to me as very valuable, but…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3k44y/if_the_first_100000_is_the_hardest_shouldnt_i_try/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3k44y/if_the_first_100000_is_the_hardest_shouldnt_i_try/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 09:30:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I started investing in Robinhood (taxable) before learning about retirement accounts and Bogleheads. Learning about index funds and compound interest was exciting, and now I want to shovel a lot of money into an optimized place as fast as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roth IRA has stood out to me as very valuable, but the big 100k stands out to me too. Besides the Roth IRA, what account can I open to shovel 100k into over the years. Would it just be an IRA? Ideally I would be able to sell my investments in Robinhood, about $15k, to put towards the 100k&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Am I crazy for buying the following stocks at the prices listed here?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm considering buying the following stocks on Monday. I'll almost definitely
buy the stocks that are near their 52-week low (unless there's some reason I
should not?). But debating whether to buy those near the 52-week average.
Thoughts? And guessing I should buy none near their 52-week…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3woxa/am_i_crazy_for_buying_the_following_stocks_at_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3woxa/am_i_crazy_for_buying_the_following_stocks_at_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 07:28:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m considering buying the following stocks on Monday. I&amp;#39;ll almost definitely buy the stocks that are near their 52-week low (unless there&amp;#39;s some reason I should not?). But debating whether to buy those near the 52-week average. Thoughts? And guessing I should buy none near their 52-week highs?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEAR 52-WEEK LOW:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CRSP @ &lt;strong&gt;$78&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;Low $77&lt;/strong&gt;; High $220, Avg $128)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DISNEY @ &lt;strong&gt;$147&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;Low $146&lt;/strong&gt;, High $201, Avg $177)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PAYPAL @ &lt;strong&gt;$187&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;Low $184&lt;/strong&gt;, High $310, Avg $257)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VISA @ &lt;strong&gt;$197&lt;/strong&gt; (Low &lt;strong&gt;$192&lt;/strong&gt;, High $252, Avg $222)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEAR 52-WEEK AVERAGE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SOFI @ &lt;strong&gt;$18&lt;/strong&gt; (Low $10, High $28, &lt;strong&gt;Avg $17&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;STARBUCKS &lt;strong&gt;@ $110&lt;/strong&gt; (Low $95, High $126, &lt;strong&gt;Avg $111&lt;/strong&gt;) (Even though it&amp;#39;s near it&amp;#39;s average I&amp;#39;m concerned it won&amp;#39;t drop below $110 this year so I might as well just buy now. Thoughts?)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEAR 52-WEEK HIGH:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AMD @ &lt;strong&gt;$154&lt;/strong&gt; (Low: $72, &lt;strong&gt;High $16&lt;/strong&gt;1, Avg $95)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple @ &lt;strong&gt;$156&lt;/strong&gt; (Low 116, &lt;strong&gt;High $165&lt;/strong&gt;, $136) (Even though it&amp;#39;s near it&amp;#39;s high I&amp;#39;m concerned it won&amp;#39;t drop below $156 this year so I might as well just buy now. Thoughts?)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Microsoft @ &lt;strong&gt;$328&lt;/strong&gt; (Low $209, &lt;strong&gt;High $349&lt;/strong&gt;, Avg $264)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nvidia @ &lt;strong&gt;$315&lt;/strong&gt; (Low $115, &lt;strong&gt;High $346&lt;/strong&gt;, Avg $178)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;QQQ &lt;strong&gt;@ $391&lt;/strong&gt; (Low $289, &lt;strong&gt;High $408&lt;/strong&gt;, Avg $353)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past I&amp;#39;ve just invested in total stock market mutual funds, but now I am looking at some company stocks. Any advice on the stocks I listed would be much appreciated. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[An ELI5 Example of I-Bonds to and from a HYSA, for an emergency fund?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bogleheads seem to like I Bonds a lot so hope this question is apropos.

Context: S/0 and I purchased 20k of I-Bonds last week (for the first time) with
money that came from our HYSA. My idea is to purchase 20k more (for 2022) at the
start of January, also funded from our HYSA.

My goal is to have a…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3so3o/an_eli5_example_of_ibonds_to_and_from_a_hysa_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3so3o/an_eli5_example_of_ibonds_to_and_from_a_hysa_for/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 07:09:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bogleheads seem to like I Bonds a lot so hope this question is apropos. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Context: S/0 and I purchased 20k of I-Bonds last week (for the first time) with money that came from our HYSA. My idea is to purchase 20k more (for 2022) at the start of January, also funded from our HYSA.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My goal is to have a 9-month EF of 35k made up of I-bonds instead of a 35k EF just sitting in a 0.5% HYSA. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If post-January 2023, f we urgently needed that 35k, or part of it,  do we just redeem the amount(s) we need, at will, into our linked HYSA? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is the best  strategy for doing this?  (We can fund the EF with other monies until we get a system in place and we&amp;#39;re post-12 month periods for the 2021 and 2022 I Bond purchases.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking for simple examples that show the steps  money goes from HYSA to I-Bond then back to HSYA in EF context. Steps to take, pitfalls to avoid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also curious, are  I-Bonds used like an escrow (word choice?) account to pay for short-term horizon goals like paying one&amp;#39;s annual property taxes?  (As opposed to having that money just sit in an HYSA.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Roth IRA vs Mutual Fund]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey guys, I’m finally debt free and just paying rent and groceries at the
moment. I will have about 500 dollars that I can put away that I don’t have to
worry about. Is it better if I do a Roth or mutual fund like Vti? Could you tell
me the pros and cons?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3nxe7/roth_ira_vs_mutual_fund/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3nxe7/roth_ira_vs_mutual_fund/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 06:30:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey guys, I’m finally debt free and just paying rent and groceries at the moment. I will have about 500 dollars that I can put away that I don’t have to worry about. Is it better if I do a Roth or mutual fund like Vti? Could you tell me the pros and cons?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The mental trick that got me to buy in at any price, instead of trying to time the market]]></title><description><![CDATA[When I started Bogleheads, I dumped in all my savings at once (about $10k). The
price immediately went down which invoked quite an uncertain/stressed reaction
in me. It turned me into a market timing person and I was ready to bail. I
thought, if only I had waited a bit longer...

Well now I don't…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3vqzz/the_mental_trick_that_got_me_to_buy_in_at_any/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3vqzz/the_mental_trick_that_got_me_to_buy_in_at_any/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 06:30:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I started Bogleheads, I dumped in all my savings at once (about $10k). The price immediately went down which invoked quite an uncertain/stressed reaction in me. It turned me into a market timing person and I was ready to bail. I thought, if only I had waited a bit longer...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well now I don&amp;#39;t try to time it, and I just buy whenever I have money to. It&amp;#39;s because of what I tell myself each time I buy. I mentally promise not to sell the newly acquired stock until 1 year has passed since its purchase. I back this up by thinking 1 year is what it takes for long-term capital gains tax to kick in. Although I don&amp;#39;t plan on selling anything for many years, that concept of waiting at least 1 year after each purchase makes me feel very indifferent to whatever happens shortly after I buy in and has allowed me to do it whenever I have money, not when I feel the price is low enough&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My portfolio since discovering this sub]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3w24v/my_portfolio_since_discovering_this_sub/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3w24v/my_portfolio_since_discovering_this_sub/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 05:47:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What ways do retail investors have to get invested in VC?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Venture Capital (as well as PE) are quite the interesting financial product, due
to them having somewhat of a different modus operandi to other types of
institutions/products. However, as far as I know, VC also still remains more of
a "big ticker" investment vehicle, and not so easily accessible to…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3pllb/what_ways_do_retail_investors_have_to_get/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3pllb/what_ways_do_retail_investors_have_to_get/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 05:22:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Venture Capital (as well as PE) are quite the interesting financial product, due to them having somewhat of a different modus operandi to other types of institutions/products. However, as far as I know, VC also still remains more of a &amp;quot;big ticker&amp;quot; investment vehicle, and not so easily accessible to the average investor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought it&amp;#39;d be interesting to gather as responses to this thread all possible means retail investors can use to get invested (Both financially and &amp;quot;personally&amp;quot;) in VC, whether it&amp;#39;d be by buying shares of a publicly-traded VC (of which there are quite few, afaik) or other means.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please share what you know, could be really interesting!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What's the point of inverse funds?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I saw there are inverse funds at Trading 212. Their KIID reports show that they
lose money almost all time. I just don't get what the point in equity that loses
money. It seems that they are made to tackle market downturns, but their fees
are really high. So high that they almost match mutual funds.…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3ji64/whats_the_point_of_inverse_funds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3ji64/whats_the_point_of_inverse_funds/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 04:47:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I saw there are inverse funds at Trading 212. Their KIID reports show that they lose money almost all time. I just don&amp;#39;t get what the point in equity that loses money. It seems that they are made to tackle market downturns, but their fees are really high. So high that they almost match mutual funds. And while they may work in short term, what&amp;#39;s the point in investing them, when something like bonds, REITs (to some extent as they are generally lagging behind stock market) or P2P loans (from my experience, if you analyze performance and invest manually, they seem to be stable and generate at least 9.3% returns even during current crisis. At worst they would be 7% profitable, but that would take something more serious than C19) seem to be profitable during those same times? They seem to be going against general wisdom of buying and holding and since you can&amp;#39;t predict bearish or bullish, even more time that precisely, I&amp;#39;m not really sure what&amp;#39;s the point of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[As a US based investor, what percentage of your equity investments are in international markets?]]></title><description><![CDATA[The below poll only applies to investors located within the USA.

There has been significant discussion about how much of your portfolio should be
allocated to US based investments vs ex-US based investments. I'm curious to see
how the portfolios of those in this subreddit compare.

When answering…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3jdhi/as_a_us_based_investor_what_percentage_of_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3jdhi/as_a_us_based_investor_what_percentage_of_your/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 04:21:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The below poll only applies to investors located within the USA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There has been significant discussion about how much of your portfolio should be allocated to US based investments vs ex-US based investments. I&amp;#39;m  curious to see how the portfolios of those in this subreddit compare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When answering please consider individual stocks as well. Exclude bonds, cash, owned property, etc...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be clear, whatever the outcome of the poll, &lt;strong&gt;I would not consider this to be advice as to how any particular portfolio should be set up&lt;/strong&gt;. I&amp;#39;m just curious about what others have done. Only the future will show whether any particular portfolio was optimal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Edit: I created a similar post last week. However, in that I asked only whether  people invested &amp;quot;significantly&amp;quot; in international markets. I received a  few comments which made me curious about the percentage people invested  in international markets, hence this new poll.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here is that previous poll:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Bogleheads/comments/qz5ktd/as_a_us_based_investor_do_you_invest/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/Bogleheads/comments/qz5ktd/as_a_us_based_investor_do_you_invest/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/poll/r3jdhi&quot;&gt;View Poll&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Dot-com bubble -- Any documentary recommendations or anecdotes?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm trying to get a better picture of how much awareness there was of the
booming tech industry in the 1990s and early 2000s.

How comparable is it to the crypto boom today or any other (tech-unrelated)
field?



It seemed very easy to just make a "startup" if you were into programming and
could…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3sqf5/the_dotcom_bubble_any_documentary_recommendations/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3sqf5/the_dotcom_bubble_any_documentary_recommendations/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 04:21:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m trying to get a better picture of how much awareness there was of the booming tech industry in the 1990s and early 2000s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How comparable is it to the crypto boom today or any other (tech-unrelated) field?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seemed very easy to just make a &amp;quot;startup&amp;quot; if you were into programming and could actually build something of value. Sure the resources were not really there and the tools were limited. Making a simple website was for example much harder than it is nowadays. However many people could have tried their luck but they didnt. I&amp;#39;m trying to figure out why. Maybe only a few people knew about the upcoming new technology or they heard of it but remained sceptical?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[“The new Omicron variant of the Coronavirus results in MILD disease, WITHOUT prominent symptoms.” 

-Angelique Coetzee, the chairwoman of the South African Medical Association.

SUNDAY FUTS RAMP]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464747781747261450</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464747781747261450</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 03:41:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What's up with the recent Dollar Cost Averaging obsession?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I see a lot of new investors who are looking to invest their savings and
everytime they ask for advice people tell them to dollar cost average to spread
out their risk.

I understand the fear of buying on top, but DCA'ing is in essence betting
against the market to trade lower, and on average that…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3ken6/whats_up_with_the_recent_dollar_cost_averaging/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3ken6/whats_up_with_the_recent_dollar_cost_averaging/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 03:41:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I see a lot of new investors who are looking to invest their savings and everytime they ask for advice people tell them to dollar cost average to spread out their risk. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand the fear of buying on top, but DCA&amp;#39;ing is in essence betting against the market to trade lower, and on average that bet is not in your favor. The market has historically shown an uptrend and therefore &amp;quot;spreading out your risks&amp;quot; is hurting your investment. In more cases than not throwing all your money in the market at once would produce better results, without even considering trading fees being part of the equation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand the use of DCA when you have a monthly income and want to invest your savings but not when you have built up a lot of cash and want to spread it out. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would love to hear your take and insights on the subject!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why do many financial products require high minimum investments?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello,

From what I've seen, many financial products, such as PE fonds or hedge funds,
have very high requirements on initial investments for investors to participate.
Even "roboadvisors" often have minimums that go into the 6-figure range,
although they target smaller investors. Why is this the…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3omci/why_do_many_financial_products_require_high/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3omci/why_do_many_financial_products_require_high/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 02:40:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From what I&amp;#39;ve seen, many financial products, such as PE fonds or hedge funds, have very high requirements on initial investments for investors to participate. Even &amp;quot;roboadvisors&amp;quot; often have minimums that go into the 6-figure range, although they target smaller investors. Why is this the case? Those businesses are essentially pooling money together and then sharing profits of the pool with the investors that make up the pool depending on how much they invested, so wouldn&amp;#39;t every &amp;quot;little bit more&amp;quot; money in the fund help them operate? What are the high minimum requirements for? There has to be some underlying reason, but I&amp;#39;m not sure I really understand it at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What's your opinion on TQQQ]]></title><description><![CDATA[My portfolio current is 100% TQQQ with no margin. My game plan is quite simple.
Buy every, single, dip. And simply continue doing that. 3% down buy 5 more. 1%
down, buy another 5 more and on and on. Do you consider this a truly good
strategy that will end up in success? I have no other positions and…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3mvha/whats_your_opinion_on_tqqq/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3mvha/whats_your_opinion_on_tqqq/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 01:15:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My portfolio current is 100% TQQQ with no margin. My game plan is quite simple. Buy every, single, dip. And simply continue doing that. 3% down buy 5 more. 1% down, buy another 5 more and on and on. Do you consider this a truly good strategy that will end up in success? I have no other positions and will NOT be needing the money in the longterm future. I expect I will hold this position for 5-10 years than revise my strategy when I&amp;#39;m 26-31 years old. Thank you very much for your time reading this and I appreciate all constructive feedbacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What’s the first thing I should invest in my new account?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m 16 and I’m about to open a custodial account through TD Ameritrade. I’ll be
able to do stocks, mutual funds and ETF’s. I have about $2K I could invest. What
should I start with, any individual stocks? Open to all ideas and suggestions,
thank you! :)]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3k6pi/whats_the_first_thing_i_should_invest_in_my_new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3k6pi/whats_the_first_thing_i_should_invest_in_my_new/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 01:15:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m 16 and I’m about to open a custodial account through TD Ameritrade.  I’ll be able to do stocks, mutual funds and ETF’s.  I have about $2K I could invest.  What should I start with, any individual stocks?  Open to all ideas and suggestions, thank you! :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Be prepared for a drawdown in pie stocks]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pi will be the next COVID variant. When the pie variant comes out, sales of pies
will plummet nationwide, because—unfortunately—the public is that stupid.

The following could be in trouble:

-Pies

-Bakeries

-Pie mixes

-Some fruit (pumpkin, rhubarb, apples, key lime)

Pies will likely become a…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3i8oq/be_prepared_for_a_drawdown_in_pie_stocks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3i8oq/be_prepared_for_a_drawdown_in_pie_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 23:59:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pi will be the next COVID variant.  When the pie variant comes out, sales of pies will plummet nationwide, because—unfortunately—the public is that stupid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following could be in trouble:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Pies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Bakeries&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Pie mixes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Some fruit (pumpkin, rhubarb, apples, key lime)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pies will likely become a political issue like masks, and congressmen and women will tweet about the oppression and atrocities of pies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, we can prepare to short pies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just be watching to see what the market has “baked in” to pie stocks (pun strongly intended).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Could be an opportunity to go long cake and doughnut stocks when pie eaters must switch to another delicacy to satisfy their sweet teeth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Omicron concerns should spur millions of unvaccinated Americans to get their Covid shots, experts say --CNN

Guess again fucked face]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464683327760252932</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464683327760252932</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 23:32:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Benefits Of Paying Off Mortgage Early]]></title><description><![CDATA[I recently paid off a 30 year mortgage in 12 years, I was at 5.5% and told by my
Dads friend in finance it would be better to pay it off rather than refinance.

What are the benefits? More money to invest? Peace of Mind?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3nir2/benefits_of_paying_off_mortgage_early/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3nir2/benefits_of_paying_off_mortgage_early/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 23:32:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I recently paid off a 30 year mortgage in 12 years, I was at 5.5% and told by my Dads friend in finance it would be better to pay it off rather than refinance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are the benefits? More money to invest? Peace of Mind?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I have been at a new company for a while now. They use Fidelity. Should I roll over my existing account to fidelity or to Vanguard? Currently, my 401k is with a group that is neither Fidelity or Vanguard.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3dxim/i_have_been_at_a_new_company_for_a_while_now_they/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3dxim/i_have_been_at_a_new_company_for_a_while_now_they/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 23:32:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why some ETFs and Indexes exclude the UK?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey all first post.

I noticed something interesting when looking through some of the ETF and Index
options and noticed that some say "ex UK", and often have 2 versions, one that
excludes and one that includes the UK.

I find this quite interesting, why would an investor chose between the two?…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3fbkh/why_some_etfs_and_indexes_exclude_the_uk/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3fbkh/why_some_etfs_and_indexes_exclude_the_uk/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 23:32:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey all first post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I noticed something interesting when looking through some of the ETF and Index options and noticed that some say &amp;quot;ex UK&amp;quot;, and often have 2 versions, one  that excludes and one that includes the UK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find this quite interesting, why would an investor chose between the two? Is there a measured reason why the UK specifically?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just a little curiosity I had. If anyone could kindly shed some light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the best!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Getting ready for Cyber Monday]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3gidn/getting_ready_for_cyber_monday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3gidn/getting_ready_for_cyber_monday/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 20:27:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Now I attract gold diggers thanks to you retards]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3l0w3/now_i_attract_gold_diggers_thanks_to_you_retards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3l0w3/now_i_attract_gold_diggers_thanks_to_you_retards/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 20:27:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[New York Declares State of Emergency due to new Covid variant]]></title><description><![CDATA[How do you think the market will react on Monday?New York declared a state of
emergency aimed at increasing hospital capacity and addressing medical staffing
shortages as the nation braces for the new omicron variant of the coronavirus.

The new protocols will take effect Dec. 3 and the order will…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3jg1m/new_york_declares_state_of_emergency_due_to_new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3jg1m/new_york_declares_state_of_emergency_due_to_new/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 19:36:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;How do you think the market will react on Monday?New York declared a state of emergency aimed at increasing hospital capacity and addressing medical staffing shortages as the nation braces for the new omicron variant of the coronavirus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new protocols will take effect Dec. 3 and the order will remain in place at least until Jan. 15, when it will be reassessed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The emergency declaration will allow the state Department of Health to limit nonessential and nonurgent hospital procedures in situations where a hospital has less than 10% staffed bed capacity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.yahoo.com/news/york-declares-state-emergency-hike-074026369.html&quot;&gt;https://www.yahoo.com/news/york-declares-state-emergency-hike-074026369.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Talking about a Wallstreetbets trader at the family dinner table]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3fh4o/talking_about_a_wallstreetbets_trader_at_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3fh4o/talking_about_a_wallstreetbets_trader_at_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 19:23:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What's your game plan for a market correction?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Now, the last thing this sub needs is more pointless speculation on whether or
not the market's going to crash/correct downward. None of us can predict the
future and we've all heard that timing the market is futile. Let's keep that
speculation to a minimum.

For those who are worried about this…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3fl3r/whats_your_game_plan_for_a_market_correction/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3fl3r/whats_your_game_plan_for_a_market_correction/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 18:52:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, the last thing this sub needs is more pointless speculation on whether or not the market&amp;#39;s going to crash/correct downward. None of us can predict the future and we&amp;#39;ve all heard that timing the market is futile. Let&amp;#39;s keep that speculation to a minimum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who are worried about this though, what positions are you taking? Do you have a small percentage of your portfolio in some type of hedge? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OTM SPY puts? VIX calls? A larger than usual cash position? What are you using and how much is it costing you? What&amp;#39;s the potential pay off?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to stay invested, but I also know that the market is historically overvalued, and I want peace of mind at night with some form of hedge. Any suggestions are welcomed. Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The price of Crude Oil fell 13.1% yesterday, the 9th largest 1-day decline ever. $WTIC https://t.co/YKYxzbXBCM]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464612670590664706</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464612670590664706</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 18:38:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Beauty of WSB]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r39952/the_beauty_of_wsb/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r39952/the_beauty_of_wsb/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 18:38:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What’s your opinion of Morningstar?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Greetings. Have anyone tried the Morningstar premium, and what’s your opinion on
it?

If you used it or currently use it, how do you like their portfolio tracking
functions? Things like * ease of loading and updating positions * custom view on
attributes like sector, market, assets breakdowns

I saw…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3fy7k/whats_your_opinion_of_morningstar/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3fy7k/whats_your_opinion_of_morningstar/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 18:15:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greetings. Have anyone tried the Morningstar premium, and what’s your opinion on it? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you used it or currently use it, how do you like their portfolio tracking functions? Things like 
* ease of loading and updating positions 
* custom view on attributes like sector, market, assets breakdowns&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I saw some fundamentals attributes in the free service, does it provide more robust data on premium?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also what do you all use for portfolio tracking? (I also got personal capital, it’s great for my main portfolio…but hard to set up secondary and mock accounts)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks all!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why are there so many new electric vehicle companies?]]></title><description><![CDATA[First of all, it’s hard enough to build a car on it’s own without things falling
apart when you hit a bump in the road. Second, to manufacture them is a
humongous undertaking and capital expense. If I wanted to start a new company,
EV’s would be the very last thing on the list, maybe that’s why? I…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3eer7/why_are_there_so_many_new_electric_vehicle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3eer7/why_are_there_so_many_new_electric_vehicle/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 18:15:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;First of all, it’s hard enough to build a car on it’s own without things falling apart when you hit a bump in the road. Second, to manufacture them is a humongous undertaking and capital expense. If I wanted to start a new company, EV’s would be the very last thing on the list, maybe that’s why? I don’t get it&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I’m completely new and thinking about investing in PayPal ?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Thought about buying just 1 share of PayPal and starting from there. I feel bad
that I’m starting late at 23 and with so little to even invest, I’ve only got 8k
to my entire name which sucks lol. I’d invest maybe $300, that’s what I’m
willing to lose, anything more would be irresponsible.

Any…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3epsv/im_completely_new_and_thinking_about_investing_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3epsv/im_completely_new_and_thinking_about_investing_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 16:54:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thought about buying just 1 share of PayPal and starting from there. I feel bad that I’m starting late at 23 and with so little to even invest, I’ve only got 8k to my entire name which sucks lol. I’d invest maybe $300, that’s what I’m willing to lose, anything more would be irresponsible. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any advice? Is this a good start? Anything I should know as a complete newbie? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Words words words hopefully my post isn’t taken down for low effort this time&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GGPI (Polestar) vs LCID (Lucid) ???? Any thoughts???]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have been thinking of adding one of these to my monthly investing list. I am a
long term investor and I have a list of stocks that I invest in every month.

My first question..... Does GGPI stock represent Polestar only?

Also, I want to know your views on these 2 Electric cars manufacturers. I…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r38awo/ggpi_polestar_vs_lcid_lucid_any_thoughts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r38awo/ggpi_polestar_vs_lcid_lucid_any_thoughts/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 15:51:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have been thinking of adding one of these to my monthly investing list. I am a long term investor and I have a list of stocks that I invest in every month. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first question..... Does GGPI stock represent Polestar only? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, I  want to know your views on these 2 Electric cars manufacturers. I am thinking of investing regularly in GGPI (Polestar) since they have successfully sold a significant number of cars. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not able to see any strong points favouring Lucid. Please fill me in if I am missing something important about them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know that scaling an electric car business is very difficult as stated by Elon Musk in multiple interviews. Keeping that in consideration I think Polestar has already solved its scaling issue since its parent company is Volve. I can&amp;#39;t say the same for Lucid though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The $VIX spiked 54% higher on Friday, the 4th largest 1-day % increase in history (note: $VIX data goes back to 1990). https://t.co/TmZcja9Otd]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464597978778382347</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464597978778382347</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 15:38:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How did you save for your house?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm a 23 year old interested in buying a house with my significant other before
we have kids in our late 20s to early 30s (ideally). Any advice on how to save
for this goal? I heard you can take money out of your Roth for a down payment is
that true? I have a meager savings right now but am putting…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r37wyd/how_did_you_save_for_your_house/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r37wyd/how_did_you_save_for_your_house/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 15:38:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m a 23 year old interested in buying a house with my significant other before we have kids in our late 20s to early 30s (ideally). Any advice on how to save for this goal? I heard you can take money out of your Roth for a down payment is that true? I have a meager savings right now but am putting away what I can when I can. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Vanguard app update took away the coolest single feature the Vanguard app had.. in my opinion. Just venting.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m posting this here because Bogle is often intertwined with Vanguard,
hopefully you see it all as applicable. This seems like a “change for the sake
of change” update they were sold on. The Vanguard app updated this week.

The best feature of the last app was you could click your account,…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r39ew4/the_vanguard_app_update_took_away_the_coolest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r39ew4/the_vanguard_app_update_took_away_the_coolest/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 14:42:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m posting this here because Bogle is often intertwined with Vanguard, hopefully you see it all as applicable. This seems like a “change for the sake of change” update they were sold on. The Vanguard app updated this week. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best feature of the last app was you could click your account, or performance, and hover/slide with your thumb over the months and see how much has changed in that one month. It was such a simple to use, nice features to see while looking at a chart. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new update? It’s gone. It’s almost as if they hired people who don’t use the app to update it. I’m sure that days is somewhere in the app, but not as cleanly and easily accessible as it was with the thumb/hold/slide feature of the last app. Bummer. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s all&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Omicron panic.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3b8sc/omicron_panic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3b8sc/omicron_panic/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 13:53:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$80,000 SPY Puts for Monday bc all you retards bought calls at close today]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2u2a0/80000_spy_puts_for_monday_bc_all_you_retards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2u2a0/80000_spy_puts_for_monday_bc_all_you_retards/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 10:54:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thoughts on investing in Airlines during this pandemic?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey all, and thanks for reading.
The world has grown to be a place where so many things are done online, and I've
decided to join in by starting with investing in stocks. So, to the main
question: What do I invest in, with a starting budget of $100. I am, of course,
not looking to make $1000 off of…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2wv59/thoughts_on_investing_in_airlines_during_this/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2wv59/thoughts_on_investing_in_airlines_during_this/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 10:54:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey all, and thanks for reading.&lt;br/&gt;
The world has grown to be a place   where so many things are done online, and I&amp;#39;ve decided to join in by  starting with investing in stocks. So, to the main question: What do I  invest in, with a starting budget of $100. I am, of  course, not looking  to make $1000 off of this $100 initial budget, but  seeing any profit  would motivate oneself to invest more in the future. I  was thinking of  investing in popular airlines I could get my hands on,  as with the new COVID variant, these businesses are likely to be worth  much less. So, thoughts on this? And, any other information anyone could  share on the  matter with how to start off?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ATTENTION SHORT POSITION TRADERS]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am the unluckiest man when it comes to making money, all I can do is lose with
anything. Everything I touch automatically turns to shit the instant I buy it
with 100% accuracy. It is clear I have the power to bear markets.

I also have the ability to instantly make anyone pissed off just by my…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r38uub/attention_short_position_traders/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r38uub/attention_short_position_traders/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 10:42:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am the unluckiest man when it comes to making money, all I can do is lose with anything. Everything I touch automatically turns to shit the instant I buy it with 100% accuracy. It is clear I have the power to bear markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also have the ability to instantly make anyone pissed off just by my mere presence alone. I am a true form of perfect negative energy in the universe, and thus I can be weaponized for hire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use my powers to short anything. Pay me up front, tell me what to buy one share of, and short your way to billions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What stocks are strong plays with or without COVID?]]></title><description><![CDATA[At this point, I just anticipate new variants popping up every few months so
airlines and some sectors like cruise liens are just too risky for me to gamble
on for very little reward.

On the other hand, what stocks are good plays to get with or without COVID news?
I personally like Costco which is…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r36gk8/what_stocks_are_strong_plays_with_or_without_covid/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r36gk8/what_stocks_are_strong_plays_with_or_without_covid/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 09:57:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this point, I just anticipate new variants popping up every few months so airlines and some sectors like cruise liens are just too risky for me to gamble on for very little reward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, what stocks are good plays to get with or without COVID news? I personally like Costco which is defensive but also a trade that has sailed from earnings even post &amp;quot;delta&amp;quot;, Roblox which is another great stock in case of shutdowns but also had phenomenal earnings despite things reopening and kids going back to school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What else?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Retail Stocks Sink Amid Strong Black Friday Sales. Blame Covid Variant Fears]]></title><description><![CDATA[Retail stocks, along with the broader market, were down Friday morning as fears
of a new Covid-19 variant hammered the market amid potentially strong Black
Friday sales. Shares of Dollar Tree (DLTR), which sells the majority of its
products—including toys, home decor, kitchenware, and seasonal…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2saq2/retail_stocks_sink_amid_strong_black_friday_sales/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2saq2/retail_stocks_sink_amid_strong_black_friday_sales/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 09:44:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Retail stocks, along with the broader market, were down Friday morning as fears of a new Covid-19 variant hammered the market amid potentially strong Black Friday sales. Shares of Dollar Tree (DLTR), which sells the majority of its products—including toys, home decor, kitchenware, and seasonal goods—was down nearly 4% to $140.81. Nordstrom (JWN) was down 7% at $21.04. Macy’s (M) was off 7.2%. Retailers that struggled to keep up with supply-chain crunches—as noted in their third-quarter earnings—including Kohls (KSS) and Gap (GPS) were down 2.1% to $54.09, and 3.4% to $17.25, respectively. Shares of Abercrombie &amp;amp; Fitch (ANF) were down 3.3% to $37.98.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the most part though, retail stocks have been gaining amid high demand this year. The SPDR S&amp;amp;P Retail exchange-traded fund (XRT) is up 50.05% this year as of Friday morning, still on pace for its best year since 2009, when it rose 74.8%. The ETF is down 2.8% in Friday trading. The Invesco S&amp;amp;P 500 Equal Weight Consumer Discretionary ETF (RCD) is up nearly 25% this year, a sign that despite the previous Delta variant, shoppers are ready to spend their cash and investors recognize the demand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Data from Friday morning showed U.S. consumers are expected to spend $12.9 billion in online sales and have already spent $6.9 billion online during Thanksgiving Day, up 1.1% from last year, according to data from Salesforce. The National Retail Federation estimates 58.1 million people will shop on Small Business Saturday, and 62.8 million will shop online on Cyber Monday. The trade organization projects consumers will spend an average of $997.73, with total spending up as much as 10.5% to $859 billion this season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;U.S. online sales for the first three weeks of November are up 10% year-over-year, $74 billion already spent, as consumers continue to fit in holiday shopping as early as possible over concerns regarding shipping delays and supply chain issues, according to Salesforce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Dow was on track for its worst Black Friday on record, with the S&amp;amp;P 500 and Nasdaq on pace for their worst Black Friday since 2009.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/articles/retail-stocks-sink-amid-strong-black-friday-sales-blame-covid-variant-fears-51637946074?mod=mw_latestnews&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/articles/retail-stocks-sink-amid-strong-black-friday-sales-blame-covid-variant-fears-51637946074?mod=mw_latestnews&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How do you do fellow idiots?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2xi84/how_do_you_do_fellow_idiots/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2xi84/how_do_you_do_fellow_idiots/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 07:27:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[QQQ vs. SPY?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Considering investing in either QQQ or SPY but can’t determine which is the
right one. Or should I invest in both?

My DD shows:

— QQQ tracks the NASDAQ 100 Index, while SPY tracks the S&P 500 Index — QQQ is
100 stocks in a handful of sectors, largely concentrated in tech. SPY is 500
stocks spread…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2snig/qqq_vs_spy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2snig/qqq_vs_spy/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 07:07:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Considering investing in either QQQ or SPY but can’t determine which is the right one.  Or should I invest in both? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My DD shows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;— QQQ tracks the NASDAQ 100 Index, while SPY tracks the S&amp;amp;P 500 Index
— QQQ is 100 stocks in a handful of sectors, largely concentrated in tech. SPY is 500 stocks spread across all sectors
— looks like QQQ is already inside SPY while SPY is over 1/4 tech.l
— expense fees for QQQ is higher (at 0.20%) meanwhile SPY is cheaper (at 0.09%)
— NASDAQ 100 has beaten the S&amp;amp;P 500 over the past 10 years, generating an average annual return of 20.27% vs 14.26%
— QQQ assets has $201.39B while SPY has $417.28B&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is everyone else’s thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT:  leaning towards VOO (due to low expense ratio) and QQQ.  Since SPY and VOO are so similar I think lower expense ratio is the deciding factor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bloody day but added BA,OKE, CVX,UPS,FDX, VZ]]></title><description><![CDATA[Looking long-term but use today’s selloff opportunities to buy some quality
companies.

Boeing. $197.45. (Already has a position at $238 😕)

Oneok $61.00

Chevron $112.50

United parcel system $204.85

Federal Express. $237.50

Verizon $51.60

For better or worse we will see what happens.

If you…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2u0pn/bloody_day_but_added_baoke_cvxupsfdx_vz/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2u0pn/bloody_day_but_added_baoke_cvxupsfdx_vz/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 06:29:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking long-term but use today’s selloff opportunities to buy some quality companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boeing.  $197.45. (Already has a position at $238 😕)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oneok         $61.00&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chevron  $112.50&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;United parcel system $204.85&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Federal Express.   $237.50&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verizon        $51.60&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For better or worse we will see what happens. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you purchased some shares today what did you buy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What did you want to buy that you did not buy?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MORE!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2qt2m/more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2qt2m/more/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 05:47:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>