<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 07:17:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Anyone else hate the click bait titles for stock analysis articles?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I was using M1 finance to just look around for random stocks tickers and
something I noticed that really bugged me, is the whole dramatic language they
use to say a stock went up or down.

If a stock goes up by a dollar or around 5%, they say dumb crap like, "this
stock has surged today." or…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsofa3/anyone_else_hate_the_click_bait_titles_for_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsofa3/anyone_else_hate_the_click_bait_titles_for_stock/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 06:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was using M1 finance to just look around for random stocks tickers and something I noticed that really bugged me, is the whole dramatic language they use to say a stock went up or down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If a stock goes up by a dollar or around 5%, they say dumb crap like, &amp;quot;this stock has surged today.&amp;quot; or ascended, or spiked, or is sky rocketing. But like, the stock I was looking at had an ipo price of $12 and now it&amp;#39;s $4 and its apparently &amp;quot;skyrocketing.&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;like no, no it&amp;#39;s not. if I&amp;#39;m an investor from day one, and I read the phrase skyrocket, I&amp;#39;m thinking this thing is like $100 a share or something. Like the people who write these articles, I don&amp;#39;t know how they get paid for this. These analysts are paid to type nonsense every single day, but they aren&amp;#39;t paid to be accurate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was wondering if there was some enforced rules to these fancy adjectives. Because i see it with every company. They say plummet, or downward spiral, or falling when a company goes down even 1%, but jettisoned, surged, or sky rocket when it&amp;#39;s doing mildly good. I think it&amp;#39;s meant to keep people nervous and excited so people keep buying and selling and eventually make no money in the end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Poking holes in the inflation conspiracy theory, by Larry Swedroe]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsrov3/poking_holes_in_the_inflation_conspiracy_theory/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsrov3/poking_holes_in_the_inflation_conspiracy_theory/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 06:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Big F**k Robinhood energy!]]></title><description><![CDATA[So I had $aapl 150 calls expiring today and WITHOUT notice they closed my
position at 3:02pm when the stock was $149.76. And of course it rallied into the
money by as much as $150.40 by 3:30pm!

I immediately called support and after a run around they called me back after
the market closed saying…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsllfi/big_fk_robinhood_energy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsllfi/big_fk_robinhood_energy/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 04:51:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I had $aapl 150 calls expiring today and WITHOUT notice they closed my position at 3:02pm when the stock was $149.76. And of course it rallied into the money by as much as $150.40 by 3:30pm!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I immediately called support and after a run around they called me back after the market closed saying that the risk assessment team made the decision to close. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why wouldn’t they send a notification ahead of time stating that by a certain time they would close the position? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nothing… They sold right before the stock rallied into close. The CSR offered zero condolences or any modicum of help. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this is another PSA: Fuck Robinhood!! I hope their stock burns to the ground, I’m withdrawing all my funds and moving to a better platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: Lesson learned, yes I’m retarded and don’t know how to read. More or less just venting to my fellow apes. For those who are unaware of this, we’ll now you know! Thank you for the lashing, but still fuck RH!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Here is a Market Recap for today Friday, November 12, 2021]]></title><description><![CDATA[PsychoMarket Recap - Friday, November 12, 2021

Stocks advanced firmly on Friday, with market participants continuing to balance
better-than-expected corporate earnings amid rising inflation. The S&P 500 (SPY)
closed the day 0.75% higher, the tech-heavy Nasdaq (QQQ) rose 1.05%, and the Dow
Jones…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsmfuq/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_friday_november/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsmfuq/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_friday_november/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 03:24:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Friday, November 12, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks advanced firmly on Friday, with market participants continuing to balance better-than-expected corporate earnings amid rising inflation. The S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) closed the day 0.75% higher, the tech-heavy Nasdaq (QQQ) rose 1.05%, and the Dow Jones (DIA) broke a three day losing streak to finish 0.51% higher. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of Friday’s close, the SPY closed the week 0.4% lower following volatility after the release of the October Consumer Price Index. However, after five consecutive weeks of gains, the market remains marginally below previous all-time highs. The QQQ closed the week 0.91% lower, while the DIA closed the week 0.97% lower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the Labor Department released the monthly Consumer Price Index, which showed prices soared 6.2% in a year-on-year period, accelerating from September’s 5.4% YoY rate, and higher than the 5.9% expected. This represents that fastest pace of inflationary expansion since 1990, though one has to take into account easy comparisons to last year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The staying power and magnitude of inflationary pressures has, perhaps, become the central question for market participants, with companies across the board reporting rising input costs and price hikes passed on to the consumers to preserve margins. While Q3 earning results have robustly demonstrated that companies in the SPY were largely able to navigate these cost pressures, the possibility remains that if inflation runs hotter than expected for longer than expected, it could begin to hamper consumer demand. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While a rise in inflation was expected, the pace of the increase surprised to the upside. If the pace of increase is not moderated soon, it carries meaningful implications for corporations, consumers, and the Federal Reserve. As input costs rise, companies will pass the increase in cost to consumers to preserve their bottom line, who will be forced to pay the higher prices. The Fed would then be forced to step in and rise interest rates, which will makes the cost to borrow money more expensive, which means people and companies will likely spend less, leading to a fall in demand for goods and services. A rise in interest rates would particularly hurt high P/E tech stocks that have been flying in the last two years, as these companies rely on borrowing to fund their aggressive expansion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still, the Federal Reserve and many economists have reaffirmed that the inflationary pressures are transitory, caused by pandemic-era disruptions in global trade and will eventually ease, albeit while likely settling at a higher level than had been present before the pandemic. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gabriela Santos, Global Market Strategist at JP Morgan, said “Inflation should moderate. We’re talking about settling at 2%, 2.5% over the course of the next 12 months. So we&amp;#39;re still talking about real wage gains, and that&amp;#39;s extremely supportive, certainly of people&amp;#39;s livelihoods, but also of consumption and hence the economy overall. We do expect a big re-acceleration in growth starting this quarter and throughout next year, [and] 5% average growth just over the next three quarters. So we would characterize this not as stagflation, but as reflation. And that difference is, reflation is actually quite good for earnings growth and quite good for the stock market, especially cyclical sectors.&amp;quot; So far, expectations are that the Fed will step in sometime mid-2022 to raise interest rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Rivian (RIVN), which is backed by Ford and Amazon,  continue to be on absolute fire. The company, which is expected to lose $1.28 billion on no more than $1 million in revenue this quarter, now has a market cap of more than $100 billion. For perspective, they are now the fourth largest automaker in the world by market cap. I’m not a stickler for valuation, but this is absolute insanity and unsustainable. The company has not started production and is already priced to perfection, which they are bound to hit a snag with. I don’t think this price is sustainable. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The University of Michigan’s closely monitored Consumer Sentiment survey showed the consumer sentiment index decreased to 66.8 from 71.7 in October, missing estimates of 72.5. Waning confidence reflects “ an escalating inflation rate and the growing belief among consumers that no effective policies have yet been developed to reduce the damage from surging inflation,” Richard Curtin, director of the survey, said in a statement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Snap (SNAP) investor sued the social media company alleging it downplayed how Apple’s (AAPL) change in privacy would affect revenue. Remember, the stock plummeted 25% after an earnings miss, citing Apple’s changes as hampering ad revenue. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After more than a decade of explosive growth, China&amp;#39;s Singles&amp;#39; Day, the world&amp;#39;s biggest online shopping fest, is losing its gloss and bracing for more modest growth in coming years, hurt by a slower economy and tighter regulatory scrutiny. Alibaba (BABA) said on Friday its sales - or gross merchandise value (GMV) - during the 11 day event grew 8.5%, the slowest rate ever and the first time it came under double-digits growth. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Friday said it rejected an exchange-traded fund from VanEck that would have tracked Bitc… spot prices directly. This would have stood in contrast to the ProShares ETF (BITO), which was approved and which only tracks futures rather than prices directly.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current stock price was written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Affirm (AFRM) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $140 to $185 at Overweight. Stock currently around $149&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equifax (EFX) target raised by Needham &amp;amp; Co from $295 to $335 at Buy. Stock currently around $280&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nice (NICE) with two target raises. Stock currently around $312

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Citigroup from $328 to $364 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Royal Bank of Canada from $325 to $368 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NXP Semiconductors (NXPI) target raised by KeyCorp from $250 to $255 at Overweight. Stock currently around $218&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Finance Technologies (SOFI) target raised by Jefferies Financial from $4 to $26 at Buy. Stock currently around $23&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tapestry (TPR) with a host of target raises. Average price target $55 at Overweight. Stock currently around $45&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weibo (WB) target raised by Citigroup from $63 to $66 at Buy. Stock currently around $46&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“In my view, the biggest investment risk is not the volatility of prices, but whether you will suffer a permanent loss of capital. Not only is the mere drop in stock prices not risk, but it is an opportunity. Where else do you look for cheap stocks?” - Li Lu&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thanks to you all, I'm buying my wife a new Tesla for Christmas]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsiab0/thanks_to_you_all_im_buying_my_wife_a_new_tesla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsiab0/thanks_to_you_all_im_buying_my_wife_a_new_tesla/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 01:39:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wealthy young investors don’t see use for the wealth-management firms their parents rely on]]></title><description><![CDATA[> Rich Millennials to Financial Advisers: Thanks for the Golf Invite, but You
> Can’t Invest My Money

WSJ recently wrote an article about it.

Have you ever thought of going to money managers? Maybe you tried - what was the
expirince?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qslgdm/wealthy_young_investors_dont_see_use_for_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qslgdm/wealthy_young_investors_dont_see_use_for_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 01:39:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rich Millennials to Financial Advisers: Thanks for the Golf Invite, but You Can’t Invest My Money&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WSJ recently wrote an article about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever thought of going to money managers? Maybe you tried - what was the expirince?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Workers quit jobs in record numbers as consumer sentiment hits 10-year low]]></title><description><![CDATA[Its fascinating to see how workers are quitting their jobs at a torrid pace but
also that consumers are not being as confident. There could be a lag between the
higher wages and the more recent porce increases causing these issues.

Would not be surprised to see peak earnings in Q4 before lower…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsn6yl/workers_quit_jobs_in_record_numbers_as_consumer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsn6yl/workers_quit_jobs_in_record_numbers_as_consumer/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 01:39:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Its fascinating to see how workers are quitting their jobs at a torrid pace but also that consumers are not being as confident. There could be a lag between the higher wages and the more recent porce increases causing these issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would not be surprised to see peak earnings in Q4 before lower confidence and higher prices really set into corporate earnings over the next year or so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/consumer-sentiment-hits-10-year-low-while-workers-quit-jobs-in-record-numbers.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/consumer-sentiment-hits-10-year-low-while-workers-quit-jobs-in-record-numbers.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[lets do it again]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsm8mh/lets_do_it_again/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsm8mh/lets_do_it_again/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 01:39:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can we talk about GameStop?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m a bit new to the investing game so my apologies if I missed the discussions
on this. I followed the GameStoo saga earlier this year and recently started
looking again at the two big subreddits supporting it.

To my understanding, the theory goes that the shorts never actually sold…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsje5u/can_we_talk_about_gamestop/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsje5u/can_we_talk_about_gamestop/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:31:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m a bit new to the investing game so my apologies if I missed the discussions on this. I followed the GameStoo saga earlier this year and recently started looking again at the two big subreddits supporting it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To my understanding, the theory goes that the shorts never actually sold their positions (because they would have gone bankrupt), but instead used all sorts of trickery to delay and avoid. Some ppl, have caught on to this and are determined to hold the stock such that when the chickens come home to roost and the shorts are forced to close, will trigger, they’ll be able to skyrocket the price. I’ve seen claims that a single share could be worth millions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This of course sounds fantastical and far-fetched but would someone mind explaining how seemingly so many ppl have adopted this belief and are all-in on a once hated retail store? IE where are they wrong in their analysis? Is it just a case of the human factor not being realized; that once the price jumps a bit, ppl will start to sell, so the idea of holding into the 1000s plus is unrealistic?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I’m still smiling]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsa3fj/im_still_smiling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsa3fj/im_still_smiling/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:31:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just clicked on a scam on Discord and my MetaMask wallet was wiped clean. Nice way to head into the weekend. 

I'm NGMI]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459281438172491778</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459281438172491778</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 23:38:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta and Microsoft announce partnership to integrate Workplace and Teams]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/10/meta-and-microsoft-announce-partnership-to-integrate-workplace-and-teams.html

Meta, the company formerly known as Facebook, announced a partnership that will
allow customers to integrate Workplace with Microsoft Teams.

The partnership between Meta and Microsoft…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsm2ow/meta_and_microsoft_announce_partnership_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsm2ow/meta_and_microsoft_announce_partnership_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 23:38:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/10/meta-and-microsoft-announce-partnership-to-integrate-workplace-and-teams.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/10/meta-and-microsoft-announce-partnership-to-integrate-workplace-and-teams.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meta, the company formerly known as Facebook, announced a partnership that will allow customers to integrate Workplace with Microsoft Teams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The partnership between Meta and Microsoft brings together two rivals that compete in the market of enterprise communication software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The partnership could prove most beneficial to Meta, whose Workplace service lags drastically behind its competitors in terms of users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is definitely a good partnership news that will benefit both companies. Microsoft teams is gaining more marketshare as it integrates into other softwares. The partnership could prove most beneficial to Meta as teams could help to boost its Workplace enterprise social network software users. Both stocks should be in the portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pssst, need some greens Sir?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsdeyo/pssst_need_some_greens_sir/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsdeyo/pssst_need_some_greens_sir/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 22:46:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Investing your emergency fund]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello! I was listening to an episode of The Millenial Investing podcast the
other day. In this episode, the host interviews Chris Kawaja. Chris makes the
argument that it is better to invest your emergency fund rather than keep it as
cash. He proposes investing 88% in bonds and the other 12% in a…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsha3j/investing_your_emergency_fund/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsha3j/investing_your_emergency_fund/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 22:34:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello! I was listening to an episode of The Millenial Investing podcast the other day. In this episode, the host interviews Chris Kawaja. Chris makes the argument that it is better to invest your emergency fund rather than keep it as cash. He proposes investing 88% in bonds and the other 12% in a S&amp;amp;P 500 index fund. Historically, this combination has kept up or beaten inflation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you guys think? Anyone take this approach?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[About Disney Stocks]]></title><description><![CDATA[So I cashed out about 2 weeks ago and a sitting on a large sum of cash waiting
for the right opportunity. Right now with the huge 15$ drop of Disney in the
past 5 days, what do you guys think about investing all 20k into DIS?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsgldu/about_disney_stocks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsgldu/about_disney_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 22:14:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I cashed out about 2 weeks ago and a sitting on a large sum of cash waiting for the right opportunity. Right now with the huge 15$ drop of Disney in the past 5 days, what do you guys think about investing all 20k into DIS?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This bull market is like any other... or is it?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I've been investing since a few years, so I have no idea of how it felt to
invest pre 2008. I see a lot of 'PE doesn't matter anymore', 'this cycle is
different' and that kind of comments, and my first thought is to discard them as
inexperienced thoughts from people who, like me, don't know what a…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsbs5s/this_bull_market_is_like_any_other_or_is_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsbs5s/this_bull_market_is_like_any_other_or_is_it/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 22:14:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been investing since a few years, so I have no idea of how it felt to invest pre 2008. I see a lot of &amp;#39;PE doesn&amp;#39;t matter anymore&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;this cycle is different&amp;#39; and that kind of comments, and my first thought is to discard them as inexperienced thoughts from people who, like me, don&amp;#39;t know what a serious bear market feels like. But I can&amp;#39;t pass on one thought: the information has changed. Before 2008, regular folks had access to a completely different kind of information than today. I don&amp;#39;t know how the landscape changed for institutions sinc ethen, maybe they already had access to the info we use nowadays to base our decisions, maybe they even had algo trading already, but the internet was so different that it must have made a tremendous impact for them as well. It seems a relevant discussion to be had, so I&amp;#39;m asking you: do you believe this time is different? If you don&amp;#39;t, what&amp;#39;s your counter argument?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Toshiba To Split Into Three]]></title><description><![CDATA[Conglomerates are breaking up like it's nobody's business this week. First GE
and now a direct GE-competitor, Toshiba, whose roots date back to 1875. In
addition we have the Johnson and Johnson s split. We should almost expect
Siemens to follow the same
path.  https://www.wsj.com/articles/toshiba…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsd3uu/toshiba_to_split_into_three/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsd3uu/toshiba_to_split_into_three/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 21:53:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conglomerates are breaking up like it&amp;#39;s nobody&amp;#39;s business this week. First GE and now a direct GE-competitor, Toshiba, whose roots date back to 1875. In addition we have the Johnson and Johnson s split. We should almost expect Siemens to follow the same path.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/toshiba-like-ge-plans-to-split-into-three-parts-11636700609?mod=hp_lead_pos3&quot;&gt;https://www.wsj.com/articles/toshiba-like-ge-plans-to-split-into-three-parts-11636700609?mod=hp_lead_pos3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[It's just a part of basic trader skillset]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsc3lg/its_just_a_part_of_basic_trader_skillset/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsc3lg/its_just_a_part_of_basic_trader_skillset/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 20:23:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What are the most tax efficient Vanguard brokerage funds?]]></title><description><![CDATA[As of right now, I have a little too much in cash. Currently maxing out my IRA
and 401k. What are the most efficient Vanguard non-tax advantaged funds? I was
thinking a simple 80/20 VTI/VXUS. Bonds aren't doing anything right now, so no
use getting into those.

One looming concern I have, and Jack…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs9id6/what_are_the_most_tax_efficient_vanguard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs9id6/what_are_the_most_tax_efficient_vanguard/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 18:00:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of right now, I have a little too much in cash.  Currently maxing out my IRA and 401k.  What are the most efficient Vanguard non-tax advantaged funds? I was thinking a simple 80/20 VTI/VXUS.  Bonds aren&amp;#39;t doing anything right now, so no use getting into those.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One looming concern I have, and Jack Bogle talks about this in his book, is &amp;quot;reversion of the mean&amp;quot;.  He even said in an interview that sometimes you do have to time the market.  But that&amp;#39;s just my personal choice, and I am going to choose to wait until the reversion of the mean to invest in a non-tax advantaged account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So thoughts on taxable ETFs? Reinvest dividends? Use dividends to pay taxes?  Are VTI and VXUS good choices?  Is skipping bonds completely a bad choice?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How did you convince yourself to sell your last individual stock winners and go complete 3-fund portfolio?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am almost completely a Bogelhead with a 4-fund (VOO, VXUS, VGIT, TIP). But I
still hang on to a couple winners from the past: AMZN, AAPL, MSFT, ZEN, PRGFX.
How did you justify pulling the trigger?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsdb10/how_did_you_convince_yourself_to_sell_your_last/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsdb10/how_did_you_convince_yourself_to_sell_your_last/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 17:33:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am almost completely a Bogelhead with a 4-fund (VOO, VXUS, VGIT, TIP). But I still hang on to a couple winners from the past: AMZN, AAPL, MSFT, ZEN, PRGFX. How did you justify pulling the trigger?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Autism Bets]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs96pb/autism_bets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs96pb/autism_bets/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 17:04:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sky high inflation isn't due to "supply chain bottlenecks", it's due to printing too much money]]></title><description><![CDATA[I see a lot of articles and posts these days talking about supply chain issues:
whether it's about how expensive it is to buy a shipping container, or that
there isn't enough space at shipping ports, or that there aren't enough
truckers, etc. etc.

However, these are all micro-level symptoms of a…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsdxg3/sky_high_inflation_isnt_due_to_supply_chain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsdxg3/sky_high_inflation_isnt_due_to_supply_chain/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 17:04:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I see a lot of articles and posts these days talking about supply chain issues: whether it&amp;#39;s about how expensive it is to buy a shipping container, or that there isn&amp;#39;t enough space at shipping ports, or that there aren&amp;#39;t enough truckers, etc. etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, these are all micro-level symptoms of a macro-level problem. Don&amp;#39;t miss the forest for the trees. Journalists need to write something new every day (or every hour it seems), even if there isn&amp;#39;t anything new to say. Which leads to a lot of noise that clouds your mind from making sense of what is really happening in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my view, the problem is clear: governments overdid it with stimulus. Unlike the 2008 Global Financial Crisis where policymakers did too little and acted too slow, this time around governments decided to err on the side of doing too much too quickly. If you look at consumer spending on FRED, it didn&amp;#39;t just fully recovery from the 2020 shock, it&amp;#39;s arguably on a stronger trajectory than it otherwise would be without the pandemic! At the same time, unemployment is still high and labor force participation is dreadfully low! The Fed created such a tremendous wealth effect, people are earning multiple years worth of stock market returns in the span of months. I&amp;#39;m not surprised many people are taking career breaks or retiring early. So why do we have red hot inflation? Because we&amp;#39;re printing more money and making less things, it&amp;#39;s that simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The inflation problem highlights how difficult it is to be a policymaker. On one hand, you don&amp;#39;t want to under spend and risk seeing long-term economic scarring, but if you stimulate too much, you risk fueling inflation as well as asset price bubbles. The other factor at play is the politicization of economic policy. You&amp;#39;re everyone&amp;#39;s favorite politician when you&amp;#39;re fueling spending, but it&amp;#39;s hard to get reelected when you advocate for cutbacks. Prudent policymaking requires spending when times are bad, and building reserves when times are good - politicians have forgot about the latter half of that equation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[At current prices, which would you choose between V, MA, and PYPL?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Paypal at PE of 48.6

Mastercard at 43.6

Visa at 37.4

While Paypal is the most expensive purely from PE point of view, I'm leaning
more towards them because they've historically had higher revenue growth
compared to the other two and they're diversified or are trying to diversity
into things like…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs4tiv/at_current_prices_which_would_you_choose_between/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs4tiv/at_current_prices_which_would_you_choose_between/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:59:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paypal at PE of 48.6&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mastercard at 43.6&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Visa at 37.4&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Paypal is the most expensive purely from PE point of view, I&amp;#39;m leaning more towards them because they&amp;#39;ve historically had higher revenue growth compared to the other two and they&amp;#39;re diversified or are trying to diversity into things like crypto, stock broker, etc. Also Paypal is around 33% off from its 52 week high, which is far lower than V or MA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you had to pick one out of these 3? Which would you buy at today&amp;#39;s prices?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Revenue (TTM)...
Rivian: $0
GM: $131 billion
Ford: $135 billion

Net Income (TTM)...
Rivian: -$1.6 billion
GM: $11.1 billion
Ford: $2.9 billion

Market Cap...
Rivian: $105 billion
GM: $90 billion
Ford: $78 billion

$RIVN $GM $F

Data via @ycharts https://t.co/xlR1mX989K]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459153703320043523</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459153703320043523</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:47:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sell Vanguard ETFs (VTI) and move to Vanguard mutual fund(VTSAX)]]></title><description><![CDATA[I opened a non tax advantaged Vanguard account separate from my retirement
accounts. My Vanguard account is just for personal investing

I didn’t want to allot enough to meet the $3k minimums for admiral shares for my
3 fund portfolio.

As time goes on or more money becomes available should I being…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs99dt/sell_vanguard_etfs_vti_and_move_to_vanguard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs99dt/sell_vanguard_etfs_vti_and_move_to_vanguard/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:47:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I opened a non tax advantaged Vanguard account separate from my retirement accounts. My Vanguard account is just for personal investing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t want to allot enough to meet the $3k minimums for admiral shares for my 3 fund portfolio. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As time goes on or more money becomes available should I being selling the ETFs and use the proceeds to move my 3 fund portfolio to Vanguard mutual funds instead of ETFs?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Makes sense.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsbj9q/makes_sense/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsbj9q/makes_sense/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Your wife, your wife’s bf, you after your stocks blow up]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs599y/your_wife_your_wifes_bf_you_after_your_stocks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs599y/your_wife_your_wifes_bf_you_after_your_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What Do You Wish Someone Told You Before You Began Investing?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm a beginner investor learning all the basics currently and educating myself
as best as I can to be successful and was wondering: what do you guys think are
some vital concepts/methods/tools that led to your successes? Most importantly,
what led to your biggest failures and how did you recover?…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsavil/what_do_you_wish_someone_told_you_before_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsavil/what_do_you_wish_someone_told_you_before_you/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 14:47:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m a beginner investor learning all the basics currently and educating myself as best as I can to be successful and was wondering: what do you guys think are some vital concepts/methods/tools that led to your successes? Most importantly, what led to your biggest failures and how did you recover? Failure is truly a teacher and I want to hear about yours! I figure that I could go into the market and fail again myself (down 46% already lmao), or I could utilize the failures from the three million investors on here!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Johnson & Johnson plans to split into two companies, separating consumer health business]]></title><description><![CDATA[Shares of Johnson & Johnson jumped in premarket trading after the healthcare
giant announced that it is splitting itself into two publicly traded companies.

The new companies will consist of one focused on consumer products, such as
Band-Aid bandages and baby powder, and another focused on…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs9ko5/johnson_johnson_plans_to_split_into_two_companies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs9ko5/johnson_johnson_plans_to_split_into_two_companies/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 14:35:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares of Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson jumped in premarket trading after the healthcare giant announced that it is splitting itself into two publicly traded companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new companies will consist of one focused on consumer products, such as Band-Aid bandages and baby powder, and another focused on prescription drugs and medical devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson was already undergoing a major transition, as CEO Alex Gorsky has previously announced that he will step down in January. Joaquin Duato, who was tapped as Gorsky’s successor, will lead the new J&amp;amp;J following the spinoff, the company said Friday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the company said it planned to keep its total dividend “at least at the same level” following the change. J&amp;amp;J currently sports a divided yield of about 2.6%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson plans to split into two companies, separating consumer health business &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/jj-shares-jump-after-ceo-says-health-giant-plans-to-break-up-in-wsj-report.html?__source=iosappshare%7Ccom.apple.UIKit.activity.CopyToPasteboard&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/jj-shares-jump-after-ceo-says-health-giant-plans-to-break-up-in-wsj-report.html?__source=iosappshare%7Ccom.apple.UIKit.activity.CopyToPasteboard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Still don't get options/futures and how they work or what's the point of them]]></title><description><![CDATA[So I've watched the videos on options and futures and I get that they're both
different but maintain a similar principle that like you get the right to
buy/sell something in the future but fundamentally it doesn't make any sense to
me.

Like why wouldn't you just buy or hold something? What…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs3vvg/still_dont_get_optionsfutures_and_how_they_work/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs3vvg/still_dont_get_optionsfutures_and_how_they_work/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 14:35:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;#39;ve watched the videos on options and futures and I get that they&amp;#39;re both different but maintain a similar principle that like you get the right to buy/sell something in the future but fundamentally it doesn&amp;#39;t make any sense to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like why wouldn&amp;#39;t you just buy or hold something? What advantage do options or futures give you over just traditional investing? I get things like margin or leverage as in riskily buying more than you can afford but I just don&amp;#39;t get what the point or how options or futures work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, options sounds like ok I&amp;#39;ll buy the right to buy a stock at this price, if it goes down I just won&amp;#39;t fulfill the obligation because I don&amp;#39;t have to and if it goes up then sure I&amp;#39;ll fulfill the contract. Again, that&amp;#39;s definitely not right because that would just be an infinite money glitch because you would always never take the option if it&amp;#39;s going down and always take it if it goes up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Futures makes a little more sense because you have to oblige the contract. But then why wouldn&amp;#39;t you just buy something normally? What&amp;#39;s the benefit of buying at a set time?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL:DR, genuinely have no idea how options/futures work and what their point is, and I probably sound really dumb but if someone can explain in a way that makes sense I would really appreciate that, thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Paysafe - Buy the dip or GTFO?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Paysafe (PSFE) stock dropped 40% today following a soberiing Q3 earnings report
where company revenue dropped 1% from Q3 2020.

Up until now, analysts had been quite high on Paysafe, particularly as the
market for online gambling has grown, and as it acquired several smaller
European fintech…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qru6rq/paysafe_buy_the_dip_or_gtfo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qru6rq/paysafe_buy_the_dip_or_gtfo/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 14:20:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paysafe (PSFE) stock dropped 40% today following a soberiing Q3 earnings report where company revenue dropped 1% from Q3 2020. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Up until now, analysts had been quite high on Paysafe, particularly as the market for online gambling has grown, and as it acquired several smaller European fintech companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have about 2% of my portfolio in Paysafe, and until today was already at a -12% ROI, but that&amp;#39;s in part bexause I was already buying it&amp;#39;s not 10 month dip. The plan was to hold for no fewer than five years. Is it time to double down and take advantage of the freefall, or cut losses and bail?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Johnson and Johnson planning on splitting into two separate companies!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Will be separating it's consumer division from it's pharmaceutical and medical
device division. What's everyone's take on this new direction? Johnson and
Johnson is the world's largest health products companies by sales but believes
that the two divisions directions and growth are diverging rapidly.…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs9jsv/johnson_and_johnson_planning_on_splitting_into/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs9jsv/johnson_and_johnson_planning_on_splitting_into/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 13:56:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will be separating it&amp;#39;s consumer division from it&amp;#39;s pharmaceutical and medical device division. What&amp;#39;s everyone&amp;#39;s take on this new direction?   Johnson and Johnson is the world&amp;#39;s largest health products companies by sales but believes that the two divisions directions and growth are diverging rapidly. 
     Is this the right direction for them to take?   No decision yet one what they will do when it comes to holding a stock offering.&lt;br/&gt;
     I&amp;#39;ve always felt J n J was a safe long term hold how does this change that now?  More growth potential with the pharmaceutical division but comes with more risk too.  As the WSJ article states the consumer division comes with its own  issues,  as it&amp;#39;s  &amp;quot;Sales are growing more slowly than at the other businesses, and have lower margins too. &amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does this make sense? EV Discussion ($RIVN) ($LCID) ($TSLA) ($F)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Electric-vehicle startup Rivian (RIVN) has roared into public markets with a
killer public offering and a market value of $116 billion. That’s 32% more than
General Motors (GM) is worth, and 47% more than Ford (F). Rivian has never sold
a vehicle until this year. GM sells around 7 million vehicles…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrz8ji/does_this_make_sense_ev_discussion_rivn_lcid_tsla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrz8ji/does_this_make_sense_ev_discussion_rivn_lcid_tsla/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 13:31:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Electric-vehicle startup Rivian (RIVN) has roared into public markets with a killer public offering and a market value of $116 billion. That’s 32% more than General Motors (GM) is worth, and 47% more than Ford (F). Rivian has never sold a vehicle until this year. GM sells around 7 million vehicles per year; Ford, 4 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you add up the market value of Tesla (TSLA), Rivian, and 5 other startups including Lucid (LCID), Nikola (NKLA), Fisker (FSR), Lordstown Motors (RIDE) and Workhorse (WKHS), their combined capitalization is nearly $1.3 trillion. Nine of the world’s biggest automakers—GM, Ford, Stellantis, Toyota, Nissan, Honda, Volkswagen, BMW and Daimler-Benz—are only worth $845 billion. So those 9 giant automakers are worth 34% less than 7 fledgling EV manufacturers. As for sales, the established manufacturers outsell the EV upstarts 100 to 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The market now seems to view &lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rivian-ceo-sees-annual-production-144553789.html&quot;&gt;Rivian&lt;/a&gt; as a Tesla-in-the-making, especially since it already has backing from Amazon and Ford. By focusing on sport pickups and delivery vans, Rivian has one foot in consumer vehicles and the other in commercial applications, a shrewd mix that lets the company spread its bets on a trend that is already a revolution in ground transportation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Growth.&lt;/strong&gt; In market terms, investors consider &lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-is-not-enough-engine-no-1-bets-on-gm-white-paper-details-electric-vehicle-landscape-124811083.html&quot;&gt;EV newcomers&lt;/a&gt; such as Tesla and Rivian to be growth and technology companies with tons of upside potential. Traditional automakers are industrial concerns capable of incremental growth, at best. While virtually every big automaker is developing EV technology, the old ones won’t attain nearly the same rapid growth as the new ones will. That’s because they have massive investments in internal-combustion engines, or ICE—a.k.a. gas-and diesel-powered cars—that will decline as the new EV technology ramps up. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GM, for instance, sold 202,000 EVs in 2020, which was third most of any automaker, behind Tesla and Volkswagen. But for GM the technology of the future represented just 3% of all sales. The other 97% were legacy ICE vehicles likely to decline as a share of the overall market for years to come. At Tesla, 100% of sales were EVs, with no legacy business to manage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new technology is where the growth is. Tesla’s revenue growth rate during the last two years has been 39%, according to S&amp;amp;P Capital IQ. GM’s has been a negative 5%. Pandemic disruptions have been a factor in both company’s performance, but the trend was the same before the pandemic. GM still makes a lot of money selling high-margin pickups and SUVs, but investors view that as a business that could someday dwindle to no profit at all. Electrics, by contrast, will only get more profitable as costs drop, technology advances and more people buy them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capital.&lt;/strong&gt; Traditional carmakers such as GM and Ford argue that the profitability of existing lineups gives them an advantage because they have in-house funding for new EV technology. But startups haven’t needed in-house funding because capital markets have been a ready source of money. “Capital for EV [manufacturers] is widely available and cheap in current market conditions, so we believe momentum/support for many of the stocks will persist,” analyst John Murphy of Bank of America wrote in a recent research note. “As has proven the case for Tesla over the past decade, the higher the upward spiral of stock, the cheaper capital becomes to fund growth.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/its-bizarro-world-in-the-auto-industry-again-203740250.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/its-bizarro-world-in-the-auto-industry-again-203740250.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Investing with Leverage [Ben Felix on Leveraged ETFs]]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrs6wk/investing_with_leverage_ben_felix_on_leveraged/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrs6wk/investing_with_leverage_ben_felix_on_leveraged/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 12:38:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[One way or another I'm getting there!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs6dd0/one_way_or_another_im_getting_there/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs6dd0/one_way_or_another_im_getting_there/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 12:38:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ford stock and Rivian stock]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ok, I’m completely confused and need help understanding. I can’t possibly
understand how Ford motor company has been around for so long and has an
established business model that is progressively going to change here in the
next couple of years to electric vehicles. Since Rivian hit the market all…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs3uds/ford_stock_and_rivian_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs3uds/ford_stock_and_rivian_stock/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 11:34:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok, I’m completely confused and need help understanding. I can’t possibly understand how Ford motor company has been around for so long and has an established business model that is progressively going to change here in the next couple of years to electric vehicles. Since Rivian hit the market all kinds of questions have come to mind especially the market cap of these companies and how they’re surpassing other companies that have been around for decades. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can someone explain to me how Ford stock is $19.00 a share at $100B market value and the most sold truck in America…Yet, Rivian sold 156 trucks to date and the stock is $124.00 ish and $120B market. This makes so sense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Analysts seem to just make up price targets as stocks shoot higher]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-nvda-stock-price-target-boosts-earnings-51636640350?siteid=yhoof2

"Nvidia Stock Gets a 49% Price Target Boost Before Earnings. Why Analysts Are
Bullish.
Analysts led by Rick Schafer at Oppenheimer reiterated their Outperform rating
on Nvidia stock and raised…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs5xcq/analysts_seem_to_just_make_up_price_targets_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs5xcq/analysts_seem_to_just_make_up_price_targets_as/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 11:22:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-nvda-stock-price-target-boosts-earnings-51636640350?siteid=yhoof2&quot;&gt;https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-nvda-stock-price-target-boosts-earnings-51636640350?siteid=yhoof2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Nvidia Stock Gets a 49% Price Target Boost Before Earnings. Why Analysts Are Bullish.&lt;br/&gt;
 Analysts led by Rick Schafer at Oppenheimer reiterated their Outperform rating on Nvidia stock and raised their target price on the shares by 49% to $350 from $235.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Meanwhile, Christopher Rolland at Susquehanna reiterated his Positive rating on Nvidia stock and hiked his target price to $360 from $250. &amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it just me or do these guys just raise their prise targets as the stock soars so their performance on websites like tipranks doesn&amp;#39;t suffer? Nothing about nvidia&amp;#39;s performance has changed this quarter that would suddenly warrant an increase of nvidia&amp;#39;s market cap by 300 billion dollars. I think price targets are an important tool, especially for retail investors, but lately these guys seem to just make it up as they go. At $350b nvidia is a 900b company on 10b of forward net earnings. That&amp;#39;s just bonkers and these guys seem to base their price targets on how far they think the current bull market can inflate the ever increasing sentiment instead of what the stock is fundamentally worth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Things to do on January 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[My state has tax deductions on money contributed to a 529 account so I plan to
invest it all on (the first trading day after) January 1. Are there any things I
should be doing at the start of the year?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrxckw/things_to_do_on_january_1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrxckw/things_to_do_on_january_1/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 07:56:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My state has tax deductions on money contributed to a 529 account so I plan to invest it all on (the first trading day after) January 1. Are there any things I should be doing at the start of the year?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is an actual logical reason that Berkshire does not pay a dividend?]]></title><description><![CDATA[So the old excuse "Buffett is better at investing it than you" simply doesn't
make sense (anymore)

 1. Buffett is stockpiling his cash in savings and not even investing it
 2. The company has reached economies of scale and has a hard time growing so
    realistically, even if you aren't better off…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs1a74/what_is_an_actual_logical_reason_that_berkshire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs1a74/what_is_an_actual_logical_reason_that_berkshire/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 07:43:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So the old excuse &amp;quot;Buffett is better at investing it than you&amp;quot; simply doesn&amp;#39;t make sense (anymore)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Buffett is stockpiling his cash in savings and not even investing it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The company has reached economies of scale and has a hard time growing so realistically, even if you aren&amp;#39;t better off investing it, it makes more sense for the cash to be distributed to shareholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It really makes no sense. Can someone explain it to me?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Need a good brokerage account, ASAP]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tried to set up my Roth IRA account today through Vanguard but for some reason
the site wasn't letting me go through with the setup- whatever. Decided to call
Vanguard, and after 30 minutes of waiting I was finally on the phone with an
associate. Turns out they've been having site issues for 2…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs2q71/need_a_good_brokerage_account_asap/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs2q71/need_a_good_brokerage_account_asap/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 07:30:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tried to set up my Roth IRA account today through Vanguard but for some reason the site wasn&amp;#39;t letting me go through with the setup- whatever. Decided to call Vanguard, and after 30 minutes of waiting I was finally on the phone with an associate. Turns out they&amp;#39;ve been having site issues for 2 months now- how convenient. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The associate created an account for me which I greatly appreciated, and he gave me some paperwork to fill out about taxes, place of work, etc. I was pretty frustrated after my call, so I decided that I&amp;#39;d work on this paperwork later, so I logged out of the site. Tried to log back on just now and it turns out that I can&amp;#39;t even log back, and now I have to recall about getting back in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After the nightmare that was setting up an account in the first place&lt;/strong&gt;, I really don&amp;#39;t want to go through this process again. Is it worth it just to set up an account with Fidelity instead? Even Robinhood seems better than this. What should I do?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aswath Damodoran's Tesla Valuation]]></title><description><![CDATA[Whatever your thoughts on Tesla, gotta respect one of the best teacher's of
finance who I know for his work in calculating the equity risk premium. Pretty
interesting read. I have no hard opinions on Tesla beyond the fact that I like
their cars, but this is one of the more intellectually honest and…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs0jf3/aswath_damodorans_tesla_valuation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs0jf3/aswath_damodorans_tesla_valuation/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 06:32:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever your thoughts on Tesla, gotta respect one of the best teacher&amp;#39;s of finance who I know for his work in calculating the equity risk premium. Pretty interesting read.  I have no hard opinions on Tesla beyond the fact that I like their cars,  but this is one of the more intellectually honest and humble attempts at intrinsically valuing the company. &lt;a href=&quot;https://aswathdamodaran.blogspot.com/2021/11/teslas-trillion-dollar-moment-valuation.html&quot;&gt;https://aswathdamodaran.blogspot.com/2021/11/teslas-trillion-dollar-moment-valuation.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Footage of JPow finding out about inflation.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrpp8b/footage_of_jpow_finding_out_about_inflation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrpp8b/footage_of_jpow_finding_out_about_inflation/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 06:32:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[It's ya boy, bundog. I'm back with another YOLO. (WISH)]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qruurh/its_ya_boy_bundog_im_back_with_another_yolo_wish/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qruurh/its_ya_boy_bundog_im_back_with_another_yolo_wish/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 06:03:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Q3 2021]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs2sii/q3_2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs2sii/q3_2021/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 06:03:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The rise of NFT marketplaces is mostly because there is demand for a regulated property exchange that doesn't yet exist.]]></title><description><![CDATA[NFTs aren't new or innovative. We've been attaching unique IDs to items for
thousands of years. I think people will soon figure out that not everything
needs to be on the blockchain and that NFT marketplaces would be better suited
on a centralized server, not Ethereum. When you own an NFT, you don't…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qru4zs/the_rise_of_nft_marketplaces_is_mostly_because/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qru4zs/the_rise_of_nft_marketplaces_is_mostly_because/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 05:49:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NFTs aren&amp;#39;t new or innovative. We&amp;#39;ve been attaching unique IDs to items for thousands of years. I think people will soon figure out that not everything needs to be on the blockchain and that NFT marketplaces would be better suited on a centralized server, not Ethereum.   When you own an NFT, you don&amp;#39;t own the legal rights to the JPEG, nor do you even own a JPEG. You are really just buying a shitcoin that has a link to a JPEG URL. In ten years time all their NFTs will be deleted 404 pages and all you will have is a worthless shitcoin. There&amp;#39;s also a lot of problems with NFTs regarding intellectual property theft, as people can auction off property they have no legal right to sell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is merit to a marketplace of property though. There isn&amp;#39;t a regulated exchange for collectables in America. We have the NYSE for stocks, CME for commodities, but we don&amp;#39;t have one to trade collectable/non fungible items. Because such a thing doesn&amp;#39;t exist, blockchain based marketplaces are filling the void for that niche in the meantime. I think the preferred medium is a regulated exchange where real people are KYC&amp;#39;d and vetted before pushing an auction to sale. The obvious advantage of it is that governments will recognize property rights of the sales. You can still settle all of the transactions digitally, but it will take place on centralized servers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Here is a Market Recap for today Thursday, Nov 11, 2021. Please enjoy!]]></title><description><![CDATA[PsychoMarket Recap - Thursday, November 11, 2021

The market finished mixed on Thursday, as market participants continue to
grapple with the implication of the latest inflation report and third-quarter
earnings, which are showing signs of slowing down as it winds down. The S&P 500
(SPY) and Nasdaq…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrvj62/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_thursday_nov_11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrvj62/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_thursday_nov_11/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 05:00:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Thursday, November 11, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The market finished mixed on Thursday, as market participants continue to grapple with the implication of the latest inflation report and third-quarter earnings, which are showing signs of slowing down as it winds down. The S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) and Nasdaq (QQQ) rose after two consecutive down days, as tech stocks made a comeback, closing 0.04% and 0.28% higher, led by a rebound in technology stocks, while the Dow Jones (DIA) closed 0.44% lower. The Russell 2000 (IWM), which tracks the performance of small-caps, rose 0.8% higher. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a slow news days due to it being Veteran’s Day holiday in the US, market participants continue to digest the Consumer Price Index released tomorrow, which showed prices of consumer good surging 6.2%.  in a year-on-year period, accelerating from September’s 5.4% YoY rate, and higher than the 5.9% expected. This represents that fastest pace of inflationary expansion since 1990, though one has to take into account easy comparisons to last year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The staying power and magnitude of inflationary pressures has, perhaps, become the central question for market participants, with companies across the board reporting rising input costs and price hikes passed on to the consumers to preserve margins. While Q3 earning results have robustly demonstrated that companies in the SPY were largely able to navigate these cost pressures, the possibility remains that if inflation runs hotter than expected for longer than expected, it could begin to hamper consumer demand. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matthew Luzzetti, Chief US Economist at Deutsche Bank, said “This [the CPI report] is certainly telling us, I think, that price pressures are more persistent. They are broader. They are not just narrowly focused on those categories, whether it&amp;#39;s autos and the supply-constrained items. And it&amp;#39;s going to last longer than expected. We do think that the Fed is going to have to raise rates next year. They&amp;#39;ve signaled that they&amp;#39;re going to taper through the middle of the year, and that&amp;#39;s our baseline at this point. But if you continue to see price pressures like this over the coming months and more persistent, it may cause them to have to act earlier than expected.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With roughly 89% of companies in the S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) having already reported earnings, 81% of those have so far posted better than expected earnings per share and 75% of those reported better than expected revenue. FactSet projects that the year-on-year earnings growth rate for the index stands at 40%, though this number has continued creeping higher as earnings season unfolds. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_110521.pdf&quot;&gt;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_110521.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disney (DIS) stock slipped to an 11-month low following disappointing earnings. For the first time ever, Netflix (NFLX) has overtaken Disney’s market cap.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After its blockbuster debut to the market yesterday, shares of EV maker Rivian (RIVN) remained on fire, pushing the company well past a $100b market cap in only two days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elon Musk, CEO of Tesla (TSLA) is carrying thru with his promise to sell Tesla stock and sold about $5 billion worth of stock today&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toyota says large parts of the world are not ready for EVs and committed $240 million to building a hybrid car parts plant in West Virginia. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General Mills Inc is considering the sale of its soup brand Progresso and ready-to-eat meals label Helper for $3 billion, according to a report by Bloomberg&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chinese social media giant Tencent Holdings expects Beijing to allow &amp;#39;metaverse&amp;#39; virtual environment services, now the talk of Silicon Valley, to operate in China - provided they fall in line with Chinese rules. &amp;quot;There&amp;#39;s a lot of technologies that&amp;#39;s related to the development of games as well as for the metaverse,&amp;quot; Tencent president Martin Lau told analysts on a call peppered with questions about the metaverse.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google lost an appeal against a 2.42-billion-euro ($2.8-billion) European antitrust decision on Wednesday&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unity Software (U) buy special effects company Weta Digital for $1.3 billion. The studio, founded by Peter Jackson, was responsible for special effects in Avatar and the Lord of the Rings trilogy. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be.&amp;quot; -&lt;em&gt;Ralph Waldo Emerson&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dividends during periods of low growth]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey Bogles, this is just something rattling around in my head and I figure
smarter people have graphs to put up against it.

A lot of people talk about low growth periods like post tech bubble 2000’s, or
stagflation during the 70’s. This is often talked about as a period where “the
market remains…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrmkqg/dividends_during_periods_of_low_growth/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrmkqg/dividends_during_periods_of_low_growth/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 04:16:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey Bogles, this is just something rattling around in my head and I figure smarter people have graphs to put up against it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of people talk about low growth periods like post tech bubble 2000’s, or stagflation during the 70’s. This is often talked about as a period where “the market remains flat.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But during those periods, aren’t companies (and index funds) still paying dividends? Seems to me that you’ll have growth on the way back up as an existing asset holder. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hence why it’s important to stay the course. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully the question makes sense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Real Central Bank Rates (rate minus inflation)...
Argentina: -14.1%
US: -6.1%
Poland: -5.6%
Eurozone: -4.6%
Canada: -4.2%
Peru: -3.8%
Denmark: -3.6%
Norway: -3.3%
Chile: -3.3%
Czech Rep: -3.1%
UK: -3.0%
Brazil: -2.9%
Australia: -2.9%
Philippines: -2.6%
Sweden: -2.5%
Swiss: -2.0%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458951280450285576</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458951280450285576</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 02:08:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Paysafe ($PSFE) down 42% today, dip opportunity?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Missed earnings by a bit and guidance of the year was reduced.

Is the dip justify? Most will agree: heck no

That’s just how the current market is operating. Miss earnings and you’ll get
killed.

I believe these companies that are losing half their valuation from missed
earnings are severely…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrr105/paysafe_psfe_down_42_today_dip_opportunity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrr105/paysafe_psfe_down_42_today_dip_opportunity/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 02:08:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Missed earnings by a bit and guidance of the year was reduced. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is the dip justify? Most will agree: heck no&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s just how the current market is operating. Miss earnings and you’ll get killed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe these companies that are losing half their valuation from missed earnings are severely undervalued and will rebound in due time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe $PSFE will rebound much easier than most other beaten down stock because it was previously a spac traded publicly at $10. Institutional buyers got in at this price and now we’re 60% down from there. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s trading at a low $4 penny stock range which could be appealing to retail investors. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am starting to load up massively. Possibly make a in-depth DD post if its worth while. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is everyone thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit : in for 75k shares at 4.22 // planning to make extensive DD over the weekend&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Should I Quit?]]></title><description><![CDATA[One year ago I began "investing". After the GME frenzy I started trading options
to gain more leverage. At one point I was up 15%, but now after countless losses
I have a total account at -86%.

This upsets me greatly and I feel I've financially failed at the stock market. A
year of stressing over…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrx48u/should_i_quit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrx48u/should_i_quit/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 02:08:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;One year ago I began &amp;quot;investing&amp;quot;. After the GME frenzy I started trading options to gain more leverage. At one point I was up 15%, but now after countless losses I have a total account at -86%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This upsets me greatly and I feel I&amp;#39;ve financially failed at the stock market. A year of stressing over positions just to lose over 11K. And this isn&amp;#39;t fun money either, it&amp;#39;s all I have to my name. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My current strategies consists of calls and puts with 1-2 month expiration. Sometimes risky earnings plays. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should I try and keep trading and build my account back up? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR After one year of trading I&amp;#39;ve lost 11K (86%), where do I go from here?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>