<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 07:20:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Aswath Damodoran's Tesla Valuation]]></title><description><![CDATA[Whatever your thoughts on Tesla, gotta respect one of the best teacher's of
finance who I know for his work in calculating the equity risk premium. Pretty
interesting read. I have no hard opinions on Tesla beyond the fact that I like
their cars, but this is one of the more intellectually honest and…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs0jf3/aswath_damodorans_tesla_valuation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs0jf3/aswath_damodorans_tesla_valuation/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 06:32:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever your thoughts on Tesla, gotta respect one of the best teacher&amp;#39;s of finance who I know for his work in calculating the equity risk premium. Pretty interesting read.  I have no hard opinions on Tesla beyond the fact that I like their cars,  but this is one of the more intellectually honest and humble attempts at intrinsically valuing the company. &lt;a href=&quot;https://aswathdamodaran.blogspot.com/2021/11/teslas-trillion-dollar-moment-valuation.html&quot;&gt;https://aswathdamodaran.blogspot.com/2021/11/teslas-trillion-dollar-moment-valuation.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Footage of JPow finding out about inflation.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrpp8b/footage_of_jpow_finding_out_about_inflation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrpp8b/footage_of_jpow_finding_out_about_inflation/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 06:32:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[It's ya boy, bundog. I'm back with another YOLO. (WISH)]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qruurh/its_ya_boy_bundog_im_back_with_another_yolo_wish/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qruurh/its_ya_boy_bundog_im_back_with_another_yolo_wish/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 06:03:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Q3 2021]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs2sii/q3_2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs2sii/q3_2021/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 06:03:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The rise of NFT marketplaces is mostly because there is demand for a regulated property exchange that doesn't yet exist.]]></title><description><![CDATA[NFTs aren't new or innovative. We've been attaching unique IDs to items for
thousands of years. I think people will soon figure out that not everything
needs to be on the blockchain and that NFT marketplaces would be better suited
on a centralized server, not Ethereum. When you own an NFT, you don't…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qru4zs/the_rise_of_nft_marketplaces_is_mostly_because/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qru4zs/the_rise_of_nft_marketplaces_is_mostly_because/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 05:49:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NFTs aren&amp;#39;t new or innovative. We&amp;#39;ve been attaching unique IDs to items for thousands of years. I think people will soon figure out that not everything needs to be on the blockchain and that NFT marketplaces would be better suited on a centralized server, not Ethereum.   When you own an NFT, you don&amp;#39;t own the legal rights to the JPEG, nor do you even own a JPEG. You are really just buying a shitcoin that has a link to a JPEG URL. In ten years time all their NFTs will be deleted 404 pages and all you will have is a worthless shitcoin. There&amp;#39;s also a lot of problems with NFTs regarding intellectual property theft, as people can auction off property they have no legal right to sell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is merit to a marketplace of property though. There isn&amp;#39;t a regulated exchange for collectables in America. We have the NYSE for stocks, CME for commodities, but we don&amp;#39;t have one to trade collectable/non fungible items. Because such a thing doesn&amp;#39;t exist, blockchain based marketplaces are filling the void for that niche in the meantime. I think the preferred medium is a regulated exchange where real people are KYC&amp;#39;d and vetted before pushing an auction to sale. The obvious advantage of it is that governments will recognize property rights of the sales. You can still settle all of the transactions digitally, but it will take place on centralized servers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Here is a Market Recap for today Thursday, Nov 11, 2021. Please enjoy!]]></title><description><![CDATA[PsychoMarket Recap - Thursday, November 11, 2021

The market finished mixed on Thursday, as market participants continue to
grapple with the implication of the latest inflation report and third-quarter
earnings, which are showing signs of slowing down as it winds down. The S&P 500
(SPY) and Nasdaq…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrvj62/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_thursday_nov_11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrvj62/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_thursday_nov_11/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 05:00:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Thursday, November 11, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The market finished mixed on Thursday, as market participants continue to grapple with the implication of the latest inflation report and third-quarter earnings, which are showing signs of slowing down as it winds down. The S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) and Nasdaq (QQQ) rose after two consecutive down days, as tech stocks made a comeback, closing 0.04% and 0.28% higher, led by a rebound in technology stocks, while the Dow Jones (DIA) closed 0.44% lower. The Russell 2000 (IWM), which tracks the performance of small-caps, rose 0.8% higher. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a slow news days due to it being Veteran’s Day holiday in the US, market participants continue to digest the Consumer Price Index released tomorrow, which showed prices of consumer good surging 6.2%.  in a year-on-year period, accelerating from September’s 5.4% YoY rate, and higher than the 5.9% expected. This represents that fastest pace of inflationary expansion since 1990, though one has to take into account easy comparisons to last year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The staying power and magnitude of inflationary pressures has, perhaps, become the central question for market participants, with companies across the board reporting rising input costs and price hikes passed on to the consumers to preserve margins. While Q3 earning results have robustly demonstrated that companies in the SPY were largely able to navigate these cost pressures, the possibility remains that if inflation runs hotter than expected for longer than expected, it could begin to hamper consumer demand. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matthew Luzzetti, Chief US Economist at Deutsche Bank, said “This [the CPI report] is certainly telling us, I think, that price pressures are more persistent. They are broader. They are not just narrowly focused on those categories, whether it&amp;#39;s autos and the supply-constrained items. And it&amp;#39;s going to last longer than expected. We do think that the Fed is going to have to raise rates next year. They&amp;#39;ve signaled that they&amp;#39;re going to taper through the middle of the year, and that&amp;#39;s our baseline at this point. But if you continue to see price pressures like this over the coming months and more persistent, it may cause them to have to act earlier than expected.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With roughly 89% of companies in the S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) having already reported earnings, 81% of those have so far posted better than expected earnings per share and 75% of those reported better than expected revenue. FactSet projects that the year-on-year earnings growth rate for the index stands at 40%, though this number has continued creeping higher as earnings season unfolds. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_110521.pdf&quot;&gt;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_110521.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disney (DIS) stock slipped to an 11-month low following disappointing earnings. For the first time ever, Netflix (NFLX) has overtaken Disney’s market cap.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After its blockbuster debut to the market yesterday, shares of EV maker Rivian (RIVN) remained on fire, pushing the company well past a $100b market cap in only two days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elon Musk, CEO of Tesla (TSLA) is carrying thru with his promise to sell Tesla stock and sold about $5 billion worth of stock today&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toyota says large parts of the world are not ready for EVs and committed $240 million to building a hybrid car parts plant in West Virginia. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General Mills Inc is considering the sale of its soup brand Progresso and ready-to-eat meals label Helper for $3 billion, according to a report by Bloomberg&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chinese social media giant Tencent Holdings expects Beijing to allow &amp;#39;metaverse&amp;#39; virtual environment services, now the talk of Silicon Valley, to operate in China - provided they fall in line with Chinese rules. &amp;quot;There&amp;#39;s a lot of technologies that&amp;#39;s related to the development of games as well as for the metaverse,&amp;quot; Tencent president Martin Lau told analysts on a call peppered with questions about the metaverse.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google lost an appeal against a 2.42-billion-euro ($2.8-billion) European antitrust decision on Wednesday&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unity Software (U) buy special effects company Weta Digital for $1.3 billion. The studio, founded by Peter Jackson, was responsible for special effects in Avatar and the Lord of the Rings trilogy. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be.&amp;quot; -&lt;em&gt;Ralph Waldo Emerson&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dividends during periods of low growth]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey Bogles, this is just something rattling around in my head and I figure
smarter people have graphs to put up against it.

A lot of people talk about low growth periods like post tech bubble 2000’s, or
stagflation during the 70’s. This is often talked about as a period where “the
market remains…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrmkqg/dividends_during_periods_of_low_growth/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrmkqg/dividends_during_periods_of_low_growth/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 04:16:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey Bogles, this is just something rattling around in my head and I figure smarter people have graphs to put up against it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of people talk about low growth periods like post tech bubble 2000’s, or stagflation during the 70’s. This is often talked about as a period where “the market remains flat.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But during those periods, aren’t companies (and index funds) still paying dividends? Seems to me that you’ll have growth on the way back up as an existing asset holder. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hence why it’s important to stay the course. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully the question makes sense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Real Central Bank Rates (rate minus inflation)...
Argentina: -14.1%
US: -6.1%
Poland: -5.6%
Eurozone: -4.6%
Canada: -4.2%
Peru: -3.8%
Denmark: -3.6%
Norway: -3.3%
Chile: -3.3%
Czech Rep: -3.1%
UK: -3.0%
Brazil: -2.9%
Australia: -2.9%
Philippines: -2.6%
Sweden: -2.5%
Swiss: -2.0%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458951280450285576</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458951280450285576</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 02:08:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Paysafe ($PSFE) down 42% today, dip opportunity?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Missed earnings by a bit and guidance of the year was reduced.

Is the dip justify? Most will agree: heck no

That’s just how the current market is operating. Miss earnings and you’ll get
killed.

I believe these companies that are losing half their valuation from missed
earnings are severely…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrr105/paysafe_psfe_down_42_today_dip_opportunity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrr105/paysafe_psfe_down_42_today_dip_opportunity/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 02:08:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Missed earnings by a bit and guidance of the year was reduced. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is the dip justify? Most will agree: heck no&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s just how the current market is operating. Miss earnings and you’ll get killed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe these companies that are losing half their valuation from missed earnings are severely undervalued and will rebound in due time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe $PSFE will rebound much easier than most other beaten down stock because it was previously a spac traded publicly at $10. Institutional buyers got in at this price and now we’re 60% down from there. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s trading at a low $4 penny stock range which could be appealing to retail investors. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am starting to load up massively. Possibly make a in-depth DD post if its worth while. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is everyone thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit : in for 75k shares at 4.22 // planning to make extensive DD over the weekend&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Should I Quit?]]></title><description><![CDATA[One year ago I began "investing". After the GME frenzy I started trading options
to gain more leverage. At one point I was up 15%, but now after countless losses
I have a total account at -86%.

This upsets me greatly and I feel I've financially failed at the stock market. A
year of stressing over…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrx48u/should_i_quit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrx48u/should_i_quit/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 02:08:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;One year ago I began &amp;quot;investing&amp;quot;. After the GME frenzy I started trading options to gain more leverage. At one point I was up 15%, but now after countless losses I have a total account at -86%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This upsets me greatly and I feel I&amp;#39;ve financially failed at the stock market. A year of stressing over positions just to lose over 11K. And this isn&amp;#39;t fun money either, it&amp;#39;s all I have to my name. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My current strategies consists of calls and puts with 1-2 month expiration. Sometimes risky earnings plays. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should I try and keep trading and build my account back up? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR After one year of trading I&amp;#39;ve lost 11K (86%), where do I go from here?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Claiming Rittenhouse is innocent isn’t being brave. Of course he’s innocent. If you think he’s not, you’re scum]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458933743637475333</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458933743637475333</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 01:14:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Oops. I bought Disney puts at about 3 min to close yesterday and they made money. Sorry.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrn46w/oops_i_bought_disney_puts_at_about_3_min_to_close/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrn46w/oops_i_bought_disney_puts_at_about_3_min_to_close/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 01:14:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Paysafe releasing earning]]></title><description><![CDATA[Well today Paysafe announced earnings. Unfortunately they haven’t been that
good. Stock down 40%. My investment in Paysafe is down 70% now. For those of you
holding Paysafe, what are you gonna do? Buy more, sell or hold? Don’t know what
to do]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qroguj/paysafe_releasing_earning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qroguj/paysafe_releasing_earning/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 01:14:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well today Paysafe announced earnings. Unfortunately they haven’t been that good. Stock down 40%. My investment in Paysafe is down 70% now. For those of you holding Paysafe, what are you gonna do? Buy more, sell or hold? Don’t know what to do&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What does this sub think about home buying in this market?]]></title><description><![CDATA[With the maxed out 3 fund portfolios, what’s housing market mean to you guys?

“Buy when you need” regardless of price? (Obviously if you can afford it)

Thank you all for the responses!]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrsyt5/what_does_this_sub_think_about_home_buying_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrsyt5/what_does_this_sub_think_about_home_buying_in/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 01:14:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the maxed out 3 fund portfolios, what’s housing market mean to you guys?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Buy when you need” regardless of price? (Obviously if you can afford it)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you all for the responses!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ELON MUSK DID IT. HE SOLD 3,588,047 SHARES FOR $3,880,768,307.13.]]></title><description><![CDATA[FROM FINTEL:

Insider Musk Elon reports selling 242,006 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc.
at a total cost of $258,484,236.01

Insider Musk Elon reports selling 58,101 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc. at
a total cost of $59,206,941.35

insider Musk Elon reports selling 199,893 shares of $TSLA…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrcua2/elon_musk_did_it_he_sold_3588047_shares_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrcua2/elon_musk_did_it_he_sold_3588047_shares_for/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 23:46:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FROM FINTEL:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insider Musk Elon reports selling 242,006 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc. at a total cost of $258,484,236.01&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insider Musk Elon reports selling 58,101 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc. at a total cost of $59,206,941.35&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;insider Musk Elon reports selling 199,893 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc. at a total cost of $209,580,233.67&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insider Musk Elon reports selling 411,476 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc. at a total cost of $478,474,857.65&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insider Musk Elon reports selling 613,316 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc. at a total cost of $669,801,010.71&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insider Musk Elon reports selling 528,687 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc. at a total cost of $601,885,328.77&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insider Musk Elon reports selling 952,211 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc. at a total cost of $1,004,977,896.06&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insider Musk Elon reports selling 582,357 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc. at a total cost of $598,357,802.91&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One source said it was for taxes........&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s see where this lands...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nine US governors press U.S. lawmakers to pass 52 Billion semiconductor funding bill. Taiwan unreliable potentially trillions at risk.]]></title><description><![CDATA[> https://www.governor.pa.gov/newsroom/governor-wolf-bipartisan-governors-urge-congress-to-pass-chips-act-to-create-american-jobs-boost-semiconductor-production/

So far the shortage has cost 2.2 Million vehicles. That could just be a tiny
fraction if Taiwan has more serious future issues such as…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrvyuc/nine_us_governors_press_us_lawmakers_to_pass_52/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrvyuc/nine_us_governors_press_us_lawmakers_to_pass_52/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 23:15:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.governor.pa.gov/newsroom/governor-wolf-bipartisan-governors-urge-congress-to-pass-chips-act-to-create-american-jobs-boost-semiconductor-production/&quot;&gt;https://www.governor.pa.gov/newsroom/governor-wolf-bipartisan-governors-urge-congress-to-pass-chips-act-to-create-american-jobs-boost-semiconductor-production/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far the shortage has cost 2.2 Million vehicles. That could just be a tiny fraction if Taiwan has more serious future issues such as natural disasters or China invasion, which could cost businesses TRILLIONS in damages to companies such as:  Ford (F) , General Motors (GM) , and Toyota (TM), Dell Technologies (DELL),  Apples (AAPL), Google (GOOGL), AMD, NVDA, and many more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The group, which also includes the governors of auto-producing states like Alabama, said the shortage had cost automakers 2.2 million vehicles and affected 575,000 jobs in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The semiconductor funding passed the U.S. Senate earlier this year by 68-32 as part of the broader U.S. Innovation and Competition Act, or USICA. But it has not passed the House of Representatives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/world/us/nine-governors-press-us-lawmakers-pass-semiconductor-funding-bill-2021-11-10/&quot;&gt;https://www.reuters.com/world/us/nine-governors-press-us-lawmakers-pass-semiconductor-funding-bill-2021-11-10/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How much do you allocate for Large/Mid/Small caps?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Normally I’d just “VT and Chill” but I have a limited fund selection in my 401K.
The plan then would be something like this, but I worry the Smallcap allocation
is a bit too high looking at target date funds for reference:

70% FID 500 Index (FXAIX)

20% FID MID CAP IDX (FSMDX)

10% FID SM CAP IDX…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrox4q/how_much_do_you_allocate_for_largemidsmall_caps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrox4q/how_much_do_you_allocate_for_largemidsmall_caps/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 22:24:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Normally I’d just &lt;em&gt;“VT and Chill”&lt;/em&gt; but I have a limited fund selection in my 401K. The plan then would be something like this, but I worry the Smallcap allocation is a bit too high looking at target date funds for reference:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;70% FID 500 Index (FXAIX)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;20% FID MID CAP IDX (FSMDX)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;10% FID SM CAP IDX (FSSNX)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently I’m just doing a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TRowePrice Target Date Fund&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (TRPLX — it’s the only TDF available to me in the 401K), but the Expense Ratio on that is nearly half a percent (0.46) so I’m weighing just switching it over to the Fidelity SP500 + Fidelity Mid / Fidelity Small cap (significantly lower expense ratios).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly there aren’t any good options for International or Bond Funds in my 401K (options are all actively managed with laughable expense ratios) so I’d have to get those in my Taxable/Roth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I’ve done is look at Target Date Funds and it looks like Schwab for example allocates about 20% to mid cap and about 6% to Small cap. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I analyzed $SOFI so you don't have to]]></title><description><![CDATA[SOFI Technologies, Inc. is an online personal finance company. They provide a
range of lending and wealth management services. At the time of this post, they
are trading at about $23.65. They released earnings for Q3 on November 10. They
reported Revenue of $272.01 million for the 3rd quarter of…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qru1ch/i_analyzed_sofi_so_you_dont_have_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qru1ch/i_analyzed_sofi_so_you_dont_have_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 22:24:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOFI Technologies, Inc. is an online personal finance company. They provide a range of lending and wealth management services. At the time of this post, they are trading at about $23.65. They released earnings for Q3 on November 10. They reported Revenue of $272.01 million for the 3rd quarter of 2021 which is a 35.5% increase from the same prior-year period. SoFi beat estimates by $16.38M. Furthermore, they added 377,000 new members which is the second-highest quarterly increase in the company&amp;#39;s history. That being said, SoFi looks to be a potential buy. Not convinced yet? Here are some other reasons why I believe SoFi is a good company to buy into. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SoFi’s total members grew 96% Year-over-Year. Part of the reason why this occurred is because the products they offer have doubled Year-over-Year. The company beat Revenue Expectations, Earnings Per Share, almost doubled their member growth Year-over-Year and began offering way more products. Most people can find a product that suits them through SoFi’s financial services. In Quarter 3, they did a great job at  demonstrating their ability to capture market share. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SoFi has increased the amount of marketing they’ve been doing. They’ve been working with influencers across Twitter, Instagram, Youtube, and Tik Tok. Which has driven an additional 400 Million impressions and 775K engagements with SoFi content. SoFi has been investing a lot in their marketing strategy and attempts to acquire customers which has obviously translated into very great results. By the looks of it, SoFi has started to get creative in adopting additional customers. These new strategies could help boost the company by a lot. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In relation to their valuation, SoFi experienced strong growth which was driven by the growth of users they had experienced and the products they offer, especially in the personal loans sector. Right now, the company looks like it’s trading at a decent price in comparison with other companies in this sector. If the company can somehow increase their Earnings before interest, taxes, depreciation, and amortization over the years coming, they could see it’s multiples inflate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve made it this far into this post you’re probably asking yourself, Are there any risks involved with investing in this company? Like any investment, there is always a risk. Despite the fact that SoFi reported a strong quarter, they need to show that they can keep up their strength. The stock continuing to go up will be contingent on continued success and an increase in profitability over the future quarters. That being said, I wouldn’t say this is a strong buy, but a potential one. It could be a great buy if it dips again. However, This company is currently trading at reasonable multiples. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading everyone! If you have any questions let me know in the comments below or feel free to message me! I hope this helped you figure out whether or not to buy into SoFi. Also, feel free to check out my profile and see the analysis I did on Digital Turbine AKA $APPS. You will definitely learn something from it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Understanding and Profiting from our Current Inflationary Environment]]></title><description><![CDATA[Inflation is a persistent issue coming out of the COVID lockdown economy and
continues to create a great amount of confusion for the retail investor space.
Many retail traders don't know what it means or how to respond. More
specifically, many are having trouble with tailoring their portfolios to…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrtkox/understanding_and_profiting_from_our_current/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrtkox/understanding_and_profiting_from_our_current/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 22:24:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inflation is a persistent issue coming out of the COVID lockdown economy and continues to create a great amount of confusion for the retail investor space. Many retail traders don&amp;#39;t know what it means or how to respond. More specifically, many are having trouble with tailoring their portfolios to either avoid risk or take advantage of inflationary circumstances. I aim to somewhat remedy this. I hope the pointers below will help you better understand the inflationary environment and identify economically favorable industries/sectors. This is not the end all or be all and I welcome your observations and comments on what I could have missed. Enjoy this and lets make some money taking advantage of these once in a lifetime economic circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inflations is Measured by a Change in Rate:&lt;/strong&gt; Inflation doesn&amp;#39;t usually go down. The RATE of inflation goes up or down, but inflation itself is persistent. This is by design. Could you imagine what would happen to the economy if you knew that your dollar would be worth more tomorrow than it is today? Spending on goods other than necessities would come to a very dramatic reduction (&lt;em&gt;Note: You might be rethinking crypto right now huh?&lt;/em&gt;). So it is important to understand that what we are looking at is the CHANGE IN RATE of inflation. There is no deflation!! Deflation is 1000x worse for the economy than inflation. So do not expect deflation. The Fed simply will not allow it. Nor should they!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Current Inflation is Largely a Result of too Much Demand:&lt;/strong&gt; During the COVID lock downs many businesses were forced to grind their operations to a halt. Remember food, toilet paper, &amp;amp; other essentials flying off the shelves? Indeed many grocery stores were limiting the amount of water you could buy. It only stands to reason that when you force businesses to close down you create a situation where the goods that people demand are not being replaced by a steady supply. So what happens as the economy opens back up? Suddenly those same businesses have reduced inventories, they need to hire back workers, they need to order new supplies, &amp;amp; they need to meet an increased demand as a result of some competitors closing their doors for good. Now the quantity of goods demanded well exceeds the quantity of goods supplied ... on all fronts. Reopening firms are competing against other reopening firms for the same raw materials, supplies, resources, shipping, etc. They are also competing for the same labor pool. Remember that goods &amp;amp; services in times of extreme scarcity go to the highest bidder.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secondary &amp;amp; Tertiary Effects of too Much Demand (Or too Little Supply):&lt;/strong&gt; Below you will find the inflationary issues we find ourselves in as a result of increased demand and limited supply. Below each topic you will also find some examples of how to profit from each. You will also receive some examples of secondary and tertiary effects of each.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Supply Chain Bottlenecks:&lt;/strong&gt; First and foremost in the news are the supply chain bottlenecks. We&amp;#39;ve all seen the ships floating off the Port of Los Angeles, or the very long line of trucks waiting to pick up freight from the ports. The United States &amp;amp; Europe have but a limited number of ports and they&amp;#39;re taking on all the supplies that firms ordered as the economy opened back up. Making things worse ... its holiday shopping season. So cost of shipping dry bulk overseas is not just rising as a result of increased demand, but as a result of the fact that it costs money to have all these carriers waiting weeks to offload their goods. Making matters worse many of the imported goods are perishables which can spoil and reduce the supply of foodstuffs amid an already high demand. As a result many firms are opting for alternative methods of shipping like the much more expensive option of air freight.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: Moderately bullish on sea freight carriers, rail, trucking, logistics, logistics outsourcing, and air freight&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Supply Chain Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; As if the bottlenecks weren&amp;#39;t bad enough, there are but a limited number of domestic shipping firms. Firms that not only transport materials to businesses, or, finished goods to retailers, but also delivering orders to retail shoppers. Here we are once again talking about rail, trucking, mail delivery, air freight, logistics firms, logistics outsourcing, etc. So yet again we have an increased demand for shipping and logistics with but a limited supply. And while this demand will keep up for some time, many firms know it will eventually come back down to normal, and therefore, are very hesitant to expand too fast too quickly for fear that they will one day have too much fleet for future business.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: Moderately bullish on rail, trucking, logistics, logistics outsourcing, and air freight&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Semiconductor Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; Everything these days has a semiconductor. Whether its semiconductors, passive semiconductors, diodes, you name it, chances are if it was an electronic made in the last 5 years, it needs a semiconductor to properly operate. Indeed before the supply chain shortages hit critical mass, we were dealing with semiconductor shortages. Now we will not likely fix the semiconductor issue until we fix the supply chain issue. Once again as the economy opened back up &amp;amp; demand skyrocketed, semiconductors too experienced a complementary spike in demand. Semiconductors alone are preventing the automakers from producing at full capacity. There are not enough semiconductors to make vehicles. And with the holidays on the horizon semiconductors are in higher demand than ever. Even Sony had to reduce the number of PlayStations they could manufacture and ship due to component shortages and logistics issues. So expect the price of any new electronic device that has a semiconductor to increase in price.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: Bullish on electronics &amp;amp; semiconductors&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vehicle Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; As noted with the semiconductors, vehicles are in short supply. As a result the quantity of vehicles demanded exceed the quantity of vehicles supplied. Therefore we not only have a shortage of vehicles but the price o vehicles have skyrocketed. Have you seen the empty lots at your local dealership? There&amp;#39;s nothing to sell! People are ordering direct from factory. As a result people turned toward used vehicles which now are also in short supply. As a result people who could not afford the increased price of used vehicles resulted to maintaining their current vehicles. And as a result of people maintaining their current vehicles, the demand for auto parts &amp;amp; auto mechanics have skyrocketed. And I don&amp;#39;t know many large firms that do not need a frequent supply of vehicles to maintain operations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Note:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Moderately bullish to bullish on used car firms, auto parts, and car repair&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;**)**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Raw Material Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; Raw materials were the first to explode out of COVID. Wood, steel, ore, oil, &amp;amp; minerals ... you name it, its all going up. The quantity of supply demanded exceed the current supply ... and for many reasons.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Note:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Moderately bullish on miners, steel, mining equipment suppliers, and oil/gas producers ... see energy shortage below for more detail on oil/gas&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;**)**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Increased Demand for Housing:&lt;/strong&gt; Largely as a result of low interest rates incentivizing lending, we experienced a housing and construction boom in the middle of a Pandemic. Houses and industrial builds in many areas have skyrocketed in value. But this was not only as a result of low interest rates. When the federal government instituted a ban on evictions from rental properties, many took advantage by simply not paying their rent. The forgone payments to the landlord forced the renter to pass on the costs on to new tenants, which increased the cost of rental properties beyond that just owning a home in many areas. So people bought homes instead. Moreover many people moved out of urban areas to escape burdensome COVID restrictions which furthermore increased the demand of housing. Furthermore lifetime renting millennials saw the low interest rates as a great time to buy their first home. Finally, mortgage forbearance reduced a lot of foreclosures during COVID. Less foreclosures means less supply, less supply amid high demand results in higher prices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Note:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Not very bullish on housing &amp;amp; real estate at this time but still moderately bullish on construction, furniture, paint, fixtures, and infrastructure&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;**).**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Energy Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; As we began to put the COVID economy behind us, more people are travelling to work, to school, and going on vacation. More recently international travel is opening back up.  Moreover firms are expanding rapidly to meet demand and shippers are using more energy than ever. This all of course increases the price of oil, natural gas, jet fuel, and the fuel you pay at the pump. Making matters worse, no matter what your politics are, the current administration in the White House is the most ardently unfriendly domestic coal and fossil fuel administrations we&amp;#39;ve had in 5 years. OPEC, perhaps realizing that such demand will be but temporary for the next 1-2 years, refuses to entertain the Biden administrations request to ramp up oil supply. Oddly enough big oil hasn&amp;#39;t been in this good of a position for the last 4 years where the increase of supply made it seriously hard for oil firms to profit. Energy is used for producing everything. When energy goes up the cost of everything goes up. When energy goes up, people spend more on energy and less on other things. So the increase in energy costs are a result of both increased post COVID demand and politics. Of all the issues we are experiencing with inflated prices, energy is among the easiest to fix.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Note: B&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;ullish on oil, natural gas, oil and natural gas equipment maintainers and suppliers, and perhaps oil exploration if the Biden administration would quit putting up road blocks&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;**)**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Worker Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;quot;Worker Shortages&amp;quot; is misleading. When people think of a &amp;quot;worker shortage&amp;quot; they generally think that we don&amp;#39;t have enough workers to meet demand. They would be correct. But we should phrase it as &amp;quot;firms do not have enough workers to meet CURRENT demand.&amp;quot; Lets face it we are rear view looking creatures. Simply because a firm doesn&amp;#39;t have enough workers does not indicate that they cant beat previous profit/revenue, but rather they can not only beat previous revenue projections, but also be in a position where they cannot meet CURRENT demand. And just like anything else, when the quantity of labor demanded exceeds the quantity of labor supplied, we run into increased labor costs ... namely wages. And wages are overwhelmingly the highest cost for most firms. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Note:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bullish on staffing and outsourcing firms&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;**)**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secondary &amp;amp; Tertiary Effects of too Much Demand ... Conclusion:&lt;/strong&gt; Lets keep this simple. You want to buy a car. That car is made from raw materials such as aluminum &amp;amp; steel. The car requires electronics. Those electronics require semiconductors. You need a labor force to put that car together. You need energy to manufacture that car. You need truckers &amp;amp; freighters to ship those cars or bring manufacturers the materials to make cars. You need equipment to make cars. In short 100% of the price of all components of that car, or the components used to make that car, have gone up. Still, you have a high demand market where people and businesses require vehicles, but the manufacturer cant meet that demand due to the lack of supplies available. Nevertheless the vehicle manufacturer still needs to pay for overhead costs to keep the doors open. And as so many people are demanding such a short supply of cars, the manufacturers simply increase the price of that car to meet the demand of the highest paying bidders. And this phenomenon is happening in each step of the chain to make that car from the folks who supply the materials, to the folks who produce the energy, to the folks who ship the finished product. When the quantity of goods demanded exceed the quantity of goods supplied, prices necessarily must go up.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monetary Drivers of Inflation:&lt;/strong&gt;  As a result of the dramatic initial downward shift in demand amid COVID lockdowns, the Federal Reserve made money cheap, essentially lowering interests rates to both incentivize borrowing and make borrowing more affordable. The result? Massive influxes of borrowing and lending which in turn flooded the economy with cash. At first this excess cash was used to make it through the pandemic. Later this cash was used by firms to expand rapidly to meet demand. People also used cheap money via extremely low interest rates to purchase homes, which increased the demand for housing. Eventually the Fed is going to need to raise interest rates to disincentive lending and cool off a hot economy. If allowed to persist for too long the influx of cash will lead to investments by firms looking to to stave off losing the value of money via inflation and thereby creating a massive bubble. There are already indicators of this happening by virtue of equity valuations in the market. (&lt;em&gt;Note: the Fed has also been incentivizing investment in the stock market by buying treasury bonds on the secondary market which resulted in keeping the yields artificially low. As a result people were less inclined to buy treasury bonds and more incentivized to invest in other equity&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Government Drivers of Inflation:&lt;/strong&gt; The rapid inflation we are experiencing has not deterred President Biden for advocating for trillions in spending measures. The U.S. Government is a customer just like anyone else, and the government competes for the same goods and services you and I do. Increased spending will to some extent result in crowding out the private sector that competes for the same goods and services. Remember that an increase in demand with limited supply generally results increased prices. If the government spends too much, it can seriously hurt consumers in the form of increased prices. Moreover the Biden administration isn&amp;#39;t the most friendly administration when it comes to mining for coal, oil, minerals, etc.. This inevitably leads to increased costs of energy and raw materials. (&lt;em&gt;Note: This comment used a political figure as an example of a negative economic consequence. Do me a favor, take the example for what its worth to you, and realize I am not going to entertain heated political discussion. There is a cost and benefit to everything, and I don&amp;#39;t have the time to entertain the talking points you pulled from a political webpage or favorable news site and tell you why you&amp;#39;re wrong, when no matter how much the evidence is stacked against you, you&amp;#39;re not going to change your mind anyway. Ergo a massive waste of time that benefits no one&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inflation is Excellent for Debt!:&lt;/strong&gt; I will keep this one quick. Lets say you took out a 30 year fixed mortgage in 1990. You paid $90,000 for your home and have a mortgage of $400 per month. In the year 2019 your home is now worth $200,000 in market value but you&amp;#39;re still paying $400 per month at a fixed rate. Through inflation your wages have eventually increased while your fixed rate mortgage remained stagnant. In short, you may have been scrimping for pennies when you took out the mortgage, but years later you can make your payment while working at a fast food restaurant. Neat huh? Inflation is excellent for debt ridden companies. As their profit margins increase over time through inflation they will find it much easier to pay off their long term debt. (&lt;em&gt;Note: Perhaps this put some of the companies you were looking at into better perspective, and if debt was a major factor for not investing, then you may or may not want to revisit your decision.&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bullish Sectors You Can Profit From that I did not Mention Above:&lt;/strong&gt; Industrial Chemicals, Industrial Equipment, Fertilizers, Farm Equipment/Construction, and Pesticides. As firms ramp up production they will increase the demand for industrial chemicals. Moreover, as food prices continue to increase the more land farmers will be incentivized to clear for additional farming which requires more farming construction, farming equipment, chemicals/pesticides, and fertilizers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Canary in the Inflation Coal Mine:&lt;/strong&gt; If the change in prices rise beyond the change in incomes to the point where people need to start economizing their necessities and forgoing their wants, we could be looking at a very serious correction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/strong&gt; I hope the pointers above have helped you better understand the inflationary environment and identify economically favorable industries/sectors. Please understand that I will be reading this over and over again to identify typos &amp;amp; unclear sentences. I may even edit it as people bring ideas to my attention. Anyway I hope you enjoyed it and can turn this into long term investment opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Do tech, semicondutor stocks take in consideration possible Taiwan invasion by China?]]></title><description><![CDATA[After a lot of reluctance I bought TSMC for what I consider a bargain price. The
initial reluctance comes from a simple fear: China’s possible disruption of the
region.

Now, I don’t wanna get political. I have not much interest over geopolitics, and
I tend to ignore such influences when buying a…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrlnmy/do_tech_semicondutor_stocks_take_in_consideration/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrlnmy/do_tech_semicondutor_stocks_take_in_consideration/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 21:59:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a lot of reluctance I bought TSMC for what I consider a bargain price. The initial reluctance comes from a simple fear: China’s possible disruption of the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I don’t wanna get political. I have not much interest over geopolitics, and I tend to ignore such influences when buying a business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eventually I came to a conclusion: If TSMC is under threat, so is Apple, AMD, and many other industries for that matter. In fact, every single company on this planet has some exposure if China invades Taiwan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But at the end of the day we cannot paralyze ourselves and wait for a possible tragedy that may or may not happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the stock market does not compute the macro bc the macro is impossible to be predicated. So What you guys think?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I was invited to join my company's 401k committee. Any suggestions as to what I should ask or propose?]]></title><description><![CDATA[We have a 10-person 401k review committee and I've been asked to join after our
CFO caught onto my outwardly enthusiasm for investing. Any tips as to what I
should be paying attention to?

Background: We use Fidelity. I've been at the company for 4 years and have a
pretty good understanding of the…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrqced/i_was_invited_to_join_my_companys_401k_committee/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrqced/i_was_invited_to_join_my_companys_401k_committee/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 21:47:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have a 10-person 401k review committee and I&amp;#39;ve been asked to join after our CFO caught onto my outwardly enthusiasm for investing. Any tips as to what I should be paying attention to? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Background: We use Fidelity. I&amp;#39;ve been at the company for 4 years and have a pretty good understanding of the basics when it comes to retirement accounts. I already contribute the IRS max but am curious about contributing more via mega backdoor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[THIS IS AMERICA 
https://t.co/5hO930dHv0]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458856640598487049</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458856640598487049</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 21:35:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fuck off vegans]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrs7oa/fuck_off_vegans/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrs7oa/fuck_off_vegans/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 21:34:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$SFT Shift Technologies is going to print]]></title><description><![CDATA[Shift has amassed a HUGE amount of pre-owned inventory in the past three years
leading up to this unprecedented surge in used car prices. Their timing (mostly
by sheer luck) could not have been more perfect. More importantly, they
specifically have amassed a huge inventory of what were previously 10…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrodnr/sft_shift_technologies_is_going_to_print/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrodnr/sft_shift_technologies_is_going_to_print/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 21:19:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shift has amassed a HUGE amount of pre-owned inventory in the past three years leading up to this unprecedented surge in used car prices. Their timing (mostly by sheer luck) could not have been more perfect. More importantly, they specifically have amassed a huge inventory of what were previously 10-20k cars to appeal to the lower/middle income demographic. This range has appreciated more than any range of used vehicle. We’re talking 50-60% from a couple years ago in many cases. Best part is, used car prices continue to skyrocket as supply shortages and inflation show no signs of retreat. At some point the carousel will stop but until then I think Shift will experience rapid growth and profitability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anecdotally, I have heard more and more people talk about buying from Shift, and it’s relative ease compared to Carvana.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shift is rapidly stealing market share from Carvana, yet is valued at only 600mil to Carvana’s 49Bil valuation. For whatever it’s worth, last I checked it’s short interest was about 22%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shift reports earnings today after market close. I think it’s a nice opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;100 1/2023 $10C&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Parent has 100% stocks IRA post retirement.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Was chatting with my retired parent who told me they were up 70k this year in
IRA worth a total of 375k - 400k but position is 100% Large Cap fund.

Parent is retired and receiving deceased spouses pension. Post-retirement
financials are something I am not familiar with, but my understanding is…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrsr4o/parent_has_100_stocks_ira_post_retirement/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrsr4o/parent_has_100_stocks_ira_post_retirement/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 20:56:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Was chatting with my retired parent who told me they were up 70k this year in IRA worth a total of 375k - 400k but position is 100% Large Cap fund.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Parent is retired and receiving deceased spouses pension. Post-retirement financials are something I am not familiar with, but my understanding is she should transition to a large percentage of bonds at this point to significantly lessen her risk tolerance (60/40 or 50/50?). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a little overwhelmed of what to recommend. I think she should speak to a fiduciary possibly?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for any guidance or if a suggestion of a different subreddit that would be more appropriate. I have learned a lot here about my own retirement savings so wanted to ask here first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Robinhood is GARBAGE]]></title><description><![CDATA[Once again, I was let down today by YET ANOTHER glitch in Robinhood. For those
of you who don’t already know, or who were not affected by it, I woke up this
morning (on my first day of a 4 day weekend). Checked my portfolio after seeing
my biggest position was up 5.2%. A great feeling! I logged in…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrtijr/robinhood_is_garbage/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrtijr/robinhood_is_garbage/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 20:31:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once again, I was let down today by YET ANOTHER glitch in Robinhood. For those of you who don’t already know, or who were not affected by it, I woke up this morning (on my first day of a 4 day weekend). Checked my portfolio after seeing my biggest position was up 5.2%. A great feeling! I logged in and saw all my options moved from out of to in the money, and I was up a couple hundred on my shares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robinhood did not update my portfolio balance and I figured it was bad WiFi. I switched to LTE. Same thing. Then I was hit with an unexpected error message, so I restarted the app. Then, I get told I could not log in. With the recent hacks, I became nervous. I did a web search and found that “several users were experiencing problems with login preventing them from logging into their account”. One hour later, I log back in to see that the moment I was checking my account I was up $2,000 and was now up $500. I love the Robinhood interface and commission free trades but damn. That was the last straw&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$Wish bagholders are the MLM huns of this subreddit now.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrl1c1/wish_bagholders_are_the_mlm_huns_of_this/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrl1c1/wish_bagholders_are_the_mlm_huns_of_this/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 19:50:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A summary of the measured response by Central Banks to the Pandemic]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrf5jb/a_summary_of_the_measured_response_by_central/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrf5jb/a_summary_of_the_measured_response_by_central/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 19:37:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hong Kong and Shanghai index are up over a percent after Evergrande confirms default. Is this a good or bad sign for the markets?]]></title><description><![CDATA[So yeah pretty much how will this effect the market moving forward. All Chinese
indexes closed up about a percent yet Evergrande has just confirmed that they
are defaulting on their loans. Is this good or bad things for the overall market
and will this cause an upcoming crash?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrh2z3/hong_kong_and_shanghai_index_are_up_over_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrh2z3/hong_kong_and_shanghai_index_are_up_over_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 18:52:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So yeah pretty much how will this effect the market moving forward. All Chinese indexes closed up about a percent yet Evergrande has just confirmed that they are defaulting on their loans. Is this good or bad things for the overall market and will this cause an upcoming crash?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Beyond Meat, Net Income...
2021 YTD (Q1-3): -$102 million
2020: -53 million
2019: -$12 million
2018: -$30 million
2017: -$30 million
2016: -$25 million
$BYND]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458792238515953665</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458792238515953665</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 18:35:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thoughts on the current state of semiconductors?]]></title><description><![CDATA[So I think it's pretty clear just how important semiconductors are, and will
continue to be for a long time. However, they boomed massively in the last 1 to
2 years because of the supply shortages and I'm wondering, do you guys think
there will be a correction? I do want to get into it for the long…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrj20t/thoughts_on_the_current_state_of_semiconductors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrj20t/thoughts_on_the_current_state_of_semiconductors/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 18:09:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I think it&amp;#39;s pretty clear just how important semiconductors are, and will continue to be for a long time. However, they boomed massively in the last 1 to 2 years because of the supply shortages and I&amp;#39;m wondering, do you guys think there will be a correction? I do want to get into it for the long term, and am considering the VanEck Semiconductors ETF but am curious if I should wait. Naturally, since I&amp;#39;m in it for a long term it doesn&amp;#39;t matter that much if there is a correction, however a correction does mean I could get more shares in it. I&amp;#39;m not sure if I&amp;#39;m falling for the classic &amp;quot;it&amp;#39;s too late already&amp;quot; bias here or not. Does anyone have some more insight on the current state of them?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Investment amount vs savings amount]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello

My wife and I decided to start our bogleheads journey 3 months ago. We are both
working fulltime and are still figuring out how much we can allocate to our
Vanguard index fond.

We do monthly contributions to our savings account (emergency fund, vacation
money etc. ) and to our index fond. My…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrkbfi/investment_amount_vs_savings_amount/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrkbfi/investment_amount_vs_savings_amount/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 17:37:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife and I decided to start our bogleheads journey 3 months ago. We are both working fulltime and are still figuring out how much we can allocate to our Vanguard index fond. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We do monthly contributions to our savings account (emergency fund, vacation money etc. ) and to our index fond. My question is do you guys reach a certain point after you eliminate the monthly contributions to your savings account? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are still discussing about this because if we stop contributing to our savings account we could of course invest way more into vanguard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently we contribute 2k into Vanguard and 2k into savings account each month - we have around 30k in Vanguard and 100k in savings account. Together we make about 180k per year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Whats is a proven, reasonable and reliable way of using leverage in correlation with the boglehead approach?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Many books (e.g. Lifecycle investing) argue that using leverage is actually the
smarter approach for young people with low capital.

Can anyone share some strategies that you apply for yourself?

I am not talking about "buy TQQQ" and hold forever but actually looking for
strategies using historical…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrj5bz/whats_is_a_proven_reasonable_and_reliable_way_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrj5bz/whats_is_a_proven_reasonable_and_reliable_way_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 17:37:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many books (e.g. Lifecycle investing) argue that using leverage is actually the smarter approach for young people with low capital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can anyone share some strategies that you apply for yourself?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not talking about &amp;quot;buy TQQQ&amp;quot; and hold forever but actually looking for strategies using historical data and reason&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[(30M) I created and used these on my journey to 650k NW and I'm hoping these can help you too. Links in body]]></title><description><![CDATA[Thorough budgeting Template:
https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1Do-Efenrh0net1DBy6PFvOARNaG6QQutcqh33g4Mvok/edit?usp=sharing
(has links in top right to some resources)

Net Worth Tracker:
https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1N-WkOAIAoaSu-fpt_itJTOTtcy-Lze63p6F4nn_W6Tk/edit?usp=sharing

Time…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrn3e5/30m_i_created_and_used_these_on_my_journey_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrn3e5/30m_i_created_and_used_these_on_my_journey_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 17:09:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thorough budgeting Template: &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1Do-Efenrh0net1DBy6PFvOARNaG6QQutcqh33g4Mvok/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1Do-Efenrh0net1DBy6PFvOARNaG6QQutcqh33g4Mvok/edit?usp=sharing&lt;/a&gt; (has links in top right to some resources)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Net Worth Tracker: &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1N-WkOAIAoaSu-fpt_itJTOTtcy-Lze63p6F4nn_W6Tk/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1N-WkOAIAoaSu-fpt_itJTOTtcy-Lze63p6F4nn_W6Tk/edit?usp=sharing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time Value - stocks vs cash: &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1qS411RjSOpilZTw9poLfQ3783pbb1CpoH_JEsjZ4tTU/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1qS411RjSOpilZTw9poLfQ3783pbb1CpoH_JEsjZ4tTU/edit?usp=sharing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$WISH fires its CEO as core revenue plummets 55% and company burns 25% of its remaining cash balance…]]></title><description><![CDATA[Link to the PR:
https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211110006210/en/Wish-Reports-Third-Quarter-2021-Financial-Results-and-Provides-Business-Update

 1. Company fires its CEO without a named successor

 2. Core marketplace revenue down 55%

 3. Q4 revenue expected to be even worse than Q3…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrd11e/wish_fires_its_ceo_as_core_revenue_plummets_55/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrd11e/wish_fires_its_ceo_as_core_revenue_plummets_55/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 16:42:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Link to the PR: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211110006210/en/Wish-Reports-Third-Quarter-2021-Financial-Results-and-Provides-Business-Update&quot;&gt;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211110006210/en/Wish-Reports-Third-Quarter-2021-Financial-Results-and-Provides-Business-Update&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Company fires its CEO without a named successor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Core marketplace revenue down 55%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Q4 revenue expected to be even worse than Q3 despite the holidays… unheard of.  The company had already completely shut off marketing in Q3, so this means customers are ditching Wish left and right&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most importantly, Free Cash Flow was -$344M this quarter.  The company is burning roughly $300M/quarter this year (despite shutting off sales and marketing) and has $1.1B left… At this rate, the company will be insolvent by next summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not saying short the stock, but if you think the stock has “bottomed”, I think there’s a good chance the bottom is at $0/share and it’ll get there as soon as next summer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian customers who pre-ordered electric SUVs and trucks were able to buy pre-ipo shares and made millions from IPO pop]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/rivian-pre-order-customers-made-over-240-million-in-profit-on-ipo-pop.html

Rajiv Patel, an environmental consultant in Austin, Texas, put down a $1,000
deposit on a Rivian electric SUV earlier this year. He has no idea when he’ll
get his vehicle, called the R1S, but…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrkqtb/rivian_customers_who_preordered_electric_suvs_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrkqtb/rivian_customers_who_preordered_electric_suvs_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 15:48:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/rivian-pre-order-customers-made-over-240-million-in-profit-on-ipo-pop.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/rivian-pre-order-customers-made-over-240-million-in-profit-on-ipo-pop.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rajiv Patel, an environmental consultant in Austin, Texas, put down a $1,000 deposit on a Rivian electric SUV earlier this year. He has no idea when he’ll get his vehicle, called the R1S, but his down payment is paying off in a very different way. As a pre-order customer, Patel was able to buy into Rivian’s IPO on Tuesday night as part of the company’s directed share program. He purchased the maximum 175 shares for $13,650 at the $78 IPO price. After the stock popped 29% on Wednesday, Patel’s stake is now worth $17,628. “When I invest in these companies, I’m always a long hold guy,” said Patel, 45, adding that he invested in Tesla not long after its 2010 IPO and also bought shares in Lucid Motors, which went public in July. “I’m definitely not a meme stock guy. With these three, I feel good about the tech.” The tech is all Patel can currently bet on. Following its Nasdaq debut on Wednesday, Rivian has a market cap of $86 billion, higher than Ford and about equal to General Motors, even though the company is projecting revenue of between zero and $1 million for the third quarter. Rivian reserved up to 7% of the IPO shares for DSP participants, as the company laid out in its prospectus. Eligible investors fell into two categories: People who reserved either an R1S or an R1T electric truck as of Sept. 30, and company officers, directors and their affiliates. The deposits are refundable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The program follows similar moves by Airbnb, Uber and Doximity, which set aside shares in their offerings for hosts, drivers and doctors, respectively. What sets Rivian’s DSP apart is that the EV company doesn’t have actual customers yet, despite a backlog of 55,400 pre-orders, as of Oct. 31. Assuming the DSP allocated all its available shares, participants collectively invested about $835 million into Rivian’s stock. As of Wednesday’s close, those shares are worth a total of close to $1.08 billion, representing a paper gain of around $245 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joshua White, a finance professor at Vanderbilt University, said it’s a great deal for those who can participate because hot IPO stocks almost always enjoy a first-day pop, and retail investors usually get shut out. DSP investors can also sell immediately if they choose because they’re not subject to a post-IPO lock-up period. “You kind of know going in this is going to be a pretty good sweetheart deal for customers who sign up,” said White, who previously served as an economist for the Securities and Exchange Commission. “Not having a product, it’s a way to extend some goodwill upfront so they can lock in those returns right away.” Patel received his first email about Rivian’s DSP last month and was told he needed to pre-register by Oct. 25. The program was being run by Morgan Stanley, the lead underwriter on the IPO. After the stock priced at $78 late Tuesday, Patel was able to go into his Morgan Stanley account and select how many shares he wanted, up to 175. He selected the max and transferred the money.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Disney's plans to go to Metaverse]]></title><description><![CDATA[> In its full-year earnings call today, Disney CEO Bob Chapek brought up the
> idea of the metaverse to shareholders for the first time. He began by pointing
> out Disney's "long track record as an early adopter in the use of technology
> to enhance the entertainment experience," offering examples…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr88fh/disneys_plans_to_go_to_metaverse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr88fh/disneys_plans_to_go_to_metaverse/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 15:30:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In its full-year earnings call today, Disney CEO Bob Chapek brought up the idea of the metaverse to shareholders for the first time. He began by pointing out Disney&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;long track record as an early adopter in the use of technology to enhance the entertainment experience,&amp;quot; offering examples such as Steamboat Willie (one of the first cartoons to be produced with synchronized sound), its historical use of animatronics, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ign.com/movies/thor-love-and-thunder&quot;&gt;and&lt;/a&gt; broadly the technological work of Pixar in its animations.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He went on: &amp;quot;Suffice it to say, our efforts today are merely a prologue to a time when we&amp;#39;ll be able to connect the physical and digital worlds even more closely, allowing for storytelling without boundaries in our own Disney metaverse. We look forward to creating unparalelled opportunities for consumers to experience everything Disney has to offer across our product and platforms wherever the consumer may be.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;As we look ahead to this next frontier, given our unique combination of brands, franchises, physical and digital experiences, and global reach, we see limitless potential, and that makes us as excited as ever about the Walt Disney Company&amp;#39;s next 100 years.&amp;quot;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you feel like we&amp;#39;ve been hearing about the metaverse a lot lately, it&amp;#39;s because in the last year a lot of massive tech companies have been getting in on the idea. We&amp;#39;ve been hearing about it for a while now, with companies in gaming like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ign.com/articles/what-is-epic-games-metaverse-and-is-it-worth-billions&quot;&gt;Epic Games&lt;/a&gt; seemingly interested in creating a persistent, virtual space that bridges the gap between virtual and the real world, and where people can interact with one another in real time. As more gaming companies brought it up, some have suggested that games such as Roblox, Minecraft, and Second Life already exist as a sort of proto-metaverse. But that hasn&amp;#39;t stopped companies like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ign.com/articles/microsoft-metaverse-announcement&quot;&gt;Microsoft&lt;/a&gt; and Facebook (which just &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ign.com/articles/facebook-new-name-meta&quot;&gt;rebranded to Meta&lt;/a&gt; for exactly this reason) for also trying to take control of whatever this virtual future looks like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ign.com/articles/disney-metaverse&quot;&gt;Now Disney&amp;#39;s Going in on the Metaverse, Too - IGN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Johnson &amp; Johnson’s single-dose vaccine plunged from 86% to just 13% protection against COVID over 6 months ***]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458716009645420546</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458716009645420546</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 13:35:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Are we heading down the shitter?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Genuine question here. I know everyone here is just a gambler and no one knows
shit, including myself. But does anyone feel like or better yet have any
evidence that we are fucked? By that I mean that are we headed for a market
collapse worse than 08?

From what is happening, inflation going to 30…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr9ri8/are_we_heading_down_the_shitter/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr9ri8/are_we_heading_down_the_shitter/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 13:17:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Genuine question here. 
I know everyone here is just a gambler and no one knows shit, including myself. But does anyone feel like or better yet have any evidence that we are fucked? By that I mean that are we headed for a market collapse worse than 08?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From what is happening, inflation going to 30 year record, Chinese housing market collapsing, supply shortages, labor shortages, govt that seems to be sitting on a very large dildo, it seems like all of this is not going to end well. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is all of this going to lead to an I am Legend scenario without the zombies or is the fed just going to keep lying and is everyone just going to not care at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From my position it seems that all the shit happening cannot last forever and it has to come crumbling down some time. But I am also very stupid. Any input welcome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I would like to also add that everyone always thought “oh I live in America where everything is made of sunshine and rainbows” but recently people have woken up to the fact that we are vulnerable to the same shit the third world countries have been dealing with for years. So if you think you are protected just because you live in a nice neighborhood, you are wrong. And you can primarily blame the government for that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit 2: of all the people saying “oh people have been saying this for years” or “just another gay bear.” None of those people have offered any evidence that I’m wrong, which I find interesting. And you dorks just saying “we had 12 green days in a row” that literally proves my point. That the market is stupid and not based on anything close to resembling fundamentals and that this market is simply unsustainable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bought the WISH dip months ago]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrie43/bought_the_wish_dip_months_ago/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrie43/bought_the_wish_dip_months_ago/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 13:17:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I’m a importer, in my point of view, the true cost of inflation isn’t there’s too much money, it’s because—]]></title><description><![CDATA[It’s because the logistic is a nightmare right now.

I import things from China. There are thousands of companies like mine. We are
the one that sells shit to ur the distributors, the distributors sells to
stores. We are also the one directly sells on Amazon and other e-commerce
website.

Pre COVID,…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qriwag/im_a_importer_in_my_point_of_view_the_true_cost/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qriwag/im_a_importer_in_my_point_of_view_the_true_cost/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 13:17:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s because the logistic is a nightmare right now. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I import things from China. There are thousands of companies like mine. We are the one that sells shit to ur the distributors, the distributors sells to stores. We are also the one directly sells on Amazon and other e-commerce website. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pre COVID, a 40ft high cube costs me only $4000 from China to Long Beach. Currently it costs me god damn $20000, and that doesn’t include land transport. If I want to sent a container of goods to Ohio, the total cost on shipping alone is like $40000, excluding import duties. Back in the day shipping make up abt 30% of my cost, it makes up 60-70% now. Pre COVID a container of nice double layer fleece lining hoodies cost me 60k includes shipping. It costs me 100k this year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are 110 some container ships stuck outside of Long Beach. You probably have no idea how many that is..ima use the nice fleece lining hoodies as example again. Each 40ft high cube carry’s 6000 this hoodie (so 20ft carry abt 3000). Each ship carry 20000 TEU (20ft equivalent units). there are also some 2 million TEU still in the port waiting to be hauled.. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s do the math&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3000&lt;em&gt;20000=60 million hoodies 
110&lt;/em&gt;20000=2.2million containers on ship stuck outside still. 
2.2million+2million=4.2 millions on containers total. 
4200000*60000000=252000000000000&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;US population is 333000000 
That’s 756 thousand hoodies for each person just stuck there waiting to be distributed! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s say my number is off by 50%, it’s still 378 thousands hoodies just stuck there! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can’t unload at Houston or New York cuz it will cost us even more… &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem Is not the demand, it’s supply. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not that there are too many monies were printed, who cares if we print more money, we can print unlimited useless pieces of paper and buy real goods from China ( export our Inflation)!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, if u see on the news that the supply chain has been fixed, or the port of Long Beach has been cleared, or you know inflation is about to stapled.. until that , whatever the fed say is bs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Side note Biden should declare national emergency and have nat guard come in and help haul these sticker goods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just some thoughts on some things starting to worry me about the near to mid term markets]]></title><description><![CDATA[Just wanted to give some attention to a few metrics I've been keeping an eye on.



 * The CAPE Schiller P/E 10 ratio for the S&P is nearing all time highs
   (CAPE=39.29). It hasn't been as great at predicting recessions as some other
   analysis methods, but, two key points that stand out on the…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr5eb1/just_some_thoughts_on_some_things_starting_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr5eb1/just_some_thoughts_on_some_things_starting_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 11:51:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just wanted to give some attention to a few metrics I&amp;#39;ve been keeping an eye on. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The CAPE Schiller P/E 10 ratio for the S&amp;amp;P is nearing all time highs (CAPE=39.29).  It hasn&amp;#39;t been as great at predicting recessions as some other analysis methods, but, two key points that stand out on the historical chart did precede crashes.  We exceeded one of those levels and are approaching the other. The last time the Schiller ratio was near 40 was right before the dotcom bubble burst in 2000.  Prior to that, the last time it spiked to these levels it preceded the great depression (CAPE = 32) in 1929. The economist who developed this ratio was given the Nobel prize for using this ratio to predict the dot com bubble, so this measurement does carry some weight.&lt;br/&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://data.nasdaq.com/data/MULTPL/SHILLER_PE_RATIO_MONTH-shiller-pe-ratio-by-month&quot;&gt;https://data.nasdaq.com/data/MULTPL/SHILLER_PE_RATIO_MONTH-shiller-pe-ratio-by-month&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rumors are surfacing that Evergrande has defaulted on one of it&amp;#39;s payments.  This is hearsay at this point, but it seems very suspicious that some banks and bond holders are not commenting on if they are receiving payment from Evergrande.  It also stands to reason, the company is fighting to keep their heads above water to make these payments but they are over $300b in debt.  In reality they are just kicking the can down the road.  It&amp;#39;s a house of cards at this point and the bottom is being pulled out, it&amp;#39;s only a matter of time.

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-await-evergrandes-overdue-148-mln-payment-amid-contagion-fears-2021-11-09/&quot;&gt;https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-await-evergrandes-overdue-148-mln-payment-amid-contagion-fears-2021-11-09/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Treasury yield curves are flattening.  This is a potentially huge indicator of the uncertainty within the market.  It has reliably predicted the last 7 recessions up to and within 18 months of an inverted yield curve.  The curve is not currently inverted but is starting to flatten. 

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;Strategists are watching the move in the Treasury curve which is showing a narrowing between long end yields, like the 30-year and the shorter end, like the 5-year.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The flattening of the curve reflects more hawkish fed assumptions, also reflected in the fed funds futures market,” said Jeffery. He said the spread between the 5-year and 30-year is narrower, at 68 basis points, or 0.68 percentage points. That is the flattest since the early weeks of the pandemic in March, 2020.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;A flattening yield curve can indicate that investors are worried about a weakening economy.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/the-first-fed-rate-hike-is-now-expected-as-early-as-july-following-the-hot-cpi-data.html?&amp;amp;qsearchterm=flatten%20yield%20curve&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/the-first-fed-rate-hike-is-now-expected-as-early-as-july-following-the-hot-cpi-data.html?&amp;amp;qsearchterm=flatten%20yield%20curve&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Q3 2021 😂 https://t.co/G4KW6IvN0i]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458751697518481408</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458751697518481408</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 11:38:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wait, there's more: Elon Musk has sold $5B in Tesla stock so far this week https://t.co/S19eRPcvSB]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458646216925921281</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458646216925921281</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 11:38:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cathie Wood Flagship Sees Highest Quarterly Outflow on Record]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrcrcy/cathie_wood_flagship_sees_highest_quarterly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrcrcy/cathie_wood_flagship_sees_highest_quarterly/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 09:41:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA['The Big Short' investor Michael Burry says Tesla stock could plunge 90% - and notes Elon Musk said it was overpriced at $160 last year]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr994g/the_big_short_investor_michael_burry_says_tesla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr994g/the_big_short_investor_michael_burry_says_tesla/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 09:24:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can someone explain the difference in stock price for Rivian, Ford and Tesla?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ford: $19 market cap 77.37B, P/E 27.47

Tesla: 1,067. market cap $1.06T, P/E 346.55

Rivian: 100, Market cap 85.9 billion,

What's going on? How does this make any sense for Rivian when they haven't even
sold a single car yet? I'm having trouble deciding if this is something to get
into or not.…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrb5b7/can_someone_explain_the_difference_in_stock_price/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrb5b7/can_someone_explain_the_difference_in_stock_price/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 08:29:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ford: $19 market cap 77.37B, P/E 27.47&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla: 1,067. market cap $1.06T, P/E 346.55&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rivian: 100, Market cap 85.9 billion, &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s going on? How does this make any sense for Rivian when they haven&amp;#39;t even sold a single car yet? I&amp;#39;m having trouble deciding if this is something to get into or not. Compared to a Tesla which is most often compared to, 100 actually doesn&amp;#39;t seem too bad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What should I buy in kids Roth IRA]]></title><description><![CDATA[I just opened a Roth IRA for my kid. She is 16. I am a custodian account holder
until she reaches 21.

What should I buy with $6000? Equally split between NFLX, Apple, Google, Amazon,
Microsoft & tesla? or Just Tesla?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr4tam/what_should_i_buy_in_kids_roth_ira/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr4tam/what_should_i_buy_in_kids_roth_ira/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 08:29:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just opened a Roth IRA for my kid. She is 16. I am a custodian account holder until she reaches 21. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What should I buy with $6000? Equally split between NFLX, Apple, Google, Amazon, Microsoft &amp;amp; tesla? or Just Tesla?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WSB Tomorrow]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr9kno/wsb_tomorrow/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr9kno/wsb_tomorrow/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 07:35:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Elon Musk has sold roughly $5 billion in Tesla stock so far this week, and may not be done.
https://t.co/e4nweaIsSQ]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458649047649107971</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458649047649107971</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 06:43:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>