<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 12:24:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[The surge in US inflation expectations continues unabated, rising to their highest levels ever recorded (3.17% for 5-year breakevens). https://t.co/faPSer3Q4F]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460406986785411073</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460406986785411073</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 11:44:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[20M unemployed - I have been given 2000 dollars to invest by my parents, are these good choices I am making..?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I just opened an account with fidelity and about to buy these index funds/bonds,
but I just want some verification from you people whether if these are my best
options.

 * domestic stocks: FSKAX (total market - 0.015%)

 * international stocks: FSPSX (international - 0.035%)

 * emerging markets:…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qupyu7/20m_unemployed_i_have_been_given_2000_dollars_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qupyu7/20m_unemployed_i_have_been_given_2000_dollars_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 09:57:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just opened an account with fidelity and about to buy these index funds/bonds, but I just want some verification from you people whether if these are my best options.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;domestic stocks:            FSKAX (total market - 0.015%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;international stocks:     FSPSX (international - 0.035%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;emerging markets:         FPADX (emerging markets - 0.075%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. treasury bonds:      FUAMX (treasury bonds - 0.03%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. TIPS:                    FIPDX (inflation protected bonds - 0.05%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;real estate:                   FSRNX (real estate index fund - 0.07%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;and this will be the % split I am doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;30% domestic equity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% international equity &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;10% emerging market equity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% U.S. Treasury bonds&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% TIPS (inflation protected bonds)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% Real estate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Not sure what Papa Elon's endgame is but he's been on some supervillain vibes as of late]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quyhqs/not_sure_what_papa_elons_endgame_is_but_hes_been/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quyhqs/not_sure_what_papa_elons_endgame_is_but_hes_been/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 08:35:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tilray To the Moon DD inside.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Republican Nancy Mace is presenting her Marijuana bill conference today at
2:00pm EDT at Capitol Hill.
https://twitter.com/RepNancyMace/status/1459565180585656325?s=20

Germany's new coalition government in talks of legalizing Marijuana. Tilray
sells medical marijuana already in Germany and has…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qukdev/tilray_to_the_moon_dd_inside/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qukdev/tilray_to_the_moon_dd_inside/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 08:10:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican Nancy Mace is presenting her Marijuana bill conference today at 2:00pm EDT at Capitol Hill.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/RepNancyMace/status/1459565180585656325?s=20&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/RepNancyMace/status/1459565180585656325?s=20&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Germany&amp;#39;s new coalition government in talks of legalizing Marijuana. Tilray sells medical marijuana already in Germany and has license. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-10/germany-s-next-coalition-close-to-deal-on-legalizing-cannabis&quot;&gt;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-10/germany-s-next-coalition-close-to-deal-on-legalizing-cannabis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s go my precious little Diamond hands. Tilray currently up over 6%. This is not financial Advice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I’m 25 and this is my Roth. What can I do better here?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qungve/im_25_and_this_is_my_roth_what_can_i_do_better/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qungve/im_25_and_this_is_my_roth_what_can_i_do_better/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 07:50:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is the VTSAX equivalent at Fidelity?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qulqnk/what_is_the_vtsax_equivalent_at_fidelity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qulqnk/what_is_the_vtsax_equivalent_at_fidelity/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 06:49:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley is out with its 2022 market outlook, and it sees a decline]]></title><description><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley sees a more challenging year ahead for U.S. equities against a
backdrop of higher interest rates, slowing growth and supply chain disruptions.

The Wall Street firm recently set its S&P 500 target for next year at 4,400,
implying a 5% decline from current levels. The negative…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quo6jl/morgan_stanley_is_out_with_its_2022_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quo6jl/morgan_stanley_is_out_with_its_2022_market/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 05:22:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morgan Stanley sees a more challenging year ahead for U.S. equities against a backdrop of higher interest rates, slowing growth and supply chain disruptions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Wall Street firm recently set its S&amp;amp;P 500 target for next year at 4,400, implying a 5% decline from current levels. The negative projection followed a blockbuster year for stocks that has seen the &lt;a href=&quot;https://link.cnbc.com/click/25708849.282877/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuY25iYy5jb20vcXVvdGVzLy5TUFg_X19zb3VyY2U9bmV3c2xldHRlciU3Q21hcmtldGluZw/5ba060792ddf9c38dd023063Bd6668e6e&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/a&gt; rallying 25% and raking in more than 60 record highs despite fears of persistent inflation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Historically it's way better to invest at market close than at market open, most gains happen overnight]]></title><description><![CDATA[There is an interesting article back from 2018 that says

> If you had bought the SPY at the last second of trading on each business day
> since 1993 and sold at the market open the next day — capturing all of the net
> after-hour gains — your cumulative price gain would be 571%
> 
> On the other…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quxd2t/historically_its_way_better_to_invest_at_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quxd2t/historically_its_way_better_to_invest_at_market/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 04:11:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is an interesting article back from 2018 that says&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you had bought the SPY at the last second of trading on each business day since 1993 and sold at the market open the next day — capturing all of the net after-hour gains — your cumulative price gain would be 571%  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, if you had done the reverse, buying the ETF at the first second of regular trading every morning at 9:30 a.m. and selling at the 4 p.m. close, you would be down 4.4%&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have backtested the same for 2020 and 2021, see the results below. Every day I was buying/selling just 1 share of $SPY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Buy at open, sell at close&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Buy at close, sell at open&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2020&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-$4.88&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$45.42&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2021&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-$38.05&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$53.92&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: all calculations made using BreakingEquity&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Here is a Market Recap for today Monday, Nov 15, 2021. Please enjoy!]]></title><description><![CDATA[PsychoMarket Recap - Monday, November 15, 2021

Stocks finished mixed, with the Dow Jones (DIA) and tech-heavy Nasdaq (QQQ)
closing modestly lower, as market participants digested upbeat economic data
coming from China and await for a key report on retail sales in the US later
this week. The Russell…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qushen/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_nov_15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qushen/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_nov_15/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:51:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Monday, November 15, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks finished mixed, with the Dow Jones (DIA) and tech-heavy Nasdaq (QQQ) closing modestly lower, as market participants digested upbeat economic data coming from China and await for a key report on retail sales in the US later this week. The Russell 2000 (IWM), which tracks the performance of small-caps, underperformed on the day, closing 0.44% lower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stronger than expected economic data coming out of China helped lift the sentiments of market participants following last week’s inflation report. The world&amp;#39;s second-largest economy saw both retail sales and industrial production unexpectedly rise in October in a year-over-year period, suggesting that China’s economy is holding up better than expected amid new stay-in-place restrictions and ongoing power shortages. However, prices of new homes dropped 0.25% in October versus September, marking the biggest drop in more than six years as the nation’s real estate market remains under pressure from the Evergrande situation. Here are the numbers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retail Sales: +4.9% YoY vs +3.5 expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Industrial Production: +3.5% YoY vs +3% expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow, market participants will receive the Commerce Department’s monthly Retail Sales report, which is expected to show a 1.3% year-over-year rise in retail sales, improving from September’s disappointing 0.7% rise. Moreover, major retailers like Walmart (WMT), Target (TGT), Home Depot (HD), and Lowe’s (LOW) are set to report Q3 earnings, which will offer additional data regarding the state of consumer demand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week, markets were spooked by the pace of inflation, with the recent Consumer Price Index (CPI) showing the fastest pace of increase in roughly 30 years. which showed prices soared 6.2% in a year-on-year period, accelerating from September’s 5.4% YoY rate, and higher than the 5.9% expected. The staying power and magnitude of inflationary pressures has, perhaps, become the central question for market participants, with companies across the board reporting rising input costs and price hikes passed on to the consumers to preserve margins. While Q3 earning results have robustly demonstrated that companies in the SPY were largely able to navigate these cost pressures, the possibility remains that if inflation runs hotter than expected for longer than expected, it could begin to hamper consumer demand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ian Shepherdson, Chief Economist at Pantheon Macroeconomics, wrote in a note to clients, “The surge in core inflation in October marks the start of a run of big gains, thanks to surging used auto prices, rebounding airline fares, and faster increases in housing costs. We think core inflation will peak at almost 7% in March, which will pose a serious challenge to the Fed&amp;#39;s benign medium-term view. Chair [Jerome] Powell will have to convince markets that the combination of rocketing payrolls and soaring inflation does not threaten the transitory story, to which he appears still to be committed. We remain of the view that the Fed will start to hike in September, but a June hike can&amp;#39;t be ruled out. If labor participation shows no sign of life by the March FOMC meeting, we expect the Fed to accelerate the taper and then hike in June. This would play badly across all asset markets.” As always, it is important to acknowledge and understand the risks present in the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Boeing (BA) surged after the company said it was “hopeful” China would resume order of the 737 Max two years after its grounding.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;U.S. crude oil output from the Permian Basin of West Texas and New Mexico is set to jump to a record 4.95 million barrels per day in December, a new government forecast showed on Monday. This would bring production in the key U.S. shale patch well above its pre-pandemic average from March 2020.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of oat-milk maker Oatly (OTLY) fell more than 20% after missing earnings expectations and cutting guidance. The stock is down roughly 50% since IPO back in late-May.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Snap (SNAP) were up after the company reached a deal with Sony Music Entertainment to allow the company to use its artist and sounds on the Snapchat App.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Twitter Inc said on Monday it will expand free access to the social networking site&amp;#39;s data to help software developers create tools and products that could promote safer online conversations or curate content. The move is part of Twitter&amp;#39;s growing effort over the past year to decentralize the company, a vision that aims to give users more control over what content they see in their Twitter feed or have new ways of sharing content on the site, Amir Shevat, Twitter&amp;#39;s head of product for the developer platform, said in an interview.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amazon.com Inc has reached a deal to sell virtual medical services to Hilton Hotels in the United States, one of the first major customers for the company’s burgeoning healthcare business. Amazon Care is an on-demand health offering that lets users message or video-chat clinicians and receive home visits in some cities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UK ministers are expected to order an in-depth investigation of Nvidia Corp&amp;#39;s planned $40 billion acquisition of British chip designer ARM over antitrust and national security concerns. As a huge NVDA bull, hope all goes well!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Finance Tech (SOFI) announced an offering of 50 million shares. The stock is down as a result. Not surprising for management to take advantage of this massive runup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of oat-meal maker Oatly (OTLY) gapped down -20% after missing earnings expectations and cutting guidance moving forward. After a promising start, the stock is now roughly -50% since its IPO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current stock price was written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AutoDesk (ADSK) target raised by Mizuho from $350 to $380 at Buy. Stock currently around $326&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Broadcom (AVGO) target raised by Argus from $560 to $620 at Buy. Stoick currently around $565&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coupang (CPNG) target raised by Mizuho from $32 to $40 at Overweight. Stock currently around $28&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salesforce (CRM) target raised by Mizuho from $320 to $360 at Buy. Stock currently around $305&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crowdstrike (CRWD) target raised by Mizuho from $330 to $360 at Buy. Stock was also downgraded by Morgan Stanley to $250, so there are competing perspectives here&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intuit (INTU) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $615 to $715 at Overweight. Stock currently around $626&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MasterCard (MA) target raised by Mizuho from $50 to $465 at Buy. Stock currently around $360&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Netflix (NFLX) target raised by KeyCorp from $690 to $725 at Overweight. Stock currently around $680&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NVIDIA (NVDA) with three target raises. Stock currently around $300

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Citigroup from $223 to $350 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robert W Baird from $240 to $360 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UBS Group from $230 to $350 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Palo Alto Networks (PANW) with three target raises. Stock currently around $518

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mizuho from $560 to $625 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deutsche Bank from $560 to $605 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Royal Bank of Canada from $560 to $590 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roblox (RBLX) target raised by BTIG Research from $98 to $133 at Buy. Stock currently around $108&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Signature Bank (SBNY) target raised by Raymond James from $360 at $400 at Outperform. Stock currently around $321&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snowflake (SNOW) target raised by Mizuho from  $340 to $450 at Buy. Stock currently around $393&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Finance Tech (SOFI) target raised by Mizuho from $28 to $30 at Buy. Stock currently around $22&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Valero Energy (VLO) target raised by Wells Fargo from $102 to $106 at Overweight. Stock currently around $77&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Don&amp;#39;t judge each day by the harvest you reap but by the seeds that you plant.&amp;quot; -Robert Louis Stevenson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Metaverse: Next Biggest Opportunity]]></title><description><![CDATA[It was the internet in the late ’90s, social media in the 2000s, and digital
currency (crypto) in the 2010s. Facebook’s Metaverse might be one of the
greatest investment opportunities in the 2020s. If you are following Facebook’s
Connect 2021 conference you will realize how much deep Facebook now…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quvg93/metaverse_next_biggest_opportunity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quvg93/metaverse_next_biggest_opportunity/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the internet in the late ’90s, social media in the 2000s, and digital currency (crypto) in the 2010s. Facebook’s Metaverse might be one of the greatest investment opportunities in the 2020s. If you are following Facebook’s Connect 2021 conference you will realize how much deep Facebook now Meta has invested in the platform. They own Oculus which is the first step towards VR/AR metaverse. The application of Metaverse based platforms is immense and beyond gaming and virtually every aspect of our lives. Here are some of the potential companies to benefit from:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unity Software: Virtually all applications will be developed either on Unity or Unreal Engine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Autodesk: They own 3D Max and Maya which again might be used to develop VR/AR applications. Plus they have various Building Information Modelling tools like Revit and Navisworks which might be useful in creating Metaverse beyond gaming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Matterport: 3D scanning &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trimble: Again they have Sketchup and various 3D scanning tools&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shopify and Amazon: They might be the first ones to create virtual stores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft: They own Minecraft and have developed ‘Hololens’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roblox: The platform already works with Oculus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me know if there are any other key players which I have missed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My depressing investment story. Today I took most of what I had left out and a 90 day ban, I won’t be back for awhile. Gg market.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qul0k6/my_depressing_investment_story_today_i_took_most/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qul0k6/my_depressing_investment_story_today_i_took_most/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rocket Lab (RKLB ) to acquire Planetary Systems Corp.]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation

Looks like Rocket Lab is continuing to try to vertically innovate. This sounds
like good news for investors especially after they already bought Advanced
Solutions Inc…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qurofj/rocket_lab_rklb_to_acquire_planetary_systems_corp/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qurofj/rocket_lab_rklb_to_acquire_planetary_systems_corp/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation&quot;&gt;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like Rocket Lab is continuing to try to vertically innovate. This sounds like good news for investors especially after they already bought Advanced Solutions Inc earlier this year. These two acquisitions along with recent talks of selling rocket hardware to other companies look promising.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[management is one of the most important parts of a company]]></title><description><![CDATA[I see a lot of new investors looking at FCF intrisnic value, profits or
innovation. which is all important but one of the most important factors is
mostly overlooked.

strong management is going to be most of ur returns. If the CEO makes bad
decisions u will become a bagholder. especialy in market…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/queyas/management_is_one_of_the_most_important_parts_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/queyas/management_is_one_of_the_most_important_parts_of/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I see a lot of new investors looking at FCF intrisnic value, profits or innovation. which is all important but one of the most important factors is mostly overlooked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;strong management is going to be most of ur returns. If the CEO makes bad decisions u will become a bagholder. especialy in market downturns Reits or commodity&amp;#39;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best Example is Elon Musk is able to sell almost a million cars withour spending money on ads without Elon Musk tesla would be at 10/20% of their market cap max. If the company didnt go bankrupt. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ivanhoe has a legendairy CEO in mining and the company preforms well and has amazing assets. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes its better to sit on the sideline even if a stock is dirt cheap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;wereldhave has been cheap for years with an 10% dividend and even 20% for a while with a lot of intrisic value but did cut the dividend time and time again took huge losses and still holds bad assets. -80% of their peak and it use to be a large cap stock on the AEX/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intel was unable to preform with the rest of the market but when a new ceo comes he invest billions and claims the company holds a lot of tech which shows how weak management was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IBM used to be a leader but focussed on share buybacks insted of innovating. sold assets and tech cheap and the best parts. use to be one of the biggest tech companys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are countless examples of weak managment destroying share value in a small company 1 or 2 bad decisions can bankrupt the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;when looking at a stock look at management experience look at the board and insider ownership before u even touch the stock&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reasons to pick individual stocks]]></title><description><![CDATA[What are your reasons to pick individual stocks?

Is there any other reason then to try to beat the market?

With all the research showing it’s really hard to do and so many people still
choosing to hand pick stocks I was really wondering what are the reasons.

It’s a real question I am not trying…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quh9ag/reasons_to_pick_individual_stocks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quh9ag/reasons_to_pick_individual_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 02:08:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What are your reasons to pick individual stocks? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is there any other reason then to try to beat the market?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With all the research showing it’s really hard to do and so many people still choosing to hand pick stocks I was really wondering what are the reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a real question I am not trying to dismiss any market strategy. I am just curious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rocket Lab (RKLB )to acquire Planetary Systems Corporation]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation

Looks like Rocket Lab is continuing to try to vertically innovate. This sounds
like good news for investors especially after they already bought Advanced
Solutions Inc…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qurnf4/rocket_lab_rklb_to_acquire_planetary_systems/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qurnf4/rocket_lab_rklb_to_acquire_planetary_systems/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 02:08:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation&quot;&gt;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like Rocket Lab is continuing to try to vertically innovate. This sounds like good news for investors especially after they already bought Advanced Solutions Inc earlier this year. These two acquisitions along with recent talks of selling rocket hardware to other companies look promising.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How much is enough?!?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qurk7o/how_much_is_enough/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qurk7o/how_much_is_enough/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 01:14:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I Analyzed $PLTR So You Don't Have To]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello everyone, I’ve been seeing a lot of people talk about $PLTR, so today I
decided to analyze $PLTR otherwise known as Palantir. I’ve also analyzed other
companies, so feel free to check out my profile for other stock analysis!

For those that don’t know, Palantir is a software company that…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quqjjj/i_analyzed_pltr_so_you_dont_have_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quqjjj/i_analyzed_pltr_so_you_dont_have_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 01:14:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone, I’ve been seeing a lot of people talk about $PLTR, so today I decided to analyze $PLTR otherwise known as Palantir. I’ve also analyzed other companies, so feel free to check out my profile for other stock analysis! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those that don’t know, Palantir is a software company that specializes in big data analytics. At the time of this post, they’re sitting at about $23.33. They reported earnings for Quarter 3 on November 9th, 2021. Revenue was reported to be $392 million, which is up 35.5% from the same quarter last year, beating expectations by $5.54 million. Furthemore, in Q3 they added 34 new customers and closed 54 deals worth at least $1 million, 33 of which were at least $5 million, and 18 of which were worth at least $10 Million. For Q4, Palantir is expecting $418 Million in revenue, consensus is $401.87 Million. The CEO of PLTR, Alex Karp, said that they expect revenue to grow at a rate of 30% or more for 2021 - 2025. Now let’s discuss their valuation...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Since Palantir had a larger number of customers and government deals in Q3, they reported stronger revenue growth, However, growth did lag in comparison to other competitors who are in the same space such as Datadog and Snowflake. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Palantir demonstrated the highest value for EBITDA margins compared to other companies in the space. Adjusted free cash flow for quarter 3 was $119 Million, which was a $172 million improvement year-over-year, representing a margin of about 30%. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Despite the fact that this company looks like it’s trading at a cheap price compared to its peers, it is trading at 17 to 20x revenue multiples which means that if they happen to have a bad quarter, the stock can drop hard. However, keep in mind that they do seem to be executing pretty well since they’ve been growing the amount of deals they’ve been making with organizations and firms, Have strong revenue growth, and also have good EBITDA margins. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of this being said, Palantir may be a buy only if you believe in the company long-term. In order for Palantir to succeed, they will need to grow their commercial product offering, since they already have a good presence on the government side. Things do seem to be going well on that end though because the commercial side growth has been going up as of recently. In my opinion, this company is still trading at too high of a price, your money would be better off invested in a different tech company. Thanks for reading everyone, if you have any questions feel free to comment down below or message me directly. I’d also love to hear your comments!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EBITDA = Earnings Before Interest, Taxes, Debt, Amortization&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lucid releases Q3 results with 13,000 reservations]]></title><description><![CDATA[Customer reservations rose to 13,000 in Q3, reflecting an order book of
approximately $1.3B, and have since increased beyond 17,000

 * Lucid Air today won the 2022 MotorTrend Car of the Year

 * Customer vehicle production started in Q3 at Lucid's Advanced Manufacturing
   Plant ("AMP-1") in Casa…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quqg52/lucid_releases_q3_results_with_13000_reservations/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quqg52/lucid_releases_q3_results_with_13000_reservations/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 01:14:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Customer reservations rose to 13,000 in Q3, reflecting an order book of approximately $1.3B, and have since increased beyond 17,000&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lucid Air today won the 2022 MotorTrend Car of the Year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Customer vehicle production started in Q3 at Lucid&amp;#39;s Advanced Manufacturing Plant (&amp;quot;AMP-1&amp;quot;) in Casa Grande, Arizona, and the second phase of construction broke ground to add 2.85 million square feet of space&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lucid bolstered its balance sheet to close Q3 with approximately $4.8B in cash&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lucid Group, Inc. successfully listed as a public company on Nasdaq in July under the ticker symbol LCID&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Third Quarter Financial Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the third quarter of 2021, Lucid significantly strengthened its balance sheet through the closing of the de-SPAC reverse merger + PIPE, bringing approximately $4.4B onto Lucid&amp;#39;s balance sheet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Continued to invest in the business, readying production and deliveries, globalization of our retail network and adding headcount across R&amp;amp;D and SG&amp;amp;A to continue growing our core operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initiated investment in property, plant, and equipment associated with Phase 2 expansion of manufacturing, continued investment in vehicle program development, and ongoing expansion of retail, delivery, and service capacities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Looking forward&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We remain confident in our ability to achieve 20,000 units in 2022. This target is not without risk given ongoing challenges facing the automotive industry, with global disruptions to supply chains and logistics. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lucid-announces-third-quarter-2021-210000175.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lucid-announces-third-quarter-2021-210000175.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why won't the market crash soon?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pessimism on this sub (and similar financial subs) is rampant. I don't even
recall things being quite this negative during the COVID crash or anytime in the
last 5+ years.

Raising interest rates are going to kill growth stocks, China's recession is a
massive threat, inflation will kill our cash,…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qurl3z/why_wont_the_market_crash_soon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qurl3z/why_wont_the_market_crash_soon/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 01:14:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pessimism on this sub (and similar financial subs) is rampant. I don&amp;#39;t even recall things being quite this negative during the COVID crash or anytime in the last 5+ years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Raising interest rates are going to kill growth stocks, China&amp;#39;s recession is a massive threat, inflation will kill our cash, real estate has overheated, the rug is really about to be pulled on almost all asset classes -- there&amp;#39;s really no way to financially survive the next year going off sentiment here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why won&amp;#39;t the markets tank? What&amp;#39;s going to send us to DOW 40,000+ that so many people are overlooking? I&amp;#39;d love to hear what anyone might be optimistic about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lucid confirms a pathetic 20,000 cars for 2022 for a $73 billion company]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lucid confirmed after hours it would produce 20,000 cars for 2022. A $73 billion
company!

A little comparison. VW Group is double the mkt cap. It produces 20,000 cars a
day. Not a week, a month, a year. A day.

It has nearly a dozen BEV models on sale worldwide. It sold nearly 540K EV's YTD
to 3Q…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qus535/lucid_confirms_a_pathetic_20000_cars_for_2022_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qus535/lucid_confirms_a_pathetic_20000_cars_for_2022_for/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 23:46:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lucid confirmed after hours it would produce 20,000 cars for 2022.  A $73 billion company!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A little comparison.  VW Group is double the mkt cap.  It produces 20,000 cars a day.  Not a week, a month, a year.  A day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has nearly a dozen BEV models on sale worldwide.  It sold nearly 540K EV&amp;#39;s YTD to 3Q 2021.  In 2022 it will have over 20 EV models on sale and likely surpass Tesla in EV sales and be pushing 20,000 EV&amp;#39;s a day (Tesla will stil pip it in BEV&amp;#39;s by measure - and yes PHEV&amp;#39;s do matter making lots of moolah).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;20,000 EV&amp;#39;s a day...not a year, a day.  Yet just double the mkt cap.of Lucid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry to offend, but US investors are mostly utterly clueless when it comes to global EV mkts.  BYD in China knocked out 183K EV&amp;#39;s in their third quarter alone.  Again it trades for a lowly $130 billion vs Lucid&amp;#39;s absurd mkt cap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Journey to "cant beat the market" acceptance - final step]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm in search of a little confirmation bias so this sub seemed the best place to
start...

I've always heard you can't beat the market but couldn't reconcile that with my
initial assumption that 50% must be doing better than the other 50%. I mean, I'm
smart right? At least smarter than half of you!…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qumaht/journey_to_cant_beat_the_market_acceptance_final/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qumaht/journey_to_cant_beat_the_market_acceptance_final/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 23:17:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m in search of a little confirmation bias so this sub seemed the best place to start...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve always heard you can&amp;#39;t beat the market but couldn&amp;#39;t reconcile that with my initial assumption that 50% must be doing better than the other 50%. I mean, I&amp;#39;m smart right? At least smarter than half of you! Then I read Bogle and all the other data showing its single digit % of investors beat the market long term. To understand this I&amp;#39;ve come to a theory that &amp;quot;The Market&amp;quot; is an optimization, not an average. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The theory: as long as society maintains stability (bigger &amp;quot;if&amp;quot; these days), the economy will grow (for reasons) and thus companies and stocks along with it. There is always churn and noise but over the long term the duds get filtered out and the studs end up making a majority of the market. Even if you&amp;#39;re picking good stocks, so is the broader market. That makes it hard to beat when the market also has your winners every time. It also has mostly winners and very few losers so if you happen to pick one bad stock you can easily get crushed vs the index. The market is continually optimizing so the effort and reward for trying to beat it are not justified. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This concludes my surface level, non-economist, inexperienced justification for why I consolidated everything into SNDL...j/k, it starts with a V. Please destroy my optimization theory so I can learn about a hammer candle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WeWork has had net losses totaling $13.4 billion since the start of 2016. Its market cap today is $7 billion. $WE]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460261845818920970</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460261845818920970</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 22:41:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alibaba, limp dick pattern bout to erect!!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qupfzp/alibaba_limp_dick_pattern_bout_to_erect/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qupfzp/alibaba_limp_dick_pattern_bout_to_erect/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 22:41:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I Bonds vs High Yield Savings Account for Emergency Fund]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’ve tried approaching the following decision analytically but am checking if
others have experienced similar decisions or can see any of my blind spots.

I have a pretty high savings rate and hate to leave my dollars working
inefficiently. The more I save, the quicker I can reach financial…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qula33/i_bonds_vs_high_yield_savings_account_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qula33/i_bonds_vs_high_yield_savings_account_for/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 22:25:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve tried approaching the following decision analytically but am checking if others have experienced similar decisions or can see any of my blind spots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a pretty high savings rate and hate to leave my dollars working inefficiently. The more I save, the quicker I can reach financial independence. In my 20’s I’ve stayed in 100% stocks and have not purchased any bonds. I have a pretty tough skin and risk tolerance and didn’t even consider selling during the short 2020 market crash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I also understand the importance of an emergency fund. I started with around $10,000 in an Ally savings account and have increased it up to $25,000 over the past few years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More recently, I’ve considered putting most of my emergency fund into I-bonds. I understand they are less liquid than a savings account but in the long run will be less affected by inflation. Looking at historic rates, they almost always are at least 1-2% higher than a high yield savings account.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/agSHRni&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/a/agSHRni&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pro to an online savings account is only liquidity and money available within a few days. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From what I can tell about I-bonds the pros and cons are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pros:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Higher Inflation Protected Interest Rates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Locked up for 1 year from time of purchase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forfeit 3 months interest if redeemed within 5 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Limited to $10,000 purchased per year &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;May take longer to redeem in an emergency &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I can deal with all of the cons in my current situation. If I purchase 10k this year and 10k towards the end of next year I could limit my exposure to liquidity issues. My plan would be to buy 10k this December, bring my emergency fund savings account back to 20k by next December, then buy 10k more. At that point I would have 20k in I-bonds and 10k in a savings account. Ideally for small emergencies I wouldn’t even have to touch the I-bonds. Even sacrificing 3 months of interest after 1 year I would still be ahead relative to a high yield savings account. 9 months at an I bond rate beats 12 months at current savings accounts rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the short term, 15k liquidity is plenty. I have a local safety net and could both cover a 6-month lease liability ($3750) and the maximum out of pocket for health insurance ($6500). Worst case I could also move back in with parents and just pay for partial utilities and food. My current industry also has a pretty high demand so it wouldn’t be difficult to get another similar paying job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my main concerns is how difficult it is in practice to redeem I-bonds. Could I put a large emergency expense on a credit card, cash in the same amount of electronic I-bonds the same day, and be able to pay off the credit card within 3 weeks?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Oatly Shares Down 20% After Earnings, Expecting Lower Revenue for 2022.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Some third quarter highlights:

 * Revenue of $171.1 million, a 49.2% increase compared to $114.7 million in the
   prior year period
 * Net losses totaled $41.2 million, or 7 cents per share, after a loss of $10.4
   million, or 2 cents per share, last year.
 * Gross profit of $44.9 million, or a…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qukktc/oatly_shares_down_20_after_earnings_expecting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qukktc/oatly_shares_down_20_after_earnings_expecting/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 21:20:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some third quarter highlights:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue of $171.1 million, a 49.2% increase compared to $114.7 million in the prior year period&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Net losses totaled $41.2 million, or 7 cents per share, after a loss of $10.4 million, or 2 cents per share, last year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gross profit of $44.9 million, or a 26.2% gross profit margin, compared to $36.0 million, or a 31.3% gross profit margin, in the prior year period&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone looking at OTLY under $10? Honestly I&amp;#39;m not surprised by this, I already thought at $8B OTLY was pretty richly valued anyways but now it&amp;#39;s hit a new ATL of under $10. Is OTLY worth it around $5.65B valuation to anyone here? I think their oat milk sells well personally and I&amp;#39;ve seen them grow but I&amp;#39;m hesitant to invest in any vegan food companies long term. Might think about trading OTLY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What does anyone think of it at it&amp;#39;s new low? Is it heading towards $8?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[New to investing, is this a good strategy?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know very little about investing. I am in my early 20s and due to a learning
disability I doubt I will ever become good at it. I have however heard good
thing about index funds due to good results and low barrier of entry. Is it a
good idea to work as much as I can and put a lot of it into an…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qucy8u/new_to_investing_is_this_a_good_strategy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qucy8u/new_to_investing_is_this_a_good_strategy/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 20:31:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know very little about investing. I am in my early 20s and due to a learning disability I doubt I will ever become good at it. I have however heard good thing about index funds due to good results and low barrier of entry. Is it a good idea to work as much as I can and put a lot of it into an index fund and then just let it stay for 40-50 years or so? At least that has been my understanding of it so far on this subreddit. Is there something I am missing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to hedge against the current worst case scenarios?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Let's say that hypothetically, Evergrande defaults, putting China in a
recession. The USD either hyperinflates or the FED increases interest rates,
leveraged investors bail and the markets crash, European markets follow.

I'm not sure how feasible this is, i've only started my investment journey…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qumlsi/how_to_hedge_against_the_current_worst_case/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qumlsi/how_to_hedge_against_the_current_worst_case/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 20:09:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s say that hypothetically, Evergrande defaults, putting China in a recession. The USD either hyperinflates or the FED increases interest rates, leveraged investors bail and the markets crash, European markets follow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not sure how feasible this is, i&amp;#39;ve only started my investment journey one year ago. But for argument sake let&amp;#39;s assume that whatever is the current worst projection becomes a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How does a retail investor react to this type of situation?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My portfolio consists mostly of a world index (MSCI World, &lt;a href=&quot;https://IWDA.AS&quot;&gt;IWDA.AS&lt;/a&gt;), small ammount of s&amp;amp;p500 Healthcare sector and a bit of crypto.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is there any stock that holds an index fund as its only asset?]]></title><description><![CDATA[My country (Ireland) taxes unrealized gains at 41% every 8 years on all ETFs and
other funds in general, which has a very dramatic effect on compounding for my
planned holding period (70 years), therefore I'm looking for a way to buy
something as closely correlated as possible to VWCE and QQQ…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quen21/is_there_any_stock_that_holds_an_index_fund_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quen21/is_there_any_stock_that_holds_an_index_fund_as/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 20:09:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My country (Ireland) taxes unrealized gains at 41% every 8 years on all ETFs and other funds in general, which has a very dramatic effect on compounding for my planned holding period (70 years), therefore I&amp;#39;m looking for a way to buy something as closely correlated as possible to VWCE and QQQ through stocks which would only be cost me 33% capital gains upon selling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m aware some companies like Berkshire are so diversified they are said to track total market ETfs fairly well (I think brk:b has a .66 correlation, but it depends on the time period obviously, with the correlation going quite negative at times) nevertheless I would rather a company that passively holds an index fund for several reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is inflation affecting your investing habits?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Curious if folks are increasing their investment amounts or rebalancing toward
bonds with their contributions or what other (if any) inflation mitigating steps
you're taking.

I'm basically straight VT in my personal brokerage and target-dates in my
retirement accounts. Just staying the course in my…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/quib2b/is_inflation_affecting_your_investing_habits/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/quib2b/is_inflation_affecting_your_investing_habits/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 19:50:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Curious if folks are increasing their investment amounts or rebalancing toward bonds with their contributions or what other (if any) inflation mitigating steps you&amp;#39;re taking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m basically straight VT in my personal brokerage and target-dates in my retirement accounts. Just staying the course in my retirement accounts. For my personal brokerage thus far I&amp;#39;ve stuck with just VT contributions but I&amp;#39;ve upped my monthly contributions significantly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still have about $30K surplus getting ate away at the bank set-aside for a car purchase, but with interest rates being what they are it seems smarter just to finance it (especially if money is losing value). Probably will end up dumping it all into VT but wondering what others are doing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tesla drops below $1 trillion market cap]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-drops-below-1-trillion-market-cap-154047937.html

Over the weekend CEO Elon Musk said he could sell more stock, in what many saw
as an off-color response to a tweet from Senator Bernie Sanders.

Musk sold about $6.9 billion in shares last week, sending the stock…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qujwyc/tesla_drops_below_1_trillion_market_cap/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qujwyc/tesla_drops_below_1_trillion_market_cap/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 19:12:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-drops-below-1-trillion-market-cap-154047937.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-drops-below-1-trillion-market-cap-154047937.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the weekend CEO Elon Musk said he could sell more stock, in what many saw as an off-color response to a tweet from Senator Bernie Sanders. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Musk sold about $6.9 billion in shares last week, sending the stock price lower. Tesla shares are down more than 15% over the last five sessions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seem Elon will keep selling Telsa stocks this week to finish his 10% goal. Investors can start a small position this week under 1k as tesla is still the industry leader and very far ahead for many competitors. If the stock really drop back to $900, then it could consider to add more position.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian is the third largest automaker in the world (at least by market cap)]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://companiesmarketcap.com/automakers/largest-automakers-by-market-cap/

You can argue which of these are automakers (Tesla?), and I don't want to start
a discussion about this here again. But this is just crazy. What does it mean?
EV bubble? Buy Volkswagen? Sell everything and keep off the…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qukm4y/rivian_is_the_third_largest_automaker_in_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qukm4y/rivian_is_the_third_largest_automaker_in_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 18:53:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://companiesmarketcap.com/automakers/largest-automakers-by-market-cap/&quot;&gt;https://companiesmarketcap.com/automakers/largest-automakers-by-market-cap/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can argue which of these are automakers (Tesla?), and I don&amp;#39;t want to start a discussion about this here again. But this is just crazy. What does it mean? EV bubble? Buy Volkswagen? Sell everything and keep off the market?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full disclosure, I have shares of BYD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stock Battle!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey Reddit! A friend and I are having a "stock battle" starting Christmas day,
were both using 100$ and going to the end of the school year, one small problem,
I have no idea what I'm doing and would love any help I can get! Anyone can feel
free to join, at the end of the year my friend and I will…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtvis8/stock_battle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtvis8/stock_battle/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 18:53:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey Reddit! A friend and I are having a &amp;quot;stock battle&amp;quot; starting Christmas day, were both using 100$ and going to the end of the school year, one small problem, I have no idea what I&amp;#39;m doing and would love any help I can get! Anyone can feel free to join, at the end of the year my friend and I will be comparing our (hopefully) profits. whoever makes the most wins!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I figured out a solution to slow down inflation:

We should all stop buying so much stuff https://t.co/pxq6EmUwAr]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460247607008182273</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460247607008182273</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 18:41:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[FYI Container costs just jumped from $2500 to $25000. We just canceled all orders for the rest of the year so we don’t lost money. Shitz about to get wild out there. Good luck]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quh1r8/fyi_container_costs_just_jumped_from_2500_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quh1r8/fyi_container_costs_just_jumped_from_2500_to/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 17:29:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just sign out Elon, pls]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quida5/just_sign_out_elon_pls/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quida5/just_sign_out_elon_pls/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 17:29:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Down with the ship]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quaw1q/down_with_the_ship/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quaw1q/down_with_the_ship/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 16:21:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vanguard's preliminary year-end fund distribution estimates are due out today (November 15, 2021)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Not yet available as of this morning's check, but due out today. See third item
in list:

Preliminary year-end Vanguard fund distribution estimates
[https://advisors.vanguard.com/tax-center/tax-season-calendar/current-year]]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/quh2so/vanguards_preliminary_yearend_fund_distribution/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/quh2so/vanguards_preliminary_yearend_fund_distribution/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 15:53:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not yet available as of this morning&amp;#39;s check, but due out today.  See third item in list:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://advisors.vanguard.com/tax-center/tax-season-calendar/current-year&quot;&gt;Preliminary year-end Vanguard fund distribution estimates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Semiconductor Industry will see normalization and balance by the middle of 2022, with a potential for overcapacity in 2023, IDC Reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[International Data Corporation expects the semiconductor market to grow by 17.3%
in 2021 versus 10.8% in 2020. According to IDC, the industry will see
normalization and balance by the middle of 2022, with a potential for
overcapacity in 2023 as larger scale capacity expansions begin to come…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qu5pfc/semiconductor_industry_will_see_normalization_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qu5pfc/semiconductor_industry_will_see_normalization_and/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 13:20:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;International Data Corporation expects the semiconductor market to grow by 17.3% in 2021 versus 10.8% in 2020. According to IDC, the industry will see normalization and balance by the middle of 2022, with a potential for overcapacity in 2023 as larger scale capacity expansions begin to come online towards the end of 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=prAP48247621&quot;&gt;https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=prAP48247621&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why do copper prices still go down despite the increase in demand?]]></title><description><![CDATA[So recently copper prices went down despite the concerns about the shortage of
the metal. Despite the great demand for it, prices are still volatile and the
whole situation is pretty messy tbh. It’s somewhat confusing to me because I
thought that if the demand is high and producers are struggling to…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qudym9/why_do_copper_prices_still_go_down_despite_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qudym9/why_do_copper_prices_still_go_down_despite_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 13:20:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So recently copper prices went down despite the concerns about the shortage of the metal. Despite the great demand for it, prices are still volatile and the whole situation is pretty messy tbh. It’s somewhat confusing to me because I thought that if the demand is high and producers are struggling to comply, then the prices should go up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also thinking if my worries are warranted, especially since I have some copper stocks in my portfolio and I made investments recently too, placing some money in juniors. I know they’re a pretty risky investment, but I always remind myself to invest money I am willing t&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of them is Oroco Resources (ORRCF) which recently uncovered extensive copper deposits. The drilling activities that commenced in their&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.orocoresourcecorp.com/projects/santo-tomas/&quot;&gt; Santo Tomas Project&lt;/a&gt; confirmed the presence of polymetallic copper mineralization. They hold 100% interest in two contiguous mineral concessions in Guerrero, Mexico which are included in their project in Xochipala.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also placed some on&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.threevalleycopper.com/&quot;&gt; Three Valley Copper&lt;/a&gt; (TVC) since they’re pretty much on a roll recently. They will start mining next month or in early 2022 and are expected to have an annual production between 13,000 and 16,000 tonnes of copper cathode by 2023. The company recently announced an upsize with a recent deal financing to $16 million due to investor demand. Also just last month they released their second quarter results where they were able to mine 178,105 tonnes of ore at a grade of 0.50%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now I’m going to hold back from investing despite the price dip because I’m pretty anxious because of the whole situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Plz Papa don’t hurt me no more]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtwxkm/plz_papa_dont_hurt_me_no_more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtwxkm/plz_papa_dont_hurt_me_no_more/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 11:39:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I finally added bonds!]]></title><description><![CDATA[I set up a account and purchased $1000 in I bonds. It isn't even a percent of my
wealth and it's mainly to eventually become an emergency fund. I feel like it's
a good life choice.]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qu6uo8/i_finally_added_bonds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qu6uo8/i_finally_added_bonds/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 11:26:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I set up a account and purchased $1000 in I bonds.
It isn&amp;#39;t even a percent of my wealth and it&amp;#39;s mainly to eventually become an emergency fund. I feel like it&amp;#39;s a good life choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weed Could Run Next]]></title><description><![CDATA[It seems towards the end of the rotations we've been having starting with value
stocks and ending with mega pumps from SPACs, companies with zero revenue *cough
Rivian*, and weed stonks.

Catalyst

Rumor has it, that Rep. Mace (R) from SC is proposing a bill to legalize
Marijuana at the Federal…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qu13sv/weed_could_run_next/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qu13sv/weed_could_run_next/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 10:38:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seems towards the end of the rotations we&amp;#39;ve been having starting with value stocks and ending with mega pumps from SPACs, companies with zero revenue *cough Rivian*, and weed stonks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Catalyst&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rumor has it, that Rep. Mace (R) from SC is proposing a bill to legalize Marijuana at the Federal level. &amp;quot;Those who’ve &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-12/republicans-pot-bill-to-propose-lower-taxes-more-state-control&quot;&gt;seen&lt;/a&gt; Mace’s draft say it would regulate cannabis more like alcohol&amp;quot;. This bill coming from the republican side may garner more support than Sen. Schumer&amp;#39;s already proposed bill. &amp;quot; Mace’s proposed excise tax is 3.75%, according to Cobb -- a fraction of the 25.5% that Schumer’s legislation would put on marijuana products.&amp;quot; Personally, I&amp;#39;ve heard this bill could be brought forward as early as Monday 11/15. But, that&amp;#39;s just chatter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Well, which dank stock should I buy?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve looked at various companies and honestly diversifying into a few may be worth it. However, I have the greatest conviction in &lt;strong&gt;$TLRY&lt;/strong&gt; the largest market share in Canada, Germany, and ties to the US with Sweetwater brewing. Those with the greatest dependence on the US may outperform. But, screw the fundamentals because that&amp;#39;s not how this market works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*for simplicity I&amp;#39;ll just illustrate $TLRY to represent the Marijuana sector since it has the largest market cap*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Institutions buying $420M+?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In general, Institutions have been buying these Cannabis companies as they blew off earlier in the year. Heaviest buying has been in $TLRY with the heaviest selling in $SNDL. Interestingly most of the buys come during Q2 which means most of these institutional apes are holding some serious bags. They could be down anywhere from -4% to -33% depending on when they bought in Q2. So, don&amp;#39;t be surprised if this gets pumped and ultimately dumped to lighten their bags.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/n0904d0bzmz71.png?width=2386&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=fb69d29fe355abc07e40a01cc412993d9f8b3b3b&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/n0904d0bzmz71.png?width=2386&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=fb69d29fe355abc07e40a01cc412993d9f8b3b3b&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leaders in the Sector?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$ACB&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;$SNDL&lt;/strong&gt; currently lead the move upward as they are right at their 200-day moving average. Does that mean they&amp;#39;ll continue leading the way? I don&amp;#39;t know. Does that mean the others have more to run? I can&amp;#39;t see the future, you twit. As a result, diversifying in this sector might be the way to go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Crayons&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It appears &lt;strong&gt;$TLRY&lt;/strong&gt; has started to round out and will try to push hire. The green lines are historical supply/demand lines at candle closes. I&amp;#39;m setting my stop near the recent low of $9.98 and will continue to sell out starting at $15.50 to $30.00 for a gain close to between 20% and 130%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/cssq7ipczmz71.png?width=2712&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=80aa4805f62ae8a139a233ae266c836122544bd9&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/cssq7ipczmz71.png?width=2712&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=80aa4805f62ae8a139a233ae266c836122544bd9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social Traction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another reason I am choosing to look at &lt;strong&gt;$TLRY&lt;/strong&gt; is because of all the weed stocks, &lt;strong&gt;$TLRY&lt;/strong&gt; gains the most attention on google trends and is the 2nd most mentioned on WSB behind &lt;strong&gt;$SNDL.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Positions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I literally have none and plan on buying Monday with any of you that like the stock(s). I&amp;#39;ll update after buys are in. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*This is literally my uneducated, unlicensed opinion. Don&amp;#39;t listen to me. You&amp;#39;ll Lose money\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[If people were angry when brokers halted GME buy's, what would happen if a stock market crash occurs and ordinary investors are not able to sell?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I was just listening to a podcast with an investment advisor who said that he
and his clients are all long equities and they have stop loss orders placed in
case of a crash. As the market goes up they raise their stop price.

However, I was wondering how this would work if the market is closed, or…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qu188u/if_people_were_angry_when_brokers_halted_gme_buys/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qu188u/if_people_were_angry_when_brokers_halted_gme_buys/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 06:31:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was just listening to a podcast with an investment advisor who said that he and his clients are all long equities and they have stop loss orders placed in case of a crash. As the market goes up they raise their stop price. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I was wondering how this would work if the market is closed, or if the circuit breakers kick in, and when the market re-opens the prices are all well below their limit/stop price. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, lets say the Dow closes at 36,000 and some terrible news event occurs overnight there might be no way people would be able to exit their positions at 36,000. They wlll have to sell after the market opens right? And the market wil open much lower than 36,000.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, if word gets out that certain investors were able to sell, while retail investors were unable to get their orders filled this could lead to a full scale revolt. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is this concern legitimate, or are their controls in place to prevent retail investors from getting hosed while the well connected all exit their long positions?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Waiting for the Evergrande Collapse.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qu77t9/waiting_for_the_evergrande_collapse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qu77t9/waiting_for_the_evergrande_collapse/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 06:00:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AI to create opportunity for an $80 trillion market cap. Is Cathie Wood trolling?]]></title><description><![CDATA[“We were assuming that in the next 10 years, artificial intelligence would
deliver, in the enterprise software space, a market cap opportunity of $30
trillion,” the star stockpicker said at a Milken Institute conference last
month. “Our new number is $80…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtxork/ai_to_create_opportunity_for_an_80_trillion/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtxork/ai_to_create_opportunity_for_an_80_trillion/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 04:59:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We were assuming that in the next 10 years, artificial intelligence would deliver, in the enterprise software space, a market cap opportunity of $30 trillion,” the star stockpicker said at a Milken Institute conference last month. “Our new number is $80 trillion.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-wood-just-called-technology-140000074.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-wood-just-called-technology-140000074.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is an interesting use of terminology.  “Market cap” is the market value of a publicly-traded company&amp;#39;s outstanding shares.  Therefore, I’m to take it that AI is an opportunity for a single company to be worth 80T. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alphabet is one of the leaders in the AI space; at an almost $2T market cap, they would need to grow 45% YoY over the next 10 years to hit 80T.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost any other company in the world would need significantly more growth to get to $80T. No one would have thought APPL would be a $2.5T company 10 years ago when they were $335b, but to get there was a 20% YoY growth from 2011 -&amp;gt; 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where is she pulling this info from? How can she justify these claims?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are your thoughts? Do you see the possibility of an $80T company in 10 years? Will it come from AI?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Are there monthly market cycle patterns that I can use when DCA-ing into a highly diversified ETF?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am DCA-ing into VWRA (think VT if you are in the US) every month and am
wondering if there is a specific day where statistically the price is the
lowest?

I was asking myself if a lot of people DCA-ing at the same day would have an
impact on price. I can imagine there being some patterns and was…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qtphhb/are_there_monthly_market_cycle_patterns_that_i/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qtphhb/are_there_monthly_market_cycle_patterns_that_i/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 04:59:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am DCA-ing into VWRA (think VT if you are in the US) every month and am wondering if there is a specific day where statistically the price is the lowest?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was asking myself if a lot of people DCA-ing at the same day would have an impact on price. I can imagine there being some patterns and was wondering if anyone has ever done this analysis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe it&amp;#39;s the last days of the month because people have to sell to cover bills etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or it&amp;#39;s on any of Mondays in a month because ... everyone hates Mondays and that affects buying pressure ...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[VAX UP!
 https://t.co/1a6iyAfVD2]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460083117172080643</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460083117172080643</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 04:43:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[More Americans have $1 million saved for retirement than ever before]]></title><description><![CDATA[> Fidelity’s data show hundreds of thousands of people with million-dollar
> retirement accounts, and I say hurray for them. Their golden years are looking
> good.
> 
> Together, the number of accounts with $1 million or more grew 74.5%, but it’s
> not clear how many individuals this represents,…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qu6vu5/more_americans_have_1_million_saved_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qu6vu5/more_americans_have_1_million_saved_for/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 04:11:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fidelity’s data show hundreds of thousands of people with million-dollar retirement accounts, and I say hurray for them. Their golden years are looking good.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Together, the number of accounts with $1 million or more grew 74.5%, but it’s not clear how many individuals this represents, since investors can have multiple accounts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you grown you retirement account to any decent numbers? What&amp;#39;s the approach that you are taking?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$90,000 in Cannabis Stocks - is this a bad idea?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi all,

I (31M) have 90,000 dollars in marijuana stocks. With the impending departure
from prohibition, I feel this must be a safe bet, right? I have the money fairly
evenly distributed across about 13 USA based marijuana stocks and ETFs. I am not
an extremely experienced investor. I am writing…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qu4fer/90000_in_cannabis_stocks_is_this_a_bad_idea/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qu4fer/90000_in_cannabis_stocks_is_this_a_bad_idea/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 03:38:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi all,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I (31M) have 90,000 dollars in marijuana stocks. With the impending departure from prohibition, I feel this must be a safe bet, right? I have the money fairly evenly distributed across about 13 USA based marijuana stocks and ETFs. I am not an extremely experienced investor. I am writing this post to get a few pieces of information: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;1.  Is this a good idea? Either way, please back up your response with credible information. 
2.  If you’re invested in pot stocks, what’s your strategy? How much do you have in? I am curious to know how many other people out there are like me.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Extraordinary market situation for Tesla (TSLA) right now. Musk is selling 10% of his holdings. I found daily repeating patterns, is it poss]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ok so I there is an extraordinary opportunity to trade Tesla right now


HOW IT STARTED:

https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1457064697782489088

As per this tweet he announced to sell 10% of his stocks, which was at the time
of his tweet: 172,6m ordinary shares

He started on monday 8th november…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtzgu6/extraordinary_market_situation_for_tesla_tsla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtzgu6/extraordinary_market_situation_for_tesla_tsla/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 02:39:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok so I there is an extraordinary opportunity to trade Tesla right now&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;How it started:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1457064697782489088&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1457064697782489088&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As per this tweet he announced to sell 10% of his stocks, which was at the time of his tweet: 172,6m ordinary shares&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He started on monday 8th november and started selling. We know exactly how much he sells each day since he needs to file those numbers to the SEC. You can find them here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://ir.tesla.com/sec-filings&quot;&gt;click&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the proof he is really selling as announced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may check this article to see its legit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/elon-musk-sells-tesla-stock-in-plan-set-before-twitter-poll-sec-filing-shows-11636591389&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/elon-musk-sells-tesla-stock-in-plan-set-before-twitter-poll-sec-filing-shows-11636591389&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;How it is going:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found this graphic on Twitter which visualizes his sales in relation to the performance of the Tesla share price: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/RawBooty2/status/1459121681549733893&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This shows that Elons sales continously move the price downwards. Please note that the graphic wasnt updated for fridays sales yet. I will update it as soon as its available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Now the interesting part We know how many shares he still has to sell !&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is 17,3m shares (10% of 172,6m) minus what has been sold already.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So that is 11,4m shares left for sale&lt;/strong&gt; since we know from SEC files he sold 4,9m shares until friday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I copied all the SEC files in one Excel document and calculated the sales volumes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we assume he will continue to sell 500 - 639k shares a day as he did the last three days that means &lt;strong&gt;he will be selling for another 18-23 trading days&lt;/strong&gt;. Which would be 8th dec - 15th dec&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So how do we use this knowledge ?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well I assume and the chart proves it that the buyers will not be willing to jump in front of the bus while Elon dumps his shares. So there is a really good chance we see lower prices until he is done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately i cant include pictures in this post. I will give you guys a link to a post with pictures in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a rise in SP on Wednesday but he filed his first SEC report on Wednesday evening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So ever since it is public knowledge that he &lt;strong&gt;really&lt;/strong&gt; started selling and how much he sells it was going down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;How to play it:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see several possibilities to take profit from this knowledge&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold puts until Elon is almost done&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sell a part of holding now and buy it back later at lower prices (some say thats what EMusk might intend to do)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold puts until Elon is done and reinvest your gains in calls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look at the daily patterns, caused by Elons broker dumping shares&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, i cant post pictures here. I will include the link to the pictured post in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might notice that each day from Wednesday to Friday starts with a dip and then a mini rally which peaks between 10:30 AM and 11:00 AM. Followed by descending prices through the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently i am holding puts which i bought last monday and wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am no financial advisor and please dont regard this as any form of advice or recommendation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please do your own due dilligence!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>