<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 07:48:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[QQQ vs. SPY?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Considering investing in either QQQ or SPY but can’t determine which is the
right one. Or should I invest in both?

My DD shows:

— QQQ tracks the NASDAQ 100 Index, while SPY tracks the S&P 500 Index — QQQ is
100 stocks in a handful of sectors, largely concentrated in tech. SPY is 500
stocks spread…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2snig/qqq_vs_spy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2snig/qqq_vs_spy/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 07:07:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Considering investing in either QQQ or SPY but can’t determine which is the right one.  Or should I invest in both? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My DD shows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;— QQQ tracks the NASDAQ 100 Index, while SPY tracks the S&amp;amp;P 500 Index
— QQQ is 100 stocks in a handful of sectors, largely concentrated in tech. SPY is 500 stocks spread across all sectors
— looks like QQQ is already inside SPY while SPY is over 1/4 tech.l
— expense fees for QQQ is higher (at 0.20%) meanwhile SPY is cheaper (at 0.09%)
— NASDAQ 100 has beaten the S&amp;amp;P 500 over the past 10 years, generating an average annual return of 20.27% vs 14.26%
— QQQ assets has $201.39B while SPY has $417.28B&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is everyone else’s thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT:  leaning towards VOO (due to low expense ratio) and QQQ.  Since SPY and VOO are so similar I think lower expense ratio is the deciding factor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bloody day but added BA,OKE, CVX,UPS,FDX, VZ]]></title><description><![CDATA[Looking long-term but use today’s selloff opportunities to buy some quality
companies.

Boeing. $197.45. (Already has a position at $238 😕)

Oneok $61.00

Chevron $112.50

United parcel system $204.85

Federal Express. $237.50

Verizon $51.60

For better or worse we will see what happens.

If you…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2u0pn/bloody_day_but_added_baoke_cvxupsfdx_vz/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2u0pn/bloody_day_but_added_baoke_cvxupsfdx_vz/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 06:29:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking long-term but use today’s selloff opportunities to buy some quality companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boeing.  $197.45. (Already has a position at $238 😕)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oneok         $61.00&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chevron  $112.50&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;United parcel system $204.85&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Federal Express.   $237.50&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verizon        $51.60&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For better or worse we will see what happens. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you purchased some shares today what did you buy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What did you want to buy that you did not buy?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MORE!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2qt2m/more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2qt2m/more/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 05:47:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tesla decides against state aid for German battery plant as Musk opposes subsidies]]></title><description><![CDATA[ * Tesla withdraws application for state funding
 * All subsidies should be eliminated, Musk tweets
 * Car plant construction progressing well - economy ministry
 * Regional funding application still underway

BERLIN, Nov 26 (Reuters) - Tesla (TSLA.O) said on Friday it has withdrawn its
application…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2xgg0/tesla_decides_against_state_aid_for_german/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2xgg0/tesla_decides_against_state_aid_for_german/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 03:52:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tesla withdraws application for state funding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All subsidies should be eliminated, Musk tweets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Car plant construction progressing well - economy ministry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regional funding application still underway&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BERLIN, Nov 26 (Reuters) - Tesla (TSLA.O) said on Friday it has withdrawn its application for state aid for its planned battery factory near Berlin as CEO Elon Musk declared the electric vehicle maker opposed all subsidies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The European Union in January approved a plan that included giving state aid to Tesla, BMW (BMWG.DE) and others to support production of electric vehicle batteries and help the bloc to reduce imports from industry leader China.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla was expected to receive 1.14 billion euros ($1.28 billion) in EU funding for its battery plant in Gruenheide, Brandenburg under the plan, with a final decision likely by the end of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Tesla has informed the Federal Ministry of Economics and the Brandenburg Ministry of Economics... it is withdrawing its IPCEI application for state funding for the battery factory in Grünheide,&amp;quot; a Tesla spokesperson said, referring to European subsidies allocated to so-called &amp;#39;Important Projects of Common European Interest&amp;#39;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Construction plans for the plant would not be affected by the decision, the spokesperson said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;It has always been Tesla’s view that all subsidies should be eliminated,&amp;quot; Musk posted on Twitter in response to a tweet by another user after Tesla said it had withdrawn its funding application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;But that must include the massive subsidies for oil &amp;amp; gas. For some reason, governments don’t want to do that...,&amp;quot; Musk added, deviating from the subject of the factory grant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla itself is investing 5 billion euros in the battery plant, according to German economy ministry estimates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, construction of a car production site alongside the battery plant, which Tesla has begun building under pre-approval permits while it awaits final approval from the regional government, has made good progress in the last few weeks, a spokesperson for the federal economy ministry said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The electric vehicle maker also applied in November 2020 for regional funding from Brandenburg, according to the regional government&amp;#39;s website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Brandenburg economy ministry spokesperson said this application had not been withdrawn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The amount Tesla applied for is undisclosed, but investments worth over 100 million euros are generally given 6.8% of their value, the website says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The latest round of online consultations for the public to express environmental and other concerns about the car factory and battery plant closed last week and Tesla CEO Elon Musk has said he hopes to formally begin production by the end of the year and then ramp up as quickly as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Musk has made his irritation for German laws and processes known, saying in a letter to authorities in April that the country&amp;#39;s complex planning requirements were at odds with the urgency needed to fight climate change. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-withdrew-state-funding-application-german-battery-plant-economy-ministry-2021-11-26/&quot;&gt;https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-withdrew-state-funding-application-german-battery-plant-economy-ministry-2021-11-26/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[https://t.co/WYYPr7IR71]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464429941706182667</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464429941706182667</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 03:40:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cathie Wood updates price target for ARKK in latest CNBC interview to ~440]]></title><description><![CDATA[Previous target, ~310, 15% per year for 5 years

New Target, ~440, 4x in 5 years or 33% per year for 5 years

Or in table format

Today 2022 2023 2024 2025 2026 15% 155 178 205 236 271 312 33% 108 144 191 254
338 449]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2gt66/cathie_wood_updates_price_target_for_arkk_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2gt66/cathie_wood_updates_price_target_for_arkk_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 03:23:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous target, ~310, 15% per year for 5 years&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New Target, ~440, 4x in 5 years or 33% per year for 5 years&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or in table format&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Today&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2022&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2023&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2024&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2025&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2026&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;15%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;155&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;178&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;205&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;236&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;271&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;312&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;33%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;108&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;144&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;191&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;254&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;338&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;449&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Bogleheads method just for rich people?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm interested in investing money for long term and end up here, but I just see
people who put 400k+ and end with a million. I don't have that much money to
invest, do I have a chance to try with little money? Like more little.]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r30qt2/is_bogleheads_method_just_for_rich_people/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r30qt2/is_bogleheads_method_just_for_rich_people/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 02:56:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m interested in investing money for long term and end up here, but I just see people who put 400k+ and end with a million. I don&amp;#39;t have that much money to invest, do I have a chance to try with little money? Like more little.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$PSFE Paysafe down 50% recently. Good opportunity for bounce trade?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Down so dramatically seemingly because of their adjusted guidance? Seems like an
extreme drop and it's below the lower band of analyst price targets. It's
putting in a bullish rsi divergence on the daily chart too.

Can someone fill me in on what's going on with the stock price here? Looks like
a…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2r9dk/psfe_paysafe_down_50_recently_good_opportunity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2r9dk/psfe_paysafe_down_50_recently_good_opportunity/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 02:40:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Down so dramatically seemingly because of their adjusted guidance? Seems like an extreme drop and it&amp;#39;s below the lower band of analyst price targets. It&amp;#39;s putting in a bullish rsi divergence on the daily chart too. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can someone fill me in on what&amp;#39;s going on with the stock price here? Looks like a good buying opportunity to me but I haven&amp;#39;t done much research yet. Hoping one of you has been looking into this and can shed some light. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[So the market dropped by more than 2% in a day. Can we predict anything from that? The answer might not surprise you (it is "no").]]></title><description><![CDATA[So today S&P500 dropped about 2 point something%, ending about 3% below its ATH.
Of course, the market being 3% under its ATH is nothing to write home about, but
the fact that it dropped by two percentage points in a single day seemed to
raise some concerns.

So I wondered: how common is it for the…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2xegl/so_the_market_dropped_by_more_than_2_in_a_day_can/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2xegl/so_the_market_dropped_by_more_than_2_in_a_day_can/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 02:40:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So today S&amp;amp;P500 dropped about 2 point something%, ending about 3% below its ATH. Of course, the market being 3% under its ATH is nothing to write home about, but the fact that it dropped by two percentage points in a single day seemed to raise some concerns.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I wondered: how common is it for the market to drop by two percentage points or more in a single day, and does this tell us anything about its likely return after, say, 100 days (this is likely much shorter than the time horizon of many of us here, but longer periods would likely make the effect - if any - of the drop harder to notice)? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I downloaded from yahoo finance  the daily S&amp;amp;P500 data for the 1994-2021 period and played around a little with it trying to see if any correlation could be found. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This graph shows the percentage change from the previous day versus the percentage return after 100 days: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/FzScbjp&quot;&gt;One day fluctuations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not seeing much of a correlation between one-day fluctuations and 100-days returns here. Also worth noting is that the days which saw a drop of 2% or more from the previous day were uncommon but not &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; uncommon (I found 299 of them in 6998 days, that is, about one every 23 days). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I tried anyway to try to see if I could find a correlation, just for completeness&amp;#39; sake, and the result is what you would expect from that graph: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/0Lt9SRt&quot;&gt;No correlation&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If anything, it would seem that the change from the previous day might be slightly &lt;em&gt;negatively&lt;/em&gt; correlated to the 100-days return - i.e., great days might lead to poorer returns after 100 days - but the correlation coefficient is so low and the standard error so high that the only reasonable conclusion is that one-day changes are of no predictive value for 100-days returns. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what about extremes? What if we consider only the &amp;quot;bad&amp;quot; days in which the market dropped by more than 2%? Here is what we get:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/6Pd1kN8&quot;&gt;Bad days&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let us compare this with the (235 out of 6998) days in which the market rose by more than 2%: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/q1Cl1eR&quot;&gt;Good days&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About the same mean, slightly lower standard deviation but that&amp;#39;s too close to say anything meaningful. For completeness&amp;#39;s sake, I also looked at the &amp;quot;meh days&amp;quot; in which the market did not change by more than 2% in either direction from the previous day: for those days, the average return after 100 days was by 4% - more or less in line with the others - and the standard deviation was by by 0.09 -- lower than the others, but not enough that I&amp;#39;d be confident making any conclusions out of this. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion: the fact that the market dropped by more than 2% today tells us nothing meaningful about what it will do in the next 100 days. Is it possible that the market will crash soon? Sure, that is always possible; but today&amp;#39;s drop, in itself, tells us nothing about its chances.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Any Bogleheads in New Zealand?]]></title><description><![CDATA[It is a slightly different investing and tax landscape in NZ compared to the US.

I’d be keen to compare notes on the best approach if anyone is interested.

For asset allocation, I’m currently:

 * 85% AMP ACWI (60% US / 40% rest of the world) - 69% hedged to NZD; and

 * 15% home bias (Simplicity…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2xg0t/any_bogleheads_in_new_zealand/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2xg0t/any_bogleheads_in_new_zealand/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 01:04:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a slightly different investing and tax landscape in NZ compared to the US. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d be keen to compare notes on the best approach if anyone is interested.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For asset allocation, I’m currently:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;85% AMP ACWI (60% US / 40% rest of the world) - 69% hedged to NZD; and &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% home bias (Simplicity NZ Share a fund)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we approach retirement I’m looking to move toward 60% shares / 40% fixed interest.   Weighing up the pros/cons of moving out of PIE funds and investing direct.  Although I don’t like the currency risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Covid: It’s Time for Africa]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2v5f7/covid_its_time_for_africa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2v5f7/covid_its_time_for_africa/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 01:04:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why banks go down heavily on new Covid variant news?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Title is self-explanatory, but what's the reasoning behind the heavy downtrend
of banks and the new covid variant? The way I see it banks will benefit from the
most than likely interest hike if inflation persists. Anyone can shed some light
on this?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2q5zd/why_banks_go_down_heavily_on_new_covid_variant/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2q5zd/why_banks_go_down_heavily_on_new_covid_variant/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 23:55:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Title is self-explanatory, but what&amp;#39;s the reasoning behind the heavy downtrend of banks and the new covid variant?
The way I see it banks will benefit from the most than likely interest hike if inflation persists. 
Anyone can shed some light on this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Market F**CK Cockatoo is Back!!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2r088/market_fck_cockatoo_is_back/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2r088/market_fck_cockatoo_is_back/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 23:29:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Stock Market Today Be Like]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2xdc2/the_stock_market_today_be_like/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2xdc2/the_stock_market_today_be_like/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 23:29:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[China Asks Didi to Delist From U.S. On Security Fears]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://archive.md/20211126053013/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-26/china-is-said-to-ask-didi-to-delist-from-u-s-on-security-fears

Chinese regulators have asked Didi Global Inc.’s top executives to devise a plan
to delist from U.S. bourses, people familiar with the matter said,…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2m6n2/china_asks_didi_to_delist_from_us_on_security/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2m6n2/china_asks_didi_to_delist_from_us_on_security/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 23:07:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.md/20211126053013/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-26/china-is-said-to-ask-didi-to-delist-from-u-s-on-security-fears&quot;&gt;https://archive.md/20211126053013/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-26/china-is-said-to-ask-didi-to-delist-from-u-s-on-security-fears&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chinese regulators have asked Didi Global Inc.’s top executives to devise a plan to delist from U.S. bourses, people familiar with the matter said, an unprecedented request that’s likely to revive fears about Beijing’s intentions for its giant tech industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The country’s tech watchdog wants management to take the company off the New York Stock Exchange because of concerns about leakage of sensitive data, the people said, asking not to be identified discussing a sensitive matter. The Cyberspace Administration of China, the agency responsible for data security in the country, has directed Didi to work out precise details, subject to government approval, they said.  Proposals under consideration include a straight-up privatization or a share float in Hong Kong followed by a delisting from the U.S., the people added. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the privatization proceeds, the proposal will likely be at least the $14 IPO price since a lower offer so soon after the June initial public offering could prompt lawsuits or shareholder resistance, the people said. If there is a secondary listing in Hong Kong, the IPO price would probably be a discount to the share price in the U.S., $8.11 as of Wednesday’s close. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shares in SoftBank Group Corp., Didi’s biggest minority shareholder, slid more than 5% in Tokyo. Deliberations continue and it’s possible regulators will backtrack on their request, the people said. Either option would deal a severe blow to a ride-hailing giant that pulled off the largest U.S. IPO by a Chinese firm since Alibaba Group Holding Ltd.’s in 2014. Representatives for Didi and the CAC didn’t respond to requests for comment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi sparked the ire of Beijing when it proceeded with its New York stock offering this summer, despite regulatory requests that it ensure the security of its data before the IPO. Chinese regulators quickly launched multiple investigations into the company and have considered a range of unprecedented penalties, Bloomberg News reported in July. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s possible that the delisting would be part of a package of punishments for Didi. Beijing’s municipal government has proposed an investment in the company that would give state-run firms effective control, Bloomberg News reported in September. Such an investment could help Didi finance the repurchase of its U.S.-traded shares. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi is currently controlled by the management team of co-founder Cheng Wei and President Jean Liu, which received aggregate voting power of 58% after the company’s U.S. initial public offering. SoftBank and Uber Technologies Inc. are Didi’s biggest minority shareholders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if Didi shifts its listing to Hong Kong, it will have to address the data security concerns that have drawn regulatory scrutiny. The company may have to give up control of its data to a third-party -- again undercutting its price tag.
Read more about Didi’s brushes with Beijing regulators&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regulators have weighed a delisting for Didi since the summer, after the world’s largest ride-hailing company infuriated officials by ploughing ahead with its U.S. IPO, Bloomberg News has reported. A withdrawal from U.S. bourses could stoke fears of an exodus of Chinese firms as Washington and Beijing quarrel about access to listed firms’ books. On Thursday, a senior Chinese regulatory official said such delistings would be a setback for relations with the U.S., while offering broad support for Hong Kong as an alternative venue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi -- once feted for defeating Uber in China -- has now become a test case for a broader Chinese government effort to curb the power of internet titans. Xi Jinping’s administration, keen to promote his vision of sharing the wealth or “common prosperity,” has targeted an internet sector that’s accumulated vast wealth by operating on the periphery of the law, minted an unprecedented number of billionaires and enriched local and foreign investors in the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A state-directed privatization would be unprecedented for a private firm of Didi’s stature, affirming that the Chinese government remains bent on curtailing the power of the country’s internet firms and unlocking the data and wealth hoarded during a decade of heady expansion. It would send a chilling signal to American investors, long accustomed to investing freely in China’s largest corporations from Alibaba to Baidu Inc. and JD.com Inc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beijing’s moves against Didi have been particularly harsh, even after a crackdown that has penalized giants like Alibaba and Tencent Holdings Ltd. The Cyberspace Administration of China saw Didi’s IPO decision as a challenge to the central government’s authority, which led to the CAC, the Ministry of Public Security, the Ministry of State Security and several other agencies initiating on-site inspections at Didi’s offices in July.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s since been ensnared by probes into data security and the way it treats its millions of drivers. Many of the options Beijing is weighing involve re-asserting state control over a company that’s traditionally operated in a legal gray zone, Bloomberg News has reported.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Waking up to check how much money my SPY calls are worth]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2pbv0/waking_up_to_check_how_much_money_my_spy_calls/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2pbv0/waking_up_to_check_how_much_money_my_spy_calls/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 22:37:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Book recommendations]]></title><description><![CDATA[What books would you recommend on investing beyond the Boglehead guide to
investing?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2q1y4/book_recommendations/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2q1y4/book_recommendations/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 21:43:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What books would you recommend on investing beyond the Boglehead guide to investing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Today's trading strategy in 12 seconds]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2ni8n/todays_trading_strategy_in_12_seconds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2ni8n/todays_trading_strategy_in_12_seconds/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 21:43:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anyone Tax Loss Harvesting today?]]></title><description><![CDATA[My new money has been going into bonds and international, so I don’t have any
losses on US ETFs today. I am over a TLH threshold for international.

Anybody tax loss harvesting today?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2qzda/anyone_tax_loss_harvesting_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2qzda/anyone_tax_loss_harvesting_today/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 21:14:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My new money has been going into bonds and international, so I don’t have any losses on US ETFs today. I am over a TLH threshold for international. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anybody tax loss harvesting today?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[r/Stocks Daily Discussion & Fundamentals Friday Nov 26, 2021]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is the daily discussion, so anything stocks related is fine, but the theme
for today is on fundamentals, but if fundamentals aren't your thing then just
ignore the theme and/or post your arguments against fundamentals…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2kb5u/rstocks_daily_discussion_fundamentals_friday_nov/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2kb5u/rstocks_daily_discussion_fundamentals_friday_nov/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 20:53:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the daily discussion, so anything stocks related is fine, but the theme for today is on fundamentals, but if fundamentals aren&amp;#39;t your thing then just ignore the theme and/or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+%22r%2Fstocks+semiannual+arguments+against+TA%22&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;post your arguments against fundamentals here&lt;/a&gt; and not in the current post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some helpful day to day links, including news:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finviz.com/quote.ashx?t=spy&quot;&gt;Finviz&lt;/a&gt; for charts, fundamentals, and aggregated news on individual stocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/markets&quot;&gt;Bloomberg market news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;StreetInsider news:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Market+Check&quot;&gt;Market Check&lt;/a&gt; - Possibly why the market is doing what it&amp;#39;s doing including sudden spikes/dips&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Reuters&quot;&gt;Reuters aggregated&lt;/a&gt; - Global news&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most fundamentals are updated every 3 months due to the fact that corporations release earnings reports every quarter, so traders are always speculating at what those earnings will say, and investors may change the size of their holdings based on those reports.  Expect a lot of volatility around earnings, but it usually doesn&amp;#39;t matter if you&amp;#39;re holding long term, but keep in mind the importance of earnings reports because a trend of declining earnings or a decline in some other fundamental will drive the stock down over the long term as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the following word cloud and click through for the wiki:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/wiki/fundamentals-themed-post&quot;&gt;Market Cap - Shares Outstanding - Volume - Dividend - EPS - P/E Ratio - EPS Q/Q - PEG - Sales Q/Q - Return on Assets (ROA) - Return on Equity (ROE) - BETA - SMA - quarterly earnings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a basic question, for example &amp;quot;what is EBITDA,&amp;quot; then google &amp;quot;investopedia EBITDA&amp;quot; and click the Investopedia article on it; do this for everything until you have a more in depth question or just want to share what you learned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Useful links:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/fundamental-analysis-4689757/&quot;&gt;Investopedia page&lt;/a&gt; on fundamental analysis including &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/university/dcf/&quot;&gt;Discounted Cash Flow&lt;/a&gt; analysis; see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/d/dcf.asp&quot;&gt;definition here&lt;/a&gt; and read &lt;a href=&quot;http://i.investopedia.com/inv/pdf/tutorials/fundamentalanalysis_intro.pdf&quot;&gt;their PDF on the topic.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finviz.com/quote.ashx?t=aapl&quot;&gt;FINVIZ&lt;/a&gt; for fundamental data, charts, and aggregated news&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.earningswhispers.com/stocks/aapl&quot;&gt;Earnings Whisper&lt;/a&gt; for earnings details&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See our past &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+%22r%2Fstocks+daily+discussion%22&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;daily discussions here.&lt;/a&gt;  Also links for:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Atechnicals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Technicals&lt;/a&gt; Tuesday, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Aoptions&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Options Trading&lt;/a&gt; Thursday, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Afundamentals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Fundamentals&lt;/a&gt; Friday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[U.S. bans travel from South Africa, Botswana, Zimbabwe, Namibia, Lesotho, Eswatini, Mozambique, and Malawi

Sounds racist]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464309113484107784</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464309113484107784</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 20:41:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Had to bring back the classic]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2s89n/had_to_bring_back_the_classic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2s89n/had_to_bring_back_the_classic/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 20:25:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Do you agree that the B.1.1.529 'horrific' killer virus strain (50 spike protein mutations) is now going to be a margin-call catalyst for anyone shorting meme stocks?]]></title><description><![CDATA[The virus mutation also has 10 other genetic mutations. WHO convening emergency
meeting. Airlines shutting down travel. Markets tumbling. As of this writing,
DOW futures are down 850 points, and russel 2000 index futures are down 4.5%.

Some talks with my friends going on about how this alone could…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2iejk/do_you_agree_that_the_b11529_horrific_killer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2iejk/do_you_agree_that_the_b11529_horrific_killer/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:59:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The virus mutation also has 10 other genetic mutations.  WHO convening emergency meeting.  Airlines shutting down travel.  Markets tumbling.  As of this writing, DOW futures are down 850 points, and russel 2000 index futures are down 4.5%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some talks with my friends going on about how this alone could serve as a GME, AMC &amp;#39;MOASS&amp;#39; catalyst, since collateral and margin maintenance requirements.  With markets crashing like this, the NSCC algos do indeed raise capital requirements.  What are your thoughts on the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GME, AMC, and other meme stocks have a negative beta and therefore serve as a hedge against falling markets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;These stocks remain heavily shorted, and therefore, funds that are stuck in egregious short positions have to buy to cover to get out, and potentially very quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.1.1.529 &amp;#39;horrific&amp;#39; killer virus strain could induce this market catalyst (as unfortunate as that is to say that it came to this in order to have free and fair markets).  Thoughts?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A heavily-mutated Covid variant emerges in Southern Africa

Fuck off]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464136788583329792</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464136788583329792</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:35:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Investing vs Trading: What is the easiest way to build wealth?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’ve been investing since February of this year with $26,000 deposited in the
stock market and I’m currently up to $33,014 so I made a 25% profit so far. My
portfolio currently consists of nine stocks. I’ve been looking into options
trading recently which involves high risk but can give high returns…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r24bqb/investing_vs_trading_what_is_the_easiest_way_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r24bqb/investing_vs_trading_what_is_the_easiest_way_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:34:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been investing since February of this year with $26,000 deposited in the stock market and I’m currently up to $33,014 so I made a 25% profit so far. My portfolio currently consists of nine stocks. I’ve been looking into options trading recently which involves high risk but can give high returns if I know what I’m doing. However, investing in established companies is obviously safer but takes longer to build wealth unless I have at least $200,000 in the market, and I can’t afford to deposit anywhere near that amount right now. Between investing in a diverse set of stocks, investing in two or three startup company stocks that may blow up one day, or doing options trading, which of these strategies do you think would be the easiest for building significant wealth within ten years?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thanks for the insurance money]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2pexn/thanks_for_the_insurance_money/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2pexn/thanks_for_the_insurance_money/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:34:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anyone DCA-ing into Disney?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Disney is official well below my average cost of $154. It was at $200 at one
point and now has crashed down to $148. I’ve been steadily buying more shares
but don’t want to fall into the falling knife thing.

Anyone else buying more of Disney? Anything I should be aware of or is this just
a covid…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2qwft/anyone_dcaing_into_disney/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2qwft/anyone_dcaing_into_disney/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 18:49:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disney is official well below my average cost of $154. It was at $200 at one point and now has crashed down to $148. I’ve been steadily buying more shares but don’t want to fall into the falling knife thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone else buying more of Disney? Anything I should be aware of or is this just a covid scare?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Happy BlackFriday from a Vietnamese retard! Should I sell or hold my MRNA calls?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2orio/happy_blackfriday_from_a_vietnamese_retard_should/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2orio/happy_blackfriday_from_a_vietnamese_retard_should/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 18:49:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ima just post this in hopes of the market turning green.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2oe7s/ima_just_post_this_in_hopes_of_the_market_turning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2oe7s/ima_just_post_this_in_hopes_of_the_market_turning/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 17:48:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is the impact of Intel returning to the GPU market on Nvidia being underestimated?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have noticed that most people on here are very bullish towards Nvidia even at
its current valuation but I haven't seen much talk about how Intel's return to
the GPU market will affect Nvidia's valuation and future growth.

Intel has the money and talent especially with Raja Koduri leading the…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2l9n8/is_the_impact_of_intel_returning_to_the_gpu/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2l9n8/is_the_impact_of_intel_returning_to_the_gpu/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 17:48:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have noticed that most people on here are very bullish towards Nvidia even at its current valuation but I haven&amp;#39;t seen much talk about how Intel&amp;#39;s return to the GPU market will affect Nvidia&amp;#39;s valuation and future growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intel has the money and talent especially with Raja Koduri leading the Graphics department to become highly competitive with Nvidia if not a leader in the market. Intel will also have the advantage of using their new fabs in the future to produce their GPU&amp;#39;s whereas Nvidia will be reliant on TSMC/Samsung.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With AMD also becoming more competitive and both Intel and AMD not being as limited to just the GPU market unlike Nvidia, should people be worried that Nvidia may have to lower profit margins and suffer from lower growth that could make their current price look extremely high?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For disclosure I do own some INTC and would be interested in NVDA if the valuation was more reasonable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NVDA calls are ready to F*ck me today]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2iqrz/nvda_calls_are_ready_to_fck_me_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2iqrz/nvda_calls_are_ready_to_fck_me_today/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 17:34:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is your view on UIPath right now?]]></title><description><![CDATA[The stock has dropped 34% since it IPO'd this year and the market cap has
dropped $10 billion. I have been considering picking up some shares recently and
after seeing their recent earnings I understand that they are not profitable
because they have been dramatically increasing their R&D plus…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r25k25/what_is_your_view_on_uipath_right_now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r25k25/what_is_your_view_on_uipath_right_now/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 17:05:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The stock has dropped 34% since it IPO&amp;#39;d this year and the market cap has dropped $10 billion. I have been considering picking up some shares recently and after seeing their recent earnings I understand that they are not profitable because they have been dramatically increasing their R&amp;amp;D plus Marketing Spend even though Revenues are increasing a good amount.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Research report on DraftKings ($DKNG)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey all, I’d appreciate it if someone could take a look at my equity research
report and provide some feedback or discussion. Thanks! -a college freshman
interested in Equity research

https://www.theancienteconomist.com/post/draftkings-dkng-equity-research-report

DraftKings is regarded as one of…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r28h7w/research_report_on_draftkings_dkng/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r28h7w/research_report_on_draftkings_dkng/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 15:47:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey all, I’d appreciate it if someone could take a look at my equity research report and provide some feedback or discussion.
Thanks! -a college freshman interested in Equity research&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theancienteconomist.com/post/draftkings-dkng-equity-research-report&quot;&gt;https://www.theancienteconomist.com/post/draftkings-dkng-equity-research-report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DraftKings is regarded as one of the current leaders of the sports gambling indus- try. The company, since its founding in 2012, has obtained lucrative partnering agree- ments with the biggest players in sports and entertainment, establishing contracts with MLB, NFL, NASCAR, UFC, ESPN, 21st Century Fox Sports, and Bleacher Report. DraftK- ings offers live daily fantasy contests for over 13 sports. The online sports gambling in- dustry has huge growth potential, which has yielded a large number of competitors to spring up, such as Penn National Gaming (NASDAQ: $PENN), fuboTV (NYSE: $FUBO), and Flutter Entertainment (OTCMKTS: $PDYPY). Despite the lure of the sports gambling industry, the bearish case for DraftKings lies in waiting for a further correction before in- vesting due to competitive pressure, limited growth, and their profitability track record.
The quality of services is critical in determining the long-term growth and customer retainment for a firm, especially within the gaming sector. DraftKings’ narrow yet compact focus on live online sports betting limits their presence in the overall gam- bling industry, as opposed to other firms such as Penn National Gaming, which employs a generalist approach to available services. Penn, in addition to sports and casino style bet- ting, is a large operator of casino and resort locations. This versatility in gambling ser- vices could provide greater growth in a post-COVID world less reliant on virtual gaming, which DraftKings does not offer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Be greedy when others are fearful. Be fearful when others are greedy.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Looks like all of the markets are going to take a shit on the news of the new
Covid variant. Funny thing about the news on that, it is simply the new strain
is heavily mutated and we don’t know if that’s bad. We should see this as an
opportunity to buy more stocks at a discount. This happened…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2lpz7/be_greedy_when_others_are_fearful_be_fearful_when/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2lpz7/be_greedy_when_others_are_fearful_be_fearful_when/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 15:27:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looks like all of the markets are going to take a shit on the news of the new Covid variant. Funny thing about the news on that, it is simply the new strain is heavily mutated and we don’t know if that’s bad. We should see this as an opportunity to buy more stocks at a discount. This happened earlier in the year and most stocks have recovered since then. Just like the Warren Buffett quote in the title. Sure everyone’s portfolio is red at the moment. Some people see the red and panic, I see a green opportunity on the horizon. Someone else once said, “scared money don’t make money”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dow futures plunge 400 points amid fears of new Covid variant found in South Africa]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2e6ss/dow_futures_plunge_400_points_amid_fears_of_new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2e6ss/dow_futures_plunge_400_points_amid_fears_of_new/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 13:31:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gotta print them all 💵]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2jd98/gotta_print_them_all/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2jd98/gotta_print_them_all/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 13:31:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What are you buying when the market opens??]]></title><description><![CDATA[As everyone knows, futures are bloody red right now on fears of a new variant.
There are really two things you should do when things open and that is nothing,
or buy. Do not sell in these conditions because I guarantee you will regret it.

With that being said…if you are in the buy group, what are…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2ivb9/what_are_you_buying_when_the_market_opens/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2ivb9/what_are_you_buying_when_the_market_opens/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 13:05:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As everyone knows, futures are bloody red right now on fears of a new variant. There are really two things you should do when things open and that is nothing, or buy. Do not sell in these conditions because I guarantee you will regret it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said…if you are in the buy group, what are you looking at when the markets open?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m looking at tech: APPLE, AMAZON and MSFT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dow futures plunge 800 points amid fears of new Covid variant found in South Africa]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/26/stock-futures-open-to-close-market-news.html

> U.S. stock futures dropped in early morning trading on Friday as investors
> geared up for a shortened trading day amid renewed Covid fears over a new
> variant found in South Africa.
> 
> Futures for the Dow Jones…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2ko1v/dow_futures_plunge_800_points_amid_fears_of_new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2ko1v/dow_futures_plunge_800_points_amid_fears_of_new/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 12:39:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/26/stock-futures-open-to-close-market-news.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/26/stock-futures-open-to-close-market-news.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;U.S. stock futures dropped in early morning trading on Friday as investors geared up for a shortened trading day amid renewed Covid fears over a new variant found in South Africa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Futures for the Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 800 points, while those for the S&amp;amp;P 500 and Nasdaq 100 were also in in negative territory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The downward moves came after WHO officials on Thursday warned of a new Covid-19 variant that&amp;#39;s been detected in South Africa. The United Kingdom temporarily suspended flights from six African countries due to the variant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bond yields tumbled amid the flight to safety. The yield on the benchmark U.S. 10-year Treasury note fell to 1.5380%, a sharp reversal after surging above 1.65% earlier this week. Bond yields move inversely to prices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oil prices also tumbled, with U.S. crude futures down 6.2% to $73.57 per barrel, while the South African rand weakened 1.7% against the greenback to 16.231 per dollar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Asia markets were hit hard in Friday trade, with Japan&amp;#39;s Nikkei 225 and Hong Kong&amp;#39;s Hang Seng index both falling more than 2% each.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Asian markets sink as investors weigh latest global virus concerns]]></title><description><![CDATA[Asian stock markets sank Friday after some European countries tightened curbs on
travel and business following a surge in coronavirus infections and South Africa
reported a new variant. Shanghai, Tokyo, Hong Kong and Sydney declined. U.S.
markets were closed Thursday for the Thanksgiving holiday.…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2g92r/asian_markets_sink_as_investors_weigh_latest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2g92r/asian_markets_sink_as_investors_weigh_latest/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 11:35:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asian stock markets sank Friday after some European countries tightened curbs on travel and business following a surge in coronavirus infections and South Africa reported a new variant. Shanghai, Tokyo, Hong Kong and Sydney declined. U.S. markets were closed Thursday for the Thanksgiving holiday. Austria imposed a nationwide 10-day lockdown after its daily virus deaths tripled, while Italy imposed curbs on activity by unvaccinated people. The U.S. government advised Americans to avoid travel to Germany and Denmark. Scientists in South Africa said a new variant was spreading among young people in its most populous province.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Investors are likely to shoot first and ask questions later until more is known,” Jeffrey Halley of Oanda said in a report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Shanghai Composite Index CN:SHCOMP lost 0.6% to 3,560.15 and the Nikkei 225 JP:NIK NIY00 in Tokyo plunged by an unusually wide 2.8% margin to 28,656.17. The Hang Seng HK:HSI in Hong Kong tumbled 2.3% to 24,161.55. The Kospi KR:180721 in Seoul lost 1.4% to 2,938.09 and Sydney’s S&amp;amp;P-ASX 200 AU:XJO fell 1.7% to 7,279. New Zealand and Southeast Asian markets also declined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wall Street’s benchmark S&amp;amp;P 500 SPX closed up 0.2% on Wednesday. U.S. markets are due to reopen Friday for a shortened post-Thanksgiving trading session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/asian-markets-sink-as-investors-weigh-latest-global-virus-concerns-01637900804?mod=mw_quote_news&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/asian-markets-sink-as-investors-weigh-latest-global-virus-concerns-01637900804?mod=mw_quote_news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What are my options since China is pushing Didi to delist from the US?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I own a small amount of Didi shares. China has asked Didi to delist from the US
over security fears. What are my options?

I use ME by BofA to trade stocks. They don't allow trading of securities that
trade over-the-counter.

Should I take a wait and see approach or offload immediately?

I've read…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2dmfx/what_are_my_options_since_china_is_pushing_didi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2dmfx/what_are_my_options_since_china_is_pushing_didi/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 10:11:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I own a small amount of Didi shares.  China has asked Didi to delist from the US over security fears.  What are my options?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use ME by BofA to trade stocks.  They don&amp;#39;t allow trading of securities that trade over-the-counter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should I take a wait and see approach or offload immediately?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve read that if privatization were to occur, it would be at the $14 IPO price.  The stock closed at $8.11 on Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If they were to delist, how would I go about trading the stock?  Or is it just considered a total loss?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How will Nu covid variant affect the markets compared to the Delta variant?]]></title><description><![CDATA[First issues with the Nu variant -

 * B.1.1.529, to be named Nu
 * 32 mutations in spike protein
 * Earliest known case: South Africa, Nov. 12
 * Fears it could be more transmissible, evade immunity
 * UK & Israel impose travel bans
 * SA reports 2,465 new cases, up 321% from last week

According…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2e5iy/how_will_nu_covid_variant_affect_the_markets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2e5iy/how_will_nu_covid_variant_affect_the_markets/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 06:52:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;First issues with the Nu variant -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.1.1.529, to be named Nu&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;32 mutations in spike protein&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earliest known case: South Africa, Nov. 12&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fears it could be more transmissible, evade immunity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UK &amp;amp; Israel impose travel bans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SA reports 2,465 new cases, up 321% from last week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According here &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/drericding/status/1463998740340121601?s=21&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/drericding/status/1463998740340121601?s=21&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost double the mutations as delta&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Was vaccine resistant as people tested were double vaccinated with Pfizer (but did not have 3rd booster) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WHO already emergency meeting and UK and Israel have shut down flights coming from 6 nations. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biggest issue is that the new variant is VACCINE RESISTANT which seems awful long term unless people are really going to attempt to get us to take brand new vaccine shots in 3-4 months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[South African scientists detect new coronavirus variant amid spike in cases. Futures down bad at the moment…]]></title><description><![CDATA[What are your thoughts? I couldn’t link any articles due to mods and rules, but
do a quick search online.

Will retails lose their cold blood? I think a lot of people on margin will eat
their socks in the next days…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2eo5e/south_african_scientists_detect_new_coronavirus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2eo5e/south_african_scientists_detect_new_coronavirus/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 06:30:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What are your thoughts? I couldn’t link any articles due to mods and rules, but do a quick search online. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will retails lose their cold blood? I think a lot of people on margin will eat their socks in the next days…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can I fund a Roth IRA with money that I had previously put into a regular brokerage?]]></title><description><![CDATA[If this has been addressed, please let me know. I have googled and searched
through this sub and can’t seem to find an answer to my question.

I didn’t contribute enough to my Roth this year and want to reach the $6000
maximum. The problem is that my income went into my brokerage and I’m…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2ddl7/can_i_fund_a_roth_ira_with_money_that_i_had/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2ddl7/can_i_fund_a_roth_ira_with_money_that_i_had/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 05:22:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If this has been addressed, please let me know. I have googled and searched through this sub and can’t seem to find an answer to my question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t contribute enough to my Roth this year and want to reach the $6000 maximum. The problem is that my income went into my brokerage and I’m concerned about how it may look to the IRS if I withdraw money from my brokerage and deposit into my Roth. This money would not be in surplus to what I deposited into my brokerage. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The IRS website just says that the money used to fund it has to be earned wages, but doesn’t go into further depth. Is it still “earned” if I’m just withdrawing money that I had earned and churned through some day trades? Am I over thinking this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any answer is appreciated and thank you for your time&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[China Asks Didi to Delist From U.S. On Security Fears]]></title><description><![CDATA[(Bloomberg) -- Chinese regulators have asked Didi Global Inc.’s top executives
to devise a plan to delist from U.S. bourses, people familiar with the matter
said, an unprecedented request that’s likely to revive fears about Beijing’s
intentions for its giant tech industry.

The country’s tech…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2d32w/china_asks_didi_to_delist_from_us_on_security/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2d32w/china_asks_didi_to_delist_from_us_on_security/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 04:43:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Chinese regulators have asked Didi Global Inc.’s top executives to devise a plan to delist from U.S. bourses, people familiar with the matter said, an unprecedented request that’s likely to revive fears about Beijing’s intentions for its giant tech industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The country’s tech watchdog wants management to take the company off the New York Stock Exchange because of concerns about leakage of sensitive data, the people said, asking not to be identified discussing a sensitive matter. The Cyberspace Administration of China, the agency responsible for data security in the country, has directed Didi to work out precise details, subject to government approval, they said. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proposals under consideration include a straight-up privatization or a share float in Hong Kong followed by a delisting from the U.S., the people added. If the privatization proceeds, the proposal will likely be at least the $14 IPO price since a lower offer so soon after the June initial public offering could prompt lawsuits or shareholder resistance, the people said. If there is a secondary listing in Hong Kong, the IPO price would probably be a discount to the share price in the U.S., $8.11 as of Wednesday’s close. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shares in SoftBank Group Corp., Didi’s biggest minority shareholder, slid more than 5% in Tokyo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deliberations continue and it’s possible regulators will backtrack on their request, the people said. Either option would deal a severe blow to a ride-hailing giant that pulled off the largest U.S. IPO by a Chinese firm since Alibaba Group Holding Ltd.’s in 2014. Representatives for Didi and the CAC didn’t respond to requests for comment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi sparked the ire of Beijing when it proceeded with its New York stock offering this summer, despite regulatory requests that it ensure the security of its data before the IPO. Chinese regulators quickly launched multiple investigations into the company and have considered a range of unprecedented penalties, Bloomberg News reported in July. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s possible that the delisting would be part of a package of punishments for Didi. Beijing’s municipal government has proposed an investment in the company that would give state-run firms effective control, Bloomberg News reported in September. Such an investment could help Didi finance the repurchase of its U.S.-traded shares. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi is currently controlled by the management team of co-founder Cheng Wei and President Jean Liu, which received aggregate voting power of 58% after the company’s U.S. initial public offering. SoftBank and Uber Technologies Inc. are Didi’s biggest minority shareholders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if Didi shifts its listing to Hong Kong, it will have to address the data security concerns that have drawn regulatory scrutiny. The company may have to give up control of its data to a third-party -- again undercutting its price tag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regulators have weighed a delisting for Didi since the summer, after the world’s largest ride-hailing company infuriated officials by ploughing ahead with its U.S. IPO, Bloomberg News has reported. A withdrawal from U.S. bourses could stoke fears of an exodus of Chinese firms as Washington and Beijing quarrel about access to listed firms’ books. On Thursday, a senior Chinese regulatory official said such delistings would be a setback for relations with the U.S., while offering broad support for Hong Kong as an alternative venue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi -- once feted for defeating Uber in China -- has now become a test case for a broader Chinese government effort to curb the power of internet titans. Xi Jinping’s administration, keen to promote his vision of sharing the wealth or “common prosperity,” has targeted an internet sector that’s accumulated vast wealth by operating on the periphery of the law, minted an unprecedented number of billionaires and enriched local and foreign investors in the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A state-directed privatization would be unprecedented for a private firm of Didi’s stature, affirming that the Chinese government remains bent on curtailing the power of the country’s internet firms and unlocking the data and wealth hoarded during a decade of heady expansion. It would send a chilling signal to American investors, long accustomed to investing freely in China’s largest corporations from Alibaba to Baidu Inc. and JD.com Inc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beijing’s moves against Didi have been particularly harsh, even after a crackdown that has penalized giants like Alibaba and Tencent Holdings Ltd. The Cyberspace Administration of China saw Didi’s IPO decision as a challenge to the central government’s authority, which led to the CAC, the Ministry of Public Security, the Ministry of State Security and several other agencies initiating on-site inspections at Didi’s offices in July.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s since been ensnared by probes into data security and the way it treats its millions of drivers. Many of the options Beijing is weighing involve re-asserting state control over a company that’s traditionally operated in a legal gray zone, Bloomberg News has reported.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/china-asks-didi-to-delist-from-u-s-on-security-fears-1.1687281&quot;&gt;https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/china-asks-didi-to-delist-from-u-s-on-security-fears-1.1687281&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Costco (COST) - Why does it just keep running?]]></title><description><![CDATA[COST has gone on a ridiculous run this year, breaking out of the 300s and
leaping now well into the 500s. I grabbed 10 shares when I started investing in
April because I knew it was a profitable company that’s well-run with a solid
loyal customer base, but never in my wildest dreams did I expect it…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2advu/costco_cost_why_does_it_just_keep_running/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2advu/costco_cost_why_does_it_just_keep_running/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 03:37:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;COST has gone on a ridiculous run this year, breaking out of the 300s and leaping now well into the 500s. I grabbed 10 shares when I started investing in April because I knew it was a profitable company that’s well-run with a solid loyal customer base, but never in my wildest dreams did I expect it to go on this kind of run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone find any reasons that COST is climbing like this? Seemingly not even the September correction could slow it down (unlike in March).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[About to be 18 next year, need some advices…]]></title><description><![CDATA[My goal is to learn to develop a good perception of money/investing/common
social systems (banks, etc which are country dependent) and apply my knowledge
to achieve financial independence and maybe develop businesses or just be aware
of these things at an early age (any suggested topics which might…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2367p/about_to_be_18_next_year_need_some_advices/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2367p/about_to_be_18_next_year_need_some_advices/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 02:38:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My goal is to learn to develop a good perception of money/investing/common social systems (banks, etc which are country dependent) and apply my knowledge to achieve financial independence and maybe develop businesses or  just be aware of these things at an early age (any suggested topics which might be useful to know at 18/19 are welcome)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m willing to read any novels/books regarding this… though I have 0 idea of commercial studies etc since I picked sciences as subjects at 16…so I don’t know basic stuff about accounting/economics (though I can read about it if required)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-with all these currency, stocks etc which I currently have no idea about, which one should I approach and what mentality should I keep before approaching these things? What books/sources do you recommend to gain knowledge about these things?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Please recommend any books which can help me develop my perception of money, maybe learn about investing/stocks, or which can help me develop my understanding of basic social systems like banks etc (if required) 
[ive only read basic books like rich dad, poor dad  etc but I don’t have formal knowledge regarding these in any way…]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-ANY general advice, maybe mistakes you made in early stage, any miscellaneous books or knowledge about the topics (like budgeting etc) you think are beneficial for me are welcome… go all out…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks in advance&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit- thank you all for the advices… I’ll take a ss and will review each advice and try my best to follow the suggestions the moment my entrance exams are done (assuming I go to a good uni, seems likely)
Thank you all again for the lists, I will save them 100%%%&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anyone Boglehead through the dot com bubble? That would be over 7 years of staying the course. I'm not sure I would be able to hang in there]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2a7be/anyone_boglehead_through_the_dot_com_bubble_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2a7be/anyone_boglehead_through_the_dot_com_bubble_that/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 02:01:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Took a line of credit to YOLO, suggestions anyone?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r23rx6/took_a_line_of_credit_to_yolo_suggestions_anyone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r23rx6/took_a_line_of_credit_to_yolo_suggestions_anyone/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 00:58:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[About sums it up]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r280jm/about_sums_it_up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r280jm/about_sums_it_up/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 23:54:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is your most speculative stock?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Give me them pre-revenue SPACs, the unprofitable pennies, and the sleeping
giants at their 52 week lows. I'm looking for those 100x opportunities with the
0x possibility. Shill me your heaviest bag that you are still adding too and
believe in. Make me feel fomo for not investing in your moonshot…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r260wh/what_is_your_most_speculative_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r260wh/what_is_your_most_speculative_stock/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 23:54:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Give me them pre-revenue SPACs, the unprofitable pennies, and the sleeping giants at their 52 week lows. I&amp;#39;m looking for those 100x opportunities with the 0x possibility. Shill me your heaviest bag that you are still adding too and believe in. Make me feel fomo for not investing in your moonshot tech stock. I&amp;#39;ll go first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$BLGO&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BioLargo OTC $.20&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These guys are basically pre-revenue, but they have spent the last few years making a water filtration system for PFAS&amp;#39;s. If the stars align just right with the EPA declaring PFAS a hazardous material and their tech works as advertised they are looking to lead a $180B industry. They also have a consumer product releasing soon called Pooph. It&amp;#39;s an anti smell cleaning product which could bring in a good amount of steady revenue in 2022. Management seems to have their head on straight and be focused on the right things. All in all definitely worth the ~2% of my portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>