<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 02:43:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Should my portfolio be at least as good as S&P 500?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey guys, I recently got a job and this year I managed to both get 6000 in a
ROTH IRA and start a 401k. The S&P 500 is up 20% since September (when I started
my positions). But my returns are much less. Should I just be investing in the
S&P 500? Sorry i am noob investor]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz5thz/should_my_portfolio_be_at_least_as_good_as_sp_500/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz5thz/should_my_portfolio_be_at_least_as_good_as_sp_500/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 02:07:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey guys, I recently got a job and this year I managed to both get 6000 in a ROTH IRA and start a 401k. The S&amp;amp;P 500 is up 20% since September (when I started my positions). But my returns are much less. Should I just be investing in the S&amp;amp;P 500? Sorry i am noob investor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[At the Waukesha Holiday parade and a car just broke through the police line, plowing through pedestrians and firing rounds out the window. Family and I are safe. Happened 20 feet in front of us.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462560182857310208</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462560182857310208</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 23:43:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to 3x the S&P CAGR with less risk | Leverage for the Long Run]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2741701

For those of your wondering what the hell to do now, I introduce you to a new
unsung hero Michael Gayed. Michael has found a way to systemically outperform
the S&P 500 by over 3x while taking on less risk and it's an extremely…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qz07zp/how_to_3x_the_sp_cagr_with_less_risk_leverage_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qz07zp/how_to_3x_the_sp_cagr_with_less_risk_leverage_for/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 23:43:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2741701&quot;&gt;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2741701&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of your wondering what the hell to do now, I introduce you to a new unsung hero Michael Gayed. Michael has found a way to systemically outperform the S&amp;amp;P 500 by over 3x while taking on less risk and it&amp;#39;s an extremely simple investment strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone says that triple leveraged ETFs have volatility decay and are not meant for long-term holding. Well guess what, those people are idiots. Let&amp;#39;s look at the data: If you invested in UPRO using this guy&amp;#39;s simple strategy, backtested all the way back to 1928, you would have returned 27% CAGR while the S&amp;amp;P did 9% and by taking on half as much risk (0.6 Sharpe ratio for this strategy vs. 0.3 for buy &amp;amp; hold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rules are simple, if the underlying index closes below the 200 day moving average, you sell. Once it crosses back above the 200 MA, then reenter. That is it. &lt;strong&gt;Investing $10k in 1928 with this strategy would have returned $28 TRILLION (with a T) while the S&amp;amp;P would have returned $39 million.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason this works is because of the lack of volatility above the 200 MA, and higher volatility below the 200 MA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the sweet taste of compounding returns my friends because this is a ticket to an early retirement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR: Read the damn paper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why should I invest now when a crash might be coming …]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qz63mh/why_should_i_invest_now_when_a_crash_might_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qz63mh/why_should_i_invest_now_when_a_crash_might_be/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 23:43:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[New Post:

7-Chart Sunday...

https://t.co/uZLzNqvOAy https://t.co/QJJsFAgJgh]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462535662641590287</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462535662641590287</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 22:38:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Noob Question: Why International?]]></title><description><![CDATA[So we're just starting out on our investing adventure. We've met with a couple
advisors and Vanguard PAS. Everyone and the wiki says you should some
international stock VTIAX in a 3/4 fund portfolio. PAS recommended as high as
30% international in a 75/25 stock bond portfolio. We had a AUM guy say…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyyhnt/noob_question_why_international/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyyhnt/noob_question_why_international/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 22:22:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So we&amp;#39;re just starting out on our investing adventure. We&amp;#39;ve met with a couple advisors and Vanguard PAS. Everyone and the wiki says you should some international stock VTIAX in a 3/4 fund portfolio. PAS recommended as high as 30% international in a 75/25 stock bond portfolio. We had a AUM guy say 8% international. Just trying to wrap my mind around this. I have no business running backtests, but when I do = portfolios with higher % international don&amp;#39;t perform as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trade $50k worth index into NVIDIA ?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know, KNOW NVIDIA is the spinal cord that's going to be changing the future. I
think in 10 years it'll be worth at least $1000-$1500 per share. I really
believe in it, and being a computer engineer I understand it well.

I've known about the omniverse announcement for awhile, so bought 227 shares…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0x1l/trade_50k_worth_index_into_nvidia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0x1l/trade_50k_worth_index_into_nvidia/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 22:22:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know, KNOW NVIDIA is the spinal cord that&amp;#39;s going to be changing the future. I think in 10 years it&amp;#39;ll be worth at least $1000-$1500 per share. I really believe in it, and being a computer engineer I understand it well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve known about the omniverse announcement for awhile, so bought 227 shares at $220 ($49,940) two months ago. But &lt;a href=&quot;/r/bogleheads&quot;&gt;/r/bogleheads&lt;/a&gt; convinced me it was gambling so I took it out and I&amp;#39;m pissed I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, in order to get that $50k I&amp;#39;d be having to sell 50k worth of VTSAX, meaning forfeiting early capital gains. I&amp;#39;ve only been investing for like 2 years, so it&amp;#39;s not that much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or.... should I just leave the VTSAX alone, invest $500 per week in that, then another $500 per week in QQQ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Future of AMD?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have a small position in AMD. 50 Shares. I've made a little bit of money on
them but I'm wondering what exactly the future holds for the company? I know
they have an upcoming merger with xilinx and they've partnered with Meta, but is
more growth for the stock possible? I can't exactly see…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0sab/the_future_of_amd/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0sab/the_future_of_amd/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 21:44:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have a small position in AMD. 50 Shares. I&amp;#39;ve made a little bit of money on them but I&amp;#39;m wondering what exactly the future holds for the company? I know they have an upcoming merger with xilinx and they&amp;#39;ve partnered with Meta, but is more growth for the stock possible? I can&amp;#39;t exactly see Semiconductors going anywhere, so I feel like the sky&amp;#39;s the limit. What are everyone&amp;#39;s thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[When did you know you were stock investor or a stock trader?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I've been reading a bunch of random posts online about different companies I'm
currently interested in, and I realize I'm happy that I'm an investor and I
always will be.

I don't understand how people can exist with a trader mindset. It's seems like
you need to study alot of quasi science, be on…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyw688/when_did_you_know_you_were_stock_investor_or_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyw688/when_did_you_know_you_were_stock_investor_or_a/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 21:44:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been reading a bunch of random posts online about different companies I&amp;#39;m currently interested in, and I realize I&amp;#39;m happy that I&amp;#39;m an investor and I always will be. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t understand how people can exist with a trader mindset. It&amp;#39;s seems like you need to study alot of quasi science, be on social media constantly, do alot of cocaine, and it really just seems stressful. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The neat thing about reddit is I can look and see when people post their &amp;quot;analysis&amp;quot; of a stock. Which for 99% of reddit, is just a trader saying voodoo witch craft nonsense about enter and exit points, resistance this and that, cutting losses, and special orders. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then you ask for their portfolio and they have none or its top secret or something. It&amp;#39;s not illegal to share your portfolio you great traders. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m an average Joe, and I&amp;#39;m not that smart. so I feel really good when I read posts from people who buy a stock like MU, three years ago, at 40-43 a share, and sell it saying they see no future in it. It&amp;#39;s trading at like $83 now. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love it when I read people saying they bought Uber near ipo at 40 and sold at 32 and say it&amp;#39;s doomed to fail. But Uber is still around, in fact it hit a height of $60 last spring and now it&amp;#39;s $44. You haven&amp;#39;t even given it a chance to grow or become something yet. Like the company is a verb, give it a few years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think traders are like fake friends in high school. They&amp;#39;re only around you if you&amp;#39;re cool. Once you&amp;#39;re not cool anymore they abandon you. But traders are onlu a small portion of money for a company a company makes stuff to sell to people and that&amp;#39;s what really draws in revenue to grow. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see alot of people talk about the &amp;quot;opportunity cost&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;oppurtuniy lost, &amp;quot; something like that when you&amp;#39;re not trading. Like if I buy something that isn&amp;#39;t moving fast, or something is in the red, it&amp;#39;s better to &amp;quot;cut my losses.&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But that&amp;#39;s like... Buying high and selling low. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That sounds like the exact opposite of what you&amp;#39;re supposed to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honestly, I&amp;#39;d rather sink with my ship if you&amp;#39;re telling me to always sell the moment my stock goes red. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;if I was so foolish as to pick a bad company, I&amp;#39;d rather just take the full loss, rather then death by a thousand cuts. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I pick companies that make more revenue every year, have increasing dividends, and are medium to large size growth companies. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m boring. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just look at the best performing companies, read their 10k and just invest. My first two companies I bought were Apple and Starbucks, I then bought Nvidia and Realty Income. I bought Pennymac and Weyerhaeuser afterward. I just sorta sit on them. I just hold them and buy more. If I somehow become broke instantly from these decisions then damn. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m investing in known companies with easy business models. I like safety and simplicity. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t believe I&amp;#39;m gonna become a multi millionaire with several cars and boats. I just want to make enough money to be the first millionaire in my family, and have my children live of my dividends so they don&amp;#39;t have to work so hard. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It just seems like people don&amp;#39;t have patience on the internet. And when you take the time to read people who argue about a particular stock, and then for those same people to be proven wrong by time. It feels good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is there a strong reason to switch to Vanguard from Fidelity or Schwab?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know they essentially can do the same things, but I like the whole ethos of
Vanguard and have often wondered if I should switch. Is it just a preference
thing or are there clear advantages from using Vanguard?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyy6h0/is_there_a_strong_reason_to_switch_to_vanguard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyy6h0/is_there_a_strong_reason_to_switch_to_vanguard/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 21:16:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know they essentially can do the same things, but I like the whole ethos of Vanguard and have often wondered if I should switch. Is it just a preference thing or are there clear advantages from using Vanguard?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Should I Open A Roth IRA?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have a 401k that I'm putting 20% of pay in a week. I put about $500 or so a
month in a taxable account. Currently my taxable is 23% of my total savings for
retirement.

Should I open a Roth as well? They sound very attractive for several reasons.

I was using a taxable account as a safety net…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyu75h/should_i_open_a_roth_ira/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyu75h/should_i_open_a_roth_ira/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 20:42:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have a 401k that I&amp;#39;m putting 20% of pay in a week. I put about $500 or so a month in a taxable account. Currently my taxable is 23% of my total savings for retirement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should I open a Roth as well? They sound very attractive for several reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was using a taxable account as a safety net should I need to access some of the money. Also I was hoping to retire at 55 and use this account to bridge me over to my 401k.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But from my understanding I could open a Roth and take some or all of the principle out at anytime without penalty.  Also this money grows tax free and can be withdrawn tax free at 59.5. So essentially I could start taking the principle out early if I want to retire early.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe its best to have a combination of all 3 401k, Roth, Taxable?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why SP500 when there is NASDAQ]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello there, it has been 3-4 years since I'm investing in the market. I just DCA
like most of you. I don't know much tbh.

At first, I bought WORLD Tracker, then I realized most of the % comes from the
US (I live in Europe btw), so I switched to S&P500 and now I realize most of the
% comes from…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyv4a9/why_sp500_when_there_is_nasdaq/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyv4a9/why_sp500_when_there_is_nasdaq/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 20:27:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello there, it has been 3-4 years since I&amp;#39;m investing in the market. I just DCA like most of you. I don&amp;#39;t know much tbh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At first, I bought WORLD Tracker, then I realized most of the % comes from the US (I live in Europe btw), so I switched to S&amp;amp;P500 and now I realize most of the % comes from NASDAQ100. (Yeah I&amp;#39;m not a quick learner).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, why wouldn&amp;#39;t I want to put everything in NASDAQ100? I know the drawdown is higher but the profit is as well. And inflation is just starting imo...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[news about Russia preparing to attack Ukraine in late Jan.]]></title><description><![CDATA[news article here
https://www.militarytimes.com/flashpoints/2021/11/20/russia-preparing-to-attack-ukraine-by-late-january-ukraine-defense-intelligence-agency-chief/

I was wondering is this of any concern? normally these thinsg wouldnt affect the
US stock market because it usually from 2 small…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0kx4/news_about_russia_preparing_to_attack_ukraine_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0kx4/news_about_russia_preparing_to_attack_ukraine_in/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 20:27:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;news article here &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.militarytimes.com/flashpoints/2021/11/20/russia-preparing-to-attack-ukraine-by-late-january-ukraine-defense-intelligence-agency-chief/&quot;&gt;https://www.militarytimes.com/flashpoints/2021/11/20/russia-preparing-to-attack-ukraine-by-late-january-ukraine-defense-intelligence-agency-chief/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was wondering is this of any concern? normally these thinsg wouldnt affect the US stock market because it usually from 2 small countries. but this seems like a different situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vanguard on hold times, I gave up at 1:17]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyw6vc/vanguard_on_hold_times_i_gave_up_at_117/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyw6vc/vanguard_on_hold_times_i_gave_up_at_117/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 17:53:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[We the people https://t.co/UUuzClMemw]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461790163177295884</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461790163177295884</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 17:41:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Purchased all these stocks in feb at all time highs, they are all down still while the markets are hitting all time highs. Cut losses now?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know the saying time in the market beats timing the market, which is why I
bought during all time highs. But when the nasdaq and s&p keep going up every
other day it’s tough to want to average down when these stocks keep trading
sideways/ down. How does one get over the mindset of not wanting to…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyx5s1/purchased_all_these_stocks_in_feb_at_all_time/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyx5s1/purchased_all_these_stocks_in_feb_at_all_time/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 17:22:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know the saying time in the market beats timing the market, which is why I bought during all time highs. But when the nasdaq and s&amp;amp;p keep going up every other day it’s tough to want to average down when these stocks keep trading sideways/ down. How does one get over the mindset of not wanting to sell for a loss?
Arkf -16%
Arkg -37%
Arkw -17%
Moon -32%
Expi -40%
Prnt -24%&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This is how you invest.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyth8s/this_is_how_you_invest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyth8s/this_is_how_you_invest/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 15:40:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[First time on the Vanguard site....is it really this easy?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Someone can just make an account, buy VTI and get the tax paper each year and
that’s it in a nutshell?

Almost seems too easy?

Is picking the account easy? Roth/brokerage etc? I keep thinking there has to be
something tricky somewhere]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyuykq/first_time_on_the_vanguard_siteis_it_really_this/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyuykq/first_time_on_the_vanguard_siteis_it_really_this/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 15:21:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Someone can just make an account, buy VTI and get the tax paper each year and that’s it in a nutshell? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost seems too easy? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is picking the account easy? Roth/brokerage etc? I keep thinking there has to be something tricky somewhere&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Overallocating your time and effort to portfolio optimization is suboptimal]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm not sure how common this is, but this is a strategic mistake I realized I'm
making and I think that it might be worth thinking about.

Geeking out about portfolios and studying and backtesting and so on is fun, I
know, and I certainly agree that it is important to take the time to design…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyry5y/overallocating_your_time_and_effort_to_portfolio/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyry5y/overallocating_your_time_and_effort_to_portfolio/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 13:03:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not sure how common this is, but this is a strategic mistake I realized I&amp;#39;m making and I think that it might be worth thinking about. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Geeking out about portfolios and studying and backtesting and so on is fun, I know, and I certainly agree that it is important to take the time to design a portfolio that is compatible with one&amp;#39;s objectives and risk tolerance; but, as with many other things, extra effort has diminishing returns and there soon comes a time when your time (heh) and work would be better spent elsewhere. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Case in point: lately I have been obsessing about whether to increase my bond allocation by 5% now or 2/3 years from now as per my initial plan (this has nothing to do with the market being &amp;quot;high&amp;quot;, I&amp;#39;m just concerned that I might be overestimating a little my risk tolerance), and I spent way more time thinking about this than putting extra work towards a certification that could increase my wages by about &lt;strong&gt;10%&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I... don&amp;#39;t think I have to spell out why this is not the best use of my time and effort. So yeah, it might be worth it to keep in mind that it is suboptimal to overallocate one&amp;#39;s resources towards portfolio optimization. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now if I know myself, the danger is that I&amp;#39;ll spend the next four months designing and refining the perfect allocation of my time and mental efforts towards my various work and life objectives rather than doing what I am supposed to do... :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tesla over the weekend when i don’t own calls vs when i own calls]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qykw6v/tesla_over_the_weekend_when_i_dont_own_calls_vs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qykw6v/tesla_over_the_weekend_when_i_dont_own_calls_vs/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 13:03:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My first post on WSB - should I hold or sell?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyedi1/my_first_post_on_wsb_should_i_hold_or_sell/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyedi1/my_first_post_on_wsb_should_i_hold_or_sell/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 12:36:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is ZIM looking ok? 17% dividend?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Darn I sold my small position in ZIM at 45 and now it's back to 57!

I also noticed they have a 17% dividend now. Is that as good as it sounds?

Anyways I'm thinking of throwing $1500 in ZIM Monday. New price target is $80
and I guess shipping is finally starting to ease a bit?

Any info on…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qykjyh/is_zim_looking_ok_17_dividend/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qykjyh/is_zim_looking_ok_17_dividend/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 11:33:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Darn I sold my small position in ZIM at 45 and now it&amp;#39;s back to 57!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also noticed they have a 17% dividend now.  Is that as good as it sounds?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways I&amp;#39;m thinking of throwing $1500 in ZIM Monday.  New price target is $80 and I guess shipping is finally starting to ease a bit?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any info on shipping? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is ZIM a good move now?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Empower Taxed My 401k Rollover?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Help! I’m in the middle of a rollover to an IRA and Roth IRA (from a 401k and
Roth 401k) I went through everything pretty thoroughly on the phone with the rep
from Empower (Keeping it with Empower in an IRA, to their IRA brokerage acct
product) and rolling everything over in kind. There should be no…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyb85h/empower_taxed_my_401k_rollover/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyb85h/empower_taxed_my_401k_rollover/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 10:59:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Help! I’m in the middle of a rollover to an IRA and Roth IRA (from a 401k and Roth 401k) I went through everything pretty thoroughly on the phone with the rep from Empower (Keeping it with Empower in an IRA, to their IRA brokerage acct product) and rolling everything over in kind. There should be no taxes associated with the transaction, but it’s showing I’m paying state and fed taxes on this. It seems like Empower screwed something up here, hopefully they aren’t screwing me in the process. I’ve rolled over 401ks before and this has always been a pretty uneventful process, has anyone seen this happen?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[El Salvador to Create ‘Bitcoin City,’ Use $500M of Planned $1B Bond Offering to Buy More Bitcoin]]></title><description><![CDATA[El Salvador, the only country in which bitcoin is a legal tender, is going to
build an entire city based on the largest cryptocurrency, President Nayib Bukele
said in a Saturday night presentation at Bitcoin Week in El Salvador.

“Bitcoin City” will be located along the Gulf of Fonseca near a…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyp4ry/el_salvador_to_create_bitcoin_city_use_500m_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyp4ry/el_salvador_to_create_bitcoin_city_use_500m_of/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 10:47:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;El Salvador, the only country in which bitcoin is a legal tender, is going to build an entire city based on the largest cryptocurrency, President Nayib Bukele said in a Saturday night presentation at Bitcoin Week in El Salvador.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Bitcoin City” will be located along the Gulf of Fonseca near a volcano. The government plans on locating a power plant by the volcano to provide energy for both the city and bitcoin mining, the president said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Bukele, Bitcoin City will be a full-fledged metropolis with residential and commercial areas, restaurants, an airport as well as a port and rail service. The city will be laid out in a circle (like a coin) and in the city center will be a plaza that will be host to a huge bitcoin symbol. The city will have no income, property, capital gains or payroll taxes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bukele also said El Salvador plans on issuing $1 billion US “bitcoin bond,” a tokenized financial instrument developed by Blockstream, on the Liquid Network. Of that amount, $500 million will be used to help construct needed energy and bitcoin mining infrastructure and $500 million to buy even more bitcoin. At the cryptocurrency’s recent trading price of about $59,000, that would bring the country’s treasury stash to just under 2,000 bitcoins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coindesk.com/business/2021/11/21/el-salvador-to-create-bitcoin-city-use-500m-of-planned-1b-bond-offering-to-buy-more-crypto/&quot;&gt;https://www.coindesk.com/business/2021/11/21/el-salvador-to-create-bitcoin-city-use-500m-of-planned-1b-bond-offering-to-buy-more-crypto/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is The Basic At Retirement Boglehead Portfolio?]]></title><description><![CDATA[60/40 Stocks/Bonds - Assuming 20% Foreign - Using VTI/VXUS/BND/BNDX

Like this?

VTI 48% VXUS 12% 32% BND 8% BNDX

That's it? and use the 4% rule? Bogglehead approved?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyf4h9/what_is_the_basic_at_retirement_boglehead/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyf4h9/what_is_the_basic_at_retirement_boglehead/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 10:47:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;60/40 Stocks/Bonds - Assuming 20% Foreign - Using VTI/VXUS/BND/BNDX&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VTI 48% VXUS 12% 32% BND 8% BNDX&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s it? and use the 4% rule? Bogglehead approved?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This was my fortune cookie tonight. They misspelled positions though.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyl6pd/this_was_my_fortune_cookie_tonight_they/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyl6pd/this_was_my_fortune_cookie_tonight_they/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 10:11:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Very bullish indicator on my wife’s labor contractions daily chart.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qymmak/very_bullish_indicator_on_my_wifes_labor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qymmak/very_bullish_indicator_on_my_wifes_labor/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 09:22:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[‘As long is we don’t fall into a recession,’ we’re in a long bull market, says ARK Invest’s Cathie Wood https://t.co/OE9BPCgVjO]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462118090112737291</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462118090112737291</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 08:45:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[These are the bags that I am holding. Which ones do you think I should retire, and which ones I DCA down?]]></title><description><![CDATA[These are the stocks that I hold that have been hit quite hard recently and
where I am10% or more down

TPIC, -44%, -5.313K$

BFLY, -38%, -2.871K

CRSR, -29%, -1.98k

TDOC, -26%, -13.9K

EXPI, -22%, -1.3K

MGNI, -19%, -1.6K

BABA, -16%, -3.96K

BIDU, -16%, -12.7K

PYSF, -12%, -0.25K

Which ones do…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyf4oo/these_are_the_bags_that_i_am_holding_which_ones/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyf4oo/these_are_the_bags_that_i_am_holding_which_ones/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 08:45:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are the stocks that I hold that have been hit quite hard recently and where I am10% or more down&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TPIC, -44%, -5.313K$&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BFLY, -38%, -2.871K&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CRSR, -29%, -1.98k&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TDOC, -26%, -13.9K&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EXPI, -22%, -1.3K&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MGNI, -19%, -1.6K&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BABA, -16%, -3.96K&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BIDU, -16%, -12.7K&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PYSF, -12%, -0.25K&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which ones do you think are gonna take the longest to break even (if at all) and which ones are hopeless? BABA, BIDU and TDOC, I am long, but the others I am not sure..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS: I have been very bad in my timing with EXPI, MGNI and TDOC (EXPI was up about 10% at the end of October, MGNI was up 100% in march and break even beginning of Sep, TDOC I was break even in July)...missed all these exit or position reduction points..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BMO Sees S&P 500 Hitting 5,300 Next Year, a 12% Gain]]></title><description><![CDATA[> BMO believes the stock market will continue to ascend next year, though less
> vigorously, after the S&P 500 has soared 25% year to date, 16% in 2020 and 30%
> in 2019.
> 
> The bank’s Chief Investment Strategist Brian Belski predicts the index will
> hit 5,300 in 2022. That would represent a gain…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qy62wa/bmo_sees_sp_500_hitting_5300_next_year_a_12_gain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qy62wa/bmo_sees_sp_500_hitting_5300_next_year_a_12_gain/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 07:17:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BMO believes the stock market will continue to ascend next year, though less vigorously, after the S&amp;amp;P 500 has soared 25% year to date, 16% in 2020 and 30% in 2019.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bank’s Chief Investment Strategist Brian Belski predicts the index will hit 5,300 in 2022. That would represent a gain of 13% from the Friday’s recent level of 4,699.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you ready for more pump? What&amp;#39;s your top pick?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A contrarian perspective on index funds.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I always love hearing contrarian perspectives. This guy has a perspective that
investing in SPY, IVV, VOO And Other S&P 500 ETFs may not be as wise or
diversified as standard investment advice would make it seem.

His perspective is that a large percentage of investors just buy SPY or similar
ETFs.…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyjoxz/a_contrarian_perspective_on_index_funds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyjoxz/a_contrarian_perspective_on_index_funds/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 06:54:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I always love hearing contrarian perspectives. This guy has a perspective that investing in SPY, IVV, VOO And Other S&amp;amp;P 500 ETFs may not be as wise or diversified as standard investment advice would make it seem. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His perspective is that a large percentage of investors just buy SPY or similar ETFs. Such a sizable amount that the diversity argument for them is effected. Diversity only works well if there&amp;#39;s enough buyers and sellers of the individual stocks that make up the index. But if mostly everyone is buying the index, diversity doesn&amp;#39;t matter: as instead of the index &amp;quot;tracking&amp;quot; these stocks the index is influencing their price instead; thus you start to have similar liquidity issues as you would it you only bought stock in one or two companies. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words, the more people invest in index funds, the less effective the diversity of the index fund is, and the more liquidity risk you are exposed to. Basically it&amp;#39;s better to handle diversification more actively rather than rely on indexes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Article was written in 2017, so he may not have foreseen the liquidity injections of 2020 and 2021. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not quite sold on his thesis. What do you all think?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hvst.com/posts/4-reasons-you-should-run-away-from-spy-ivv-voo-and-other-s-p-500-etfs-E2ATWDnB&quot;&gt;https://www.hvst.com/posts/4-reasons-you-should-run-away-from-spy-ivv-voo-and-other-s-p-500-etfs-E2ATWDnB&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can't stop trading Stock/Options? You may be addicted]]></title><description><![CDATA[> Addiction is the inability to stop consuming a chemical or pursuing an
> activity despite causing harm.

Very much the same happens to people who trade. Can we define trading addiction
as a crossing a line between being passionate about investing and losing the
ability to stop trading.

> The…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyms02/cant_stop_trading_stockoptions_you_may_be_addicted/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyms02/cant_stop_trading_stockoptions_you_may_be_addicted/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 05:53:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Addiction is the inability to stop consuming a chemical or pursuing an activity despite causing harm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very much the same happens to people who trade. Can we define trading addiction as a crossing a line between being passionate about investing and losing the ability to stop trading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The problem focuses on the brain and understanding how its reward systems can train you to trade compulsively and dangerously.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some signs of addiction&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You spend far too much of your free time trading.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are trading stocks at work (and it isn’t your job)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The “high” of trying to find the next “moonshot” is the focus of attention.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have feelings for frustration, aggression or attempt to suppress other personal problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Losing money on a position makes you depressed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can’t stop trading.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continually looking at your phone to check the latest value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You lie to others about what you are doing on your phone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The bulk of your investing advice comes from social media “experts.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You borrowed money on a credit card, home equity line, or a personal loan to invest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your emotional state is directly tied to the outcome of the stock market.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is a lack of self-control or ability to stay away from your trading app.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sounds like many people that I know are addicted...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Michael Burry’s Latest Holdings (Scion Asset Management)]]></title><description><![CDATA[SCION ASSET MANAGEMENT, LLC

HTTP://WWW.SCIONASSET.COM • SARATOGA, CA

## SCION ASSET MANAGEMENT IS BASED OUT OF SARATOGA AND IS RUN BY DR. MICHAEL J.
BURRY. SCION ASSET MANAGEMENT IS A HEDGE FUND WITH 5 CLIENTS AND DISCRETIONARY
ASSETS UNDER MANAGEMENT (AUM) OF $638,901,404 (FORM ADV FROM 2021-03…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qy9nxu/michael_burrys_latest_holdings_scion_asset/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qy9nxu/michael_burrys_latest_holdings_scion_asset/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 03:43:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;h1&gt;SCION ASSET MANAGEMENT, LLC&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;HTTP://WWW.SCIONASSET.COM&quot;&gt;HTTP://WWW.SCIONASSET.COM&lt;/a&gt; • SARATOGA, CA&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;## Scion Asset Management is based out of Saratoga and is run by Dr. Michael J. Burry. Scion Asset Management is a hedge fund with 5 clients and discretionary assets under management (AUM) of $638,901,404 (Form ADV from 2021-03-31). Their last reported 13F filing for Q3 2021 included $41,719,000 in managed 13F securities and a top 10 holdings concentration of 100.0%. Scion Asset Management’s largest holding is CVS Health Corp. (Melville Shoe) with shares held of 200,000. Whalewisdom has at least 16 13F filings, and 7 13D filings.&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Click link for current holdings with detail:&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/HpdNN83.jpg&quot;&gt;https://i.imgur.com/HpdNN83.jpg&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Original link to 13F&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://whalewisdom.com/filer/scion-asset-management-llc#tabholdings_tab_link&quot;&gt;https://whalewisdom.com/filer/scion-asset-management-llc#tabholdings_tab_link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CVS  40.68% of Portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LMT  24.82%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GEO 20.75%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CXW 8.79%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DNOW 2.75%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SCYX 2.21%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a lot to unpack here, but have at it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Few notes. Massive reduction in securities:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Q2 ‘21 USD 147,257,000.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Q3 ‘21 USD  41,719,000.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TSLA PUTS comprised the largest portion of his portfolio in previous quarters and now make up 0%. Unknown what the actual loss was, but assume it was substantial. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Q2 ‘21 35% -&amp;gt; Q3 ‘21 0%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Current lineup looks a hedge to some great coming apocalypse. This will end badly for Burry. I’d be surprised if SCION doesn’t shut down within a year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is the inflation trend in the US really that scary?]]></title><description><![CDATA[The October inflation in the US was 6.2% on an annual basis, which is super high
given the recent history of sub-3% rates.

That said, I come from a place where people were high-fiving when they get
anywhere 6% inflation. Double digits were the norm back there. When I was a kid
we lived under…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyjgng/is_the_inflation_trend_in_the_us_really_that_scary/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyjgng/is_the_inflation_trend_in_the_us_really_that_scary/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 03:00:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The October inflation in the US was 6.2% on an annual basis, which is super high given the recent history of sub-3% rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That said, I come from a place where people were high-fiving when they get anywhere 6% inflation. Double digits were the norm back there. When I was a kid we lived under hyperinflation which is a complete shit show, people get their paychecks and immediately go buy their groceries for the month. This is not a figure of speech, they really did go IMMEDIATLY because the prices were readjusted 1 or 2 times IN THE SAME DAY. Concept of savings was non-existent. Either you buy as much US Dollars as possible or put in some asset that has intrinsic value like real estate. The house I grew up was huge, and I learned that was not because my father was in a good financial situation, but rather it was the only option to dump all his savings before it lose half of its value in matter of weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Long story short, my bar is a bit out of place here... so should I be concerned with the 6.2% rate? My take on this: likely FED will increase rates, which will devalue bonds and stock prices. But then this should be already embedded in the current asset prices, so I don&amp;#39;t think I should be doing anything with my portfolio here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Market bubble explained for dummies]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyhjq0/market_bubble_explained_for_dummies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyhjq0/market_bubble_explained_for_dummies/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 01:46:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CORRECTION: MarketWatch deleted an earlier tweet that inaccurately implied that $5-a-gallon gasoline, $90 bottles of wine and $200 concert tickets were typical purchases of late among average Americans. The story has been corrected.

https://t.co/Y8kBdRHPKI https://t.co/n48rruC9h7]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462160448665665544</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462160448665665544</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 23:39:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Do not trust financial market risk models. Reality is always too complex to be accurately modeled.]]></title><description><![CDATA[In 2010 investor and founder of the Baupost Group Seth Klarman described key
lessons from the financial crisis which were either never learned or else
immediately forgotten by most market participants. With him at the helm the
Baupost Group has averaged around 18% and that since 1982 - a…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyaa0c/do_not_trust_financial_market_risk_models_reality/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyaa0c/do_not_trust_financial_market_risk_models_reality/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 22:46:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2010  investor and founder of the Baupost Group Seth Klarman described key lessons from the financial crisis which were either never learned or else immediately forgotten by most market participants. With him at the helm the Baupost Group has averaged around 18% and that since 1982 - a spectacular return. Some of these lessons are very relevant today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do not trust financial market risk models. Reality is always too complex to be accurately modeled. Attention to risk must be a 24/7/365 obsession, with people – not computers – assessing and reassessing the risk environment in real time. Despite the predilection of some analysts to model the financial markets using sophisticated mathematics, the markets are governed by behavioral science, not physical science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s your take on where the stock market going in 2022?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Good idea to put most of emergency funds in I bonds]]></title><description><![CDATA[Given inflation and current I bond interest rate, I’m considering starting to
move a big chunk of my emergency fund into I bonds. Of course I would space this
out over a number of years so that I wouldn’t be in a position where I would
need to access that money before the 1 year holding…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyck93/good_idea_to_put_most_of_emergency_funds_in_i/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyck93/good_idea_to_put_most_of_emergency_funds_in_i/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 22:34:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given inflation and current I bond interest rate, I’m considering starting to move a big chunk of my emergency fund into I bonds. Of course I would space this out over a number of years so that I wouldn’t be in a position where I would need to access that money before the 1 year holding period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interest to hear thoughts - do people think this is a good idea? How quickly can I bond funds be transferred to a bank account (after the 1 year hold period of course). My thinking is that in a major emergency, I could use a credit card to hold us over for a few weeks while we transfer the I bond money. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just hate to have a decent amount of money sitting in an online savings account making 0.4% when it could be making 7.12% in an I bond.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The parents sitting in first class and making the kids sit in coach on Home Alone is the ultimate boomer move]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462119945270177796</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462119945270177796</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 20:40:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[how ETFs work behind the scenes, rebalancing and preventing capital gains]]></title><description><![CDATA[Imagine VOO. Folks (like me) buy and sell the VOO ETF and behind the scenes
Vanguard takes the steps to periodically rebalance the index. It's my
understanding that this rebalancing happens on dates known in advance. As owners
of the ETF, we hope not to see capital gains triggered by these…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qy7q2x/how_etfs_work_behind_the_scenes_rebalancing_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qy7q2x/how_etfs_work_behind_the_scenes_rebalancing_and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 18:50:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine VOO.   Folks (like me) buy and sell the VOO ETF and behind the scenes Vanguard  takes the steps to periodically rebalance the index.  It&amp;#39;s my understanding that this rebalancing happens on dates known in advance.   As owners of the ETF, we hope not to see capital gains triggered by these rebalancing events because that means taxes.   My question is, how this rebalancing happens and is there some aspect around the ETF construct which allows vanguard to (say) sell a stock at a profit (as part of the rebalancing) yet somehow not pass that capital gain back to folks holding the ETF?   Or is vanguard leveraging tax loss harvesting as a means to counter capital gains and thus not pass gains to folks holding VOO?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If vanguard is leveraging tax loss harvesting to counter gains in order to prevent capital gains from being passed on to VOO holders, can vanguard shuffle, behind the scenes, those tax losses between different ETFs or must those losses remain associated with the stocks tied to VOO?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just trying to understand the details here...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I'm retarded]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qy8vmy/im_retarded/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qy8vmy/im_retarded/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 18:34:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Intel as a derivative trade on ASML. Intel is finally catching up with Moore's Law]]></title><description><![CDATA[Moore's Law states the amount of transistors on a chip doubles every two years
but the cost of production drops by half. This concept was created by Gordon
Moore, the co-founder of Intel and has actually held up for decades.

ASML designs and manufactures EUV lithography machines, which are…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qy7sk6/intel_as_a_derivative_trade_on_asml_intel_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qy7sk6/intel_as_a_derivative_trade_on_asml_intel_is/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 18:34:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moore&amp;#39;s Law states the amount of transistors on a chip doubles every two years but the cost of production drops by half. This concept was created by Gordon Moore, the co-founder of Intel and has actually held up for decades.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ASML designs and manufactures EUV lithography machines, which are extremely high precision machines that put complex designs on incredibly small chips. ASML is the only EUV lithography design and manufacturer in the world. Look up their stock performance and financials if you question these claims.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intel used to be a top class chip manufacturer but they&amp;#39;ve struggled with the 7nm chips and their stock has been punished. The simple reason for Intel&amp;#39;s shortcomings is they&amp;#39;ve not been using EUV lithography machines from ASML.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plain and simple, without EUV lithography, Intel has been handicapping itself for years now and is a big reason they have fallen behind. The last link below notes how their 7nm chip design is now using EUV lithography at the 2 new fab plants they are building for $20B in Arizona. Intel is going to start to catch up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR: ASML provides the technology to keep Moore&amp;#39;s Law alive and Intel hasn&amp;#39;t been using it until now. Their depressed, low P/E stock valuation will begin to correct with outperformance as their technology begins to catch-up after major mistakes not using EUV lithography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/asml-extreme-ultraviolet-lithography-chips-moores-law/&quot;&gt;ASML Keeping Moore&amp;#39;s Law Alive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://semiwiki.com/semiconductor-services/semiconductor-advisors/302806-asml-is-the-key-to-intels-resurrection-just-like-asml-helped-tsmc-beat-intel/&quot;&gt;ASML is the Key to Intel&amp;#39;s Resurrection Just like TSMC beat Intel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.intel.com/content/www/us/en/newsroom/news/idm-manufacturing-innovation-product-leadership.html#gs.h19m75&quot;&gt;Intel 7nm Chip Design to Now Use EUV Lithography&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[No taxes 😎]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qy72b5/no_taxes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qy72b5/no_taxes/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 17:16:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Average Americans are paying as much as $100 to $200 for a single concert ticket, $90 for a bottle of wine, and $5 a gallon for gas.  

https://t.co/rTciIVOEfn]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462062684103450624</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462062684103450624</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 16:52:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bogleheads on YouTube to watch]]></title><description><![CDATA[Just looking for some suggestions on who to follow and watch on YouTube to learn
from. Whether it be talking about the boglehead way, economy, financial advice,
stock market or anything along those lines. As an example, I follow Rob Berger
and he almost always has informative videos. Thanks for…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxyqll/bogleheads_on_youtube_to_watch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxyqll/bogleheads_on_youtube_to_watch/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 16:52:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just looking for some suggestions on who to follow and watch on YouTube to learn from. Whether it be talking about the boglehead way, economy, financial advice, stock market or anything along those lines.  As an example, I follow Rob Berger and he almost always has informative videos.  Thanks for suggestions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[New WSJ article: The 4% Retirement Rule Is in Doubt. Will Your Nest Egg Last?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nothing earth shattering or surprising here. Except maybe that 50% stocks and
50% bonds portolio isn't likely to be able to support a 4% SWR for a typical 30
year retirement over the next few years.

Link to the article:

https://www-wsj-com.cdn.ampproject.org/c/s/www.wsj.com/amp/articles/the-4…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxvgu9/new_wsj_article_the_4_retirement_rule_is_in_doubt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxvgu9/new_wsj_article_the_4_retirement_rule_is_in_doubt/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 16:12:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nothing earth shattering or surprising here. Except maybe that 50% stocks and 50% bonds portolio isn&amp;#39;t likely to be able to support a 4% SWR for a typical 30 year retirement over the next few years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link to the article:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www-wsj-com.cdn.ampproject.org/c/s/www.wsj.com/amp/articles/the-4-retirement-rule-is-in-doubt-will-your-nest-egg-last-11636713035&quot;&gt;https://www-wsj-com.cdn.ampproject.org/c/s/www.wsj.com/amp/articles/the-4-retirement-rule-is-in-doubt-will-your-nest-egg-last-11636713035&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Evergrande to be removed from Hang Seng China Enterprises Index]]></title><description><![CDATA["HONG KONG, Nov 19 (Reuters) - Embattled developer China Evergrande Group
(3333.HK) [https://www.reuters.com/companies/3333.HK] will be removed from Hong
Kong's Hang Seng China Enterprises Index (.HSCE)
[https://www.reuters.com/quote/.HSCE], the benchmark provider said on Friday
following its…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxn8ji/evergrande_to_be_removed_from_hang_seng_china/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxn8ji/evergrande_to_be_removed_from_hang_seng_china/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 15:50:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;HONG KONG, Nov 19 (Reuters) - Embattled developer China Evergrande Group &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/companies/3333.HK&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(3333.HK)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; will be removed from Hong Kong&amp;#39;s Hang Seng China Enterprises Index &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/quote/.HSCE&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(.HSCE)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the benchmark provider said on Friday following its regular quarterly review.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Hang Seng Indexes Company does not typically give reasons for changes to its indexes, and did not in Friday&amp;#39;s statement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Hang Seng China Enterprises Index is designed to reflect the performance of mainland Chinese companies listed in Hong Kong, and includes the top 50 eligible stocks by a measure of their market value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evergrande&amp;#39;s shares have fallen over 80% year to date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Separately, Hang Seng Indexes said they had added technology firms JD.com &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/companies/9618.HK&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(9618.HK)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and Netease &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/companies/9999.HK&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(9999.HK)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to the benchmark Hang Seng Index &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/quote/.HSI&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(.HSI)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hang Seng Indexes is trying to include more securities in the benchmark to make it more reflective of the companies listed in Hong Kong.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;($1 = 7.7917 Hong Kong dollars)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/evergrande-be-removed-hang-seng-china-enterprises-index-2021-11-19/?utm_source=reddit.com&amp;amp;utm_source=reddit.com&quot;&gt;https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/evergrande-be-removed-hang-seng-china-enterprises-index-2021-11-19/?utm_source=reddit.com&amp;amp;utm_source=reddit.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bloomberg: U.S. Supply-Chain Crisis Is Already Easing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Some good news from Bloomberg
[https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2021-11-18/the-u-s-supply-chain-crisis-is-already-easing]
(archive [https://archive.fo/Mhyri#selection-3845.0-3845.184])

 * "Global average ocean freight rates for a 40-foot container have now declined
   for eight straight…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qy35da/bloomberg_us_supplychain_crisis_is_already_easing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qy35da/bloomberg_us_supplychain_crisis_is_already_easing/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 15:16:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some good news from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2021-11-18/the-u-s-supply-chain-crisis-is-already-easing&quot;&gt;Bloomberg&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.fo/Mhyri#selection-3845.0-3845.184&quot;&gt;archive&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Global average ocean freight rates for a 40-foot container have now declined for eight straight weeks&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Spot pricing for the busy Shanghai-to-Los Angeles trade route has bounced around more but is still down about 19% from its September peak.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Meanwhile, the number of containers lingering for longer than nine days at the Port of Los Angeles has dropped by about a third since the hub announced a plan in October to start fining ocean carriers for excessive dwell times, Executive Director Gene Seroka said this week.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;For all the doomsday warnings about the knock-on effects of the logjams on corporate earnings, companies generally seem to be managing fine — at least the large, public ones. [like Target]&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot; U.S. manufacturing output rose in October to the highest level since March 2019, Federal Reserve data showed this week.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;The factory production rebound was driven in part by an 11% jump in motor vehicles and parts, suggesting that even the automotive industry, hit hard by the semiconductor shortage, is navigating the supply crunch.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bloomberg concludes that not everything is back to normal as many problems persists. But at least things are not getting worse and are improving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Does this affect any of your investing strategy? What stocks will improve or go down based on this easing trend? Will J Powell&amp;#39;s job depend on this trend continuing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How did you come through bad years?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Recently I read many posts in this sub and others about inflation hedge and/or
depression hedge. Indeed we Bogleheads should buy-and-hold-and-chill, however
young investors may not came through bad years and have no idea what it would be
like when a crash really comes.

So, how long have you been…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qy1uhi/how_did_you_come_through_bad_years/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qy1uhi/how_did_you_come_through_bad_years/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 14:41:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently I read many posts in this sub and others about inflation hedge and/or depression hedge. Indeed we Bogleheads should buy-and-hold-and-chill, however young investors may not came through bad years and have no idea what it would be like when a crash really comes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, how long have you been investing? What is your story when a crash came, and what advice(s) will give to young investors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally Im a young investor too and will just uninstall the App and look away from financial news, hoping to ease the panic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for your story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Are there any companies too evil to invest in?]]></title><description><![CDATA[A Big Pharma company that got millions of Americans addicted to oxycontin and
100,000s killed from overdoses? A chocolate company who relies on child slave
labor in West African cocoa plantations? A fast food chain that gets its
hamburger beef from devastated deforested areas of the Amazon?…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qy3pz7/are_there_any_companies_too_evil_to_invest_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qy3pz7/are_there_any_companies_too_evil_to_invest_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 14:12:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Big Pharma company that got millions of Americans addicted to oxycontin and 100,000s killed from overdoses? A chocolate company who relies on child slave labor in West African cocoa plantations? A fast food chain that gets its hamburger beef from devastated deforested areas of the Amazon? Etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serious question - are there any rating systems for corporate evil and/or investment funds that will allow for moral investments?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>