<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 10:36:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[$PLTR CEO sells 16m worth of shares]]></title><description><![CDATA[I by no means have any professional knowledge on the subject, but I just saw on
finviz that pltr ceo sold a bunch of shares on November 5th, 4 days before
earnings.

Should I as a $PLTR holder be worries about this?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpmor1/pltr_ceo_sells_16m_worth_of_shares/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpmor1/pltr_ceo_sells_16m_worth_of_shares/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 09:58:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I by no means have any professional knowledge on the subject, but I just saw on finviz that pltr ceo sold a bunch of shares on November 5th,  4 days before earnings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should I as a $PLTR holder be worries about this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What even is a strategy?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpsxtv/what_even_is_a_strategy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpsxtv/what_even_is_a_strategy/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 09:32:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can someone explain to me the EV craze?]]></title><description><![CDATA[What exactly is it about electric vehicles that is going to make selling cars a
better business? Cars are an asset heavy, low margin business. In other words,
the opposite of what you want.

Yet EV companies who will have to compete with all the legacy car makers in the
EV market, plus Tesla, plus…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpt8sc/can_someone_explain_to_me_the_ev_craze/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpt8sc/can_someone_explain_to_me_the_ev_craze/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 08:52:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What exactly is it about electric vehicles that is going to make selling cars a better business? Cars are an asset heavy, low margin business. In other words, the opposite of what you want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet EV companies who will have to compete with all the legacy car makers in the EV market, plus Tesla, plus all the other EV startups, are getting absurd valuations. What is it about making the powertrain electric that will suddenly make this a great business model? Autonomous driving subscriptions? Leasing cars to uber/lyft? I feel like I&amp;#39;m missing something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t doubt that EVs are the future and that it&amp;#39;s a huge market. But again, selling cars is an asset heavy, low margin business. So what am I missing? Or am I correct that the EV craze is overblown?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[🎮 $GME 🎮 The #1 Indicator - of you know what - is here again:]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpt7ya/gme_the_1_indicator_of_you_know_what_is_here_again/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpt7ya/gme_the_1_indicator_of_you_know_what_is_here_again/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 07:28:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I’ve always viewed target date funds as a close alternative to the Boglehead method. Can anyone give me some general perspective on the fund below and it’s composition/performance compared to a true Bogle approach? Retirement account is now to a point where I want to make sure I’m getting it right!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qpu0dw/ive_always_viewed_target_date_funds_as_a_close/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qpu0dw/ive_always_viewed_target_date_funds_as_a_close/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 06:50:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Not a 🌈🐻, but gotta be honest I expected worse.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpi4s0/not_a_but_gotta_be_honest_i_expected_worse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpi4s0/not_a_but_gotta_be_honest_i_expected_worse/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 05:21:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I've officially become a Bagholder]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qppebv/ive_officially_become_a_bagholder/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qppebv/ive_officially_become_a_bagholder/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 04:40:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is there a Fidelity equivalent to VT?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know that they have some funds that track the SP 500 and the total stock
market without fees but do they have a feeless equivalent to VT?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qpps5y/is_there_a_fidelity_equivalent_to_vt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qpps5y/is_there_a_fidelity_equivalent_to_vt/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 04:40:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know that they have some funds that track the SP 500 and the total stock market without fees but do they have a feeless equivalent to VT?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Robinhood had a security breach last week]]></title><description><![CDATA[They sent out emails and various news outlets have started to pick the story up:

https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-08/robinhood-data-breach-exposes-data-on-millions-of-customers

The hack apparently happened on 11/3 (so last Wednesday). They claim no personal
information other than…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qppj3n/robinhood_had_a_security_breach_last_week/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qppj3n/robinhood_had_a_security_breach_last_week/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 04:40:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;They sent out emails and various news outlets have started to pick the story up:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-08/robinhood-data-breach-exposes-data-on-millions-of-customers&quot;&gt;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-08/robinhood-data-breach-exposes-data-on-millions-of-customers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hack apparently happened on 11/3 (so last Wednesday). They claim no personal information other than email addresses was compromised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---edit---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;from joecop&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.robinhood.com/2021/11/8/data-security-incident&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt; in the comments:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The unauthorized party socially engineered a customer support employee by phone and obtained access to certain customer support systems. At this time, we understand that the unauthorized party obtained a list of email addresses for approximately five million people, and full names for a different group of approximately two million people. We also believe that for a more limited number of people—approximately 310 in total—additional personal information, including name, date of birth, and zip code, was exposed, with a subset of approximately 10 customers having more extensive account details revealed. We are in the process of making appropriate disclosures to affected people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;so ultimately 4 different groups compromised with different amounts of data leaked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What if Bill Gates kept his MSFT shares?]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://ca.news.yahoo.com/bill-gates-hadn-t-sold-110000787.html

Wow, that is almost 700B today.

Of course at the end of the day, it doesn't matter that much as he is still
worth almost 130B, and don't think he will be losing his sleep over this. The
guy who sold 10% of Apple for 2300 bucks, well…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpoxh5/what_if_bill_gates_kept_his_msft_shares/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpoxh5/what_if_bill_gates_kept_his_msft_shares/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 04:40:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ca.news.yahoo.com/bill-gates-hadn-t-sold-110000787.html&quot;&gt;https://ca.news.yahoo.com/bill-gates-hadn-t-sold-110000787.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wow, that is almost 700B today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course at the end of the day, it doesn&amp;#39;t matter that much as he is still worth almost 130B, and don&amp;#39;t think he will be losing his sleep over this. The guy who sold 10% of Apple for 2300 bucks, well it is amazing that guy is still alive (&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ronald_Wayne&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ronald_Wayne&lt;/a&gt;). Knowing how much I regurgitate my mistakes over and over again, I think I would have killed myself or gone completely insane a long time ago... I could clearly see myself being a crazy homeless dude just repeating ..&amp;quot;2300 bucks, now worth more than 200B, fuck fuck fuck...&amp;quot;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What are your high risk/high reward stocks for the next 5-10 years?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am out of the loop since I am preparing for medical school admission and
havent researched into any kind of stocks in the last months/years, so I would
like to hear your predictions and your reasons for it :)]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpnbwd/what_are_your_high_riskhigh_reward_stocks_for_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpnbwd/what_are_your_high_riskhigh_reward_stocks_for_the/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 04:07:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am out of the loop since I am preparing for medical school admission and havent researched into any kind of stocks in the last months/years, so I would like to hear your predictions and your reasons for it :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sanjay Gupta and CNN may have thought they were being cute, but marketing an unlicensed vaccine directly to children crosses mulitple major ethical lines. They deserve to be sued, boycotted, and Gupta should lose his license to practice medicine for this. Quite serious. NOT OK!!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1457909035286646789</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1457909035286646789</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 03:37:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[S&amp;P 500 closes at an all-time high for the 8th day in a row and 65th time this year. Needs 13 more to break the record set in 1995 (77). $SPX https://t.co/GmoSL8Gkaf]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1457815519105536005</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1457815519105536005</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 03:37:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[FYI: Today J.P. Morgan posted their 2022 Long-Term Capital Market Assumptions]]></title><description><![CDATA[Link here
[https://am.jpmorgan.com/content/dam/jpm-am-aem/global/en/insights/portfolio-insights/ltcma/ltcma-full-report.pdf]

Briefs here
[https://am.jpmorgan.com/us/en/asset-management/institutional/insights/portfolio-insights/ltcma/executive-summary/]

My personal takeaways: 60/40 is still okay…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qpsu0v/fyi_today_jp_morgan_posted_their_2022_longterm/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qpsu0v/fyi_today_jp_morgan_posted_their_2022_longterm/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 02:54:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://am.jpmorgan.com/content/dam/jpm-am-aem/global/en/insights/portfolio-insights/ltcma/ltcma-full-report.pdf&quot;&gt;Link here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://am.jpmorgan.com/us/en/asset-management/institutional/insights/portfolio-insights/ltcma/executive-summary/&quot;&gt;Briefs here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My personal takeaways: 60/40 is still okay-ish as in 2021. Higher returns can be achieved via:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PE (private equity, not widely accessible to individual investors AFAIK other than SPAC)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Global Transport (Cannot find a corresponding ETF. Perhaps &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.blackrock.com/americas-offshore/en/products/299086/blackrock-future-of-transport-fund&quot;&gt;https://www.blackrock.com/americas-offshore/en/products/299086/blackrock-future-of-transport-fund&lt;/a&gt; but given that it&amp;#39;s a UCITS fund US investors need to purchase via a fund manager)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Value-add real-estate (Fundrise provided a value-add fund to accredited investors)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Global infrastructure ($IGF)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct landing (Yieldstreet? Worth checking the fee structure and the underlying products)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;EM debt (tons of closed-end funds and ETFs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall it&amp;#39;s a very detailed a report covering lots of topics including inflation, crypto, tax hikes and 60/40 for 2022 with statistics. Highly recommend giving it a read.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Here is a Market Recap for today Monday, November 8, 2021]]></title><description><![CDATA[PsychoMarket Recap - Monday, November 8, 2021

Stocks finished mixed today, with the tech-heavy Nasdaq (QQQ) closing modestly
in the red, breaking an insane rally pulled down by a decline in Tesla (TSLA)
while the S&P 500 (SPY) and Dow Jones (DIA) continued their march higher. The
Russell 2000…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpo0je/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_november/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpo0je/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_november/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 02:54:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Monday, November 8, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks finished mixed today, with the tech-heavy Nasdaq (QQQ) closing modestly in the red, breaking an insane rally pulled down by a decline in Tesla (TSLA) while the S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) and Dow Jones (DIA) continued their march higher. The Russell 2000 (IWM), which tracks the performance of small-caps, finished the day 0.33% higher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week, the Labor Department released the monthly October jobs report, which showed the pace of employment greatly improved after two disappointing months, with the report citing declining coronavirus cases and increased demand for workers for the uptick. Here are the numbers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Change in non-farm payrolls, October:&lt;/strong&gt; +531,000 vs. +450,000 expected, and a great improvement over the +194,000 job added in September&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unemployment rate:&lt;/strong&gt; 4.6% vs. 4.7% expected, 4.8% in September&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During a press conference, President Joe Biden said of the Labor report, “Our economy is starting to work for more Americans. Thanks to the economic plan we put through in Congress earlier this year and a successful vaccine deployment, America continues to add jobs at a record pace. In this historically strong recovery, unemployment has fallen again today,” President Joe Biden said during a press conference on Friday.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though payrolls have grown every month so far in 2021, the economy remains more than 4 million jobs short of its pre-pandemic levels following plunges in employment between March and April of 2020. And the civilian labor force was still down by nearly 3 million individuals compared to February 2020 as of October 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the inflation front, market participants are closely monitoring the Bureau of Labor’s October Consumer Price Index (CPI) report, which is expected to show yet another acceleration in consumer prices on both a monthly and annual basis, as ongoing supply-chain disruptions and labor market imbalances continue to cap production of goods at a time of soaring demand. Estimates as of Monday showed that consensus economists expect to see the CPI rise by 5.9% in October compared to last year, accelerating from September&amp;#39;s 5.4% annual rate to reach the fastest rise since 1990.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rubella Farooqi, Chief Economist at High Frequency Economics wrote in a note to clients, “We continue to expect that a normalization of demand and supply constraint or time will take pressure off inflation statistics. The exact timing is uncertain, given we cannot predict when supply chains will adjust. However, our best guess is that prices will start moderating by the middle of next year - possibly sooner if goods that are stuff in ports reach their destinations in the early part of the year, which will result in an excess supply of goods after holidays.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ford Motors (F) crossed the $20 per share threshold for the first time since mid-2001, with investors seemingly encouraged by the company’s pivot into electric vehicles and the upcoming blockbuster Rivian IPO, of which Ford owns 12%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Tesla (TSLA) fell today but held onto the critical $1150 support after CEO Elon Musk asked his Twitter followers via a poll if he should sell 10% of his stake in Tesla, a position worth roughly $20 billion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Though it was unable to hold the gains by close, Alphabet (GOOG, GOOGL) became the third company to breach the $2 trillion market cap threshold, joining Apple (AAPL) and Microsoft (MSFT).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Italy&amp;#39;s antitrust regulator has started proceedings to fine Google for allegedly restrictive clauses in the terms of service consumers have to accept to use Google Drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) surged more than 10% after Meta Platforms (FB, soon to be MVRS) selected their chips to power its data center. AMD explained that the two companies worked together to develop a high performance processor based on the company’s 3rd Generation EPYC Processor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Moreover, AMD announced new chips called  &lt;a href=&quot;https://ir.amd.com/news-events/press-releases/detail/1032/new-amd-instinct-mi200-series-accelerators-bring&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AMD Instinct MI200 series accelerators&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which are optimized for high-performance computing and artificial-intelligence workloads. The company described them as &amp;quot;the first exascale-class GPU accelerators.&amp;quot; AMD competes with &lt;strong&gt;Nvidia&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;NVDA&lt;/strong&gt;) in GPUs. Sorry it sounds like jargon but as a massive semiconductor bull I could not be more excited for the future. I’ve said it many times before but personally NVDA is my #1, AMD is my #2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SoftBank’s Vision Fund, the largest tech-focused investment firm in the world with over $100 billion in capital, lost $10 billion this quarter amid the regulatory crackdown in China. The fund announced it was launching a $9 billion share buyback amid pressure from investors. The group’s largest asset, Chinese e-commerce firm Alibaba , saw its valuation fall by around a third in the second quarter. Its stake in Chinese ride-hailer Didi, acquired for $12 billion, was valued at $7.5 billion. Another notable hit was Coupang (CPNG), a South Korean eCommerce company which gave up a third of its value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current stock price was written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) target raised by Wells Fargo from $145 to $180 at Overeweight. Stock currently around $150&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Booking (BKNG) target raised by Susquehanna from $2850 to $3100 at Positive. Stock currently around $2640&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cigna (CI) target raised by Credit Suisse from $270 to $300 at Outperform. Stock currently around $218&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ConocoPhillips (COP) target raised by Argus from $75 to $89 at Buy. Stock currently around $76&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Datadog (DDOG) with two target raises. Stock currently around $191

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Barclays from $180 to $225 at Overweight&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Needham &amp;amp; Co from $173 to $236 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DigitalOcean (DOCN) target raised by Oppenheimer from $100 to $130 at Outperform. Stock currently around $113&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Home Depot (HD) target raised by Wells Fargo from $365 to $400 at Overweight. Stock currently around $369&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lowe’s (LOW) target raised by Wells Fargo from $230 to $260 at Overweight. Stock currently around $235&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;McKesson (MCK) target raised by Argus from $230 to $270 at Buy. Stock currently around $220&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sunrun (RUN) target raised by Truist Securities from $74 to $76 at Buy. Stock currently around $58&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tesla (TSLA) target raised by Jefferies Financial from $950 to $1400 at Buy. Stock currently around $1160&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uber (UBER) with two target raises. Stock currently around $46

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BTIG Research from $75 to $90&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JMP Securities from $77 to $80 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The way I see it, if you want the rainbow, you gotta put up with the rain.” - Dolly Parton&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin $67,000. $BTC https://t.co/UsRVQfbZvP]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1457871545825693696</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1457871545825693696</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 02:40:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Do Fidelity's lower expense ratios result in higher return? [BH Thread]]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qpqx6r/do_fidelitys_lower_expense_ratios_result_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qpqx6r/do_fidelitys_lower_expense_ratios_result_in/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 02:07:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Other subs ..?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Was curious what other subs some of you find useful or have overlap with
bogleing or good general financial insights ...?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qpeyjs/other_subs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qpeyjs/other_subs/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 02:07:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Was curious what other subs some of you find useful or have overlap with bogleing or good general financial insights ...?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PayPal reports 13% revenue increase in the third quarter but lowers annual forecast]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/08/paypal-pypl-earnings-q3-2021.html

Earnings per share: $1.11, adjusted, vs. $1.07 expected in a Refinitiv survey of
analysts

Revenue: $6.18 billion vs. $6.23 billion expected

PayPal reported a 13% increase in year-over-year revenue for the third quarter.

The…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpnqqe/paypal_reports_13_revenue_increase_in_the_third/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpnqqe/paypal_reports_13_revenue_increase_in_the_third/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 01:13:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/08/paypal-pypl-earnings-q3-2021.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/08/paypal-pypl-earnings-q3-2021.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earnings per share: $1.11, adjusted, vs. $1.07 expected in a Refinitiv survey of analysts&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revenue: $6.18 billion vs. $6.23 billion expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PayPal reported a 13% increase in year-over-year revenue for the third quarter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company issued a fourth-quarter forecast that fell well short of analysts’ expectations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting next year, customers will be able to make purchases on Amazon.com and the Amazon mobile shopping app using their Venmo accounts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stock is down 5% after the earning report. It has been down from $310 to $230 and it is definitely oversold. Investors should buy the stock here as PayPal is still growing very healthy and there is still plenty of opportunities for PayPal to expand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Investing Quiz]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qpmdw8/investing_quiz/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qpmdw8/investing_quiz/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 23:58:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[RBLX up over 30% after earning call today.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Here is the quote from the article.

> Nov 8 (Reuters) - Roblox Corp exceeded market estimates for quarterly bookings
> on Monday as demand for its video games "MeepCity" and "Adopt Me!" stayed
> strong even after pandemic-led curbs eased.
> 
> Shares of Roblox, among the world's most popular gaming…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpnv3o/rblx_up_over_30_after_earning_call_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpnv3o/rblx_up_over_30_after_earning_call_today/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 23:45:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here is the quote from the article. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nov 8 (Reuters) - Roblox Corp exceeded market estimates for quarterly bookings on Monday as demand for its video games &amp;quot;MeepCity&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Adopt Me!&amp;quot; stayed strong even after pandemic-led curbs eased.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shares of Roblox, among the world&amp;#39;s most popular gaming sites for children, jumped 14% in extended trading.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People had turned to video games for entertainment during last year&amp;#39;s months-long isolation, sparking a boom that is yet to slow down despite the lifting of COVID-19 restrictions.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Data from analytics firm Sensor Tower shows consumer spending on video games rose 7.7% in the third quarter.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;San Mateo, California-based Roblox has capitalized on the boom by allowing users to create an in-game metaverse, a shared virtual world where people in the form of avatars can interact with others.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company posted a 28% rise in bookings to $637.8 million for the third quarter. Analysts had expected bookings of $636.5 million, according to IBES data from Refinitiv.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Paypal Q3 earnings release]]></title><description><![CDATA[Q3’21: Total Payment Volume (TPV) reaches $310 billion with 416 million active
accounts • TPV of $310 billion, growing 26%, and 24% on an FX-neutral basis
(FXN); net revenue of $6.18 billion, growing 13% on a spot and FXN basis • GAAP
EPS of $0.92 compared to $0.86 in Q3’20; non-GAAP EPS of $1.11…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpnmhb/paypal_q3_earnings_release/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpnmhb/paypal_q3_earnings_release/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 23:33:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Q3’21: Total Payment Volume (TPV) reaches $310 billion with 416 million active accounts • TPV of $310 billion, growing 26%, and 24% on an FX-neutral basis (FXN); net revenue of $6.18 billion, growing 13% on a spot and FXN basis • GAAP EPS of $0.92 compared to $0.86 in Q3’20; non-GAAP EPS of $1.11 compared to $1.07 in Q3’20 • 13.3 million Net New Active Accounts (NNAs) added; ended the quarter with 416 million active accounts • Operating Cash Flow of $1.51 billion, growing 15%; Free Cash Flow of $1.29 billion, growing 20% &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FY’21: Revenue expected to grow ~18% and end the year with &amp;gt;430M active accounts • TPV growth now expected to be in the range of ~33%-34% at current spot rates and ~31%-32% on an FXN basis; net revenue expected to be in the range of ~$25.3 billion to ~$25.4 billion, representing growth of ~18% at current spot rates and ~17% on an FXN basis • GAAP EPS expected to be ~$3.62 compared to $3.54 in FY’20; non-GAAP EPS expected to grow ~19% to ~$4.60 • ~55 million NNAs expected to be added in FY’21, including ~3 million active accounts added from the acquisition of Paidy • Venmo users in the U.S. will be able to pay with Venmo on Amazon.com starting in 2022 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://s1.q4cdn.com/633035571/files/doc_financials/2021/q3/Q3-21-PayPal-Earnings-Release.pdf&quot;&gt;https://s1.q4cdn.com/633035571/files/doc_financials/2021/q3/Q3-21-PayPal-Earnings-Release.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This Nvidia run up is crazy]]></title><description><![CDATA[It just keeps going up. Im keeping thinking should i buy more. Im up almost %40
but i only investes like $100 after a shit year for me this vgt and nvidia run
the lastonth pit me at 6% for the year. When is this goinf to pop. Im tempted to
invest more into tech and in nvda because there has to be a…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpjuw9/this_nvidia_run_up_is_crazy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpjuw9/this_nvidia_run_up_is_crazy/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 23:33:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It just keeps going up. Im keeping thinking should i buy more. Im up almost %40 but i only investes like $100 after a shit year for me this vgt and nvidia run the lastonth pit me at 6% for the year. When is this goinf to pop. Im tempted to invest more into tech and in nvda because there has to be a pop right? This run and overall bull market is going to break right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Forget Elon's poll, the tax has to be paid on Tesla share option gains]]></title><description><![CDATA[Elon Musk was awarded 21.8 million stock call options in 2012 at a $6.24 strike
price. Against Friday's close that's a $28 billion gain on soon to expire stock
options. All up the tax owed would be $15 billion. The guy also owes loans taken
out against borrowed stock.

Musk and other executives have…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpb1t8/forget_elons_poll_the_tax_has_to_be_paid_on_tesla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpb1t8/forget_elons_poll_the_tax_has_to_be_paid_on_tesla/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 22:24:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk was awarded 21.8 million stock call options in 2012 at a $6.24 strike price.  Against Friday&amp;#39;s close that&amp;#39;s a $28 billion gain on soon to expire stock options.  All up the tax owed would be $15 billion.  The guy also owes loans taken out against borrowed stock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Musk and other executives have many other generous in the money stock option awards, that will require both collateral to exercise and tax to be paid which can only realistically come from share sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The shares would have had to be sold at some point, irrespective of his Twitter poll outcome.  More theatrics from Musk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla shareholders, like.most company shareholders in their defence, so often overlook the dilution effect of stock options and the inevitable share sell down by executives to cover the collateral needed to exercise the options and to pay any taxes due.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Really thought I'd be a multi-millionaire already]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qplyoh/really_thought_id_be_a_multimillionaire_already/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qplyoh/really_thought_id_be_a_multimillionaire_already/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 22:24:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is it a bad time to invest in bonds?]]></title><description><![CDATA[My portfolio is about 15% bonds. That’s mostly TLT. I want to increase this
percentage because of my age. I want to slowly increase it to around 30%.

However, it really seems like interest rates and yields will be going up in the
medium/long term. I’m concerned that that will cause TLT to drop. Is…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qpgw4v/is_it_a_bad_time_to_invest_in_bonds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qpgw4v/is_it_a_bad_time_to_invest_in_bonds/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 21:34:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My portfolio is about 15% bonds. That’s mostly TLT. I want to increase this percentage because of my age. I want to slowly increase it to around 30%. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it really seems like interest rates and yields will be going up in the medium/long term. I’m concerned that that will cause TLT to drop. Is this something I should be worried about? Am I stuck? I have about 75% in equities and I think that’s too high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[85K to 665K / 700% gain in 5 weeks & I eat crayons]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpgyr5/85k_to_665k_700_gain_in_5_weeks_i_eat_crayons/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpgyr5/85k_to_665k_700_gain_in_5_weeks_i_eat_crayons/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 21:19:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Peloton ($PTON) shares tumble another 9%, now down 45% in the past 5 days]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cramer says sell Peloton on the stock’s next bounce ‘if you haven’t sold it
already’

https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/05/cramer-says-sell-peloton-on-the-stocks-next-bounce-if-you-havent-sold-it-already.html

I bought in when PTON was down 30% so I'm currently down 15%. Any thoughts on
whether I should…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpkqdj/peloton_pton_shares_tumble_another_9_now_down_45/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpkqdj/peloton_pton_shares_tumble_another_9_now_down_45/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 21:19:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cramer says sell Peloton on the stock’s next bounce ‘if you haven’t sold it already’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/05/cramer-says-sell-peloton-on-the-stocks-next-bounce-if-you-havent-sold-it-already.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/05/cramer-says-sell-peloton-on-the-stocks-next-bounce-if-you-havent-sold-it-already.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought in when PTON was down 30% so I&amp;#39;m currently down 15%. Any thoughts on whether I should hold, sell, or average down?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anti-climax]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpey8i/anticlimax/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpey8i/anticlimax/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 20:09:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[🦃 Turkey Day is coming right up! We are thankful for all of you so we're giving away another Wall St Bull NFT! 

Enter:
1⃣Like/RT
2⃣Tell us what you are thankful for on the Bulls ST stream: https://t.co/5B9o4tkjRa

24hrs - 1 winner!

Rules: https://t.co/YXdJJ4dMiQ

#NFTGiveaway https://t.co/Y2Dj6h4nJl]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1457779945338335234</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1457779945338335234</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 19:38:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Investing for the long term.]]></title><description><![CDATA[SPY, QQQ, VTI, VXUS.

If you’re trying to keep things simple, do you really need anything else? Could
your entire portfolio just be these 4, and just set it and forget it? And is
there anything I should keep in mind about portfolio % with these stocks?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpdlng/investing_for_the_long_term/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpdlng/investing_for_the_long_term/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 19:12:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SPY, QQQ, VTI, VXUS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re trying to keep things simple, do you really need anything else? Could your entire portfolio just be these 4, and just set it and forget it? And is there anything I should keep in mind about portfolio % with these stocks?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Never bet against Musk]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpfmyu/never_bet_against_musk/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpfmyu/never_bet_against_musk/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 19:12:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Personality > Money for women (just don’t be a poor tho and all you autists have a chance with Cathie Wood or Tasha Keeney)]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpgdtr/personality_money_for_women_just_dont_be_a_poor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpgdtr/personality_money_for_women_just_dont_be_a_poor/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 19:12:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Are any fellow bogleheads facing a similar dilemma as mine?]]></title><description><![CDATA[So I'm all about the Bogleheads philosopohy, couldn't be more aligned with my
outlook on finances/investing and my future goals.

With that said, we do have to admit that this is (intentionally) the boring
option where you simply hold and stay course whilst it's human nature to want to
have some…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qp8p50/are_any_fellow_bogleheads_facing_a_similar/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qp8p50/are_any_fellow_bogleheads_facing_a_similar/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 18:16:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;#39;m all about the Bogleheads philosopohy, couldn&amp;#39;t be more aligned with my outlook on finances/investing and my future goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that said, we do have to admit that this is (intentionally) the boring option where you simply hold and stay course whilst it&amp;#39;s human nature to want to have some fun. Given that, I&amp;#39;ve put 5% of my NW in crypto and I&amp;#39;ve got to say it&amp;#39;s tough to look at a 67% gain (over the past 7 months) vs. 5% market portfolio gains and not feel some type of way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m conflicted as I genuinely believe in blockchain technology and it&amp;#39;s potential going forward but I feel like pumping more into crypto goes against all my existing values. Anyone else facing a similar dilemma?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[🌈🧸 today]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpf0lx/today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpf0lx/today/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 17:53:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can you get rich without investing in real estate?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lots of Grant Cardone and other tips showing in my feed all talk about real
estate investing. As investments grow, what are you all investing in to make it
big? Is real estate the way to scale bigger faster returns?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qpg05c/can_you_get_rich_without_investing_in_real_estate/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qpg05c/can_you_get_rich_without_investing_in_real_estate/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 17:44:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lots of Grant Cardone and other tips showing in my feed all talk about real estate investing. As investments grow, what are you all investing in to make it big? Is real estate the way to scale bigger faster returns?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just hit $100k - my first milestone]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://i.imgur.com/DJj2Rlx.jpg

I’m 28 and I’ve been investing every since I was employed FT at 22. Today hits
my first milestone of hopefully many where I hit 100k in my brokerage account.

I have another 95K in my retirement account that I’m also waiting for to hit
100k.

It feels extremely good…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qphjri/just_hit_100k_my_first_milestone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qphjri/just_hit_100k_my_first_milestone/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 17:44:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/DJj2Rlx.jpg&quot;&gt;https://i.imgur.com/DJj2Rlx.jpg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m 28 and I’ve been investing every since I was employed FT at 22. Today hits my first milestone of hopefully many where I hit 100k in my brokerage account. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have another 95K in my retirement account that I’m also waiting for to hit 100k.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It feels extremely good and I’m looking forward to what the future holds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks these big winners:
$AMD
$NVDA
$AAPL
$TSM
$COST
$SOFI
$LOW&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: fixed Apple ticker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Options made me learn physics and maths]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpaevv/options_made_me_learn_physics_and_maths/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpaevv/options_made_me_learn_physics_and_maths/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 17:44:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tesla pre-market]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpe0mv/tesla_premarket/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpe0mv/tesla_premarket/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 17:44:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chipmaker $AMD just scored a big deal with Meta (up 11.4% right now)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Article is here
[https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chipmaker-amd-just-scored-a-big-deal-with-meta-160059677.html]

> The chip giant said its EPYC chips were selected by Meta (formerly known as
> Facebook) to help power its data centers at its virtual Accelerated Data
> Center Premiere event Monday. AMD…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qphe6c/chipmaker_amd_just_scored_a_big_deal_with_meta_up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qphe6c/chipmaker_amd_just_scored_a_big_deal_with_meta_up/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 17:17:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Article is &lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chipmaker-amd-just-scored-a-big-deal-with-meta-160059677.html&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The chip giant said its EPYC chips were selected by Meta (formerly known as Facebook) to help power its data centers at its virtual Accelerated Data Center Premiere event Monday. AMD explained the two companies worked together to develop a high-performance, power-efficient processor based on the company&amp;#39;s 3rd Generation EPYC processor. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The high-profile win accompanied several announcements from AMD, including some specifics around upcoming EPYC processors codenamed “Genoa” and “Bergamo.” AMD dubbed the Genoa processor as the &amp;quot;world’s highest performance processor for general purpose computing.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fuckers https://t.co/uUD2K0r4yF]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1457588423296962565</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1457588423296962565</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 16:51:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can’t wait for Monday🥺]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qp0iuq/cant_wait_for_monday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qp0iuq/cant_wait_for_monday/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 16:51:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Never bear too much or too little risk (Bogleheads philosophy - rule #3)]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qp3kz4/never_bear_too_much_or_too_little_risk_bogleheads/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qp3kz4/never_bear_too_much_or_too_little_risk_bogleheads/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 16:08:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[IMO the market is strongly underestimating the magnitude of rate hikes required to temper inflation]]></title><description><![CDATA[Across the new sources I read, the consensus seems to be that the market is
pricing in the first rate hike around Summer 22. The magnitude of the expected
rate hike is tiny, maybe a quarter-percent. If you are of the belief that
supply-chain shortages will last well into 2022, this is hilariously…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qpe2gt/imo_the_market_is_strongly_underestimating_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qpe2gt/imo_the_market_is_strongly_underestimating_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 15:49:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across the new sources I read, the consensus seems to be that the market is pricing in the first rate hike around Summer 22. The magnitude of the expected rate hike is tiny, maybe a quarter-percent. If you are of the belief that supply-chain shortages will last well into 2022, this is hilariously inadequate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, we&amp;#39;ve seen from 10 years of monetary experiments that the direct relationship between inflation and the state of the economy + monetary policy is tenuous at best. And this has benefitted the economy at large as we have pumped more and more money and cheap debt into the system with no apparent ill effects (except the ones that we choose to ignore, but I&amp;#39;m not here to beat that debt horse!). So it&amp;#39;s already ridiculous to believe that the converse won&amp;#39;t also be true. A 25 basis-point increase will do nothing to temper inflation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, we have a new phenomenon that &lt;em&gt;does&lt;/em&gt; seem to have a strong connection to inflation, both in theory and in practice. Inflation expectations among spenders and workers are higher than they&amp;#39;ve been in over a decade, wage increases at the bottom are faster than they&amp;#39;ve been in over a decade, and supply chains are more constricted than they&amp;#39;ve been in a decade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thus, if inflation persists, even at the not-hyper-inflation levels we&amp;#39;re currently seeing, it&amp;#39;s not a stretch to see that the Fed will have to make moves that shatter the confidence driving the second point. Once you accept the first point, that the Fed&amp;#39;s tools have a weak causal relationship with inflation, it&amp;#39;s clear that the only way they can stop inflation is to raise interest rates enough to tank assets, which will shake consumer confidence and bring demand in equilibrium with supply. If that isn&amp;#39;t enough, they will be forced to go further and cause a recession, although this will take a lot of pushing, given their need to balance against the full employment mandate. Either way, I think we can all agree a quarter rate increase will do nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m curious what other people&amp;#39;s thoughts are. I&amp;#39;m not making any earth-shattering new statements, just connecting dots. To me, this outcome flows logically from the two points above, &lt;em&gt;if&lt;/em&gt; you believe that higher inflation (but not hyper-inflation) will be persistent into next year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Red light!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpbopa/red_light/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qpbopa/red_light/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 15:32:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rolls Royce set to receive £210mn in UK Government funding for development of Small Modular Nuclear Reactors.]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-59201945

Rolls Royce have been developing SMRs, targeting the change to a net-zero
economy. These reactors are much smaller than conventional reactors and aim to
be able to be mass produced.

The UK government has placed a lot of focus on nuclear power, and this…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpd7we/rolls_royce_set_to_receive_210mn_in_uk_government/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qpd7we/rolls_royce_set_to_receive_210mn_in_uk_government/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 15:07:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-59201945&quot;&gt;https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-59201945&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rolls Royce have been developing SMRs, targeting the change to a net-zero economy.  These reactors are much smaller than conventional reactors and aim to be able to be mass produced. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The UK government has placed a lot of focus on nuclear power, and this will most likely be the next step in producing a net zero economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hold 1000 shares at £1.075.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sino Ocean Group Holding Ltd., part-owned by China's finance ministry, has become the latest property company to see its bonds slump.]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://archive.md/20211108075537/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-08/chinese-developer-controlled-by-government-is-latest-to-plunge#selection-3459.0-3463.271



> Not even state-owned firms are safe from the deepening rout in Chinese
> developer bonds.
> 
> Sino Ocean Group Holding…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qpaay9/sino_ocean_group_holding_ltd_partowned_by_chinas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qpaay9/sino_ocean_group_holding_ltd_partowned_by_chinas/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 14:23:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.md/20211108075537/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-08/chinese-developer-controlled-by-government-is-latest-to-plunge#selection-3459.0-3463.271&quot;&gt;https://archive.md/20211108075537/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-08/chinese-developer-controlled-by-government-is-latest-to-plunge#selection-3459.0-3463.271&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not even state-owned firms are safe from the deepening rout in Chinese developer bonds.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sino  Ocean Group Holding Ltd., part-owned by the finance ministry, has  become the latest property company to see its bonds slump. Its 4.75%  note due 2030 fell Monday to as low as 73.48 cents on the dollar, with  spreads over comparable Treasuries widening to a record 800 basis  points, according to data compiled by Bloomberg.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s  despite the firm being rated investment-grade at two global credit  assessors and holding about 54 times more cash and equivalents than  China Evergrande Group. Sino Ocean’s shares have been doing better,  rebounding 35% from their September low. They rose 3.5% Monday.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stress  in the market for Chinese property bonds is reaching extreme levels as  surging borrowing costs make refinancing dollar debt too expensive and a  slowing housing market shrinks revenue.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;China’s  finance ministry controls just under 30% of Sino Ocean’s shares,  according to data compiled by Bloomberg. State-owned Dajia Insurance  Group -- the company that took over most of the operations of troubled  Anbang Insurance Group Co. -- holds a similar-sized stake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[It’s gonna be awesome]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qp5hz2/its_gonna_be_awesome/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qp5hz2/its_gonna_be_awesome/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 13:14:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[America, the final days https://t.co/HzYdCQURQY]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1457498356595499015</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1457498356595499015</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 12:50:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tesla down 6.9% pre-market]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qp9z5l/tesla_down_69_premarket/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qp9z5l/tesla_down_69_premarket/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 12:50:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>