<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 06:19:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[EV Company Polestar (WITH SALES) going public via SPAC - $GGPI]]></title><description><![CDATA[Overlooked SPAC deal, Polestar, an electric-focused automotive company based in
Sweden is merging with $GGPI.

They are already selling their Polestar 1, a hybrid, and the Polestar 2,
fully-electric car. They are also released a vision for the Polestar "Precept."

Financials

They did $645M in…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvmzuu/ev_company_polestar_with_sales_going_public_via/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvmzuu/ev_company_polestar_with_sales_going_public_via/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 05:56:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overlooked SPAC deal, Polestar, an electric-focused automotive company based in Sweden is merging with $GGPI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are already selling their Polestar 1, a hybrid, and the Polestar 2, fully-electric car. They are also released a vision for the Polestar &amp;quot;Precept.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Financials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They did $645M in revenue in 2020, and are projecting $1.6B in 2021. Right now, the SPAC is valued at just $1.55B.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/3jmd9c5ulvz71.png?width=624&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=54caf7be4f0b42872a22d4a633e3f28aa78b836c&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/3jmd9c5ulvz71.png?width=624&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=54caf7be4f0b42872a22d4a633e3f28aa78b836c&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;compared to other EV/automotive companies. $645M* revenue&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are also backed by Volvo, Geely, and Leonardo DiCaprio? IMO most undervalued EV company after GM and F.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[New Post:

The Stock Market Is Not the Economy...

https://t.co/HTQvTJLLHf https://t.co/mg6NMfQ2NF]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460723942314938372</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460723942314938372</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 05:43:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Not kidding: Lingerie/underwear company Naked Brand merge with EV auto maker Cenntro Automotive and soared]]></title><description><![CDATA[It was over a week ago. The companies are not very well known like Lucid or
Rivian but I'm calling market top for EV companies.

 * Naked Brands stock soared as much as 30% on Tuesday after the company
   announced a merger with Cenntro Automotive.
 * The lingerie maker is pivoting to electric…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvocts/not_kidding_lingerieunderwear_company_naked_brand/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvocts/not_kidding_lingerieunderwear_company_naked_brand/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 05:43:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was over a week ago. The companies are not very well known like Lucid or Rivian but I&amp;#39;m calling market top for EV companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Naked Brands stock soared as much as 30% on Tuesday after the company announced a merger with Cenntro Automotive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The lingerie maker is pivoting to electric vehicles as investors look to find the next Tesla.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cenntro develops electrified commercial vehicles and has sold more than 3,000 units to date.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://africa.businessinsider.com/finance/a-lingerie-makers-stock-is-soaring-on-a-deal-to-merge-with-an-ev-manufacturer/040c5jh&quot;&gt;https://africa.businessinsider.com/finance/a-lingerie-makers-stock-is-soaring-on-a-deal-to-merge-with-an-ev-manufacturer/040c5jh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thoughts on Disney (DIS)]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’ve been watching Disney for a few months now and think it’s a great stock for
my long term holdings. I began adding shares recently since it dropped sub $160.
What are everyone’s thoughts on the stock? Is it being judged too much on
Disney+ and not the company as a whole?

It’s had an…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvk3q2/thoughts_on_disney_dis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvk3q2/thoughts_on_disney_dis/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 05:43:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been watching Disney for a few months now and think it’s a great stock for my long term holdings. I began adding shares recently since it dropped sub $160. What are everyone’s thoughts on the stock? Is it being judged too much on Disney+ and not the company as a whole?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s had an underwhelming year and is now 20% below ATH. Has anyone held throughout this recent slump?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone discourse would be appreciated :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bogleheads who buy Bitcoin?]]></title><description><![CDATA[For the Bogleheads in this sub who do their 5% fun money and buy Bitcoin, which
app or provider are you using to buy Bitcoin?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvh6s9/bogleheads_who_buy_bitcoin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvh6s9/bogleheads_who_buy_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 04:32:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the Bogleheads in this sub who do their 5% fun money and buy Bitcoin, which app or provider are you using to buy Bitcoin?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian has $0 in revenue and is now the third most valuable carmaker on the planet]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvinva/rivian_has_0_in_revenue_and_is_now_the_third_most/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvinva/rivian_has_0_in_revenue_and_is_now_the_third_most/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 03:46:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Metaverse and why you should pay attention - Basic breakdown]]></title><description><![CDATA[Introduction and what is the Metaverse?:

As you all probably know by now the popular social media company formerly known
as Facebook has changed its name to Meta. This has sparked discussions about the
Metaverse and its future effect on society, and rightfully so. Although I have
seen many posts…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvc6fr/the_metaverse_and_why_you_should_pay_attention/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvc6fr/the_metaverse_and_why_you_should_pay_attention/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 03:32:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction and what is the Metaverse?:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you all probably know by now the popular social media company formerly known as Facebook has changed its name to Meta. This has sparked discussions about the Metaverse and its future effect on society, and rightfully so. Although I have seen many posts online and especially on Reddit which don’t quite seem to grasp what the Metaverse is and why it&amp;#39;s the future, please note if you are one of these people don’t worry - it’s complicated for sure! This post will explain simply what the Metaverse is and why you should get on board now. I will do my best to explain but if you have any questions please feel free to ask in the comments and I will be sure to reply.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Metaverse put simply is the combination of multiple elements of technology, but put more complexly is where virtual reality, blockchain and web3 meet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best way of explaining web3 is to first understand web1 and web2. Web1 is what many may consider the first stage of the internet, if you look at what the first iterations of the internet were, it was just code on a screen. It was complex to use and only really used for sharing scientific work. Web2 is what we now know as the internet. This includes Youtube, Reddit etc. The main downside of web2 is for the longest time other than a domain name you couldn’t own anything online. You could make a video and post it on Youtube, even though you feel you own the video and control it, Youtube at any point can remove the video and even your channel. At any point in time everything online can be controlled by someone else. This is where web3 comes in. Web3 is the next evolution of the internet. Web3 may as well be called the decentralised internet. It allows users to freely use the internet run on blockchain, so anyone can participate without having your personal data involved or monetized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a big reason crypto based items such as coins and NFT’s have taken off as they are based on web3 technology. For the first time normal everyday people are able to own their own little part of the internet, and no one, including the government, can tell you what to do. It&amp;#39;s the next step for total freedom online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Metaverse isn’t a place, the Metaverse isn’t something you can touch. A big mistake I see is people think that there is going to be some sort of invention or overnight change where suddenly the Metaverse is mainstream and that&amp;#39;s our lives, no. It will be a gradual change which has already started and will continue to the point that our virtual life is worth more to us than our physical lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why is the Metaverse the next big thing?:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the best place to start on why the Metaverse will be the next big thing will be to look back at previous technology. 99% of human attention used to be on our physical environment. TV’s dropped that to 85%. Computers dropped that to 70%. Phones dropped that to 50%. It&amp;#39;s clear that as technology advances it absorbs more and more of our time and energy. At some point something new will drop that to lower and lower numbers to the point where we are using technology 100% of the time, this may take decades but it&amp;#39;s entirely possible. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t have to be something mind-blowing but just imagine some type of augmented reality device which either connects to your brain or you see it through contact lenses, imagine it just helped with basic everyday things like arrows on a road so you don&amp;#39;t have to distract yourself with a GPS, or walking into a McDonalds and being able to see the calories of each food item on the menu. These are just basic examples of what the first iteration of augmented reality can do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Metaverse will be the next big thing because &lt;strong&gt;it will be everything.&lt;/strong&gt; Anything you could imagine will be in the Metaverse. It can range from anything from gaming to concerts to seeing family members from the other side of the world. There is no beginning, middle and end, it&amp;#39;s just infinite code waiting to be filled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real life application and potential benefits:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the potential benefits I want to start with isn’t about what will be good inside the Metaverse but outside it. A comment I’m seeing a lot online is people saying “I want to work on fixing the real world, not create a fake one”. But I think people are missing the point that this will make the real world better. Imagine the millions of cars we can get off the road and reduce pollution if people no longer had to drive to work and school, and instead would stay at home and work in the Metaverse. Of course this may vary depending on the industry but even if we could get 50% of cars off the road it would be a massive achievement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I write this more and more benefits keep popping in my head, I will just briefly write some ideas but it&amp;#39;s really going to be endless. Surgeons can practice their work virtually. Architects can design and walk around buildings before construction. Home buyers can visit a home from their own home. People on lower incomes can travel the world from their living room. Schools can visit any museum. Entrepreneurs and businesses can save money on office space. Lovers of history can travel to any time desired (DINOSAURS!). The list really is endless, so I will stop there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Potential negatives and why it won’t matter:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with any new technology there are always downsides. When the microwave first came out people were terrified of it, same with TV, radio, social media and now the Metaverse. I will note that is a good thing. As a society we should always look to protect ourselves and do what&amp;#39;s best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Metaverse won’t be perfect. Even nowadays cyber bullying is a major issue and it may not be any better in the Metaverse. We will distance ourselves further from the real world. Spending less and less physical time with our friends and family and more virtual time with them. The thing is though, the negatives don’t matter. Whether it&amp;#39;s good or bad technology has always advanced on and those who don’t get on board are left behind. Many said at the birth of the internet that it would be bad but it is undoubtedly the best thing to happen to humanity in the past century, and this will have the same effect. I greatly encourage those to at least have an open mind when it comes to the Metaverse, we are on the dawn of something great and those who capitalise on it will be rewarded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How long until the Metaverse is ready and becomes mainstream?:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this is a very hard question. Actually, I think this is an impossible question. You could try and rephrase it to ‘How long until the internet is ready and becomes mainstream?’ At no point does anyone announce the internet is ready and at no point is it officially called mainstream. At some point it just became what it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Metaverse creation will be gradual, it will most likely take a decade minimum but my guess is as good as yours. I think the point at which we accept as a society that the Metaverse is ready is when our digital selves are worth more than our physical selves. You even start to see it now. Kids care more about how they look on Fortnite than in real life. Teens care more about how many followers they have on Instagram than in real life. The world has and always will be  changing with technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to buy and how to make profit:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could list any number of companies which could make you great gains in the near future, including FB, MSFT, U, RBLX, AMZN, ADSK etc. and I would be completely wrong! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though I and many others may know a lot about the Metaverse, the truth is we won’t be able to predict even 1% of what the final product will be. If you asked a million people before the internet what the most popular websites would be you wouldn’t get a single right answer. No one knows so anyone telling you what to buy don’t actually have a clue. Yes you can make money in the short term but that’s it. Remember the dot com bubble? Watch out for a Metaverse bubble.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final thoughts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My thoughts are to tell people now to worry. This isn’t some doomsday device, it’s better to just see it as an extension of your phone. The truth is we are years off of anything serious and no one is going to be forced to use it. I also don’t see any chance of it being stopped by the government as I see some people online say. Sugar and cigarettes are bad but they are legal too. I would recommend anyone to at least try and allocate a small percentage of their portfolio to one of the bigger stock names linked to the Metaverse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The market is undervalued]]></title><description><![CDATA[Remember your lives 10 years ago? Yeah. You have way more shit than ever before.
You have way more options. Way more fucking technologies.

It is more specialized now.

So the next 10 years? It'll be a fucking rainbow. Innovation has not stopped.
Innovation picked up the speed that is the highest…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvo3kl/the_market_is_undervalued/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvo3kl/the_market_is_undervalued/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 03:32:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember your lives 10 years ago? Yeah. You have way more shit than ever before. You have way more options. Way more fucking technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is more specialized now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the next 10 years? It&amp;#39;ll be a fucking rainbow. Innovation has not stopped. Innovation picked up the speed that is the highest that it ever has been.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s an amazing ride. Enjoy it. It&amp;#39;s never been better to be alive than now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Metaverse might actually happen. Maybe it&amp;#39;s not if but when?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla is overvalued. Is it though? No idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Facebook and Coinbase are ridiculously undervalued.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$10T market cap? Will we ever see it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn&amp;#39;t matter. Hug people you care about. We are all going to die. It does not matter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is a correction even possible under current market conditions?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Genuine question. Is a broad, cross-index correction possible given the current
market conditions? I honestly think not. I think due to QE and Fed bolstering
there is so much cash sloshing around looking for a home that anything with an
even remote prospect of return is instantly invested in.

Hear…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvgi4h/is_a_correction_even_possible_under_current/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvgi4h/is_a_correction_even_possible_under_current/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 02:51:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Genuine question. Is a broad, cross-index correction possible given the current market conditions? I honestly think not. I think due to QE and Fed bolstering there is so much cash sloshing around looking for a home that anything with an even remote prospect of return is instantly invested in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hear me out. I really think this is a new paradigm, not as in oh market goes up forever and this time is different, and more as in this amount of QE and stimulus mixed with bare bones low interest rate has never been achieved before. We have never had a market with the combination of those 2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here&amp;#39;s how I see things going forward:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dumb money is here to stay. There&amp;#39;s just too damn much of it flooding the market looking for a home. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Retail investor sentiment has changed. No one is risk-adverse on a broad scale anymore. Investors are willing to hold through dips and plunge more cash into them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interest rates are rock bottom, and there&amp;#39;s the possibility they stay that way or go negative due to debt implications if they&amp;#39;re raised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s going to change? Is retail suddenly going to become risk adverse? Is the amount of capital flooding the system going to be reigned in? Are interest rates going to drastically rise, if at all?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t think so. I quite literally think that given market conditions and sentiment a correction is not even possible. Do all the remind me&amp;#39;s you want. The market is unable to correct.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The only reason Tesla is worth anything is because of the SUPER CHARGER NETWORK, which Rivian and Lucid DO NOT HAVE.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I test drove a Tesla model 3 two years ago as a joke and ended up buying one
that same day. They're actually really cool cars and fast as shit... but you
know why I, and other normal people with money (aka not you broke retards with
$500 in your RH accounts) buy them?

THE SUPER CHARGER NETWORK.…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvelvp/the_only_reason_tesla_is_worth_anything_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvelvp/the_only_reason_tesla_is_worth_anything_is/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 02:29:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I test drove a Tesla model 3 two years ago as a joke and ended up buying one that same day. They&amp;#39;re actually really cool cars and fast as shit... but you know why I, and other normal people with money (aka not you broke retards with $500 in your RH accounts) buy them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE SUPER CHARGER NETWORK. This is basically a system of electric gas stations that charge your car in 30-40 minutes, and allows you to drive ANYWHERE in America and Canada. You can drive from San Diego to NYC with this network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know what you can&amp;#39;t do with a Rivian or Lucid? Drive anywhere you don&amp;#39;t normally drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you try to charge your car at a charge port or whatever, it&amp;#39;ll take you 8 hours for a full charge. The only reason Tesla is worth anything is because of their phenomenal super charger network. How the fuck are lucid and rivian going to compete with that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;edit: looks like the truth has triggered some fuckin’ noobs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen warns that requirement in Biden's infrastructure bill could hasten U.S. default on debt]]></title><description><![CDATA[> Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen warned congressional leadership Tuesday that
> the federal government could default on its debt next month if they don’t take
> action to raise the debt ceiling.
> 
> In a letter to top lawmakers, Ms. Yellen projected that after Dec. 15, there
> are scenarios in…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvlndx/treasury_secretary_janet_yellen_warns_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvlndx/treasury_secretary_janet_yellen_warns_that/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 02:29:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen warned congressional leadership Tuesday that the federal government could default on its debt next month if they don’t take action to raise the debt ceiling.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a letter to top lawmakers, Ms. Yellen projected that after Dec. 15, there are scenarios in which the Treasury could have “insufficient resources to continue to finance the operation of the U.S. government.”  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ms. Yellen added that she has “a high degree of confidence” in the Treasury’s ability to make debt payments through Dec. 15. That’s two weeks longer than her initial forecast of Dec. 3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More money coming in? More pump?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anybody else hate the new Vanguard app?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I hate apps that try to be ultra sleek and minimalist. I don't know where
anything is, and it feels like features have been taken away.]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvj98f/anybody_else_hate_the_new_vanguard_app/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvj98f/anybody_else_hate_the_new_vanguard_app/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 01:53:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I hate apps that try to be ultra sleek and minimalist. I don&amp;#39;t know where anything is, and it feels like features have been taken away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cloudflare mitigated nearly 2 Tbps DDoS launched from 15,000 devices]]></title><description><![CDATA["Cloudflare says it mitigated a distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack that
peaked at just under 2 Tbps of bandwidth thanks to its use of approximately
15,000 compromised devices.

The company says this was the largest DDoS attack it had witnessed to date. It
was said to have used a mix of…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvhk2a/cloudflare_mitigated_nearly_2_tbps_ddos_launched/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvhk2a/cloudflare_mitigated_nearly_2_tbps_ddos_launched/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:51:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Cloudflare says it mitigated a distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack that peaked at just under 2 Tbps of bandwidth thanks to its use of approximately 15,000 compromised devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company says this was the largest DDoS attack it had witnessed to date. It was said to have used a mix of Mirai-infected Internet of Things devices, which are commonly used to launch massive DDoS attacks, as well as unpatched instances of the GitLab developer tool.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source, PCMag: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pcmag.com/news/cloudflare-mitigates-nearly-2-tbps-ddos-attack&quot;&gt;https://www.pcmag.com/news/cloudflare-mitigates-nearly-2-tbps-ddos-attack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Here is a Market Recap for today Tuesday, Nov 16, 2021. Please enjoy!]]></title><description><![CDATA[PsychoMarket Recap - Tuesday, November 16, 2021

Stocks gained today, with market participants releasing a sigh of relief as new
economic data showed consumer demand remains strong despite ongoing supply-chain
disruptions and labor shortages. Moreover, major retailers like Walmart (WMT),
Target…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjo3j/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_tuesday_nov_16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjo3j/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_tuesday_nov_16/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:51:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Tuesday, November 16, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks gained today, with market participants releasing a sigh of relief as new economic data showed consumer demand remains strong despite ongoing supply-chain disruptions and labor shortages. Moreover, major retailers like Walmart (WMT), Target (TGT), Lowe’s (LOW), and Home Depot (HD) are set to release quarterly earnings this week, giving us more information into the state of consumer spending in the US. As a reminder, consumer spending accounts for roughly 70% of US GDP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Department of Commerce released their monthly Retail Sales Report, which showed better than expected consumer spending trends as the holiday season, by far the busiest in the year, continues to play out. Here are the numbers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retail Sales: 1.7% increase vs 1.4% expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core Retail Sales: +1.6%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manufacturing Production: +1.2%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The solid report suggests that high inflation is not dampening consumer spending. Rising household wealth, thanks to a strong stock market, house prices, and rising wages appear to be cushioning consumers against the highest annual pace of inflation in roughly thirty years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matthew Shay, President of the National Retail Federation, said of the report, “Today’s numbers show that consumers are getting a jump on their holiday shopping. We continue to urge consumers to shop early and shop safely, and we fully expect this holiday season to be one for the record books”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, two of the largest retailers in the US, Walmart (WMT) and Home Depot (HD), reported earnings today, with both companies demolishing earnings (though WMT stock did not react positively). Here are the numbers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Walmart (WMT)&lt;/strong&gt; 

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue: $140.53 billion vs $135.60 billion expected &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earnings per Share (EPS): $1.45 vs $1.40 expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sames Store Sales: +9.2% vs +6.9% expected &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;eCommerce Sales: +8% vs +1.9% expected &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Home Depot (HD)&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue: $36.82 billion vs $35.01 billion expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earnings per Share (EPS): $3.92 vs $3.40 expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Same Store Sales: +6.1% vs 1.9% expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These reports came at the tail end of what has already been an exceptionally strong earnings season. As of Friday, 92% of S&amp;amp;P 500 companies had reported actual results, and of these, 81% of them had reported better-than-expected earnings results, according to FactSet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_111221.pdf&quot;&gt;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_111221.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Somehow, someway, shares of Rivian (RIVN) keep rising after its blockbuster IPO, with the company now being the third largest auto manufacturer by market cap at roughly $150 billion despite barely completing any deliveries. This is, by far, the craziest valuation I’ve ever seen. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Commerce Department reported Tuesday that import prices rose 1.2% on a monthly basis in October, coming in well above the 0.4% rise for September. This was also above the 1.0% increase consensus economists expected for October, according to Bloomberg data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Qualcomm (QCOM) are on fire after the company projected that its chipset business will average “midteens” revenue growth through its fiscal year 2024. That’s well above the 8% average contemplated by Wall Street’s current estimates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Netflix (NFLX) is set to release the highly anticipated sequel to Tiger King tomorrow. It seems like Netflix has been on an amazing roll as of late and now has a higher market cap than Disney (DIS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lucid Motors (LCID) has now overtaken Ford Motors (F) in market cap&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple (AAPL) is reportedly working to make its own in-house modem chip that allows wireless connection for iPhones by 2023. Qualcomm (QCOM), which currently supplies modem chips for all Apple devices, estimates Apple will self-supply 80% of modem chips by 2023. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current stock price was written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance Auto Parts (AAP) with four target raises. Stock currently around $235

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Citigroup from $282 to $290 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wedbush from $250 to $270 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Credit Suisse from $250 to $255 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bank of America from $256 to $282 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Datadog (DDOG) target raised by Jefferies Financial from $210 to $230 at Buy. Stock currently around $194&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lucid Motors (LCID) price target raised by Citigroup from $28 to $57 at Buy. Stock currently around $57 after gapping up 25%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lattice Semiconductor (LSCC) target raised by Benchmark from $81 to $96 at Buy. Stock currently around $85&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NVIDIA (NVDA) target raised by Credit Suisse from $225 to $400 at Outperform. Stock currently around $300.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tyson Foods (TSN) with a host of target raises. Average price target $95 at Buy. Stock currently aroun d$84&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UnitedHealth Group (UNH) target raised by Deutsche Bank from $421 to $477 at Buy. Stock currently around $450&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Workday (WDAY) target raised by Jefferies Financial from $320 to $350 at Buy. Stock currently around $299&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Turn your wounds into wisdom.” — Oprah Winfrey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[It's part of the grind]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvfd4d/its_part_of_the_grind/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvfd4d/its_part_of_the_grind/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 23:53:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Have we entered a new Era where prolonged stock market crashes are a thing of the past?]]></title><description><![CDATA[It seems like the Powell put has worked and it only took the stock market 3
months to recover after the crash in March of 2020. Has the fed managed to
remove all real risk from the market? If so will this be the status quo for the
next few decades?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvcaii/have_we_entered_a_new_era_where_prolonged_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvcaii/have_we_entered_a_new_era_where_prolonged_stock/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 23:41:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seems like the Powell put has worked and it only took the stock market 3 months to recover after the crash in March of 2020. Has the fed managed to remove all real risk from the market? If so will this be the status quo for the next few decades?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why is the Fed not raising rates?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I hear a lot of arguments about the fed simply opening the floodgates to please
Wall St and keep the economy rising, but that argument could have been made at
any point in history; yet in the past the fed have acted responsibly.

Surely this reckless inflatory push has something to do with…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvi2d8/why_is_the_fed_not_raising_rates/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvi2d8/why_is_the_fed_not_raising_rates/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 22:35:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I hear a lot of arguments about the fed simply opening the floodgates to please Wall St and keep the economy rising, but that argument could have been made at any point in history; yet in the past the fed have acted responsibly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Surely this reckless inflatory push has something to do with competition between the US and China/Russia? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether its the fact China will overtake it quicker now or a potential conflict with either one. Could it be an experiment in whether having the “global currency” can allow a country to buy growth without insane amounts of inflation? Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta using facial recognition "Video selfies" for "suspicious accounts".]]></title><description><![CDATA[A look at where Meta is heading as a company.

I've bene having issues on my IG because nearly every day now I am having to
send in a video selfie for "verification". It seems like they want every IG
account totally public and not simply for people who want to browse IG
anonymously.

It directly…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv20ol/meta_using_facial_recognition_video_selfies_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv20ol/meta_using_facial_recognition_video_selfies_for/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 22:18:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A look at where Meta is heading as a company. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve bene having issues on my IG because nearly every day now I am having to send in a video selfie for &amp;quot;verification&amp;quot;. It seems like they want every IG account totally public and not simply for people who want to browse IG anonymously. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It directly says: &amp;quot;The video will never be visible on Instagram and will be deleted within 30 days. This won&amp;#39;t use ice recognition or collect biometric data&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Instagram/comments/qt15br/this_is_just_creepy/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/Instagram/comments/qt15br/this_is_just_creepy/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But given the new &amp;quot;Meta&amp;quot; name so focused on the meta verse, it&amp;#39;s extremely difficult to trust they aren&amp;#39;t using biometric data. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Captchas and &amp;quot;image puzzles&amp;quot; have been used for years to confirm human users and reduce bot activity, and are far less intrusive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The level of privacy is getting insane at this point and I just wonder where this is leading to for Meta. They say the data will be deleted within 30 days.. but I just don&amp;#39;t believe that and they are using it for some future Metaverse data. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I frankly wish this was a bigger news story already, because if they actually got backlash I think they would have to at least respond about it. Very interesting that I suddenly started getting these messages too around the same time Meta was announced as the name.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME net cumulative premiums keep increasing]]></title><description><![CDATA[The net cumulative premiums on GME keep increasing, suggesting that a large
amount of calls is being accumulated. Those setups are perfect for a squeeze, as
these calls, held short by MMs, net to be hedged with long…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvbkwn/gme_net_cumulative_premiums_keep_increasing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvbkwn/gme_net_cumulative_premiums_keep_increasing/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 21:42:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The net cumulative premiums on GME keep increasing, suggesting that a large amount of calls is being accumulated. Those setups are perfect for a squeeze, as these calls, held short by MMs, net to be hedged with long shares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/srnqtpergzz71.png?width=1332&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=05053ef1adf33bb2305b4ed9db3ec184adb9d4c4&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/srnqtpergzz71.png?width=1332&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=05053ef1adf33bb2305b4ed9db3ec184adb9d4c4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the past few weeks, it&amp;#39;s obvious that the calls have been leading, as you can see on the chart below. The green and purple bars at the bottom are not volume bars, they represent premiums. As you can see, recent sessions have been overwhelmingly biased towards the call side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/2urndniugzz71.png?width=1522&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=a9ab1581d51afd41c637615aec3b0c6c47ca8846&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/2urndniugzz71.png?width=1522&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=a9ab1581d51afd41c637615aec3b0c6c47ca8846&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The volume has also been skewed to the call side MTD, with the majority of large trades being for calls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/bhq044dchzz71.jpg?width=1605&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=65bdfebff36b78ac9df8c7a69c2689ad1645989b&quot;&gt;stockgrid.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Activision CEO Bobby Kotick Knew for Years About Sexual-Misconduct Allegations at Videogame Giant]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.wsj.com/articles/activision-videogames-bobby-kotick-sexual-misconduct-allegations-11637075680?st=2l46k41g4se9lc8&amp;amp;reflink=share_mobilewebshare

> Over the years, Mr. Kotick himself has been accused by several women of
> mistreatment both inside and outside the workplace, and in…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qve7ya/activision_ceo_bobby_kotick_knew_for_years_about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qve7ya/activision_ceo_bobby_kotick_knew_for_years_about/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 21:28:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/activision-videogames-bobby-kotick-sexual-misconduct-allegations-11637075680?st=2l46k41g4se9lc8&amp;amp;amp;amp;reflink=share_mobilewebshare&quot;&gt;https://www.wsj.com/articles/activision-videogames-bobby-kotick-sexual-misconduct-allegations-11637075680?st=2l46k41g4se9lc8&amp;amp;amp;amp;reflink=share_mobilewebshare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the years, Mr. Kotick himself has been accused by several women of mistreatment both inside and outside the workplace, and in some instances has worked to settle the complaints quickly and quietly, according to people familiar with the incidents and documents reviewed by the Journal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2006, one of his assistants complained that he had harassed her, including by threatening in a voice mail to have her killed, according to people familiar with the matter. He settled the matter out of court, the people said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: &lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.md/2021.11.16-160822/https://www.wsj.com/articles/activision-videogames-bobby-kotick-sexual-misconduct-allegations-11637075680&quot;&gt;Non-paywall link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I have 1/3 of my portfolio invested in VXUS..]]></title><description><![CDATA[The other 2/3 is in VTI. I just started this adventure about a month and a half
ago, but I can't help but to notice that VTI performs twice as well to date. I
picked up VXUS on advice from a rich acquaintance, but I've read some things
indicating that VXUS has underperformed for many years now. Does…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv7joe/i_have_13_of_my_portfolio_invested_in_vxus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv7joe/i_have_13_of_my_portfolio_invested_in_vxus/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 20:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other 2/3 is in VTI.  I just started this adventure about a month and a half ago, but I can&amp;#39;t help but to notice that VTI performs twice as well to date.  I picked up VXUS on advice from a rich acquaintance, but I&amp;#39;ve read some things indicating that VXUS has underperformed for many years now.  Does anyone have experience with this?  I&amp;#39;m contemplating dumping everything into VTI.  This port is worth around 136k for reference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why does Musk have to sell anything to pay for his taxes?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Don't billionaires like him borrow against the value of their shares? If he
believes in the value of his shares to appreciate then obviously it's cheaper to
get a loan at 1% interest than to sell his shares.

There's no way banks aren't willing to lend money to the world's richest man at
a minimal…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv6u5w/why_does_musk_have_to_sell_anything_to_pay_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv6u5w/why_does_musk_have_to_sell_anything_to_pay_for/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 20:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t billionaires like him borrow against the value of their shares? If he believes in the value of his shares to appreciate then obviously it&amp;#39;s cheaper to get a loan at 1% interest than to sell his shares. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s no way banks aren&amp;#39;t willing to lend money to the world&amp;#39;s richest man at a minimal interest rate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Forbes: Representative Nancy Mace Introduces Bill To End Federal Cannabis Prohibition.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvbyxa/forbes_representative_nancy_mace_introduces_bill/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvbyxa/forbes_representative_nancy_mace_introduces_bill/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:56:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Rivian IPO got me thinking. Clearly the US stock market is overvalued. And yet it keeps going higher.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Out of 698 US businesses worth over $10b, you've got 25% of those selling at 10x
sales. So, if you have only $1b in sales, you're worth $10b.

You'd have to grow sales 20% per year for the next 13 years to get to 1x sales.

Only about 4% of companies worth over $10b have grown sales at, or above,…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvacjm/the_rivian_ipo_got_me_thinking_clearly_the_us/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvacjm/the_rivian_ipo_got_me_thinking_clearly_the_us/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:56:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Out of 698 US businesses worth over $10b, you&amp;#39;ve got 25% of those selling at 10x sales. So, if you have only $1b in sales, you&amp;#39;re worth $10b.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#39;d have to grow sales 20% per year for the next 13 years to get to 1x sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only about 4% of companies worth over $10b have grown sales at, or above, 20% over the last 10 years. This figure drops to 2% if you include all US SEC reporting businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That means, roughly, about 20% of your stock market valuations are insanely overpriced. Rivian being one of them. That paired with the Shiller P/E being close to all-time highs, and inflation spiking well above expectation, signals potential disaster on the horizon. Be careful out there peeps. If the FED starts talking rate hikes, expect a sell-off. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/pressreleases/monetary20211103a.htm&quot;&gt;https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/pressreleases/monetary20211103a.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian ($0 revenue, -$1.6 billion net income) now has a higher market cap than Starbucks ($29 billion revenue, $4.2 billion net income) and Target ($100 billion revenue, $6.3 billion net income). 

$RIVN $SBUX $TGT

Data via @ycharts https://t.co/hv4gEyxqDt]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460622351582773250</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460622351582773250</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:43:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is your experience with Bernstein?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I just got off the phone with my wife's family's...I don't know what to call
them...Wealth management people? Bernstein. Sounds like they're a huge firm with
high minimums for clients, and the only reason they're talking to me is because
of who my father in law is. I'm wondering whether there's an…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvc66l/what_is_your_experience_with_bernstein/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvc66l/what_is_your_experience_with_bernstein/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:18:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just got off the phone with my wife&amp;#39;s family&amp;#39;s...I don&amp;#39;t know what to call them...Wealth management people? Bernstein. Sounds like they&amp;#39;re a huge firm with high minimums for clients, and the only reason they&amp;#39;re talking to me is because of who my father in law is. I&amp;#39;m wondering whether there&amp;#39;s an advantage to going with a group like this and what sort of benefit I&amp;#39;d see over SPY all the way. They told me in their sales pitch they determine asset allocation and they have great research blah blah etc, then have what sound like their own mini funds and at a higher level REITs available only to high net worth clients. No crypto exposure, no nft&amp;#39;s. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This all seems extremely old school and outdated. Am I missing something? They have my wife 30% bonds in her early 30&amp;#39;s, which seems...short sighted. They couldn&amp;#39;t give me a straight answer on how they do compared with a passive index fund&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can someone please explain to me why Berkshire still has a larger market cap than Rivian?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460668037032562703</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460668037032562703</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 18:45:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Please tell me to ignore all the noise and stay the course.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I want to throw money into Tesla, crypto, or some of the other hot stocks all my
friends are raving about. Please talk me out of this, and tell me to stay the
course and just invest in VTI instead. Thank you for your service.]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvb5wx/please_tell_me_to_ignore_all_the_noise_and_stay/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvb5wx/please_tell_me_to_ignore_all_the_noise_and_stay/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 18:25:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to throw money into Tesla, crypto, or some of the other hot stocks all my friends are raving about. Please talk me out of this, and tell me to stay the course and just invest in VTI instead. Thank you for your service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Home Depot earnings top estimates fueled by 9.8% jump in sales as consumers fix up homes]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/16/home-depot-hd-q3-2021-earnings.html

Earnings per share: $3.92 vs. $3.40 expected

Revenue: $36.82 billion vs. $35.01 billion expected

Home Depot topped Wall Street’s estimates for its third-quarter earnings and
revenue.

Same-store sales climbed 6.1% in the quarter,…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv7hil/home_depot_earnings_top_estimates_fueled_by_98/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv7hil/home_depot_earnings_top_estimates_fueled_by_98/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 17:59:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/16/home-depot-hd-q3-2021-earnings.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/16/home-depot-hd-q3-2021-earnings.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earnings per share: $3.92 vs. $3.40 expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revenue: $36.82 billion vs. $35.01 billion expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Home Depot topped Wall Street’s estimates for its third-quarter earnings and revenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Same-store sales climbed 6.1% in the quarter, beating StreetAccount estimates of 2.2%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consumers were spending more when they visited, raising the average ticket by 12.9% to $82.38.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Home Depot is one of the non tech stock that keep outperform. This is one of the portfolio must have stock due to the loyalty of the customers. Every time you visit there you will see a never ending long line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Big personal milestone reached today! What next?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have officially reached my personal savings goal of 50k cash. I'm 29 and have
sacrificed a lot to meet this goal, it's taken me almost a decade to get here.

Salary is 60k before taxes and deductions.

20k left on student loans, payments start up again Jan 2022.

401(a) at 16,230 - Vanguard Target…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvbw93/big_personal_milestone_reached_today_what_next/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvbw93/big_personal_milestone_reached_today_what_next/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 17:47:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have officially reached my personal savings goal of 50k cash. I&amp;#39;m 29 and have sacrificed a lot to meet this goal, it&amp;#39;s taken me almost a decade to get here. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salary is 60k before taxes and deductions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;20k left on student loans, payments start up again Jan 2022. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;401(a) at 16,230 - Vanguard Target Retire 2055 11.1% Vanguard Target Retire 2060 88.9%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;457(b) at 8,340 - Vanguard Target Retire 2055 11.1% Vanguard Target Retire 2060 88.9%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: I did not select these Target funds or allocations. It was selected automatically through my employers retirement servicer.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taxable Ally brokerage account worth: $642.52. Crypto account worth about: $600 ($400 btc). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personal note: my family is poor/working class so I pay the lion&amp;#39;s share of my family&amp;#39;s bills (mom and brother). Mom is overcoming cancer and will likely be out of work till 2022, had surgery to remove cancer and will be going through radiation sessions soon (hopefully no chemo). Fortunately (or unfortunately) she makes so little money that she&amp;#39;s always qualified for medicaid and all her treatments have been covered. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;#39;t crunched the numbers but I think all the bills (personal, communal, her personal) will likely run between 4-5k till February 2022... fingers crossed she can get back to work sooner. Brother makes about 30-35k but does not routinely contribute to communal bills, mom doesn&amp;#39;t force him and that&amp;#39;s just the way it is, it&amp;#39;s fruitless to argue about it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any advice on what my next move should be?  I feel like I stalk this sub enough to know the basics: open a Roth and split funds between an US index, international index, and bond right? I guess I need that echo chamber to confirm. I&amp;#39;m very much a serial saver. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to make this money work in my favor. Growing up in poverty I&amp;#39;ve gained a serious emergency mindset. I&amp;#39;m obsessed with preparing for the worst because bad news is the only consant. That&amp;#39;s how my family existed; constantly stressed about money, the next bill, and next big financial disaster etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry for the long post, ANY advice is GREATLY appreciated!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[US Retail Sales hit another all-time high while Consumer Sentiment is at its lowest level in 10 years.

Watch what they do, not what they say. https://t.co/x2Md4zFAj0]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460632395086974981</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460632395086974981</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:54:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian Is The Modern Day Pets.con]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rvian has obtained legendary status among the Pets.com of the world with its
ability to command a market cap of 130B+ on virtually 0 sales. Even banking
Rivian will be able to deliver on all of its pre-orders (which are never
guaranteed) there are so many obstacles and risks to their success; they…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qv3tyt/rivian_is_the_modern_day_petscon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qv3tyt/rivian_is_the_modern_day_petscon/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:30:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rvian has obtained legendary status among the Pets.com of the world with its ability to command a market cap of 130B+ on virtually 0 sales. Even banking Rivian will be able to deliver on all of its pre-orders (which are never guaranteed) there are so many obstacles and risks to their success; they should not command a massive multiple. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently their biggest competitor Tesla is trading at 25x revenue and has traded from 15-30x revenue over the last 1-2 years. Today Rivian is trading at 150–200–even 250x Price to Revenue. While comparing Tesla ( a well known, huge company with multiple production plants, battery tech, great engineers, market dominance,  Elon, a huge following, massive assets, full AI self driving and a proven production / delivery method) is like comparing apples to apes, let do it. Lets use Price to Revenue as the model and compare Rivian revenue to Tesla revenue. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be fair we should take the anticipated cars being made this year (Rivian says they hope 1k)* average cost of each car (67.5k base + extras = ~75k lets say) = 75mm in sales. To make it a better comparison lets make this a yearly number. Also lets make a great case for Rivian with great production efficiently, no problems, continued refinement, and growth from current cars per day(CPD) (current pace is ~3 CPD or ~320 by EOY but they hope to deliver 1k cars by EOY 2021 which is goal of 1k/108 days since 9/14/21 production start = CPD of 9.25) and lets double it next year. That would give us 9.25 x 2 x 365 x 75k = 506mm per year in revenue and make today’s valuation (at 131B) 258x FY 2022 revenue only after assuming a myriad of extremely positive assumptions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For fun lets triple 9.25 and even then at 760mm in revenue that is 172x FY2022 revenue. Said another way, in order for Rivian to have the same Price/Revenue as Tesla’s average of 22 they would have to produce 5.95Billion in revenue or 79.4k cars per year or ~218 CPD aka 72x their current CPD rate or 23.5x their 2021 target CPD rate. So lets reverse engineer that to find a reasonable stock price — FY2022 best case sales 760m*30 (highest Tesla P/R)=22.8B or ~21$ per share which is still ~8x what Amazon paid about a year ago. Anyone else smell this shitty bubble and going to short this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Family member is delusional about crypto. How can I wake him up?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello all, I have a family member who is approaching his 40’s and he is
hell-bent on throwing every dollar he has into Ethereum. He is one of those
people who drinks too much, is too loud, and is generally terrible with money. I
intern in the financial industry, in actual trading, but he just seems…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv6ml5/family_member_is_delusional_about_crypto_how_can/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv6ml5/family_member_is_delusional_about_crypto_how_can/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:57:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello all, I have a family member who is approaching his 40’s and he is hell-bent on throwing every dollar he has into Ethereum. He is one of those people who drinks too much, is too loud, and is generally terrible with money. I intern in the financial industry, in actual trading, but he just seems to ignore me completely. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He has this idea that he missed out on getting rich through bitcoin, so he thinks buying Ethereum at all time highs is equivalent to buying bitcoin at 4K. He’s not understanding that price means nothing and market cap is a more relevant indicator of your timing. Ethereum already has an enormous market cap and the upside is limited. He is also one of those who don’t understand that there is no thing as getting rich quick. I’ve tried telling him about just holding a diversified portfolio and making monthly/yearly contributions but of course it falls on deaf ears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m worried that if/when we see another 50% drop overnight, he’s going to be wiped out. He has kids who will feel it too.  And i get it, a lot of Americans are feeling insecure about retirement and they feel like they must make last ditch efforts to make up for years of poor finances. But this is reality, I know for certain that this guy is going to get burned chasing the next big thing. He got lucky and bought GME, which he then blew the proceeds on luxury rentals and alcohol. Now I think he’a chasing that high again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do I not feel responsible? How do I wake him up? Should I not care?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How should one value a SPAC like Gores Guggenheim (Polestar SPAC)?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi there.

Polestar, an EV company that sells electric cars in Europe, wants to go public
through a SPAC merger with Gores Guggenheim.

Polestar itself is, in my opinion, definitely worth more than 1.5 Billion
dollars in Market Cap if you compare it to other EV stocks, like Lucid, Rivian
or…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qunnan/how_should_one_value_a_spac_like_gores_guggenheim/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qunnan/how_should_one_value_a_spac_like_gores_guggenheim/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:57:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Polestar, an EV company that sells electric cars in Europe, wants to go public through a SPAC merger with Gores Guggenheim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Polestar  itself is, in my opinion, definitely worth more than 1.5 Billion  dollars in Market Cap if you compare it to other EV stocks, like Lucid,  Rivian or Fisker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Gores  Guggenheim has a market cap of only 1.5 Billion dollars. Surely, I&amp;#39;m  missing something here? I&amp;#39;m quite certain that I&amp;#39;m missing something. If  the merger goes through, what happens to the market cap and stock price  of Gores Guggenheim?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will the MC  just go to a few billion while the stock price stays the same? Will the  stock disappear? I really don&amp;#39;t know how this works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why is CRSP falling so much? CRISPR Therapeutics]]></title><description><![CDATA[Normally, with a company like this, I'd expect them to be losing money like
crazy, but their PE is 16.17. Their EPS is 5.26. They have an incredibly bright
future like 3 or 4 years from now. Why is the stock tanking so hard? Is Yahoo
Finance's information incorrect on the PE and EPS? The stocks low…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quw1p1/why_is_crsp_falling_so_much_crispr_therapeutics/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quw1p1/why_is_crsp_falling_so_much_crispr_therapeutics/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:57:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Normally, with a company like this, I&amp;#39;d expect them to be losing money like crazy, but their PE is 16.17. Their EPS is 5.26. They have an incredibly bright future like 3 or 4 years from now. Why is the stock tanking so hard? Is Yahoo Finance&amp;#39;s information incorrect on the PE and EPS? The stocks low today was $84.31. It&amp;#39;s starting to look juicy, but man, who knows...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian's market cap just passed Citigroup's.

Yes, that Citigroup: 
Founded in 1812
200 million customer accounts
4,600 branches
World's largest credit card issuer
204,000 employees
$72 billion in revenue
$23 billion net income
$2.3 trillion in total assets

$RIVN $C https://t.co/7X3zafMB3I]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460618711707140109</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460618711707140109</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:45:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sportradar reports third-quarter earnings (Nov 17th)]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://sportshandle.com/on-tap-111521/


WEDNESDAY, NOVEMBER 17

Sportradar, the Switzerland-based sports betting data provider, will report
quarterly earnings for the first time since completing its IPO in September.
Sportradar earned $478 million in 2020, with $18 million in net income. Over…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv6q19/sportradar_reports_thirdquarter_earnings_nov_17th/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv6q19/sportradar_reports_thirdquarter_earnings_nov_17th/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:27:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sportshandle.com/on-tap-111521/&quot;&gt;https://sportshandle.com/on-tap-111521/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Wednesday, November 17&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sportradar, the Switzerland-based sports betting data provider, will report quarterly earnings for the first time since completing its IPO in September. Sportradar earned $478 million in 2020, with $18 million in net income. Over the first half of 2021, Sportradar &lt;a href=&quot;https://frontofficesports.com/sportradar-looks-to-acquire-tech-companies-after-ipo/&quot;&gt;increased revenue 42%&lt;/a&gt; on a year-over-year basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Sportradar went public in September, the company indicated that it plans to pursue acquisitions of tech and artificial intelligence companies as a way of furthering its growth plans. Earlier this month, Sportradar secured an exclusive betting data rights agreement with UEFA’s portfolio of competitions, including the UEFA European Championships in soccer. Also during the quarter, Michael Jordan assumed an advisory role with Sportradar’s board while increasing his &lt;a href=&quot;https://investors.sportradar.com/news-releases/news-release-details/michael-jordan-assumes-advisory-role-sportradar&quot;&gt;investment in the company&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Preview already posted in the subreddit by &lt;a href=&quot;/u/deepdivestocks&quot;&gt;u/deepdivestocks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Sportradar/comments/qv3ba3/srad_earnings_released_on_17th_november/&quot;&gt;$SRAD Earnings Released on 17th November&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;View: $SRAD has been on a small uptick the last few weeks after reaching a low. With gambling stocks down across the board, could this be the exception?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any views on EPS and revenue targets?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WHY ON EARTH is RIVIAN still going up?!]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know everyone is hoping it's the next tesla and is FOMOing on every EV, but a
company that barely made ANY deliveries , having the 3rd highest market cap in
the car industry (140B+) , is plain ridiculous for me... And I don't care about
the Amazon rumors.]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv7y8j/why_on_earth_is_rivian_still_going_up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv7y8j/why_on_earth_is_rivian_still_going_up/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:27:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know everyone is hoping it&amp;#39;s the next tesla and is FOMOing on every EV, but a company that barely made ANY deliveries , having the 3rd highest market cap in the car industry (140B+) , is plain ridiculous for me... And I don&amp;#39;t care about the Amazon rumors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[JPMorgan says Tesla owes the bank $162 million]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quy6j8/jpmorgan_says_tesla_owes_the_bank_162_million/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quy6j8/jpmorgan_says_tesla_owes_the_bank_162_million/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 14:47:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Timeline of predicting a market crash (by Ron Paul)]]></title><description><![CDATA[2014 - The market has to correct, and who's going to call it a crash until it
happens? We're in for a major correction, I think. I think we're very, very
vulnerable
[http://www.cnbc.com/2014/07/29/ron-paul-stocks-are-in-a-bubble-and-will-crash.html]

2015 - There's a lot of instability still out…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv79af/timeline_of_predicting_a_market_crash_by_ron_paul/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv79af/timeline_of_predicting_a_market_crash_by_ron_paul/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 14:47:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnbc.com/2014/07/29/ron-paul-stocks-are-in-a-bubble-and-will-crash.html&quot;&gt;2014 -  The market has to correct, and who&amp;#39;s going to call it a crash until it  happens? We&amp;#39;re in for a major correction, I think. I think we&amp;#39;re very,  very vulnerable&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnbc.com/2015/06/19/ron-paul-stock-market-day-of-reckoning-is-near.html&quot;&gt;2015 -  There&amp;#39;s a lot of instability still out there, and this hasn&amp;#39;t been  corrected yet. I don&amp;#39;t think it&amp;#39;s going to correct easily, I don&amp;#39;t think  it&amp;#39;s going to be just a correction.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnbc.com/2017/07/02/ron-paul-not-a-shock-if-stocks-fall-25-percent-and-gold-soars-50-percent-by-oct.html&quot;&gt;2017 -  &amp;quot;If our markets are down 25 percent and gold is up 50 percent it wouldn&amp;#39;t be a total shock to me&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/14/ron-paul-market-meltdown-could-spark-depression-like-conditions.html&quot;&gt;2018 -  A 50% correction will spark depression-like conditions that may be ‘worse than 1929’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/the-dollar-is-going-to-self-destruct-talking-bitcoin-with-ron-paul&quot;&gt;2019 - The Dollar is going to self destruct&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_gbZlnyuQ6g&quot;&gt;2020 - The end result is an overinflated stock market that could see a “violent correction”, as well as a monetary system on the brink of collapse. I happen to believe it’s the biggest financial bubble in the history of monetary policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VCj-m08qPd4&quot;&gt;On the next economic crash in 2021&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[HSA accounts, what are your thoughts?]]></title><description><![CDATA[So, I was trying to find out peoples thoughts on HSA accounts. I read an article
that said it is a great vehicle to put money into so that in the future when you
are elderly you can pay for medical expenses.

It also can lower your taxable income.

My only issue with this, is that I am not young…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qv5mv6/hsa_accounts_what_are_your_thoughts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qv5mv6/hsa_accounts_what_are_your_thoughts/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 14:35:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, I was trying to find out peoples thoughts on HSA accounts.  I read an article that said it is a great vehicle to put money into so that in the future when you are elderly you can pay for medical expenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also can lower your taxable income.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My only issue with this, is that I am not young anymore and have started having health problems.  A high deductible plan would suck out the cash from me.  I am guessing this is a good option for people in their early 20s since they are probably less likely to have health problems.  Not sure if the Boglehead community has thoughts on this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Who else is thinking of shorting Rivian?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Not going to lie, I’ve never even thought of shorting a company, but this is
insane. Up to $157 in pre market with no reason to be valued at $137 billion.
For reference, Tesla, most famous for being overvalued and the stock still goes
up is trading at only 7.3x the valuation of RIVN. Yet RIVN has 0…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv44ti/who_else_is_thinking_of_shorting_rivian/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv44ti/who_else_is_thinking_of_shorting_rivian/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 13:31:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not going to lie, I’ve never even thought of shorting a company, but this is insane. Up to $157 in pre market with no reason to be valued at $137 billion. 
For reference, Tesla, most famous for being overvalued and the stock still goes up is trading at only 7.3x the valuation of RIVN. Yet RIVN has 0 sales, 0 revenue, 0 profit. 
This thing is going to fall hard. Just a matter of how long these buyers can hold the price this high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The surge in US inflation expectations continues unabated, rising to their highest levels ever recorded (3.17% for 5-year breakevens). https://t.co/faPSer3Q4F]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460406986785411073</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460406986785411073</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 11:44:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[20M unemployed - I have been given 2000 dollars to invest by my parents, are these good choices I am making..?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I just opened an account with fidelity and about to buy these index funds/bonds,
but I just want some verification from you people whether if these are my best
options.

 * domestic stocks: FSKAX (total market - 0.015%)

 * international stocks: FSPSX (international - 0.035%)

 * emerging markets:…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qupyu7/20m_unemployed_i_have_been_given_2000_dollars_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qupyu7/20m_unemployed_i_have_been_given_2000_dollars_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 09:57:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just opened an account with fidelity and about to buy these index funds/bonds, but I just want some verification from you people whether if these are my best options.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;domestic stocks:            FSKAX (total market - 0.015%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;international stocks:     FSPSX (international - 0.035%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;emerging markets:         FPADX (emerging markets - 0.075%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. treasury bonds:      FUAMX (treasury bonds - 0.03%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. TIPS:                    FIPDX (inflation protected bonds - 0.05%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;real estate:                   FSRNX (real estate index fund - 0.07%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;and this will be the % split I am doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;30% domestic equity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% international equity &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;10% emerging market equity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% U.S. Treasury bonds&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% TIPS (inflation protected bonds)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% Real estate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Not sure what Papa Elon's endgame is but he's been on some supervillain vibes as of late]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quyhqs/not_sure_what_papa_elons_endgame_is_but_hes_been/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quyhqs/not_sure_what_papa_elons_endgame_is_but_hes_been/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 08:35:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tilray To the Moon DD inside.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Republican Nancy Mace is presenting her Marijuana bill conference today at
2:00pm EDT at Capitol Hill.
https://twitter.com/RepNancyMace/status/1459565180585656325?s=20

Germany's new coalition government in talks of legalizing Marijuana. Tilray
sells medical marijuana already in Germany and has…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qukdev/tilray_to_the_moon_dd_inside/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qukdev/tilray_to_the_moon_dd_inside/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 08:10:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican Nancy Mace is presenting her Marijuana bill conference today at 2:00pm EDT at Capitol Hill.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/RepNancyMace/status/1459565180585656325?s=20&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/RepNancyMace/status/1459565180585656325?s=20&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Germany&amp;#39;s new coalition government in talks of legalizing Marijuana. Tilray sells medical marijuana already in Germany and has license. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-10/germany-s-next-coalition-close-to-deal-on-legalizing-cannabis&quot;&gt;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-10/germany-s-next-coalition-close-to-deal-on-legalizing-cannabis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s go my precious little Diamond hands. Tilray currently up over 6%. This is not financial Advice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I’m 25 and this is my Roth. What can I do better here?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qungve/im_25_and_this_is_my_roth_what_can_i_do_better/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qungve/im_25_and_this_is_my_roth_what_can_i_do_better/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 07:50:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is the VTSAX equivalent at Fidelity?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qulqnk/what_is_the_vtsax_equivalent_at_fidelity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qulqnk/what_is_the_vtsax_equivalent_at_fidelity/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 06:49:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley is out with its 2022 market outlook, and it sees a decline]]></title><description><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley sees a more challenging year ahead for U.S. equities against a
backdrop of higher interest rates, slowing growth and supply chain disruptions.

The Wall Street firm recently set its S&P 500 target for next year at 4,400,
implying a 5% decline from current levels. The negative…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quo6jl/morgan_stanley_is_out_with_its_2022_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quo6jl/morgan_stanley_is_out_with_its_2022_market/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 05:22:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morgan Stanley sees a more challenging year ahead for U.S. equities against a backdrop of higher interest rates, slowing growth and supply chain disruptions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Wall Street firm recently set its S&amp;amp;P 500 target for next year at 4,400, implying a 5% decline from current levels. The negative projection followed a blockbuster year for stocks that has seen the &lt;a href=&quot;https://link.cnbc.com/click/25708849.282877/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuY25iYy5jb20vcXVvdGVzLy5TUFg_X19zb3VyY2U9bmV3c2xldHRlciU3Q21hcmtldGluZw/5ba060792ddf9c38dd023063Bd6668e6e&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/a&gt; rallying 25% and raking in more than 60 record highs despite fears of persistent inflation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Historically it's way better to invest at market close than at market open, most gains happen overnight]]></title><description><![CDATA[There is an interesting article back from 2018 that says

> If you had bought the SPY at the last second of trading on each business day
> since 1993 and sold at the market open the next day — capturing all of the net
> after-hour gains — your cumulative price gain would be 571%
> 
> On the other…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quxd2t/historically_its_way_better_to_invest_at_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quxd2t/historically_its_way_better_to_invest_at_market/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 04:11:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is an interesting article back from 2018 that says&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you had bought the SPY at the last second of trading on each business day since 1993 and sold at the market open the next day — capturing all of the net after-hour gains — your cumulative price gain would be 571%  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, if you had done the reverse, buying the ETF at the first second of regular trading every morning at 9:30 a.m. and selling at the 4 p.m. close, you would be down 4.4%&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have backtested the same for 2020 and 2021, see the results below. Every day I was buying/selling just 1 share of $SPY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Buy at open, sell at close&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Buy at close, sell at open&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2020&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-$4.88&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$45.42&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2021&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-$38.05&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$53.92&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: all calculations made using BreakingEquity&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>