<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 22:10:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Activision CEO Bobby Kotick Knew for Years About Sexual-Misconduct Allegations at Videogame Giant]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.wsj.com/articles/activision-videogames-bobby-kotick-sexual-misconduct-allegations-11637075680?st=2l46k41g4se9lc8&amp;amp;reflink=share_mobilewebshare

> Over the years, Mr. Kotick himself has been accused by several women of
> mistreatment both inside and outside the workplace, and in…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qve7ya/activision_ceo_bobby_kotick_knew_for_years_about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qve7ya/activision_ceo_bobby_kotick_knew_for_years_about/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 21:28:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/activision-videogames-bobby-kotick-sexual-misconduct-allegations-11637075680?st=2l46k41g4se9lc8&amp;amp;amp;amp;reflink=share_mobilewebshare&quot;&gt;https://www.wsj.com/articles/activision-videogames-bobby-kotick-sexual-misconduct-allegations-11637075680?st=2l46k41g4se9lc8&amp;amp;amp;amp;reflink=share_mobilewebshare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the years, Mr. Kotick himself has been accused by several women of mistreatment both inside and outside the workplace, and in some instances has worked to settle the complaints quickly and quietly, according to people familiar with the incidents and documents reviewed by the Journal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2006, one of his assistants complained that he had harassed her, including by threatening in a voice mail to have her killed, according to people familiar with the matter. He settled the matter out of court, the people said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: &lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.md/2021.11.16-160822/https://www.wsj.com/articles/activision-videogames-bobby-kotick-sexual-misconduct-allegations-11637075680&quot;&gt;Non-paywall link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I have 1/3 of my portfolio invested in VXUS..]]></title><description><![CDATA[The other 2/3 is in VTI. I just started this adventure about a month and a half
ago, but I can't help but to notice that VTI performs twice as well to date. I
picked up VXUS on advice from a rich acquaintance, but I've read some things
indicating that VXUS has underperformed for many years now. Does…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv7joe/i_have_13_of_my_portfolio_invested_in_vxus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv7joe/i_have_13_of_my_portfolio_invested_in_vxus/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 20:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other 2/3 is in VTI.  I just started this adventure about a month and a half ago, but I can&amp;#39;t help but to notice that VTI performs twice as well to date.  I picked up VXUS on advice from a rich acquaintance, but I&amp;#39;ve read some things indicating that VXUS has underperformed for many years now.  Does anyone have experience with this?  I&amp;#39;m contemplating dumping everything into VTI.  This port is worth around 136k for reference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why does Musk have to sell anything to pay for his taxes?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Don't billionaires like him borrow against the value of their shares? If he
believes in the value of his shares to appreciate then obviously it's cheaper to
get a loan at 1% interest than to sell his shares.

There's no way banks aren't willing to lend money to the world's richest man at
a minimal…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv6u5w/why_does_musk_have_to_sell_anything_to_pay_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv6u5w/why_does_musk_have_to_sell_anything_to_pay_for/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 20:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t billionaires like him borrow against the value of their shares? If he believes in the value of his shares to appreciate then obviously it&amp;#39;s cheaper to get a loan at 1% interest than to sell his shares. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s no way banks aren&amp;#39;t willing to lend money to the world&amp;#39;s richest man at a minimal interest rate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Forbes: Representative Nancy Mace Introduces Bill To End Federal Cannabis Prohibition.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvbyxa/forbes_representative_nancy_mace_introduces_bill/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvbyxa/forbes_representative_nancy_mace_introduces_bill/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:56:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Rivian IPO got me thinking. Clearly the US stock market is overvalued. And yet it keeps going higher.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Out of 698 US businesses worth over $10b, you've got 25% of those selling at 10x
sales. So, if you have only $1b in sales, you're worth $10b.

You'd have to grow sales 20% per year for the next 13 years to get to 1x sales.

Only about 4% of companies worth over $10b have grown sales at, or above,…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvacjm/the_rivian_ipo_got_me_thinking_clearly_the_us/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvacjm/the_rivian_ipo_got_me_thinking_clearly_the_us/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:56:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Out of 698 US businesses worth over $10b, you&amp;#39;ve got 25% of those selling at 10x sales. So, if you have only $1b in sales, you&amp;#39;re worth $10b.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#39;d have to grow sales 20% per year for the next 13 years to get to 1x sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only about 4% of companies worth over $10b have grown sales at, or above, 20% over the last 10 years. This figure drops to 2% if you include all US SEC reporting businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That means, roughly, about 20% of your stock market valuations are insanely overpriced. Rivian being one of them. That paired with the Shiller P/E being close to all-time highs, and inflation spiking well above expectation, signals potential disaster on the horizon. Be careful out there peeps. If the FED starts talking rate hikes, expect a sell-off. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/pressreleases/monetary20211103a.htm&quot;&gt;https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/pressreleases/monetary20211103a.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian ($0 revenue, -$1.6 billion net income) now has a higher market cap than Starbucks ($29 billion revenue, $4.2 billion net income) and Target ($100 billion revenue, $6.3 billion net income). 

$RIVN $SBUX $TGT

Data via @ycharts https://t.co/hv4gEyxqDt]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460622351582773250</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460622351582773250</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:43:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is your experience with Bernstein?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I just got off the phone with my wife's family's...I don't know what to call
them...Wealth management people? Bernstein. Sounds like they're a huge firm with
high minimums for clients, and the only reason they're talking to me is because
of who my father in law is. I'm wondering whether there's an…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvc66l/what_is_your_experience_with_bernstein/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvc66l/what_is_your_experience_with_bernstein/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:18:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just got off the phone with my wife&amp;#39;s family&amp;#39;s...I don&amp;#39;t know what to call them...Wealth management people? Bernstein. Sounds like they&amp;#39;re a huge firm with high minimums for clients, and the only reason they&amp;#39;re talking to me is because of who my father in law is. I&amp;#39;m wondering whether there&amp;#39;s an advantage to going with a group like this and what sort of benefit I&amp;#39;d see over SPY all the way. They told me in their sales pitch they determine asset allocation and they have great research blah blah etc, then have what sound like their own mini funds and at a higher level REITs available only to high net worth clients. No crypto exposure, no nft&amp;#39;s. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This all seems extremely old school and outdated. Am I missing something? They have my wife 30% bonds in her early 30&amp;#39;s, which seems...short sighted. They couldn&amp;#39;t give me a straight answer on how they do compared with a passive index fund&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can someone please explain to me why Berkshire still has a larger market cap than Rivian?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460668037032562703</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460668037032562703</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 18:45:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Please tell me to ignore all the noise and stay the course.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I want to throw money into Tesla, crypto, or some of the other hot stocks all my
friends are raving about. Please talk me out of this, and tell me to stay the
course and just invest in VTI instead. Thank you for your service.]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvb5wx/please_tell_me_to_ignore_all_the_noise_and_stay/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvb5wx/please_tell_me_to_ignore_all_the_noise_and_stay/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 18:25:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to throw money into Tesla, crypto, or some of the other hot stocks all my friends are raving about. Please talk me out of this, and tell me to stay the course and just invest in VTI instead. Thank you for your service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Home Depot earnings top estimates fueled by 9.8% jump in sales as consumers fix up homes]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/16/home-depot-hd-q3-2021-earnings.html

Earnings per share: $3.92 vs. $3.40 expected

Revenue: $36.82 billion vs. $35.01 billion expected

Home Depot topped Wall Street’s estimates for its third-quarter earnings and
revenue.

Same-store sales climbed 6.1% in the quarter,…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv7hil/home_depot_earnings_top_estimates_fueled_by_98/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv7hil/home_depot_earnings_top_estimates_fueled_by_98/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 17:59:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/16/home-depot-hd-q3-2021-earnings.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/16/home-depot-hd-q3-2021-earnings.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earnings per share: $3.92 vs. $3.40 expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revenue: $36.82 billion vs. $35.01 billion expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Home Depot topped Wall Street’s estimates for its third-quarter earnings and revenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Same-store sales climbed 6.1% in the quarter, beating StreetAccount estimates of 2.2%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consumers were spending more when they visited, raising the average ticket by 12.9% to $82.38.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Home Depot is one of the non tech stock that keep outperform. This is one of the portfolio must have stock due to the loyalty of the customers. Every time you visit there you will see a never ending long line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Big personal milestone reached today! What next?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have officially reached my personal savings goal of 50k cash. I'm 29 and have
sacrificed a lot to meet this goal, it's taken me almost a decade to get here.

Salary is 60k before taxes and deductions.

20k left on student loans, payments start up again Jan 2022.

401(a) at 16,230 - Vanguard Target…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvbw93/big_personal_milestone_reached_today_what_next/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvbw93/big_personal_milestone_reached_today_what_next/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 17:47:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have officially reached my personal savings goal of 50k cash. I&amp;#39;m 29 and have sacrificed a lot to meet this goal, it&amp;#39;s taken me almost a decade to get here. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salary is 60k before taxes and deductions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;20k left on student loans, payments start up again Jan 2022. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;401(a) at 16,230 - Vanguard Target Retire 2055 11.1% Vanguard Target Retire 2060 88.9%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;457(b) at 8,340 - Vanguard Target Retire 2055 11.1% Vanguard Target Retire 2060 88.9%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: I did not select these Target funds or allocations. It was selected automatically through my employers retirement servicer.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taxable Ally brokerage account worth: $642.52. Crypto account worth about: $600 ($400 btc). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personal note: my family is poor/working class so I pay the lion&amp;#39;s share of my family&amp;#39;s bills (mom and brother). Mom is overcoming cancer and will likely be out of work till 2022, had surgery to remove cancer and will be going through radiation sessions soon (hopefully no chemo). Fortunately (or unfortunately) she makes so little money that she&amp;#39;s always qualified for medicaid and all her treatments have been covered. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;#39;t crunched the numbers but I think all the bills (personal, communal, her personal) will likely run between 4-5k till February 2022... fingers crossed she can get back to work sooner. Brother makes about 30-35k but does not routinely contribute to communal bills, mom doesn&amp;#39;t force him and that&amp;#39;s just the way it is, it&amp;#39;s fruitless to argue about it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any advice on what my next move should be?  I feel like I stalk this sub enough to know the basics: open a Roth and split funds between an US index, international index, and bond right? I guess I need that echo chamber to confirm. I&amp;#39;m very much a serial saver. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to make this money work in my favor. Growing up in poverty I&amp;#39;ve gained a serious emergency mindset. I&amp;#39;m obsessed with preparing for the worst because bad news is the only consant. That&amp;#39;s how my family existed; constantly stressed about money, the next bill, and next big financial disaster etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry for the long post, ANY advice is GREATLY appreciated!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[US Retail Sales hit another all-time high while Consumer Sentiment is at its lowest level in 10 years.

Watch what they do, not what they say. https://t.co/x2Md4zFAj0]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460632395086974981</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460632395086974981</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:54:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian Is The Modern Day Pets.con]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rvian has obtained legendary status among the Pets.com of the world with its
ability to command a market cap of 130B+ on virtually 0 sales. Even banking
Rivian will be able to deliver on all of its pre-orders (which are never
guaranteed) there are so many obstacles and risks to their success; they…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qv3tyt/rivian_is_the_modern_day_petscon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qv3tyt/rivian_is_the_modern_day_petscon/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:30:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rvian has obtained legendary status among the Pets.com of the world with its ability to command a market cap of 130B+ on virtually 0 sales. Even banking Rivian will be able to deliver on all of its pre-orders (which are never guaranteed) there are so many obstacles and risks to their success; they should not command a massive multiple. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently their biggest competitor Tesla is trading at 25x revenue and has traded from 15-30x revenue over the last 1-2 years. Today Rivian is trading at 150–200–even 250x Price to Revenue. While comparing Tesla ( a well known, huge company with multiple production plants, battery tech, great engineers, market dominance,  Elon, a huge following, massive assets, full AI self driving and a proven production / delivery method) is like comparing apples to apes, let do it. Lets use Price to Revenue as the model and compare Rivian revenue to Tesla revenue. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be fair we should take the anticipated cars being made this year (Rivian says they hope 1k)* average cost of each car (67.5k base + extras = ~75k lets say) = 75mm in sales. To make it a better comparison lets make this a yearly number. Also lets make a great case for Rivian with great production efficiently, no problems, continued refinement, and growth from current cars per day(CPD) (current pace is ~3 CPD or ~320 by EOY but they hope to deliver 1k cars by EOY 2021 which is goal of 1k/108 days since 9/14/21 production start = CPD of 9.25) and lets double it next year. That would give us 9.25 x 2 x 365 x 75k = 506mm per year in revenue and make today’s valuation (at 131B) 258x FY 2022 revenue only after assuming a myriad of extremely positive assumptions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For fun lets triple 9.25 and even then at 760mm in revenue that is 172x FY2022 revenue. Said another way, in order for Rivian to have the same Price/Revenue as Tesla’s average of 22 they would have to produce 5.95Billion in revenue or 79.4k cars per year or ~218 CPD aka 72x their current CPD rate or 23.5x their 2021 target CPD rate. So lets reverse engineer that to find a reasonable stock price — FY2022 best case sales 760m*30 (highest Tesla P/R)=22.8B or ~21$ per share which is still ~8x what Amazon paid about a year ago. Anyone else smell this shitty bubble and going to short this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Family member is delusional about crypto. How can I wake him up?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello all, I have a family member who is approaching his 40’s and he is
hell-bent on throwing every dollar he has into Ethereum. He is one of those
people who drinks too much, is too loud, and is generally terrible with money. I
intern in the financial industry, in actual trading, but he just seems…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv6ml5/family_member_is_delusional_about_crypto_how_can/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv6ml5/family_member_is_delusional_about_crypto_how_can/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:57:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello all, I have a family member who is approaching his 40’s and he is hell-bent on throwing every dollar he has into Ethereum. He is one of those people who drinks too much, is too loud, and is generally terrible with money. I intern in the financial industry, in actual trading, but he just seems to ignore me completely. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He has this idea that he missed out on getting rich through bitcoin, so he thinks buying Ethereum at all time highs is equivalent to buying bitcoin at 4K. He’s not understanding that price means nothing and market cap is a more relevant indicator of your timing. Ethereum already has an enormous market cap and the upside is limited. He is also one of those who don’t understand that there is no thing as getting rich quick. I’ve tried telling him about just holding a diversified portfolio and making monthly/yearly contributions but of course it falls on deaf ears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m worried that if/when we see another 50% drop overnight, he’s going to be wiped out. He has kids who will feel it too.  And i get it, a lot of Americans are feeling insecure about retirement and they feel like they must make last ditch efforts to make up for years of poor finances. But this is reality, I know for certain that this guy is going to get burned chasing the next big thing. He got lucky and bought GME, which he then blew the proceeds on luxury rentals and alcohol. Now I think he’a chasing that high again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do I not feel responsible? How do I wake him up? Should I not care?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How should one value a SPAC like Gores Guggenheim (Polestar SPAC)?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi there.

Polestar, an EV company that sells electric cars in Europe, wants to go public
through a SPAC merger with Gores Guggenheim.

Polestar itself is, in my opinion, definitely worth more than 1.5 Billion
dollars in Market Cap if you compare it to other EV stocks, like Lucid, Rivian
or…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qunnan/how_should_one_value_a_spac_like_gores_guggenheim/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qunnan/how_should_one_value_a_spac_like_gores_guggenheim/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:57:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Polestar, an EV company that sells electric cars in Europe, wants to go public through a SPAC merger with Gores Guggenheim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Polestar  itself is, in my opinion, definitely worth more than 1.5 Billion  dollars in Market Cap if you compare it to other EV stocks, like Lucid,  Rivian or Fisker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Gores  Guggenheim has a market cap of only 1.5 Billion dollars. Surely, I&amp;#39;m  missing something here? I&amp;#39;m quite certain that I&amp;#39;m missing something. If  the merger goes through, what happens to the market cap and stock price  of Gores Guggenheim?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will the MC  just go to a few billion while the stock price stays the same? Will the  stock disappear? I really don&amp;#39;t know how this works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why is CRSP falling so much? CRISPR Therapeutics]]></title><description><![CDATA[Normally, with a company like this, I'd expect them to be losing money like
crazy, but their PE is 16.17. Their EPS is 5.26. They have an incredibly bright
future like 3 or 4 years from now. Why is the stock tanking so hard? Is Yahoo
Finance's information incorrect on the PE and EPS? The stocks low…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quw1p1/why_is_crsp_falling_so_much_crispr_therapeutics/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quw1p1/why_is_crsp_falling_so_much_crispr_therapeutics/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:57:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Normally, with a company like this, I&amp;#39;d expect them to be losing money like crazy, but their PE is 16.17. Their EPS is 5.26. They have an incredibly bright future like 3 or 4 years from now. Why is the stock tanking so hard? Is Yahoo Finance&amp;#39;s information incorrect on the PE and EPS? The stocks low today was $84.31. It&amp;#39;s starting to look juicy, but man, who knows...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian's market cap just passed Citigroup's.

Yes, that Citigroup: 
Founded in 1812
200 million customer accounts
4,600 branches
World's largest credit card issuer
204,000 employees
$72 billion in revenue
$23 billion net income
$2.3 trillion in total assets

$RIVN $C https://t.co/7X3zafMB3I]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460618711707140109</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460618711707140109</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:45:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sportradar reports third-quarter earnings (Nov 17th)]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://sportshandle.com/on-tap-111521/


WEDNESDAY, NOVEMBER 17

Sportradar, the Switzerland-based sports betting data provider, will report
quarterly earnings for the first time since completing its IPO in September.
Sportradar earned $478 million in 2020, with $18 million in net income. Over…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv6q19/sportradar_reports_thirdquarter_earnings_nov_17th/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv6q19/sportradar_reports_thirdquarter_earnings_nov_17th/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:27:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sportshandle.com/on-tap-111521/&quot;&gt;https://sportshandle.com/on-tap-111521/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Wednesday, November 17&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sportradar, the Switzerland-based sports betting data provider, will report quarterly earnings for the first time since completing its IPO in September. Sportradar earned $478 million in 2020, with $18 million in net income. Over the first half of 2021, Sportradar &lt;a href=&quot;https://frontofficesports.com/sportradar-looks-to-acquire-tech-companies-after-ipo/&quot;&gt;increased revenue 42%&lt;/a&gt; on a year-over-year basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Sportradar went public in September, the company indicated that it plans to pursue acquisitions of tech and artificial intelligence companies as a way of furthering its growth plans. Earlier this month, Sportradar secured an exclusive betting data rights agreement with UEFA’s portfolio of competitions, including the UEFA European Championships in soccer. Also during the quarter, Michael Jordan assumed an advisory role with Sportradar’s board while increasing his &lt;a href=&quot;https://investors.sportradar.com/news-releases/news-release-details/michael-jordan-assumes-advisory-role-sportradar&quot;&gt;investment in the company&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Preview already posted in the subreddit by &lt;a href=&quot;/u/deepdivestocks&quot;&gt;u/deepdivestocks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Sportradar/comments/qv3ba3/srad_earnings_released_on_17th_november/&quot;&gt;$SRAD Earnings Released on 17th November&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;View: $SRAD has been on a small uptick the last few weeks after reaching a low. With gambling stocks down across the board, could this be the exception?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any views on EPS and revenue targets?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WHY ON EARTH is RIVIAN still going up?!]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know everyone is hoping it's the next tesla and is FOMOing on every EV, but a
company that barely made ANY deliveries , having the 3rd highest market cap in
the car industry (140B+) , is plain ridiculous for me... And I don't care about
the Amazon rumors.]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv7y8j/why_on_earth_is_rivian_still_going_up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv7y8j/why_on_earth_is_rivian_still_going_up/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:27:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know everyone is hoping it&amp;#39;s the next tesla and is FOMOing on every EV, but a company that barely made ANY deliveries , having the 3rd highest market cap in the car industry (140B+) , is plain ridiculous for me... And I don&amp;#39;t care about the Amazon rumors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[JPMorgan says Tesla owes the bank $162 million]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quy6j8/jpmorgan_says_tesla_owes_the_bank_162_million/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quy6j8/jpmorgan_says_tesla_owes_the_bank_162_million/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 14:47:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Timeline of predicting a market crash (by Ron Paul)]]></title><description><![CDATA[2014 - The market has to correct, and who's going to call it a crash until it
happens? We're in for a major correction, I think. I think we're very, very
vulnerable
[http://www.cnbc.com/2014/07/29/ron-paul-stocks-are-in-a-bubble-and-will-crash.html]

2015 - There's a lot of instability still out…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv79af/timeline_of_predicting_a_market_crash_by_ron_paul/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv79af/timeline_of_predicting_a_market_crash_by_ron_paul/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 14:47:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnbc.com/2014/07/29/ron-paul-stocks-are-in-a-bubble-and-will-crash.html&quot;&gt;2014 -  The market has to correct, and who&amp;#39;s going to call it a crash until it  happens? We&amp;#39;re in for a major correction, I think. I think we&amp;#39;re very,  very vulnerable&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnbc.com/2015/06/19/ron-paul-stock-market-day-of-reckoning-is-near.html&quot;&gt;2015 -  There&amp;#39;s a lot of instability still out there, and this hasn&amp;#39;t been  corrected yet. I don&amp;#39;t think it&amp;#39;s going to correct easily, I don&amp;#39;t think  it&amp;#39;s going to be just a correction.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnbc.com/2017/07/02/ron-paul-not-a-shock-if-stocks-fall-25-percent-and-gold-soars-50-percent-by-oct.html&quot;&gt;2017 -  &amp;quot;If our markets are down 25 percent and gold is up 50 percent it wouldn&amp;#39;t be a total shock to me&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/14/ron-paul-market-meltdown-could-spark-depression-like-conditions.html&quot;&gt;2018 -  A 50% correction will spark depression-like conditions that may be ‘worse than 1929’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/the-dollar-is-going-to-self-destruct-talking-bitcoin-with-ron-paul&quot;&gt;2019 - The Dollar is going to self destruct&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_gbZlnyuQ6g&quot;&gt;2020 - The end result is an overinflated stock market that could see a “violent correction”, as well as a monetary system on the brink of collapse. I happen to believe it’s the biggest financial bubble in the history of monetary policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VCj-m08qPd4&quot;&gt;On the next economic crash in 2021&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[HSA accounts, what are your thoughts?]]></title><description><![CDATA[So, I was trying to find out peoples thoughts on HSA accounts. I read an article
that said it is a great vehicle to put money into so that in the future when you
are elderly you can pay for medical expenses.

It also can lower your taxable income.

My only issue with this, is that I am not young…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qv5mv6/hsa_accounts_what_are_your_thoughts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qv5mv6/hsa_accounts_what_are_your_thoughts/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 14:35:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, I was trying to find out peoples thoughts on HSA accounts.  I read an article that said it is a great vehicle to put money into so that in the future when you are elderly you can pay for medical expenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also can lower your taxable income.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My only issue with this, is that I am not young anymore and have started having health problems.  A high deductible plan would suck out the cash from me.  I am guessing this is a good option for people in their early 20s since they are probably less likely to have health problems.  Not sure if the Boglehead community has thoughts on this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Who else is thinking of shorting Rivian?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Not going to lie, I’ve never even thought of shorting a company, but this is
insane. Up to $157 in pre market with no reason to be valued at $137 billion.
For reference, Tesla, most famous for being overvalued and the stock still goes
up is trading at only 7.3x the valuation of RIVN. Yet RIVN has 0…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv44ti/who_else_is_thinking_of_shorting_rivian/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv44ti/who_else_is_thinking_of_shorting_rivian/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 13:31:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not going to lie, I’ve never even thought of shorting a company, but this is insane. Up to $157 in pre market with no reason to be valued at $137 billion. 
For reference, Tesla, most famous for being overvalued and the stock still goes up is trading at only 7.3x the valuation of RIVN. Yet RIVN has 0 sales, 0 revenue, 0 profit. 
This thing is going to fall hard. Just a matter of how long these buyers can hold the price this high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The surge in US inflation expectations continues unabated, rising to their highest levels ever recorded (3.17% for 5-year breakevens). https://t.co/faPSer3Q4F]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460406986785411073</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460406986785411073</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 11:44:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[20M unemployed - I have been given 2000 dollars to invest by my parents, are these good choices I am making..?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I just opened an account with fidelity and about to buy these index funds/bonds,
but I just want some verification from you people whether if these are my best
options.

 * domestic stocks: FSKAX (total market - 0.015%)

 * international stocks: FSPSX (international - 0.035%)

 * emerging markets:…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qupyu7/20m_unemployed_i_have_been_given_2000_dollars_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qupyu7/20m_unemployed_i_have_been_given_2000_dollars_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 09:57:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just opened an account with fidelity and about to buy these index funds/bonds, but I just want some verification from you people whether if these are my best options.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;domestic stocks:            FSKAX (total market - 0.015%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;international stocks:     FSPSX (international - 0.035%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;emerging markets:         FPADX (emerging markets - 0.075%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. treasury bonds:      FUAMX (treasury bonds - 0.03%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. TIPS:                    FIPDX (inflation protected bonds - 0.05%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;real estate:                   FSRNX (real estate index fund - 0.07%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;and this will be the % split I am doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;30% domestic equity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% international equity &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;10% emerging market equity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% U.S. Treasury bonds&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% TIPS (inflation protected bonds)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% Real estate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Not sure what Papa Elon's endgame is but he's been on some supervillain vibes as of late]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quyhqs/not_sure_what_papa_elons_endgame_is_but_hes_been/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quyhqs/not_sure_what_papa_elons_endgame_is_but_hes_been/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 08:35:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tilray To the Moon DD inside.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Republican Nancy Mace is presenting her Marijuana bill conference today at
2:00pm EDT at Capitol Hill.
https://twitter.com/RepNancyMace/status/1459565180585656325?s=20

Germany's new coalition government in talks of legalizing Marijuana. Tilray
sells medical marijuana already in Germany and has…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qukdev/tilray_to_the_moon_dd_inside/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qukdev/tilray_to_the_moon_dd_inside/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 08:10:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican Nancy Mace is presenting her Marijuana bill conference today at 2:00pm EDT at Capitol Hill.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/RepNancyMace/status/1459565180585656325?s=20&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/RepNancyMace/status/1459565180585656325?s=20&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Germany&amp;#39;s new coalition government in talks of legalizing Marijuana. Tilray sells medical marijuana already in Germany and has license. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-10/germany-s-next-coalition-close-to-deal-on-legalizing-cannabis&quot;&gt;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-10/germany-s-next-coalition-close-to-deal-on-legalizing-cannabis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s go my precious little Diamond hands. Tilray currently up over 6%. This is not financial Advice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I’m 25 and this is my Roth. What can I do better here?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qungve/im_25_and_this_is_my_roth_what_can_i_do_better/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qungve/im_25_and_this_is_my_roth_what_can_i_do_better/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 07:50:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is the VTSAX equivalent at Fidelity?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qulqnk/what_is_the_vtsax_equivalent_at_fidelity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qulqnk/what_is_the_vtsax_equivalent_at_fidelity/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 06:49:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley is out with its 2022 market outlook, and it sees a decline]]></title><description><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley sees a more challenging year ahead for U.S. equities against a
backdrop of higher interest rates, slowing growth and supply chain disruptions.

The Wall Street firm recently set its S&P 500 target for next year at 4,400,
implying a 5% decline from current levels. The negative…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quo6jl/morgan_stanley_is_out_with_its_2022_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quo6jl/morgan_stanley_is_out_with_its_2022_market/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 05:22:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morgan Stanley sees a more challenging year ahead for U.S. equities against a backdrop of higher interest rates, slowing growth and supply chain disruptions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Wall Street firm recently set its S&amp;amp;P 500 target for next year at 4,400, implying a 5% decline from current levels. The negative projection followed a blockbuster year for stocks that has seen the &lt;a href=&quot;https://link.cnbc.com/click/25708849.282877/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuY25iYy5jb20vcXVvdGVzLy5TUFg_X19zb3VyY2U9bmV3c2xldHRlciU3Q21hcmtldGluZw/5ba060792ddf9c38dd023063Bd6668e6e&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/a&gt; rallying 25% and raking in more than 60 record highs despite fears of persistent inflation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Historically it's way better to invest at market close than at market open, most gains happen overnight]]></title><description><![CDATA[There is an interesting article back from 2018 that says

> If you had bought the SPY at the last second of trading on each business day
> since 1993 and sold at the market open the next day — capturing all of the net
> after-hour gains — your cumulative price gain would be 571%
> 
> On the other…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quxd2t/historically_its_way_better_to_invest_at_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quxd2t/historically_its_way_better_to_invest_at_market/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 04:11:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is an interesting article back from 2018 that says&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you had bought the SPY at the last second of trading on each business day since 1993 and sold at the market open the next day — capturing all of the net after-hour gains — your cumulative price gain would be 571%  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, if you had done the reverse, buying the ETF at the first second of regular trading every morning at 9:30 a.m. and selling at the 4 p.m. close, you would be down 4.4%&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have backtested the same for 2020 and 2021, see the results below. Every day I was buying/selling just 1 share of $SPY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Buy at open, sell at close&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Buy at close, sell at open&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2020&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-$4.88&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$45.42&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2021&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-$38.05&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$53.92&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: all calculations made using BreakingEquity&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Here is a Market Recap for today Monday, Nov 15, 2021. Please enjoy!]]></title><description><![CDATA[PsychoMarket Recap - Monday, November 15, 2021

Stocks finished mixed, with the Dow Jones (DIA) and tech-heavy Nasdaq (QQQ)
closing modestly lower, as market participants digested upbeat economic data
coming from China and await for a key report on retail sales in the US later
this week. The Russell…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qushen/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_nov_15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qushen/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_nov_15/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:51:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Monday, November 15, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks finished mixed, with the Dow Jones (DIA) and tech-heavy Nasdaq (QQQ) closing modestly lower, as market participants digested upbeat economic data coming from China and await for a key report on retail sales in the US later this week. The Russell 2000 (IWM), which tracks the performance of small-caps, underperformed on the day, closing 0.44% lower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stronger than expected economic data coming out of China helped lift the sentiments of market participants following last week’s inflation report. The world&amp;#39;s second-largest economy saw both retail sales and industrial production unexpectedly rise in October in a year-over-year period, suggesting that China’s economy is holding up better than expected amid new stay-in-place restrictions and ongoing power shortages. However, prices of new homes dropped 0.25% in October versus September, marking the biggest drop in more than six years as the nation’s real estate market remains under pressure from the Evergrande situation. Here are the numbers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retail Sales: +4.9% YoY vs +3.5 expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Industrial Production: +3.5% YoY vs +3% expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow, market participants will receive the Commerce Department’s monthly Retail Sales report, which is expected to show a 1.3% year-over-year rise in retail sales, improving from September’s disappointing 0.7% rise. Moreover, major retailers like Walmart (WMT), Target (TGT), Home Depot (HD), and Lowe’s (LOW) are set to report Q3 earnings, which will offer additional data regarding the state of consumer demand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week, markets were spooked by the pace of inflation, with the recent Consumer Price Index (CPI) showing the fastest pace of increase in roughly 30 years. which showed prices soared 6.2% in a year-on-year period, accelerating from September’s 5.4% YoY rate, and higher than the 5.9% expected. The staying power and magnitude of inflationary pressures has, perhaps, become the central question for market participants, with companies across the board reporting rising input costs and price hikes passed on to the consumers to preserve margins. While Q3 earning results have robustly demonstrated that companies in the SPY were largely able to navigate these cost pressures, the possibility remains that if inflation runs hotter than expected for longer than expected, it could begin to hamper consumer demand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ian Shepherdson, Chief Economist at Pantheon Macroeconomics, wrote in a note to clients, “The surge in core inflation in October marks the start of a run of big gains, thanks to surging used auto prices, rebounding airline fares, and faster increases in housing costs. We think core inflation will peak at almost 7% in March, which will pose a serious challenge to the Fed&amp;#39;s benign medium-term view. Chair [Jerome] Powell will have to convince markets that the combination of rocketing payrolls and soaring inflation does not threaten the transitory story, to which he appears still to be committed. We remain of the view that the Fed will start to hike in September, but a June hike can&amp;#39;t be ruled out. If labor participation shows no sign of life by the March FOMC meeting, we expect the Fed to accelerate the taper and then hike in June. This would play badly across all asset markets.” As always, it is important to acknowledge and understand the risks present in the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Boeing (BA) surged after the company said it was “hopeful” China would resume order of the 737 Max two years after its grounding.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;U.S. crude oil output from the Permian Basin of West Texas and New Mexico is set to jump to a record 4.95 million barrels per day in December, a new government forecast showed on Monday. This would bring production in the key U.S. shale patch well above its pre-pandemic average from March 2020.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of oat-milk maker Oatly (OTLY) fell more than 20% after missing earnings expectations and cutting guidance. The stock is down roughly 50% since IPO back in late-May.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Snap (SNAP) were up after the company reached a deal with Sony Music Entertainment to allow the company to use its artist and sounds on the Snapchat App.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Twitter Inc said on Monday it will expand free access to the social networking site&amp;#39;s data to help software developers create tools and products that could promote safer online conversations or curate content. The move is part of Twitter&amp;#39;s growing effort over the past year to decentralize the company, a vision that aims to give users more control over what content they see in their Twitter feed or have new ways of sharing content on the site, Amir Shevat, Twitter&amp;#39;s head of product for the developer platform, said in an interview.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amazon.com Inc has reached a deal to sell virtual medical services to Hilton Hotels in the United States, one of the first major customers for the company’s burgeoning healthcare business. Amazon Care is an on-demand health offering that lets users message or video-chat clinicians and receive home visits in some cities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UK ministers are expected to order an in-depth investigation of Nvidia Corp&amp;#39;s planned $40 billion acquisition of British chip designer ARM over antitrust and national security concerns. As a huge NVDA bull, hope all goes well!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Finance Tech (SOFI) announced an offering of 50 million shares. The stock is down as a result. Not surprising for management to take advantage of this massive runup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of oat-meal maker Oatly (OTLY) gapped down -20% after missing earnings expectations and cutting guidance moving forward. After a promising start, the stock is now roughly -50% since its IPO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current stock price was written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AutoDesk (ADSK) target raised by Mizuho from $350 to $380 at Buy. Stock currently around $326&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Broadcom (AVGO) target raised by Argus from $560 to $620 at Buy. Stoick currently around $565&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coupang (CPNG) target raised by Mizuho from $32 to $40 at Overweight. Stock currently around $28&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salesforce (CRM) target raised by Mizuho from $320 to $360 at Buy. Stock currently around $305&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crowdstrike (CRWD) target raised by Mizuho from $330 to $360 at Buy. Stock was also downgraded by Morgan Stanley to $250, so there are competing perspectives here&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intuit (INTU) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $615 to $715 at Overweight. Stock currently around $626&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MasterCard (MA) target raised by Mizuho from $50 to $465 at Buy. Stock currently around $360&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Netflix (NFLX) target raised by KeyCorp from $690 to $725 at Overweight. Stock currently around $680&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NVIDIA (NVDA) with three target raises. Stock currently around $300

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Citigroup from $223 to $350 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robert W Baird from $240 to $360 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UBS Group from $230 to $350 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Palo Alto Networks (PANW) with three target raises. Stock currently around $518

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mizuho from $560 to $625 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deutsche Bank from $560 to $605 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Royal Bank of Canada from $560 to $590 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roblox (RBLX) target raised by BTIG Research from $98 to $133 at Buy. Stock currently around $108&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Signature Bank (SBNY) target raised by Raymond James from $360 at $400 at Outperform. Stock currently around $321&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snowflake (SNOW) target raised by Mizuho from  $340 to $450 at Buy. Stock currently around $393&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Finance Tech (SOFI) target raised by Mizuho from $28 to $30 at Buy. Stock currently around $22&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Valero Energy (VLO) target raised by Wells Fargo from $102 to $106 at Overweight. Stock currently around $77&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Don&amp;#39;t judge each day by the harvest you reap but by the seeds that you plant.&amp;quot; -Robert Louis Stevenson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Metaverse: Next Biggest Opportunity]]></title><description><![CDATA[It was the internet in the late ’90s, social media in the 2000s, and digital
currency (crypto) in the 2010s. Facebook’s Metaverse might be one of the
greatest investment opportunities in the 2020s. If you are following Facebook’s
Connect 2021 conference you will realize how much deep Facebook now…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quvg93/metaverse_next_biggest_opportunity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quvg93/metaverse_next_biggest_opportunity/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the internet in the late ’90s, social media in the 2000s, and digital currency (crypto) in the 2010s. Facebook’s Metaverse might be one of the greatest investment opportunities in the 2020s. If you are following Facebook’s Connect 2021 conference you will realize how much deep Facebook now Meta has invested in the platform. They own Oculus which is the first step towards VR/AR metaverse. The application of Metaverse based platforms is immense and beyond gaming and virtually every aspect of our lives. Here are some of the potential companies to benefit from:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unity Software: Virtually all applications will be developed either on Unity or Unreal Engine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Autodesk: They own 3D Max and Maya which again might be used to develop VR/AR applications. Plus they have various Building Information Modelling tools like Revit and Navisworks which might be useful in creating Metaverse beyond gaming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Matterport: 3D scanning &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trimble: Again they have Sketchup and various 3D scanning tools&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shopify and Amazon: They might be the first ones to create virtual stores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft: They own Minecraft and have developed ‘Hololens’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roblox: The platform already works with Oculus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me know if there are any other key players which I have missed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My depressing investment story. Today I took most of what I had left out and a 90 day ban, I won’t be back for awhile. Gg market.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qul0k6/my_depressing_investment_story_today_i_took_most/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qul0k6/my_depressing_investment_story_today_i_took_most/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rocket Lab (RKLB ) to acquire Planetary Systems Corp.]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation

Looks like Rocket Lab is continuing to try to vertically innovate. This sounds
like good news for investors especially after they already bought Advanced
Solutions Inc…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qurofj/rocket_lab_rklb_to_acquire_planetary_systems_corp/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qurofj/rocket_lab_rklb_to_acquire_planetary_systems_corp/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation&quot;&gt;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like Rocket Lab is continuing to try to vertically innovate. This sounds like good news for investors especially after they already bought Advanced Solutions Inc earlier this year. These two acquisitions along with recent talks of selling rocket hardware to other companies look promising.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[management is one of the most important parts of a company]]></title><description><![CDATA[I see a lot of new investors looking at FCF intrisnic value, profits or
innovation. which is all important but one of the most important factors is
mostly overlooked.

strong management is going to be most of ur returns. If the CEO makes bad
decisions u will become a bagholder. especialy in market…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/queyas/management_is_one_of_the_most_important_parts_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/queyas/management_is_one_of_the_most_important_parts_of/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I see a lot of new investors looking at FCF intrisnic value, profits or innovation. which is all important but one of the most important factors is mostly overlooked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;strong management is going to be most of ur returns. If the CEO makes bad decisions u will become a bagholder. especialy in market downturns Reits or commodity&amp;#39;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best Example is Elon Musk is able to sell almost a million cars withour spending money on ads without Elon Musk tesla would be at 10/20% of their market cap max. If the company didnt go bankrupt. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ivanhoe has a legendairy CEO in mining and the company preforms well and has amazing assets. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes its better to sit on the sideline even if a stock is dirt cheap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;wereldhave has been cheap for years with an 10% dividend and even 20% for a while with a lot of intrisic value but did cut the dividend time and time again took huge losses and still holds bad assets. -80% of their peak and it use to be a large cap stock on the AEX/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intel was unable to preform with the rest of the market but when a new ceo comes he invest billions and claims the company holds a lot of tech which shows how weak management was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IBM used to be a leader but focussed on share buybacks insted of innovating. sold assets and tech cheap and the best parts. use to be one of the biggest tech companys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are countless examples of weak managment destroying share value in a small company 1 or 2 bad decisions can bankrupt the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;when looking at a stock look at management experience look at the board and insider ownership before u even touch the stock&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reasons to pick individual stocks]]></title><description><![CDATA[What are your reasons to pick individual stocks?

Is there any other reason then to try to beat the market?

With all the research showing it’s really hard to do and so many people still
choosing to hand pick stocks I was really wondering what are the reasons.

It’s a real question I am not trying…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quh9ag/reasons_to_pick_individual_stocks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quh9ag/reasons_to_pick_individual_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 02:08:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What are your reasons to pick individual stocks? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is there any other reason then to try to beat the market?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With all the research showing it’s really hard to do and so many people still choosing to hand pick stocks I was really wondering what are the reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a real question I am not trying to dismiss any market strategy. I am just curious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rocket Lab (RKLB )to acquire Planetary Systems Corporation]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation

Looks like Rocket Lab is continuing to try to vertically innovate. This sounds
like good news for investors especially after they already bought Advanced
Solutions Inc…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qurnf4/rocket_lab_rklb_to_acquire_planetary_systems/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qurnf4/rocket_lab_rklb_to_acquire_planetary_systems/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 02:08:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation&quot;&gt;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like Rocket Lab is continuing to try to vertically innovate. This sounds like good news for investors especially after they already bought Advanced Solutions Inc earlier this year. These two acquisitions along with recent talks of selling rocket hardware to other companies look promising.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How much is enough?!?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qurk7o/how_much_is_enough/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qurk7o/how_much_is_enough/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 01:14:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I Analyzed $PLTR So You Don't Have To]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello everyone, I’ve been seeing a lot of people talk about $PLTR, so today I
decided to analyze $PLTR otherwise known as Palantir. I’ve also analyzed other
companies, so feel free to check out my profile for other stock analysis!

For those that don’t know, Palantir is a software company that…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quqjjj/i_analyzed_pltr_so_you_dont_have_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quqjjj/i_analyzed_pltr_so_you_dont_have_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 01:14:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone, I’ve been seeing a lot of people talk about $PLTR, so today I decided to analyze $PLTR otherwise known as Palantir. I’ve also analyzed other companies, so feel free to check out my profile for other stock analysis! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those that don’t know, Palantir is a software company that specializes in big data analytics. At the time of this post, they’re sitting at about $23.33. They reported earnings for Quarter 3 on November 9th, 2021. Revenue was reported to be $392 million, which is up 35.5% from the same quarter last year, beating expectations by $5.54 million. Furthemore, in Q3 they added 34 new customers and closed 54 deals worth at least $1 million, 33 of which were at least $5 million, and 18 of which were worth at least $10 Million. For Q4, Palantir is expecting $418 Million in revenue, consensus is $401.87 Million. The CEO of PLTR, Alex Karp, said that they expect revenue to grow at a rate of 30% or more for 2021 - 2025. Now let’s discuss their valuation...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Since Palantir had a larger number of customers and government deals in Q3, they reported stronger revenue growth, However, growth did lag in comparison to other competitors who are in the same space such as Datadog and Snowflake. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Palantir demonstrated the highest value for EBITDA margins compared to other companies in the space. Adjusted free cash flow for quarter 3 was $119 Million, which was a $172 million improvement year-over-year, representing a margin of about 30%. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Despite the fact that this company looks like it’s trading at a cheap price compared to its peers, it is trading at 17 to 20x revenue multiples which means that if they happen to have a bad quarter, the stock can drop hard. However, keep in mind that they do seem to be executing pretty well since they’ve been growing the amount of deals they’ve been making with organizations and firms, Have strong revenue growth, and also have good EBITDA margins. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of this being said, Palantir may be a buy only if you believe in the company long-term. In order for Palantir to succeed, they will need to grow their commercial product offering, since they already have a good presence on the government side. Things do seem to be going well on that end though because the commercial side growth has been going up as of recently. In my opinion, this company is still trading at too high of a price, your money would be better off invested in a different tech company. Thanks for reading everyone, if you have any questions feel free to comment down below or message me directly. I’d also love to hear your comments!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EBITDA = Earnings Before Interest, Taxes, Debt, Amortization&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lucid releases Q3 results with 13,000 reservations]]></title><description><![CDATA[Customer reservations rose to 13,000 in Q3, reflecting an order book of
approximately $1.3B, and have since increased beyond 17,000

 * Lucid Air today won the 2022 MotorTrend Car of the Year

 * Customer vehicle production started in Q3 at Lucid's Advanced Manufacturing
   Plant ("AMP-1") in Casa…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quqg52/lucid_releases_q3_results_with_13000_reservations/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quqg52/lucid_releases_q3_results_with_13000_reservations/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 01:14:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Customer reservations rose to 13,000 in Q3, reflecting an order book of approximately $1.3B, and have since increased beyond 17,000&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lucid Air today won the 2022 MotorTrend Car of the Year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Customer vehicle production started in Q3 at Lucid&amp;#39;s Advanced Manufacturing Plant (&amp;quot;AMP-1&amp;quot;) in Casa Grande, Arizona, and the second phase of construction broke ground to add 2.85 million square feet of space&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lucid bolstered its balance sheet to close Q3 with approximately $4.8B in cash&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lucid Group, Inc. successfully listed as a public company on Nasdaq in July under the ticker symbol LCID&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Third Quarter Financial Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the third quarter of 2021, Lucid significantly strengthened its balance sheet through the closing of the de-SPAC reverse merger + PIPE, bringing approximately $4.4B onto Lucid&amp;#39;s balance sheet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Continued to invest in the business, readying production and deliveries, globalization of our retail network and adding headcount across R&amp;amp;D and SG&amp;amp;A to continue growing our core operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initiated investment in property, plant, and equipment associated with Phase 2 expansion of manufacturing, continued investment in vehicle program development, and ongoing expansion of retail, delivery, and service capacities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Looking forward&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We remain confident in our ability to achieve 20,000 units in 2022. This target is not without risk given ongoing challenges facing the automotive industry, with global disruptions to supply chains and logistics. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lucid-announces-third-quarter-2021-210000175.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lucid-announces-third-quarter-2021-210000175.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why won't the market crash soon?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pessimism on this sub (and similar financial subs) is rampant. I don't even
recall things being quite this negative during the COVID crash or anytime in the
last 5+ years.

Raising interest rates are going to kill growth stocks, China's recession is a
massive threat, inflation will kill our cash,…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qurl3z/why_wont_the_market_crash_soon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qurl3z/why_wont_the_market_crash_soon/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 01:14:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pessimism on this sub (and similar financial subs) is rampant. I don&amp;#39;t even recall things being quite this negative during the COVID crash or anytime in the last 5+ years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Raising interest rates are going to kill growth stocks, China&amp;#39;s recession is a massive threat, inflation will kill our cash, real estate has overheated, the rug is really about to be pulled on almost all asset classes -- there&amp;#39;s really no way to financially survive the next year going off sentiment here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why won&amp;#39;t the markets tank? What&amp;#39;s going to send us to DOW 40,000+ that so many people are overlooking? I&amp;#39;d love to hear what anyone might be optimistic about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lucid confirms a pathetic 20,000 cars for 2022 for a $73 billion company]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lucid confirmed after hours it would produce 20,000 cars for 2022. A $73 billion
company!

A little comparison. VW Group is double the mkt cap. It produces 20,000 cars a
day. Not a week, a month, a year. A day.

It has nearly a dozen BEV models on sale worldwide. It sold nearly 540K EV's YTD
to 3Q…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qus535/lucid_confirms_a_pathetic_20000_cars_for_2022_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qus535/lucid_confirms_a_pathetic_20000_cars_for_2022_for/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 23:46:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lucid confirmed after hours it would produce 20,000 cars for 2022.  A $73 billion company!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A little comparison.  VW Group is double the mkt cap.  It produces 20,000 cars a day.  Not a week, a month, a year.  A day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has nearly a dozen BEV models on sale worldwide.  It sold nearly 540K EV&amp;#39;s YTD to 3Q 2021.  In 2022 it will have over 20 EV models on sale and likely surpass Tesla in EV sales and be pushing 20,000 EV&amp;#39;s a day (Tesla will stil pip it in BEV&amp;#39;s by measure - and yes PHEV&amp;#39;s do matter making lots of moolah).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;20,000 EV&amp;#39;s a day...not a year, a day.  Yet just double the mkt cap.of Lucid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry to offend, but US investors are mostly utterly clueless when it comes to global EV mkts.  BYD in China knocked out 183K EV&amp;#39;s in their third quarter alone.  Again it trades for a lowly $130 billion vs Lucid&amp;#39;s absurd mkt cap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Journey to "cant beat the market" acceptance - final step]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm in search of a little confirmation bias so this sub seemed the best place to
start...

I've always heard you can't beat the market but couldn't reconcile that with my
initial assumption that 50% must be doing better than the other 50%. I mean, I'm
smart right? At least smarter than half of you!…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qumaht/journey_to_cant_beat_the_market_acceptance_final/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qumaht/journey_to_cant_beat_the_market_acceptance_final/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 23:17:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m in search of a little confirmation bias so this sub seemed the best place to start...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve always heard you can&amp;#39;t beat the market but couldn&amp;#39;t reconcile that with my initial assumption that 50% must be doing better than the other 50%. I mean, I&amp;#39;m smart right? At least smarter than half of you! Then I read Bogle and all the other data showing its single digit % of investors beat the market long term. To understand this I&amp;#39;ve come to a theory that &amp;quot;The Market&amp;quot; is an optimization, not an average. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The theory: as long as society maintains stability (bigger &amp;quot;if&amp;quot; these days), the economy will grow (for reasons) and thus companies and stocks along with it. There is always churn and noise but over the long term the duds get filtered out and the studs end up making a majority of the market. Even if you&amp;#39;re picking good stocks, so is the broader market. That makes it hard to beat when the market also has your winners every time. It also has mostly winners and very few losers so if you happen to pick one bad stock you can easily get crushed vs the index. The market is continually optimizing so the effort and reward for trying to beat it are not justified. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This concludes my surface level, non-economist, inexperienced justification for why I consolidated everything into SNDL...j/k, it starts with a V. Please destroy my optimization theory so I can learn about a hammer candle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WeWork has had net losses totaling $13.4 billion since the start of 2016. Its market cap today is $7 billion. $WE]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460261845818920970</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460261845818920970</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 22:41:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alibaba, limp dick pattern bout to erect!!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qupfzp/alibaba_limp_dick_pattern_bout_to_erect/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qupfzp/alibaba_limp_dick_pattern_bout_to_erect/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 22:41:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I Bonds vs High Yield Savings Account for Emergency Fund]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’ve tried approaching the following decision analytically but am checking if
others have experienced similar decisions or can see any of my blind spots.

I have a pretty high savings rate and hate to leave my dollars working
inefficiently. The more I save, the quicker I can reach financial…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qula33/i_bonds_vs_high_yield_savings_account_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qula33/i_bonds_vs_high_yield_savings_account_for/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 22:25:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve tried approaching the following decision analytically but am checking if others have experienced similar decisions or can see any of my blind spots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a pretty high savings rate and hate to leave my dollars working inefficiently. The more I save, the quicker I can reach financial independence. In my 20’s I’ve stayed in 100% stocks and have not purchased any bonds. I have a pretty tough skin and risk tolerance and didn’t even consider selling during the short 2020 market crash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I also understand the importance of an emergency fund. I started with around $10,000 in an Ally savings account and have increased it up to $25,000 over the past few years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More recently, I’ve considered putting most of my emergency fund into I-bonds. I understand they are less liquid than a savings account but in the long run will be less affected by inflation. Looking at historic rates, they almost always are at least 1-2% higher than a high yield savings account.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/agSHRni&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/a/agSHRni&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pro to an online savings account is only liquidity and money available within a few days. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From what I can tell about I-bonds the pros and cons are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pros:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Higher Inflation Protected Interest Rates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Locked up for 1 year from time of purchase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forfeit 3 months interest if redeemed within 5 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Limited to $10,000 purchased per year &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;May take longer to redeem in an emergency &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I can deal with all of the cons in my current situation. If I purchase 10k this year and 10k towards the end of next year I could limit my exposure to liquidity issues. My plan would be to buy 10k this December, bring my emergency fund savings account back to 20k by next December, then buy 10k more. At that point I would have 20k in I-bonds and 10k in a savings account. Ideally for small emergencies I wouldn’t even have to touch the I-bonds. Even sacrificing 3 months of interest after 1 year I would still be ahead relative to a high yield savings account. 9 months at an I bond rate beats 12 months at current savings accounts rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the short term, 15k liquidity is plenty. I have a local safety net and could both cover a 6-month lease liability ($3750) and the maximum out of pocket for health insurance ($6500). Worst case I could also move back in with parents and just pay for partial utilities and food. My current industry also has a pretty high demand so it wouldn’t be difficult to get another similar paying job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my main concerns is how difficult it is in practice to redeem I-bonds. Could I put a large emergency expense on a credit card, cash in the same amount of electronic I-bonds the same day, and be able to pay off the credit card within 3 weeks?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Oatly Shares Down 20% After Earnings, Expecting Lower Revenue for 2022.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Some third quarter highlights:

 * Revenue of $171.1 million, a 49.2% increase compared to $114.7 million in the
   prior year period
 * Net losses totaled $41.2 million, or 7 cents per share, after a loss of $10.4
   million, or 2 cents per share, last year.
 * Gross profit of $44.9 million, or a…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qukktc/oatly_shares_down_20_after_earnings_expecting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qukktc/oatly_shares_down_20_after_earnings_expecting/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 21:20:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some third quarter highlights:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue of $171.1 million, a 49.2% increase compared to $114.7 million in the prior year period&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Net losses totaled $41.2 million, or 7 cents per share, after a loss of $10.4 million, or 2 cents per share, last year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gross profit of $44.9 million, or a 26.2% gross profit margin, compared to $36.0 million, or a 31.3% gross profit margin, in the prior year period&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone looking at OTLY under $10? Honestly I&amp;#39;m not surprised by this, I already thought at $8B OTLY was pretty richly valued anyways but now it&amp;#39;s hit a new ATL of under $10. Is OTLY worth it around $5.65B valuation to anyone here? I think their oat milk sells well personally and I&amp;#39;ve seen them grow but I&amp;#39;m hesitant to invest in any vegan food companies long term. Might think about trading OTLY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What does anyone think of it at it&amp;#39;s new low? Is it heading towards $8?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[New to investing, is this a good strategy?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know very little about investing. I am in my early 20s and due to a learning
disability I doubt I will ever become good at it. I have however heard good
thing about index funds due to good results and low barrier of entry. Is it a
good idea to work as much as I can and put a lot of it into an…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qucy8u/new_to_investing_is_this_a_good_strategy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qucy8u/new_to_investing_is_this_a_good_strategy/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 20:31:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know very little about investing. I am in my early 20s and due to a learning disability I doubt I will ever become good at it. I have however heard good thing about index funds due to good results and low barrier of entry. Is it a good idea to work as much as I can and put a lot of it into an index fund and then just let it stay for 40-50 years or so? At least that has been my understanding of it so far on this subreddit. Is there something I am missing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to hedge against the current worst case scenarios?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Let's say that hypothetically, Evergrande defaults, putting China in a
recession. The USD either hyperinflates or the FED increases interest rates,
leveraged investors bail and the markets crash, European markets follow.

I'm not sure how feasible this is, i've only started my investment journey…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qumlsi/how_to_hedge_against_the_current_worst_case/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qumlsi/how_to_hedge_against_the_current_worst_case/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 20:09:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s say that hypothetically, Evergrande defaults, putting China in a recession. The USD either hyperinflates or the FED increases interest rates, leveraged investors bail and the markets crash, European markets follow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not sure how feasible this is, i&amp;#39;ve only started my investment journey one year ago. But for argument sake let&amp;#39;s assume that whatever is the current worst projection becomes a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How does a retail investor react to this type of situation?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My portfolio consists mostly of a world index (MSCI World, &lt;a href=&quot;https://IWDA.AS&quot;&gt;IWDA.AS&lt;/a&gt;), small ammount of s&amp;amp;p500 Healthcare sector and a bit of crypto.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>