<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 09:41:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Move out or live at home and invest?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m 26, Me and my gf dating for almost a year now and have lived rent free with
my parents for a months now (in a garage that’s been made into a very cramped
studio apartment) it’s very small and we’ve thought of moving to a bigger studio
apartment, however I’m on disability and work a part time gig…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxvojv/move_out_or_live_at_home_and_invest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxvojv/move_out_or_live_at_home_and_invest/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 09:08:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m 26, Me and my gf dating for almost a year now and have lived rent free with my parents for a months now (in a garage that’s been made into a very cramped studio apartment) it’s very small and we’ve thought of moving to a bigger studio apartment, however I’m on disability and work a part time gig and make roughly 1,300 a month, and she’s a hairstylist, my part of the rent would be 322 a month, with my bills I’ll be paying a total of 939, leaving me with little money to invest. Right now I’m investing 300 a month  but that would be cut to around 50-100 a month if we moved out. We would be moving out in February 2022. I’m wondering if I should just keep investing and save as much as I can until I can or just get the apartment, live by ourselves and be free, but have no money to invest for the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Not excited for tax season]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxux0t/not_excited_for_tax_season/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxux0t/not_excited_for_tax_season/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 07:52:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GIBRALTAR COVID BREAKOUT, 100% VACCINATED https://t.co/jnrTohHbLk]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461897035343355907</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461897035343355907</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 05:35:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Beyond gaming - Nvidia's Omniverse makes BMW's plants 30% more efficient]]></title><description><![CDATA[There's a lot of hype around Nvidia's role in gaming, crypto, and self driving.
But often overlooked is how their Omniverse and AI can help companies build
virtual factories and identify optimal paths to production.

This is a great video [https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6-DaWgg4zF8] showcasing
what…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxtndn/beyond_gaming_nvidias_omniverse_makes_bmws_plants/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxtndn/beyond_gaming_nvidias_omniverse_makes_bmws_plants/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 05:34:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s a lot of hype around Nvidia&amp;#39;s role in gaming, crypto, and self driving. But often overlooked is how their Omniverse and AI can help companies build virtual factories and identify optimal paths to production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6-DaWgg4zF8&quot;&gt;great video&lt;/a&gt; showcasing what they&amp;#39;ve done to help BMW&amp;#39;s factories become 30% more efficient. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/19/nvidia-ceo-says-the-metaverse-could-save-companies-billions.html&quot;&gt;Jensen said&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We want to simulate &lt;strong&gt;all factories&lt;/strong&gt; in metaverses, in this omniverse. We want to simulate plants in omniverse. We want to simulate the world’s power grids in the omniverse.... By doing that, we could decrease the amount of waste, and that’s the reason why the economics are so good for companies,” he continued. “They’re willing to invest a small amount of money to buy into this artificial intelligence capability but what they save is hopefully hundreds and hundreds and &lt;strong&gt;hundreds of billions of dollars&lt;/strong&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this explains why Nvidia&amp;#39;s valuation is skyrocketing. This line of business is not reliant on securing chips. This is a subscription based software model -- and right now no one else is close to doing anything like this except for Nvidia. Their combination of Omniverse + AI seems like an unassailable moat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Chronicles of WISHick]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxqguf/the_chronicles_of_wishick/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxqguf/the_chronicles_of_wishick/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 03:53:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Nasdaq 100 Index is on pace for its 13th straight positive year (total return)...
2009: +55%
2010: +20%
2011: +4%
2012: +18%
2013: +37%
2014: +19%
2015: +10%
2016: +7%
2017: +33%
2018: +0.04%
2019: +39%
2020: +49%
2021 YTD: +29%
$NDX

Data via @ycharts]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461723027612262402</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461723027612262402</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 03:40:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This is a tough decision]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxqj1d/this_is_a_tough_decision/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxqj1d/this_is_a_tough_decision/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 03:23:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How are you planning to combat inflation?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxmkwk/how_are_you_planning_to_combat_inflation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxmkwk/how_are_you_planning_to_combat_inflation/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 02:41:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why is no one talking about Enphase Energy $ENPH??]]></title><description><![CDATA[This company seems to be doing everything right! Rapid growth and navigating
down turns to come soaring back from $178 to almost $270 as I write this. My 100
shares are up 50% since the end of June and all the big names are racing to
raise the target price points.

Their technology is well founded…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxmbb1/why_is_no_one_talking_about_enphase_energy_enph/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxmbb1/why_is_no_one_talking_about_enphase_energy_enph/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 02:41:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This company seems to be doing everything right! Rapid growth and navigating down turns to come soaring back from $178 to almost $270 as I write this. My 100 shares are up 50% since the end of June and all the big names are racing to raise the target price points. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their technology is well founded and unique. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clearly I’m not good at posting, but I’m in the gains column. (Doh) - Thought I could share a pic of my Schwab account.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Citadel CEO Ken Griffin Outbid a Group of Coin Investors for Copy of U.S. Constitution]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxoibq/citadel_ceo_ken_griffin_outbid_a_group_of_coin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxoibq/citadel_ceo_ken_griffin_outbid_a_group_of_coin/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 02:05:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to get rich]]></title><description><![CDATA[Okay so I’ve come up with a plan based on the notion that with options plays
“the first one is free.” Seems like there’s something to that so I’ve decided to
not make any decisions on my account trades anymore. I will find somebody who
know nothing about options. Teach them how options work, show…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxj8p2/how_to_get_rich/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxj8p2/how_to_get_rich/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 01:10:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Okay so I’ve come up with a plan based on the notion that with options plays “the first one is free.” Seems like there’s something to that so I’ve decided to not make any decisions on my account trades anymore. I will find somebody who know nothing about options. Teach them how options work, show them the dumbasses on this sub and ask them to pick a play for me based on what they’ve learned. In this way I can harvest the energy of that first trade indefinitely while leeching the opportunity away from unsuspecting people who might never play around with options anyway. How’s my logic here? Am I a genius or absolute moron? 
Pretty sure I’ll be rich next month&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is my juice jug telling me to YOLO into Jan 2023 BB leaps?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxpla7/is_my_juice_jug_telling_me_to_yolo_into_jan_2023/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxpla7/is_my_juice_jug_telling_me_to_yolo_into_jan_2023/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 01:10:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian drops Ford Partnership]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/19/ford-and-rivian-cancel-plans-to-jointly-develop-an-electric-vehicle.html

Based on this latest news, Couple of points which came to my mind

1 ) Was this intentionally done by Ford, They invested $500M in Rivian, then
Rivian IPOed, Stock p[rice was pumped up and now…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxslp4/rivian_drops_ford_partnership/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxslp4/rivian_drops_ford_partnership/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 01:10:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/19/ford-and-rivian-cancel-plans-to-jointly-develop-an-electric-vehicle.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/19/ford-and-rivian-cancel-plans-to-jointly-develop-an-electric-vehicle.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on this latest news, Couple of points which came to my mind&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1 ) Was this intentionally done by Ford, They invested $500M in Rivian, then Rivian IPOed, Stock p[rice was pumped up and now Ford exits out, Did they they make billions by investing $500M in Rivian ? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Ford also is now openly entering as official competitor for Rivian. They have already released their F150 Lightning and for sure looks good (at least to me)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s gonna happen on Monday !&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit : Ford drops Rivian Partnership&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Theoretically, Could I buy out a company’s entire free float?]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is probably a stupid question. I don’t know if this is possible but I just
want to know what would happen. Let’s take a company with a very small market
cap. $WORX has a market cap of 16M at the moment. Could a retail trader buy out
half or even an entire float on a broker like robinhood? I…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxnf19/theoretically_could_i_buy_out_a_companys_entire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxnf19/theoretically_could_i_buy_out_a_companys_entire/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 01:10:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is probably a stupid question. I don’t know if this is possible but I just want to know what would happen. Let’s take a company with a very small market cap. $WORX has a market cap of 16M at the moment. Could a retail trader buy out half or even an entire float on a broker like robinhood? I know putting a huge buy order would inflate the price dramatically but let’s say it stays around this range for the next 30 days. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To keep the price action stable, I buy 10K-50K shares per order. I do this every few hours. I have about $10M of fake money in my account. I do this in stealth mode for the next 30 days till I own more than 70% of the float. Current free float is over 8M.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Would this cause it to skyrocket way before the 30 day mark? 
2) Is this illegal? 
3) Would I have to file 13D or would my broker automatically file it for me and put it under the company’s newsfeed? 
4) Would management find out immediately and can they just dilute me even though I’m technically a majority shareholder?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The 5th major wave of covid-19 in the US has begun... https://t.co/0buCAhNvGW]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461811842188296200</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461811842188296200</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 23:44:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[You cannot rationally believe that USA stock has a higher expected return than international at the same time that it has lower risk than international. Same for ESG/clean energy. You must pick one.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Just a simple fact about how markets work and how relative safety lowers
expected returns. Shockingly, I find almost everyone who overweights USA stock
will consciously look you in the eyes and say that it is quite obvious that USA
stock is less risky, and it is because of that lower risk that USA…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxpe52/you_cannot_rationally_believe_that_usa_stock_has/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxpe52/you_cannot_rationally_believe_that_usa_stock_has/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 23:30:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just a simple fact about how markets work and how relative safety lowers expected returns. Shockingly, I find almost everyone who overweights USA stock will consciously look you in the eyes and say that it is quite obvious that USA stock is less risky, and it is because of that lower risk that USA stock will bring a higher return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People often make the mirror claim as well: They point out that investing in Chinese or EM companies is far riskier than investing in the USA, and therefore if you want long term high returns you&amp;#39;d be a fool to overweight China/EM!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And another related claim: Some say that ESG/clean energy companies are obviously the safe future bet, and at the same time they say that ESG/clean energy companies will obviously outperform the rest of the market going forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In all of these cases, -you can only pick one.- Given that in none of these instances is the person claiming to be a subject matter expert who is knowledgeable beyond the total knowledge of the market. They will in all cases give basic, known information such as: &amp;quot;America has long been the center of corporate innovation, and maintains a business friendly environment regardless of political party, whereas China is becoming increasingly controlling of their market.&amp;quot; Or ESG folks will say, &amp;quot;Fossil fuel consumption is down across the board, and solar energy is now cost competitive or cost superior in most areas of the globe.&amp;quot; This is day-one minute-one basic information for any institutional investor or fund manager. Since they all know that the risk of Chinese stock is higher than the risk of American stock, then they will demand a lower price and therefore a higher expected return to take on that risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, if you are tempted to believe USA stock is safer and less risky due to it&amp;#39;s superior environment, or sector positioning, or technological foundation, or whatever, then the next words out of your mouth should be, &amp;quot;and that&amp;#39;s why USA stock is expensive and I expect it to underperform.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ford drops plan for Rivian-powered EV.]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.theverge.com/2021/11/19/22791984/ford-rivian-ev-canceled-investment-ipo-jim-farley

Anyone holding this stock is holding onto a ticking time bomb. Ford's lockup
ends in 6 months and they aren't a hedgefund. They aren't going to baghold a
direct…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxq0e5/ford_drops_plan_for_rivianpowered_ev/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxq0e5/ford_drops_plan_for_rivianpowered_ev/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 23:09:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2021/11/19/22791984/ford-rivian-ev-canceled-investment-ipo-jim-farley&quot;&gt;https://www.theverge.com/2021/11/19/22791984/ford-rivian-ev-canceled-investment-ipo-jim-farley&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone holding this stock is holding onto a ticking time bomb. Ford&amp;#39;s lockup ends in 6 months and they aren&amp;#39;t a hedgefund. They aren&amp;#39;t going to baghold a direct competitor. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/jimcramer/status/1461797200460070912&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/jimcramer/status/1461797200460070912&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Global Inflation Rates... https://t.co/qOlu4vYcSB]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461804771866730501</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461804771866730501</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 21:43:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[% Below High...
$PYPL: -37%
$TWTR: -38%
$SNAP: -38%
$DKNG: -50%
$PINS: -50%
$ROKU: -51%
$PAGS: -51%
$BIDU: -55%
$ZM: -56%
$BABA: -56%
$TDOC: -60%
$CRSP: -61%
$PENN: -61%
$BYND: -67%
$PTON: -71%
$Z: -71%
$LMND: -71%
$SFIX: -73%
$CHGG: -76%
$AI: -77%
$STNE: -79%
---
Nasdaq 100: 0%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461769545849487365</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461769545849487365</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 20:40:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Elon Musk: “I’m the richest troll in the world”

Ken Griffin: “Hold my Constitution”]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461791683327283203</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461791683327283203</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 20:40:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What alternatives to Boglehead investing do you find compelling?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I came across Hedgefundie's excellent adventure (55% 3x SPY + 45% 3x 20 Year
Treasury) a few years ago and recently allocatrd a small portion of my portfolio
to it. It doesn't exactly fit the Boglehead mantra but I think it has potential
to outperform normal index investing. It will be an…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxjj5a/what_alternatives_to_boglehead_investing_do_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxjj5a/what_alternatives_to_boglehead_investing_do_you/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 19:46:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I came across Hedgefundie&amp;#39;s excellent adventure (55% 3x SPY + 45% 3x 20 Year Treasury) a few years ago and recently allocatrd a small portion of my portfolio to it. It doesn&amp;#39;t exactly fit the Boglehead mantra but I think it has potential to outperform normal index investing. It will be an interesting experiment. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are there any other strategies around that you think have have the potential to complement a Boglehead portfolio? I can&amp;#39;t think of anything else aside from maybe crypto.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Value creation vs. Greed in Community Based Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[In pretty much any game where money's a concern, I enter it with the assumption
it's already rigged. Even if you can't see it, there's always a house, and the
house...we know what the house does, and it ain't losing.

I feel that's where the market's at with the big players. Even the most boomer
or…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qxml71/value_creation_vs_greed_in_community_based_crypto/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qxml71/value_creation_vs_greed_in_community_based_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 19:33:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;In pretty much any game where money&amp;#39;s a concern, I enter it with the assumption it&amp;#39;s already rigged. Even if you can&amp;#39;t see it, there&amp;#39;s always a house, and the house...we know what the house does, and it ain&amp;#39;t losing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel that&amp;#39;s where the market&amp;#39;s at with the big players. Even the most boomer or normie-tier investors have, at the very least, HEARD of these. It&amp;#39;s been made extremely available, too. It&amp;#39;s almost easier to buy it than not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;#39;s what people are doing. They&amp;#39;re hearing the buzz and forking over the dough. But why? Is it the low price? Is it the success stories? Is it the easy access? Is it the presence in the cultural zeitgeist?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Probably all of these, really. But in all of these things, one critical element is missing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honest, real discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just try to have any real discussion about these types of coins with anyone who holds, or is purported to hold, a big-ass bag. Or a small bag. Whatever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You start talking about market cap, inflation, burn - honestly, any real concern that any reasonable buyer or holder may have, and watch how far you get. Watch how quickly your reasonable questions or concerns get swallowed up by the fervor of the irritated hivemind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ever wonder what it feels like to be one of those huge hornets that gets vibrated to death by a bunch of bees? Just do the above. Closest human approximation there is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s no actual reason for the few of these tokens to have succeeded beyond pure novelty and greed, but that won&amp;#39;t be enough for long. They&amp;#39;re simply vehicles by which the illusion of potential riches are delivered to the hungry, wanting masses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Truly disheartening to see how many people there are who are so eager to march to the beat of any drum, even if that march is gonna take them right off a cliff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve spent some time lurking many, many crypt-communities. All are largely what I&amp;#39;ve described above: willing masses easily duped into closing their minds and opening their wallets, and their attitude reflects it. There&amp;#39;s no real sense of community or belonging. It&amp;#39;s simply &amp;quot;I put my money here, and now I must defend my money.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That shit don&amp;#39;t work. Money&amp;#39;s no sufficient coagulating agent for the commingled blood of men. Pursuit of money and wealth alone are, by nature, selfish and isolating. Any community built around those as a central principle are doomed either to fail honestly or - worse - succeed dishonestly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now, no one really gives a shit about these tokens. Nobody in those communities, or any others like them, gives a shit about each other on an individual level either. You&amp;#39;re a drone. You&amp;#39;re a Wallet. You&amp;#39;re not Steve or Jane or William or Kate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To them, you&amp;#39;re a Nobody. You&amp;#39;re only as good as your ability to buy or sell, because there is no other element to their culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All that said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you think they will all always be like this, I think you&amp;#39;ve got the wrong of it. The next generation will be those that have a culture and community in in which the making of money is NOT the central element.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s mostly about content&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Truly. If a true community can be created, one where creating content on its behalf is the fun of it, it can be an extremely powerful flywheel. When the basis of the coin is community and fun, a self-reinforcing and bootstrapping process can occur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The money comes because of content, the creativity, and the enjoyment everyone gets from it. This is what attracts and retains new holders. It isn&amp;#39;t the other way around. If participating in the community is a fun thing to do, generating money just happens to be a convenient side effect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why is Paypal keep trading lower everyday]]></title><description><![CDATA[My Paypal cost basis is around $235, paypal and venmo are very widely used by
many people. But the stock just keep trading lower everyday and now it is
hitting 52 week low from November 2020. Does anyone know is this a macro-trend
issue or reasons from paypal itself.]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxjgcu/why_is_paypal_keep_trading_lower_everyday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxjgcu/why_is_paypal_keep_trading_lower_everyday/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 19:33:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My Paypal cost basis is around $235, paypal and venmo are very widely used by many people. But the stock just keep trading lower everyday and now it is hitting 52 week low from November 2020. Does anyone know is this a macro-trend issue or reasons from paypal itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tilray +4000% (Citadel & Legalisation)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ITS HAPPENING

Yesterday Germany announced a government wide agreement to legalize marijuana.
That alone is projected to be a 5-10b market. Worldwide weed is a 100-1000b usd
market.
Legalisation is happening "as we speak" in US, South America, Europe and even
some parts in Asia.

Tilray…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxcn0g/tilray_4000_citadel_legalisation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxcn0g/tilray_4000_citadel_legalisation/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 19:03:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ITS HAPPENING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday Germany announced a government wide agreement to legalize marijuana.&lt;br/&gt;
That alone is projected to be a 5-10b market. Worldwide weed is a 100-1000b usd market.&lt;br/&gt;
Legalisation is happening &amp;quot;as we speak&amp;quot; in US, South America, Europe and even some parts in Asia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/NASDAQ-TLRY/&quot;&gt;Tilray &lt;/a&gt;is the number one leading international company in the cannabis game.&lt;br/&gt;
They already have operations in Canada, US and Europe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would compare weed today to where tobacco were for 100 years ago.&lt;br/&gt;
Investing in weed right now is a opportunity of a life time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add the fact that &lt;strong&gt;ROTTEN CITADEL INC&lt;/strong&gt; just increased their short position in Tilray with +20%. Shoutout to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/UMNMURTY/&quot;&gt;u/UMNMURTY&lt;/a&gt; for finding that out! Here is his thread for reference: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx0rxy/citadel_is_up_to_no_good_again/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx0rxy/citadel_is_up_to_no_good_again/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Edit: For informational purposes Citadel Inc is actually NET LONG on Tilray. They however massively increased their short position the stock on 18th of November in order to bring the price down, before the German legalisation news hit the market).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/fyghn8t1ui081.png?width=1390&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c56565a587ba44395ffff788842c31833f1de955&quot;&gt;Boys. We have to do this.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DISCLAIMER:&lt;/strong&gt; Im not a financial advisor. I&amp;#39;m a hobby investor but i do make +30% yearly from stocks and have done so for 10 years. I have recently opened a 10000 stock position in Tilray at 9.99 usd. I also own Curaleaf for better exposure to the US market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2 things that are true:

(1) Gas prices are 60% higher than they were a year ago

(2) Gas prices are still 16% lower than they were 13.5 years ago in July of 2008 https://t.co/DTId5yUUNV]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461695640669413376</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461695640669413376</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 18:49:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Opening up WSB every morning]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxfxkc/opening_up_wsb_every_morning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxfxkc/opening_up_wsb_every_morning/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 18:29:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[There's an extremely blatant astroturfing effort to promote mining-related stocks on this and other investment subreddits]]></title><description><![CDATA[(I'm copying this post from my post on /r/investing here
[https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qxjwg0/theres_an_extremely_blatant_astroturfing_effort/]
since it seems like I can't cross-post. I want to raise awareness because this
subreddit is a…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxknuz/theres_an_extremely_blatant_astroturfing_effort/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxknuz/theres_an_extremely_blatant_astroturfing_effort/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 18:29:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;(I&amp;#39;m copying this post from my post on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/investing&quot;&gt;/r/investing&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qxjwg0/theres_an_extremely_blatant_astroturfing_effort/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; since it seems like I can&amp;#39;t cross-post. I want to raise awareness because this subreddit is a target.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qxeym8/buying_copper_stocks_now_that_prices_are_taking_a/&quot;&gt;This&lt;/a&gt; post about copper miners just hit the top of &lt;a href=&quot;/r/investing&quot;&gt;/r/investing&lt;/a&gt;, and it&amp;#39;s a good example of the obvious astroturfing effort that&amp;#39;s going on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a look at this account&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/KatheKnuth/submitted/&quot;&gt;post history&lt;/a&gt; and you&amp;#39;ll see a common pattern: a few karma-farming posts from a couple of months ago that invariably come in subreddits like &lt;a href=&quot;/r/aww&quot;&gt;/r/aww&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/r/nextfuckinglevel&quot;&gt;/r/nextfuckinglevel&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/r/MadeMeSmile&quot;&gt;/r/MadeMeSmile&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/r/funny&quot;&gt;/r/funny&lt;/a&gt;, etc. Then nothing, then a submission to a stock subreddit. Anybody with experience moderating subreddits can pick this out as a bought account immediately. This is an extremely common pattern where people build up some easy karma on a clean account and then sell it for use in various promotional campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a look at the post content and you&amp;#39;ll see a pattern that will repeat: one or two paragraphs of content-free &amp;#39;analysis&amp;#39; about events in whatever mining sector, then a series of &amp;#39;pitch&amp;#39; paragraphs where they link to a random junior miner and include the ticker. Presumably this is an attempt to pump/draw attention to these stocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been noticing this happening in &lt;a href=&quot;/r/investing&quot;&gt;/r/investing&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;/r/stocks&quot;&gt;/r/stocks&lt;/a&gt; over the past few months, here are a few examples that I picked up in just 15 minutes by searching for recent posts about &amp;#39;mining&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;copper&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;gold&amp;#39;, and other such keywords. On each of these posts note the exact same post framework and then click on the username -&amp;gt; &amp;#39;posted&amp;#39; tab to see the exact same type of post history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qvx11z/is_investing_in_junior_mining_stocks_worth_it/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 2 days ago, &amp;#39;junior mining&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qqs5bp/coppers_current_situation_is_concerning/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 8 days ago, &amp;#39;copper&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qb8e3y/going_big_on_some_gold_stocks/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 1 month ago, &amp;#39;gold stocks&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/q8le51/investing_in_gold_mining_stocks_after_the_recent/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 1 month ago, &amp;#39;gold mining&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/peh0q5/mining_companies_and_engaging_with_communities/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 1 month ago, &amp;#39;mining companies&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/qudym9/why_do_copper_prices_still_go_down_despite_the/&quot;&gt;/r/stocks, 4 days ago, &amp;#39;copper prices&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/qlsbil/im_about_to_invest_in_some_copper_and_lithium/&quot;&gt;/r/stocks, 16 days ago, &amp;#39;copper and lithium&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/q3vsf4/will_the_recent_fall_in_copper_production_affect/&quot;&gt;/r/stocks, 1 month ago, &amp;#39;copper prices&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is just quickly scanning over posts in these two subreddits over the past month - it&amp;#39;s been going on longer than that and I&amp;#39;m guessing is probably in other investing-related subreddits as well that I just don&amp;#39;t see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I don&amp;#39;t have any personal opinion on the stocks or sectors in question, but I do feel it&amp;#39;s good to point this out and to remind everybody that when you&amp;#39;re reading stuff on Reddit you are not necessarily reading agenda-free or good faith discussions, you are being marketed to. So be suspicious about this stuff. Not sure how much the moderators can realistically do but maybe good for them to be aware of this as well (&lt;a href=&quot;/u/Fauster&quot;&gt;/u/Fauster&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/u/CriticDanger&quot;&gt;/u/CriticDanger&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/u/ScottyStellar&quot;&gt;/u/ScottyStellar&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[You do not understand your stocks and you do not know the value of them.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The most popular phrase to see reading posts in this sub is the investing for
the long term. Literally every shared portfolio, due diligence and stock opinion
is finshed with the I invest for the long term, so I do not really care about
the price fluctuations.

Yet the sheer panic and mood changes…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxg8e6/you_do_not_understand_your_stocks_and_you_do_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxg8e6/you_do_not_understand_your_stocks_and_you_do_not/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 18:29:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most popular phrase to see reading posts in this sub is the investing for the long term. Literally every shared portfolio, due diligence and stock opinion is finshed with the I invest for the long term, so I do not really care about the price fluctuations. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet the sheer panic and mood changes on stocks are made after every small dip, missed earnings or change in analyst estimates. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The thing is, that the value of company and mass concensus here is not made by anything, but simple price change. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company’s stock rose singnificantly in the last year?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a complete beast and literally everyone needs it in their portfolio!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They missed earnings by 50 basis points, there is small change in the estimates for next year and the stock had not changed in a 6 months?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Immediately sell the company, because you are lacking after the last year biggest homeruns!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason why this thing is happening is, because most people do not know or have the slightest idea about how much they value their business! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would have a strong opinion on how much you value your business, you want sell it after you believed that you have paid 50 cents on a dollar for it. Most of you are valueing business on the market price that is quoted last second. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other thing is that you do not understand the businesses you own!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, saying Iunderstand Coca-Cola because i know it sells Coke is not understanding business. How many of you know the balance sheet of KO, how many of you read the 10Q and 10K, do you know that KO’s payout ratio of their dividends is above 80% and often was 100% plus? Do you know the management? Can you give a pricetag on these cash flows, that KO will make? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this is talking about KO, which is relatively easy to understand company, that nearly everyone has some experience with. I really do not believe that even 0,1% of people who read palantirs reports, looked at its valuation, and most importantly understand the business of the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Answer honestly to yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you really know the business you own?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly i would want to say a story about mass opinions on companies. Microsoft and Apple were for many years considered mature companies with limited growth. Apple was even considered with negative growth rate. After last three years rally in their prices, the opinion on them changed so much that literally everyone believes that they must have them in their portfolio. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would you also consider this if the price of the stock did not change?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[There's an extremely blatant astroturfing effort to promote mining-related stocks on this and other investment subreddits]]></title><description><![CDATA[This
[https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qxeym8/buying_copper_stocks_now_that_prices_are_taking_a/]
post about copper miners just hit the top of this subreddit, and it's a good
example of the obvious astroturfing effort that's going on.

Take a look at this account's post…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qxjwg0/theres_an_extremely_blatant_astroturfing_effort/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qxjwg0/theres_an_extremely_blatant_astroturfing_effort/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 17:32:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qxeym8/buying_copper_stocks_now_that_prices_are_taking_a/&quot;&gt;This&lt;/a&gt; post about copper miners just hit the top of this subreddit, and it&amp;#39;s a good example of the obvious astroturfing effort that&amp;#39;s going on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a look at this account&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/KatheKnuth/submitted/&quot;&gt;post history&lt;/a&gt; and you&amp;#39;ll see a common pattern: a few karma-farming posts from a couple of months ago that invariably come in subreddits like &lt;a href=&quot;/r/aww&quot;&gt;/r/aww&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/r/nextfuckinglevel&quot;&gt;/r/nextfuckinglevel&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/r/MadeMeSmile&quot;&gt;/r/MadeMeSmile&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/r/funny&quot;&gt;/r/funny&lt;/a&gt;, etc. Then nothing, then a submission to a stock subreddit. Anybody with experience moderating subreddits can pick this out as a bought account immediately. This is an extremely common pattern where people build up some easy karma on a clean account and then sell it for use in various promotional campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a look at the post content and you&amp;#39;ll see a pattern that will repeat: one or two paragraphs of content-free &amp;#39;analysis&amp;#39; about events in whatever mining sector, then a serious of &amp;#39;pitch&amp;#39; paragraphs where they link to a random junior miner and include the ticker. Presumably this is an attempt to pump/draw attention to these stocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been noticing this happening in &lt;a href=&quot;/r/investing&quot;&gt;/r/investing&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;/r/stocks&quot;&gt;/r/stocks&lt;/a&gt; over the past few months, here are a few examples that I picked up in just 15 minutes by searching for recent posts about &amp;#39;mining&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;copper&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;gold&amp;#39;, and other such keywords. On each of these posts note the exact same post framework and then click on the username -&amp;gt; &amp;#39;posted&amp;#39; tab to see the exact same type of post history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qvx11z/is_investing_in_junior_mining_stocks_worth_it/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 2 days ago, &amp;#39;junior mining&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qqs5bp/coppers_current_situation_is_concerning/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 8 days ago, &amp;#39;copper&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qb8e3y/going_big_on_some_gold_stocks/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 1 month ago, &amp;#39;gold stocks&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/q8le51/investing_in_gold_mining_stocks_after_the_recent/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 1 month ago, &amp;#39;gold mining&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/peh0q5/mining_companies_and_engaging_with_communities/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 1 month ago, &amp;#39;mining companies&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/qudym9/why_do_copper_prices_still_go_down_despite_the/&quot;&gt;/r/stocks, 4 days ago, &amp;#39;copper prices&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/qlsbil/im_about_to_invest_in_some_copper_and_lithium/&quot;&gt;/r/stocks, 16 days ago, &amp;#39;copper and lithium&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/q3vsf4/will_the_recent_fall_in_copper_production_affect/&quot;&gt;/r/stocks, 1 month ago, &amp;#39;copper prices&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is just quickly scanning over posts in these two subreddits over the past month - it&amp;#39;s been going on longer than that and I&amp;#39;m guessing is probably in other investing-related subreddits as well that I just don&amp;#39;t see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I don&amp;#39;t have any personal opinion on the stocks or sectors in question, but I do feel it&amp;#39;s good to point this out and to remind everybody that when you&amp;#39;re reading stuff on Reddit you are not necessarily reading agenda-free or good faith discussions, you are being marketed to. So be suspicious about this stuff. Not sure how much the moderators can realistically do but maybe good for them to be aware of this as well (&lt;a href=&quot;/u/MasterCookSwag&quot;&gt;/u/MasterCookSwag&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/u/dvdmovie1&quot;&gt;/u/dvdmovie1&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/u/kiwimancy&quot;&gt;/u/kiwimancy&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Retirement Accounts in Clown Economy]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxgyxf/retirement_accounts_in_clown_economy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxgyxf/retirement_accounts_in_clown_economy/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 17:03:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[That’s how you F*** the Shorts: UWMC announces Intent to Accelerate Buyback in Lieu of Previously Announced Secondary Offering.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx7at0/thats_how_you_f_the_shorts_uwmc_announces_intent/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx7at0/thats_how_you_f_the_shorts_uwmc_announces_intent/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 17:03:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[poll: what age you are targeting to retire?]]></title><description><![CDATA[in another thread, the topic of time to retire age came up, made me wonder what
age bogleheads are aiming at

edit: retire or be able to, not HAVE to keep working if you don't want to.

View Poll [https://www.reddit.com/poll/qxhbyd]]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxhbyd/poll_what_age_you_are_targeting_to_retire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxhbyd/poll_what_age_you_are_targeting_to_retire/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 17:03:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;in another thread, the topic of time to retire age came up, made me wonder what age bogleheads are aiming at&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: retire or be able to, not HAVE to keep working if you don&amp;#39;t want to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/poll/qxhbyd&quot;&gt;View Poll&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I'm done ...I am never satisfied with profits so I never take profits and in back down. And I buy options like they are lottery tickets.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx6pjd/im_done_i_am_never_satisfied_with_profits_so_i/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx6pjd/im_done_i_am_never_satisfied_with_profits_so_i/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 16:37:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Roth IRA allocation for 37 year old]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m new to the Bogle philosophy, as well as investing in general; at least as
far as paying attention to market investing.

I have a roth IRA with Chase (because that’s where I happened to be when I
opened it in my mid 20’s) with $32k in it. The vast majority is invested in
SAGPX, entirely because…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qx0g5x/roth_ira_allocation_for_37_year_old/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qx0g5x/roth_ira_allocation_for_37_year_old/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 15:59:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m new to the Bogle philosophy, as well as investing in general; at least as far as paying attention to market investing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a roth IRA with Chase (because that’s where I happened to be when I opened it in my mid 20’s) with $32k in it. The vast majority is invested in SAGPX, entirely because that’s what they decided to do based on my age and tolerance risk at the time. I’m told it’s doing “well” but Bogle makes sense to me and I think things could use alterations. My question is- should I be investing in 70% stocks, or more/less than that? What portfolio/stocks/bonds would more educated people recommend? Is Chase garbage or pretty average? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m risk tolerant and intend to work til 68+. I have a 403B that’s invested via Fidelity in an age based plan. I have two young kids for whom I save in 529’s for school. I don’t know what I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I just want it to go up, PLEASE!!!!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx9gs2/i_just_want_it_to_go_up_please/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx9gs2/i_just_want_it_to_go_up_please/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 15:27:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amazing editing skills here
https://t.co/lta9mcmNkk]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461580296873287683</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461580296873287683</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 14:35:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[FUCK AUSTRALIA 
https://t.co/X8yNGH1Wxq]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461456571570040843</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461456571570040843</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 13:44:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Buying copper stocks now that prices are taking a dip]]></title><description><![CDATA[Copper prices just fell because of China’s strong industrial output despite the
weakness in their property sector. The situation is still volatile but I am
planning to buy copper stocks because of the dip knowing that the demand for
copper will just keep on increasing.

I have already placed some in…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qxeym8/buying_copper_stocks_now_that_prices_are_taking_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qxeym8/buying_copper_stocks_now_that_prices_are_taking_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 13:31:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Copper prices just fell because of China’s strong industrial output despite the weakness in their property sector. The situation is still volatile but I am planning to buy copper stocks because of the dip knowing that the demand for copper will just keep on increasing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have already placed some in&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.southerncoppercorp.com/&quot;&gt; Southern Copper Corporation&lt;/a&gt; (SCCO) since they are paying a dividend of $2.70 per share. I’m thinking of placing in Fortitude Gold, since they’re also paying a dividend which they just increased recently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also into getting some juniors seeing how these companies might have some future once the demand for copper increases even more. I’m thinking of getting &lt;a href=&quot;https://cumtn.com/&quot;&gt;Copper Mountain Mining&lt;/a&gt; (CMMC), since they are already producing approximately 100 million pounds of copper equivalent. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.threevalleycopper.com/&quot;&gt;Three Valley Copper&lt;/a&gt; (TVC) is also promising especially after their upsize with a recent deal financing up to $16 million. Their second quarter results are also remarkable and they are expected to start annual production by the end of next year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The copper demand is rising and will probably increase and even double in the next few years so I’m taking my chance on this metal. I didn’t put much anyways since I’m making sure I only invest the money I know I might lose in the end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why is the new Vanguard app so bad?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qx3aqt/why_is_the_new_vanguard_app_so_bad/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qx3aqt/why_is_the_new_vanguard_app_so_bad/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 13:04:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anyone like me invest in stocks with not much research?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have more than 100k in stocks and about 25k+ up. I don't do any deep research
on the company invest.

This is what I do to invest. - I rely mostly on YouTube stock recommendation
channels I regularly follow. - Then I read about their product for about a few
minutes (max an hour or two) and see…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx8lvt/anyone_like_me_invest_in_stocks_with_not_much/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx8lvt/anyone_like_me_invest_in_stocks_with_not_much/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 11:46:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have more than 100k in stocks and about 25k+ up. I don&amp;#39;t do any deep research on the company invest. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is what I do to invest.
- I rely mostly on YouTube stock recommendation channels I regularly follow. 
- Then I read about their product for about a few minutes (max an hour or two) and see whether I like their product. 
- Make sure that company have no much debts.
- See whether they grew 100+% in last 10 years.
- Continue to do DCA whenever their a dip in the stocks I hold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If above are met then I&amp;#39;ll just invest. That&amp;#39;s it. Have been doing this for last 2 years. I feel like I do very little personal research and taking a big risk&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are there people who invest like me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Selling stocks to buy I-bonds and eventually buy land]]></title><description><![CDATA[Please critique my logical process and let me know if this makes sense. I would
like to buy land in the next year or so. There is no real rush on it, but it's
something I'd like to do in the near term. I have plenty of stock gains from the
last couple of years, so I'm thinking of selling some to buy…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qx6vdr/selling_stocks_to_buy_ibonds_and_eventually_buy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qx6vdr/selling_stocks_to_buy_ibonds_and_eventually_buy/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 11:46:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please critique my logical process and let me know if this makes sense.  I would like to buy land in the next year or so. There is no real rush on it, but it&amp;#39;s something I&amp;#39;d like to do in the near term.  I have plenty of stock gains from the last couple of years, so I&amp;#39;m thinking of selling some to buy a property.  However, real estate prices are also high right now and so is inflation, so my plan was to sell stocks and buy I-bonds then wait until the right time to buy a property.  Is this a reasonably wise strategy?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Draftkings worthy of investment?]]></title><description><![CDATA[So i bought in on draftkings at about 53 a while back and they have tanked but i
have been holding for march madness earnings. Now with all of the deals being
made and rumors of disney and espn could it be a good time or not worth. Since
investing in something safer like SPYG or apple might have…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qx8j7c/draftkings_worthy_of_investment/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qx8j7c/draftkings_worthy_of_investment/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 10:47:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So i bought in on draftkings at about 53 a while back and they have tanked but i have been holding for march madness earnings. Now with all of the deals being made and rumors of disney and espn could it be a good time or not worth. Since investing in something safer like SPYG or apple might have more guaranteed returns but if i bought in right now and it just returned to 60 which is below its 52 week high by alot i would essentially double my money but theres a lot of uncertainty with DKNG. So i came here for more informed opinions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR; Question is do i buy in more while its below 40 or do i hold on what i have and just try to get what i can back and invest my money somewhere else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The percentage of workers in the US that are quitting their jobs has never been higher. https://t.co/bxpywwdRz4]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461459482895130640</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461459482895130640</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 06:52:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Some people just want to watch the world burn]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx4mfy/some_people_just_want_to_watch_the_world_burn/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx4mfy/some_people_just_want_to_watch_the_world_burn/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 05:48:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Any Canadians here?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m 100% XEQT, which is the equivalent of VT. Not any Canadian versions of this
sub, and it’s my favourite one so thought I’d throw it out there!]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qwt6fa/any_canadians_here/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qwt6fa/any_canadians_here/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 05:35:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m 100% XEQT, which is the equivalent of VT. Not any Canadian versions of this sub, and it’s my favourite one so thought I’d throw it out there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Intel's chip recovery plan could restore US manufacturing prowess - Cnet exclusive.]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnet.com/features/intels-chip-recovery-plan-could-restore-us-manufacturing-prowess/

> The chipmaker's come-from-behind strategy is risky and will take years, even
> with government subsidies.
> 
> First Look at Intel’s Next-Gen Meteor Lake CPUs, Sapphire Rapids Xeons & Ponte
> Vecchio…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx59wj/intels_chip_recovery_plan_could_restore_us/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx59wj/intels_chip_recovery_plan_could_restore_us/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 05:22:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnet.com/features/intels-chip-recovery-plan-could-restore-us-manufacturing-prowess/&quot;&gt;https://www.cnet.com/features/intels-chip-recovery-plan-could-restore-us-manufacturing-prowess/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The chipmaker&amp;#39;s come-from-behind strategy is risky and will take years, even with government subsidies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First Look at Intel’s Next-Gen Meteor Lake CPUs, Sapphire Rapids Xeons &amp;amp; Ponte Vecchio GPUs Fresh Out of Arizona’s Fab 42&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Summary of products and charts: &lt;a href=&quot;https://wccftech.com/first-look-at-intel-next-gen-meteor-lake-cpus-sapphire-rapids-xeons-ponte-vecchio-gpus-fresh-out-of-arizonas-fab-42/&quot;&gt;https://wccftech.com/first-look-at-intel-next-gen-meteor-lake-cpus-sapphire-rapids-xeons-ponte-vecchio-gpus-fresh-out-of-arizonas-fab-42/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The FDA has asked a federal judge to make the public wait until the year 2076 to disclose all of the data and information it relied upon to license Pfizer’s COVID-19 vaccine]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461469163839447041</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461469163839447041</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 04:47:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pro tip: only invest money in bond funds if your holding duration is longer than the fund's duration. Bonds are *not* a substitute for cash! If your holding period is under one year, cash is your best option.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qx4ycu/pro_tip_only_invest_money_in_bond_funds_if_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qx4ycu/pro_tip_only_invest_money_in_bond_funds_if_your/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 04:47:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ford plans to increase EV production to 600,000 vehicles by 2023. What would be your position with this stock tommrow based on this news]]></title><description><![CDATA[KEY POINTS

 * Ford plans to increase its production capacity of electric vehicles to
   600,000 units globally by 2023, according to CEO Jim Farley.
 * The executive expects that would make the company the second-largest
   U.S.-based producer of EVs, behind Tesla.
 * It’s unclear if 600,000 would…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx5wkv/ford_plans_to_increase_ev_production_to_600000/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx5wkv/ford_plans_to_increase_ev_production_to_600000/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 04:21:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KEY POINTS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ford plans to increase its production capacity of electric vehicles to 600,000 units globally by 2023, according to CEO Jim Farley.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The executive expects that would make the company the second-largest U.S.-based producer of EVs, behind Tesla.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s unclear if 600,000 would place it second behind Tesla. General Motors plans to sell 1 million electric vehicles globally by 2025.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/18/ford-plans-to-increase-ev-production-to-600000-vehicles-in-2023.html&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/18/ford-plans-to-increase-ev-production-to-600000-vehicles-in-2023.html&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[QQQ - If you're new today, how high can it go?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Let's say you're 21 and starting your career and choosing your investments for
the next 30 years.

Tech is absolutely "killing" it as we all know, but how long can this rally be
upkept? How much more innovation do the FAANG's of the world need considering
they are already the absolute leaders in…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwuosp/qqq_if_youre_new_today_how_high_can_it_go/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwuosp/qqq_if_youre_new_today_how_high_can_it_go/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 04:21:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s say you&amp;#39;re 21 and starting your career and choosing your investments for the next 30 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tech is absolutely &amp;quot;killing&amp;quot; it as we all know, but how long can this rally be upkept? How much more innovation do the FAANG&amp;#39;s of the world need considering they are already the absolute leaders in their fields?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or do these securities just continue to become more expensive over time due to inflation?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I&amp;#39;m really getting at is what is the &amp;#39;room to grow&amp;#39; factor with these mega-cap FAANGs?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>