<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 02:41:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[52 week lows… $WISH I never found this stock… enjoy]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwronc/52_week_lows_wish_i_never_found_this_stock_enjoy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwronc/52_week_lows_wish_i_never_found_this_stock_enjoy/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 02:08:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Apple EV]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwvbr5/apple_ev/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwvbr5/apple_ev/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 02:08:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Except for the people who had puts☹️]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx0azv/except_for_the_people_who_had_puts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx0azv/except_for_the_people_who_had_puts/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 02:08:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How do you guys deal with seeing big losses?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am a college student who recently decided to try my hand in the stock market.
I was having fun just moving shares around and making small amounts of money.
Then a few weeks ago I decided to try options. I bought an apple call that went
up a couple hundred bucks. I was amazed at how easy it was to…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwswdf/how_do_you_guys_deal_with_seeing_big_losses/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwswdf/how_do_you_guys_deal_with_seeing_big_losses/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 02:08:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am a college student who recently decided to try my hand in the stock market. I was having fun just moving shares around and making small amounts of money. Then a few weeks ago I decided to try options. I bought an apple call that went up a couple hundred bucks. I was amazed at how easy it was to make money with options. Then I decided to put a bunch of money into Delta Airlines calls expiring in January and February. Initially they went up, and I was making more money than ever before. But then they started to go down. As I&amp;#39;m writing this, my weekly chart is down almost 20%. This is all the money I had in my saving account. I&amp;#39;m not sure when I will crack, but at this rate it will be sometime soon. I&amp;#39;m still holding, but I can&amp;#39;t focus on school or anything else because all I can think about is how much money I&amp;#39;m losing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My question is, how do you guys deal with waking up in the morning and seeing huge losses? How do you keep going?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Thanks for all the great advice guys! So many responses! For now my plan is to keep holding because my &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/uV6mzeO&quot;&gt;fortune cookie &lt;/a&gt;from lunch told me to, and I still have a few months till the calls expire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I Analyzed $NVDA So You Don't Have To]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello everyone, Today I will be analyzing $NVDA otherwise known as Nvidia. I
also have done analysis for other companies as well. Feel free to check them out
on my profile! For those that don’t know, Nvidia is a company based in the
United States that designs graphics, processing units, and chip…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx1l1a/i_analyzed_nvda_so_you_dont_have_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx1l1a/i_analyzed_nvda_so_you_dont_have_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 02:08:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone, Today I will be analyzing $NVDA otherwise known as Nvidia. I also have done analysis for other companies as well. Feel free to check them out on my profile! For those that don’t know, Nvidia is a company based in the United States that designs graphics, processing units, and chip units. They reported earnings for Q3 on 11/17. They did good overall reporting revenue of $7.1 billion, which is a 50.1% Increase from the same quarter last year, and beat estimates by $290 Million. They also reported record Data Center revenue of $2.94 Billion, and record Gaming revenue of $3.22 billion. At the time of this post, NVDA is sitting at just about $316.75, gaining over $24 today alone. Some of you are probably looking for the next stock similar to TSLA in terms of growth and are thinking that this might be it, especially after their recent run up. They are up $93.85 in the last month alone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the press release, they talked about a lot of great things NVDA has done or is in the process of doing. For example NVDA discussed plans to build something which they call Earth-2, Earth-2 is an AI supercomputer which will be made specifically to predict climate change. Another cool thing they’re doing which I’m sure some of you have heard of is the Omniverse avatar, Omniverse is a technology platform which generates interactive AI avatars. The avatars that are created through this platform will be 3-D. According to NVDA they will be able to see and speak. The avatar will be able to talk about a very wide range of subjects. In the Automotive sector, They released AI technology which allows safe autonomous driving on streets and a computer architecture and sensor set made specifically for self-driving systems. I could go way more in depth on the other great advancements this company is doing but these were my favorite and I think you guys get the point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let&amp;#39;s talk about their evaluation…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nvidia beat expectations, and they had pretty strong revenue growth in Q3, however, percentage wise, they did fall short compared to their semiconductor competitors, such as AMD and TSM. Their EBITDA margins are also looking pretty good. However, compared to other competitors in the space, once again they fall short, other companies in the space captured a larger portion of the market. Overall, Nvidia’s multiples are leading more than any other company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management believes that there is a lot more growth in store. They are growing at a tremendous rate right now. In the earnings call, The CEO of NVDA said that they are finally transitioning into becoming a software company. Nvidia is the dominant leader in creating GPU hardware and now they are also becoming a leader in AI tools and virtualization technology. NVDA wants “Every transaction that goes over the internet to touch a GPU” While also selling the best software available to utilize their GPU’s.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nvidia&amp;#39;s current market cap is very substantial. This stock has had extreme hype as of recently, especially because of the anticipation regarding the Omniverse. It’s definitely possible that this company could see great growth over the coming years. Especially since they basically have a monopoly on GPU hardware and also very extensive experience in visualization and AI, but they will be fighting a lot of competition from companies that want in on the action. Furthermore, Uk regulators have been pushing back on Nvidia’s $40 billion acquisition of the chip designer Arm and if this transaction is hindered then it could put a pretty big crater in Nvidia&amp;#39;s plans. Overall, I believe their company is very overvalued right now and people should wait for a dip if they want to buy into this company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you all learned something from my analysis of this company. Thanks for reading everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EBITDA&lt;/strong&gt;, or earnings before interest, taxes, depreciation, and amortization&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Remember, the stock is not the company and the company is not the stock!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Before I start, letting you know I have no short positions on any company
whatsoever. As someone greatly explained it to me,

The problem is that with shorts you are not betting that the stocks is
undervalued, you are betting that people will realize within a short span of
time that it is overvalued…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qww4qv/remember_the_stock_is_not_the_company_and_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qww4qv/remember_the_stock_is_not_the_company_and_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 02:08:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before I start, letting you know I have no short positions on any company whatsoever. As someone greatly explained it to me,   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The problem is that with shorts you are not betting that the stocks is undervalued, you are betting that people will realize within a short span of time that it is overvalued which is more risky than the former.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, I been seeing and hearing lately a lot of people looking for long-term investments during 2021. Don&amp;#39;t mean to be a bear, but it&amp;#39;s important to understand that the stock is not the company and the company is not the stock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are plenty of companies out there going mainstream with potential for a bright future. EV sector, Renewable sector, Crypto, Fintech &amp;amp; Tech, etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I agree. I firmly believe renewables, electric vehicles, and internet-based payments are, in fact, the future. EV vehicle sales are growing at exponential paces. Solar panels will be seen more and more in your neighborhoods. ATMs probably won&amp;#39;t even exist in 2030. Major cities are pushing for 100% electric buses by 2035. Major car dealerships are expecting to sell only EVs by 2040. Crypto is making a push as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what&amp;#39;s important is also hopping in the stock at the right price. Now, I&amp;#39;m not advocating for market timing. But hopping into Rivian, whose currently valued at $100B with 0 sales is just insane. Lucid being another one whose valued at $75B with a QUARTER of a MILLION in sales. Don&amp;#39;t even get me started on $PLUG. $PLUG is a leader in hydrogen fuel cells for forklifts that reported negative revenue (wtf) and is valued $23B. We all know Tesla is a leader in its sector as well, but the price is outrageous. History has shown prices will always correct based on the company&amp;#39;s fundamentals. Too many posts on $TSLA so I won&amp;#39;t go into this. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s no doubt we are in a bubble. Lots of &amp;quot;Stock Gurus&amp;quot; on Instagram promoting all these overvalued stocks just because their &amp;quot;future looks bright&amp;quot;, and here come all these people commenting talking about how they just invested for the long term. Not saying their future isn&amp;#39;t bright, but it&amp;#39;s important to know when a stock is reasonably priced as opposed to just hearing a pitch line and going all in if they convince you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have no ounce of doubt the prices will drop substantially. I&amp;#39;m not worried about missing out on these hyped stocks. And no, I&amp;#39;m not talking about a 30% correction. Check the dot com bubble companies. I&amp;#39;m talking 95% corrections. Several bankruptcies across the globe. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The 2000 dot-com market collapse was triggered by technology stocks. Investors&amp;#39; interest in internet related companies increased to a frenzied level following massive growth and adoption of the internet.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;It was the unprecedented rise in equity valuations of internet-based tech companies during the bull market of the late 1990s&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The dotcom bubble burst when capital began to dry up. In the years preceding the bubble, record low interest rates, the adoption of the Internet, and interest in technology companies allowed capital to flow freely, especially to startup companies that had no track record of success.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not here to spark rage or scare you. It&amp;#39;s just the hard truth, lots of inexperienced investors have no idea how crazy the outcome could get. Once the big banks and heads at Wall Street realize its insanely overvalued, the rug pull will come. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me know if I&amp;#39;m wrong. Curious to hear everyone&amp;#39;s thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SROs, Complexity and Market Structure]]></title><description><![CDATA[Last week I actually lost sleep due to frustration and anger at the current
self-regulatory structure in markets. While this is kind of silly and a bit
absurd (though it did happen!), I think it’s worth examining and explaining how
the incentives for a self-regulatory, for-profit company lead to…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qww9zu/sros_complexity_and_market_structure/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qww9zu/sros_complexity_and_market_structure/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 02:08:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week I actually lost sleep due to frustration and anger at the current self-regulatory structure in markets. While this is kind of silly and a bit absurd (though it did happen!), I think it’s worth examining and explaining how the incentives for a self-regulatory, for-profit company lead to extreme complexity and subsidization in US markets. It’s easy to say “self-regulatory BAD!” but harder to understand the web of complexity that such perverse structures create.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a long post. By the end, I hope you understand what the self-regulatory structure is, why it exists, why it creates perverse incentives, and how I think it should be fixed. I’ll do my best to explain the context of these archaic structure, why it leads to unnecessary complexity, and reduces competitive forces. Most importantly, throughout the piece think about how such perverse incentives leads to lax enforcement and wrist slaps, and a cozy relationship with the industry being regulated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The financial services industry is the only industry in America (that I am aware of) in which for-profit, publicly traded firms are “self-regulatory.” What does “self-regulatory” mean and where did it come from? The structure came about from the member-owned stock exchanges that existed prior to 1934. In 1934 these exchanges were brought into partnership with federal regulators in the Exchange Act of 1934. This actually made a lot of sense. There was nobody better positioned to monitor and enforce the rules of a stock exchange (where trading happened in a physical location, on the floor of the exchange) than the exchange itself. There were conflicts-of-interest, of course, but there were also practical considerations of what technology and communication systems looked like in the early 1900s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what does “self-regulatory” mean? Now of course, I’m no lawyer, so take everything I say with that in mind. Essentially the self-regulatory structure gives the regulation arm of the exchange quasi-governmental powers (it’s been explained to me that this structure means the exchange is supposed to act as an extension of the SEC) – and gives the exchange itself immunity from prosecution when carrying out regulatory functions. It basically means that US exchanges set the rules for trading in US markets, and for interacting with their business, are then in charge of enforcing those rules and have no legal liability in the operation of that business. Those rules include things like fee structure, order types, matching priority model, co-location and data feed costs, and many other things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That means each for-profit exchange is setting its own rules, and responsible for enforcing those rules. Each exchange is responsible for monitoring its own market for manipulation (called “market surveillance”). In reality, the responsibility for market surveillance is outsourced to FINRA. FINRA is another SRO – they are not a for-profit exchange, but they are responsible for setting the rules and policing broker/dealers. You may have heard of some of the other SROs – the DTCC, the OCC, the NSCC and others listed &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/rules/sro.shtml&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FINRA, DTCC, OCC and NSCC are not for-profit, of course, but they are deeply conflicted. They operate on the fees generated by their members, who they police and regulate; stock exchanges do too – their best customers are high-speed speculators (aka HFT), who submit 95% of all orders, and are a party to ~90% of all trades. These speculators also pay for expensive, proprietary data feeds, high-speed connections and cross-connects, and other exchange services. SROs are supposed to police these customers, and are charged with ensuring that their best customers follow the rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gee Dave, that sounds like a conflict-of-interest! At least it’s not for anything important, like the foundation of the US economy, right?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is generally the SROs that have made breaking the rules a cost of doing business (naturally following the lead of the SEC, of course). While they don’t have the authority to press criminal charges (again, not a lawyer) they could easily make referrals and work with the DOJ, who does have that authority. Instead, nearly all of Wall St has decided that breaking the rules is nearly always only worth a fine, very rarely an industry ban, and practically never a perp walk and prison.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like nobody lost their banking license for fraud following the Great Financial Crisis, can you remember a time when a major broker/dealer had their license revoked? Robinhood has been fined well over $100M by FINRA and the SEC for lying to their customers, failing to provide best execution, and underinvesting in compliance, technology and any system for protecting their customers. For some reason, none of this was enough to lose their license to operate. Those guys are laughing all the way to the bank. Fine after fine is charged to every broker on Wall St, paid by the shareholders, and everyone keeps collecting their bonuses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First SRO Problem: Reluctance to exact severe consequences because the fees being collected from the perps are paying for SRO operations and bonuses.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, there’s another side to all of this. Let’s take a concrete example to start. In 2014, BATS and DirectEdge merged. Together, they represented approximately 20% of trading in the US. Each of them operated 2 copycat exchanges – a maker/taker exchange (BZX and EDGX) and an inverted exchange (BYX and EDGA). In any other industry, such a merger would result in the consolidation of these exchanges so that the resulting company would only operate 2 exchanges. But that didn’t happen here. They continued to run 4 exchanges and do to this day. Why would they do that when it costs way more to run 4 exchanges rather than 2? The answer is actually quite simple and obvious – money. To understand why, we have to take a quick step back, and reference another law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 1975 Amendments to the 1934 Exchange Act established the need (and gave the SEC the authority) to create the Securities Information Processor (SIP). It was groundbreaking at the time. The SIP is the “ticker” – a record of quotes and trades on all national securities exchanges. Ultimately the SEC did NOT create such a system though, it delegated the authority to the exchanges. The exchanges created the NMS Committees, which are responsible for managing the SIP and setting fees. From last year’s SEC press release announcing changes to the SIP:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In  1975, one of Congress’s principal objectives for the national  market  system was to assure the availability of information with respect  to  quotations for, and transactions in, securities.  The national   securities exchanges and the Financial Industry Regulatory Authority   (“FINRA” and collectively, the “SROs”) have acted jointly to collect,   consolidate, and disseminate information for NMS stocks.  For each NMS   stock, the SROs were required to provide specified NMS market data to   exclusive securities information processors (“SIPs”).  The SIPs then   consolidated that information and made it available to the public.  The   rules adopted today are designed to modernize and improve upon that   historical infrastructure, by expanding the content of NMS market data   and replacing the historical “exclusive SIP” model with a decentralized   model of “competing consolidators.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ALRIGHT ENOUGH HISTORY DAVE, WTF IS THE SIP??&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry, it’s hard to talk about this stuff without getting deep in the weeds. The SIP is generally referred to as the “public data feed” – at the moment (though this is changing), it provides top-of-book quotes across all US exchanges, calculates the NBBO and publishes it, communicates regulatory halts and other information, and publishes all trades both on- and off-exchange.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And guess what? You pay for it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s right – you are paying for the SIP. Nearly every retail broker subscribes to the SIP, and generally speaking when you see the prices that a stock is being quoted at, or trading for, you’re seeing SIP data. This public data feed costs $4 per user, per month, for non-professional, display-only users – if you’re not a financial professional, and you’re only seeing the data with your eyes (rather than programming a trading system that will automatically look at the data), then you are a non-professional, display-only user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are all of those user fees worth? Something on the order of &amp;gt; $300M per year. That money is collected by the operators of the SIP (NYSE and Nasdaq), and distributed according to a very complicated formula to each of the exchanges. On the whole, it gets divided up based on quoting and trading market share, and means that approximately $100M every year goes to CBOE, NYSE and Nasdaq (with much less going to the smaller exchanges). That’s why BATS/DirectEdge (and now CBOE, which acquired them in 2016) was incentivized to continue to operate 4 exchanges, because it meant that more of this public subsidy would go to them. Talk about perverse – it’s the exact opposite of what the 1934 Exchange Act was established to do:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5)  The rules of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.law.cornell.edu/definitions/uscode.php?width=840&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;iframe=true&amp;amp;def_id=15-USC-1989774883-482320172&amp;amp;term_occur=999&amp;amp;term_src=title:15:chapter:2B:section:78f&quot;&gt;exchange&lt;/a&gt;   are designed to prevent fraudulent and manipulative acts and  practices,  to promote just and equitable principles of trade, to foster   cooperation and coordination with&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.law.cornell.edu/definitions/uscode.php?width=840&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;iframe=true&amp;amp;def_id=15-USC-991716523-482320180&amp;amp;term_occur=999&amp;amp;term_src=&quot;&gt; persons &lt;/a&gt;engaged   in regulating, clearing, settling, processing information with respect   to, and facilitating transactions in securities, to remove impediments   to and perfect the mechanism of a free and open market and a national   market system, and, in general, to protect investors and the public   interest; and are not designed to permit unfair discrimination between   customers,&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.law.cornell.edu/definitions/uscode.php?width=840&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;iframe=true&amp;amp;def_id=15-USC-1179159879-482320179&amp;amp;term_occur=999&amp;amp;term_src=title:15:chapter:2B:section:78f&quot;&gt; issuers,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.law.cornell.edu/definitions/uscode.php?width=840&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;iframe=true&amp;amp;def_id=15-USC-1380616231-482320175&amp;amp;term_occur=999&amp;amp;term_src=title:15:chapter:2B:section:78f&quot;&gt; brokers,&lt;/a&gt; or&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.law.cornell.edu/definitions/uscode.php?width=840&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;iframe=true&amp;amp;def_id=15-USC-1335779815-482320176&amp;amp;term_occur=999&amp;amp;term_src=title:15:chapter:2B:section:78f&quot;&gt; dealers,&lt;/a&gt;   or to regulate by virtue of any authority conferred by this chapter   matters not related to the purposes of this chapter or the   administration of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.law.cornell.edu/definitions/uscode.php?width=840&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;iframe=true&amp;amp;def_id=15-USC-1989774883-482320172&amp;amp;term_occur=999&amp;amp;term_src=title:15:chapter:2B:section:78f&quot;&gt;exchange&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It gets even worse (No way Dave! How can it be worse than this??). Each exchange sells private data feeds that are faster and contain more information than the SIP. So the exchanges are incentivized to ensure that the SIP remains slow, and has less data, so they can make more money selling their private feeds. Pretty sweet gig if you can get it, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I’ve simplified the issue, of course. It gets even more complex with Reg NMS and order protection, which requires all exchanges to connect and route to one another, and brokers to manage that complexity as well. It means that CBOE gets double the revenue for private market data, and other connectivity fees, all of which ensures that CBOE earnings per share are robust and growing, and which accomplishes the opposite of the intention of the 1934 Act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Second SRO Problem: SRO structure is a classic example of regulation and subsidy creating inefficient and costly complexity.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The BATS/DirectEdge example is only one of so many that highlight the unnecessary complexity at the heart of US markets. I’ve talked many times about the need for regulators to understand complex systems and systems theory, to understand evolving regulatory structures in that context, and to focus on simplifying markets rather than making them more complex. Unnecessary complexity leads to several problems:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opacity – it becomes very difficult to understand these complex systems. That leads to mistrust, and potentially loss of confidence. We are seeing that play out right now in the retail community, and for good reason. Nobody trusts Wall St.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fragility – unnecessary complexity can lead to fragility. For example, the segmentation in US markets that diverts retail order flow to the duopoly of Citadel and Virtu leaves exchanges as toxic cesspools that discourage market making. This both widens spreads and reduces market making diversity, leading to behavior that can result in illiquidity contagions (mini flash crashes).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rent Seeking and Concentration – unnecessary complexity incentivizes a select few firms to master the complexity. This puts them in a privileged position, and creates economies of scale where the more of the market they master and control, the more information they have that others don’t, and the more they’re able to master and control. They push SROs to create ever more complexity to maintain their incumbent position, and are able to extract rents as a result. The SROs listen to these firms because they are responsible for more and more trading activity, which means they are the SROs’ best customers. Instead of SROs following their duties under the 1934 Act, they act in the interests of their shareholders to maximize revenue. This cycle continues unabated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Third SRO Problem: Unnecessary complexity makes markets opaque, fragile and leads to a feedback loop of rent seeking and concentration of power. The for-profit motive overrides the SRO’s duty to create fair and efficient markets.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mentioned before that SROs have legal immunity. This means many things, but primarily it means that the brokers who are members of the exchange don’t have legal recourse when something goes wrong. It is for this reason that retail brokers who don’t accept PFOF still route to the off-exchange duopoly of Citadel and Virtu, because they want someone’s neck to wring when something goes wrong. The legal immunity that exchanges enjoy is one of the reasons that we have dramatically segmented markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fourth SRO Problem: Legal immunity for for-profit, publicly traded companies leads to perverse incentives and terrible outcomes.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what’s the result? A huge amount of unnecessary complexity, enforcement becoming a cost of doing business, and ultimately fragile markets with low participant diversity delivering poor outcomes for investors as the for-profit SROs focus on creating churn and volume to increase earnings per share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More complexity means more fragmentation. More fragmentation means more complex order types. More fragmentation and complex order types means more unnecessary trading and churn. More unnecessary trading and churn means more earnings for publicly traded SROs. Rinse and repeat. It ultimately means that we end up with so much complexity that it’s impossible to keep track of. Take a look at the results of this 2018 RBC study on exchange fee structure (the picture is awesome, but I can&amp;#39;t seem to add pictures to a post in this sub-reddit):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exchanges have at least 1,023 pricing “paths”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3,762  separate pricing variables across the exchanges – “strongly suggest  that exchange prices are tailored and offered on a bespoke basis”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extreme complexity, customized for specific firms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extreme routing distortion (TD’s “virtually all” limit orders routed to EDGX)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fee-agnostic brokers had 7x better VWAP performance (Clearpool)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If someone can explain how this fee structure “promotes just and equitable principles of trade,” “protects investors and the public interest,” and is “not designed to permit unfair discrimination between customers, issuers, brokers or dealers” I’m all ears. Go ahead, give it a try!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, let’s take this convoluted, inefficient structure, add in a regulatory revolving door, corrupt campaign contribution system and corrupt politicians, mix it all together, and out comes the US crony capitalist system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GET OFF THE SOAP BOX DAVE, WHAT DO WE DO?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So glad you asked. I’ve been asked a bunch of times what I think should change about US market structure, what I would do if I was SEC Chair (imagine that), etc. My answer is nearly always the same – reduce complexity. When I say reduce complexity, this post is what I’m talking about:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· End the self-regulatory structure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· Build a proper regulator (complete overhaul of the SEC) with experts who are compensated appropriately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· Prioritize handcuffs, not wrist slaps and fines. Make the industry fearful of regulatory and enforcement consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· Reduce the number of exchanges, end public subsidy through SIP fees, get rid of every copycat exchange.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· Create a burden for off-exchange trading to compensate for the damage that segmenting and diverting flow does to the price discovery mechanism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· Simplify, Simplify, SIMPLIFY!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tldr;&lt;/strong&gt; Wall St cannot regulate itself. It leads to unnecessary complexity, and lax enforcement and fines instead of perp walks. It’s time to overhaul the regulatory structure, send people to jail, and simplify market structure dramatically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The rise of stock cults on the internet]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reddit, twitter, and stocktwits all have allowed for easier communication
between anyone around the world who share a similar interest. However, based on
the design of these sites (following specific communities that are often
obsessive over whatever topic it is about), it can also lead to pseudo…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx1fex/the_rise_of_stock_cults_on_the_internet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx1fex/the_rise_of_stock_cults_on_the_internet/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 02:08:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reddit, twitter, and stocktwits all have allowed for easier communication between anyone around the world who share a similar interest. However, based on the design of these sites (following specific communities that are often obsessive over whatever topic it is about), it can also lead to pseudo-cults (and circlejerks), especially with money involved. For stocks, the community will often be heavily in favor on the stock and will down vote or attack anyone who disagrees it is not the next big thing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is depressing seeing the amount of outright shaming that goes on. For example, after a rough few weeks of trading, one of the top posts on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/shroomstocks&quot;&gt;/r/shroomstocks&lt;/a&gt; (a subreddit dedicated to stocks having to do with psychedelics) is &amp;quot;Seriously, who are the losers selling at these prices right now?&amp;quot; Does this seem like healthy behavior to you? Implying your stock is a test of courage and you will be rewarded for your patience. If you are not completely faithful in the stock (which can lead to even worshipping the management), you are attacked for questioning what is obviously true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recall about a year ago and the obsession with Cathie Woods, also viewed by many to be infallible. After a couple successful years she was viewed as the next Buffet and if you dared to complain on a down day you would constantly be reminded of how it&amp;#39;s a five-year hold. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m sure many of those who were on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/PSTH&quot;&gt;/r/PSTH&lt;/a&gt; can relate. Questioning the company was seen as questioning Bill Ackman himself. Over time the sub shifted to humor as a means of getting over the losses (although there were still people who fervently believed in the SPACman!). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you think? I find some &amp;quot;communities&amp;quot; to be outright manipulative for those with dissenting views.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How do you stop yourself from checking your portfolio every day?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I started my long journey towards retirement two months ago, already got monthly
automatic contributions set up. I know I'm supposed to set it and forget it, but
it's hard. Seriously, turning on your phone once a couple of hours to watch the
chart go up and down is addicting. How do you guys do it?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qx17te/how_do_you_stop_yourself_from_checking_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qx17te/how_do_you_stop_yourself_from_checking_your/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 01:13:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I started my long journey towards retirement two months ago, already got monthly automatic contributions set up. I know I&amp;#39;m supposed to set it and forget it, but it&amp;#39;s hard. Seriously, turning on your phone once a couple of hours to watch the chart go up and down is addicting. How do you guys do it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PayPal ‘now risks getting disrupted’ by competitors, analyst says in downgrade]]></title><description><![CDATA[PayPal Holdings Inc. has a reputation for disrupting the payments ecosystem, but
it “now risks getting disrupted” itself, according to an analyst. Bernstein’s
Harshita Rawat downgraded the stock to market perform from outperform Wednesday,
citing various competitive pressures for the digital…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwqllz/paypal_now_risks_getting_disrupted_by_competitors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwqllz/paypal_now_risks_getting_disrupted_by_competitors/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 01:13:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PayPal Holdings Inc. has a reputation for disrupting the payments ecosystem, but it “now risks getting disrupted” itself, according to an analyst. Bernstein’s Harshita Rawat downgraded the stock to market perform from outperform Wednesday, citing various competitive pressures for the digital payments giant. Shares of PayPal PYPL, -4.36% are off 2.5% in premarket trading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rawat worries about the “increasing aggregation” of e-commerce activity on large platforms like Amazon.com Inc. AMZN, +0.23% and Shopify Inc. SHOP, -2.24%, which she estimates are together responsible for about 32% of U.S. commerce. “Amazon currently doesn’t accept PayPal and just agreed to accept Venmo starting in 2022,” she wrote. “Shopify has ambitions of creating its own payments business and has been pushing its merchants aggressively to convert to Shopify payments platform (and also towards the Shop Pay button).”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Smaller merchants “are PayPal’s bread and butter, and Shopify’s meteoric rise and push towards its own payments platform is particularly problematic,” Rawat continued. PayPal’s transaction economics are better with smaller businesses than with very large ones, she argued. Shopify Inc. represents an “unassailable competitor” when it comes to the small-business demographic, in her view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rawat is also concerned that PayPal’s market-share gains will slow. The company has typically won share at the expense of manual card entry onto a website, but fewer consumers are entering their card information this way, she said, meaning there is less available land to grab there. She estimates that manual card entry now accounts for about 20% of e-commerce checkout, down from roughly 33% four years back. More broadly, she thinks that share gains could slow “by a thousand cuts” thanks to the rise of a number of technologies that separately eat away at opportunities for PayPal. These include the growth of buy-now pay-later (BNPL) services, the ability to auto-fill credit-card information on some web browsers, and the threat of Apple Pay as ever more commerce shifts online. “It is an understatement to say that the payments landscape is rapidly evolving with many powerful trends emerging,” Rawat said in her note to clients. “While PayPal is actively investing and evolving, it simply has more turf to defend versus peers in our view.” Rawat acknowledged that her thesis could prove incorrect if PayPal delivers upbeat surprises with its efforts to drive more revenue from its Venmo app and its “superapp” redesign that focuses on features beyond just payments. “After years of false starts, we believe Venmo is finally on the cusp of getting monetized,” she wrote. While Rawat has “historically been skeptical of aggressive monetization estimates for Venmo,” she feels more “constructive” now. “Venmo monetization is now less about following the PayPal playbook and more about following Cash App’s journey,” she wrote, referencing Square Inc.’s SQ, -2.78% mobile wallet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shares of PayPal have declined 20% over the past three months as the S&amp;amp;P 500 SPX, -0.26% has risen about 6%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/paypal-now-risks-gettingdisrupted-by-competitors-analyst-says-in-downgrade-11637160014?mod=mw_quote_news&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/paypal-now-risks-gettingdisrupted-by-competitors-analyst-says-in-downgrade-11637160014?mod=mw_quote_news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Here is a Market Recap for today Thursday, November 18, 2021]]></title><description><![CDATA[PsychoMarket Recap - Thursday, November 18, 2021

Stocks traded mixed on Thursday, with Nasdaq (QQQ) massively outperforming on
the day, driving by strength in mega-caps like Apple (AAPL), NVIDIA (NVDA) and
Amazon (AMZN) while the Dow Jones (DIA) fell for the second straight day. Market
participants…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx0izo/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_thursday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx0izo/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_thursday/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 23:32:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Thursday, November 18, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks traded mixed on Thursday, with Nasdaq (QQQ) massively outperforming on the day, driving by strength in mega-caps like Apple (AAPL), NVIDIA (NVDA) and Amazon (AMZN) while the Dow Jones (DIA) fell for the second straight day. Market participants continue to digest the tail-end of a better-than-expected corporate earnings season amid a backdrop of rising inflation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key Numbers For Today &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY): +0.34%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nasdaq (QQQ): +1.04% &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dow Jones (DIA): -0.13%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Russell 2000 (IWM): -0.41%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple (AAPL): +2.9%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amazon (AMZN): +4.14%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NVIDIA (NVDA): +8.25%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alibaba (BABA): -11.26%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rivian (RIVN) and Lucid (LCID): -16.4% and -10.47%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a monster run-up last month, the choppiness in the market can be attributed to mixed economic reports coming out recently. While US retail sales came in better-than-expected, a great sign that consumer demand  is staying robust, the recent report on inflation showed the fastest pace of growth in roughly 30 years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier in the week, Walmart (WMT) and Target (TGT), two of the largest retailers in the US, reported earnings. While the report was better than expected, executives from both companies raised concerns over rising prices, rising labor costs, and supply-chain disruptions affecting the bottom line. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The possible staying power of inflation remains the central focus for market participants, as a potential damper to consumer spending, which accounts for roughly 70% of US GDP and as a catalyst for the Federal Reserve to raise interest rates sooner than originally expected. Despite starting to taper the pace of quantitative easing, the Fed has remained very accommodative and says an interest rate hike could take place sometime near the middle of next year. It would be really bad for markets if the timeline is accelerated. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding another wrench in the plans, President Biden is expected to announce his nominee to be the Chair of the Fed. So far, the two main candidates are incumbent Jerome Powell and current Fed Governor Lael Brainard. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Labor Department’s Weekly Unemployment Report came in slightly higher than expected but still eked out a new pandemic-era low. Here are the numbers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Initial unemployment claims, week ended November 13:&lt;/strong&gt; 268,000 vs. 260,000 expected and an upwardly revised 269,000 during prior week &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continuing claims, week ended November 5:&lt;/strong&gt; 2.080 million vs. 2.120 million expected and an upwardly revised 2.209 million during prior week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Alibaba (BABA) fell after the company disappointed in their latest earnings report and slashed guidance for the full year, citing slowing consumption trends in China. Here are the numbers:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revenue&lt;/strong&gt; $31.15 billion vs $32 billion expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EPS&lt;/strong&gt;: $1.74 vs $1.93 expected. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guidance Forecast:&lt;/strong&gt; 20-23% growth in fiscal 2022 revenue, down from 27% growth expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of NVIDIA (NVDA), my personal favorite stock, exploded higher after the company posted record revenues in gaming and data center sales and raised guidance moving forward. CEO Jensen Huang said, “Demand for NVIDIA AI is surging, driven by hyperscale and cloud scale-out, and broadening adoption by more than 25,000 companies. NVIDIA RTX has reinvented computer graphics with ray tracing and AI, and is the ideal upgrade for the large, growing market of gamers and creators, as well as designers and professionals building home workstations.&amp;quot; Here are the numbers:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revenue:&lt;/strong&gt; $7.1 billion versus $6.81 billion expected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Earnings per share:&lt;/strong&gt; $1.17 versus $1.11 expected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gaming revenue:&lt;/strong&gt; $3.22 billion versus $3.18 billion expected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Center revenue:&lt;/strong&gt; $2.94 billion versus $2.69 billion expected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Forecast for Q4:&lt;/strong&gt; Revenue and EPS expected to grow 50% year-over-year, much higher than 38% growth expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A bipartisan coalition of State Attorney Generals said it was launching an investigation into Instagram’s effects on children and Facebook’s role in promoting the service to young kids. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;According to a report by Bloomberg, citing people familiar with the matter, Apple (AAPL) is working to speed up development of its electric car and is refocusing the project around full self-driving capabilities. According to the report, the company is pushing for a debut as early as 2025. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-18/apple-accelerates-work-on-car-aims-for-fully-autonomous-vehicle&quot;&gt;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-18/apple-accelerates-work-on-car-aims-for-fully-autonomous-vehicle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amid the global shortage of semiconductors, Ford Motors (F) announced it was entering into a strategic agreement with US based chipmaker GlobalFoundries (GFS) to develop its own chips. General Motors (GM) as also stated their intention to deepen ties with chipmakers to eventually co-develop their own chips as well. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Starbucks (SBUX) partnered with Amazon Go to use their technology to develop their first cashier-less location&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tesla (TSLA) recalls 7,600 vehicles in the US for potential problems with the airbags. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current stock price was written premarket and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bed &amp;amp; Bath Works (BBWI) with a host of target raises. Average price target $86 at Buy. Stock currently around $78&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Baidu (BIDU) target raised by Citigroup from $254 to $258 at Buy. Stock currently around $155&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enphase Energy (ENPH) with two target raises. Stock currently around $256. 

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Citigroup from $231 to $315 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BMO Capital Markets from $220 to $284 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IQVIA (IQV) target raised by Mizuho from $282 to $290 at Buy. Stock currently around $265&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lowe’s (LOW) with a host of target raises following blowout earnings.  Average price target $280 at Buy. Stock currently around $248&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NVIDIA (NVDA) with a host of target (literally got 13 upgrades)  raises after demolishing earnings. Average price target $375 at Buy. Stock currently around $316&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Target (TGT) with two target raises. Stock currently around $252

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Raymond James from $285 to $290 at Strong-Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bank of America from $317 to $329 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Workday (WDAY) target raised by BMO Capital Markets from $295 to $355 at Outperform. Stock currently around $283&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Whether you think you can or you think you can&amp;#39;t, you&amp;#39;re right.” -Henry Ford&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BREAKING: Vice President Kamala Harris' communications director resigns]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461456637596684296</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461456637596684296</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 22:39:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why is Intel INTC getting beat down like this?]]></title><description><![CDATA[They have excellent fundamentals and 21B in revenue, hot sector and with
sympathies (NVDA, AMD) at all time highs why is this making new lows every day?
One would argue that competitors are doing better but every other chip company
is doing better. What is going on?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwu6tc/why_is_intel_intc_getting_beat_down_like_this/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwu6tc/why_is_intel_intc_getting_beat_down_like_this/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 22:39:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;They have excellent fundamentals and 21B in revenue, hot sector and with sympathies (NVDA, AMD) at all time highs why is this making new lows every day? One would argue that competitors are doing better but every other chip company is doing better. What is going on?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[60K in savings. What to do?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey, all, this may not be the right place, but here goes:

I have some surplus in saving from selling my house, and I'm trying to keep the
momentum going. I have two employer-matched 401Ks, and I've already bought some
individual stocks and some crypto.

After putting aside ~6 months of savings +…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qwqhdc/60k_in_savings_what_to_do/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qwqhdc/60k_in_savings_what_to_do/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 22:23:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey, all, this may not be the right place, but here goes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have some surplus in saving from selling my house, and I&amp;#39;m trying to keep the momentum going. I have two employer-matched 401Ks, and I&amp;#39;ve already bought some individual stocks and some crypto.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After putting aside ~6 months of savings + some other planned expenses, I&amp;#39;d have 60 - 80K left over doing nothing but losing value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m hearing a lot about a market crash, but even that sounds better than letting inflation eat away at my savings. I currently make small purchases through the Public app, but I&amp;#39;m considering wealthfront, or something similar, to manage a larger portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What would you do? I&amp;#39;m up for real estate, stocks, crypto, whatever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this is not the right place, kindly redirect me. Thanks!  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks, all. Given all the advice, I think I&amp;#39;m going to start with a smaller lump sum right now and then cost-average bi-weekly. I&amp;#39;ll probably add another lump sum Q1 next year after budgeting a little for real estate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How does this subreddit view ETFs?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Last night someone posted about investing $500 and wanted to know about some
stocks to throw their money into. I said my tried and true answer VTI. I was
then followed up by a redditor saying that VTI is an ETF and not a stock and
that comment doesn’t belong here. I begged the differ that ETFs…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwpoey/how_does_this_subreddit_view_etfs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwpoey/how_does_this_subreddit_view_etfs/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 22:23:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last night someone posted about investing $500 and wanted to know about some stocks to throw their money into. I said my tried and true answer VTI. I was then followed up by a redditor saying that VTI is an ETF and not a stock and that comment doesn’t belong here. I begged the differ that ETFs should be considered a stock since you can say trade it and buy options on them. He also stated that I was breaking the rule of the sub by going off topic by saying to invest in an ETF. His last comment was that if the OP wanted an ETF as an answer he would posted on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/investing&quot;&gt;r/investing&lt;/a&gt;. The amount of karma I was getting from the comment and the amount of people basically agreeing with me help solidified by thinking but I wanted to end this once and for are and see what this Reddits views on ETFs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rather than comparing P/E to History, Compare Earnings Yields to Treasury Yields]]></title><description><![CDATA[S&P 500 forward price to earnings ratios are at the highest they've been since
the tech bubble. This may lead to the question- are we in a bubble?

One way of valuing the true value of a stock is how much in earnings it will
produce in the future. Present earnings are worth more than future…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwth1y/rather_than_comparing_pe_to_history_compare/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwth1y/rather_than_comparing_pe_to_history_compare/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 21:44:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 forward price to earnings ratios are at the highest they&amp;#39;ve been since the tech bubble. This may lead to the question- are we in a bubble?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One way of valuing the true value of a stock is how much in earnings it will produce in the future. Present earnings are worth more than future earnings. Generally, a discount rate is used, which is based on treasury yields, but at a higher interest rate to compensate for the risk of owning equities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Historically, the S&amp;amp;P 500 earnings yield has often closely tracked the 10 year treasury yield, because earnings are expected to grow over time, providing further upside potential, whereas treasuries pay a fixed rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.yardeni.com/pub/valuationfed.pdf&quot;&gt;https://www.yardeni.com/pub/valuationfed.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This hasn&amp;#39;t been the case in current years. Currently, the S&amp;amp;P500&amp;#39;s forward earnings yield is 4.68%, vs a 1.53% treasury yield.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contrast this with the &amp;#39;99 tech bubble, where treasury yields were much higher than the S&amp;amp;P500 earnings yield prior to the crash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The big risk is of course rising treasury yields as the fed tapers, and eventually raises benchmark rates. Rising treasury yields make bonds more attractive relative to current equity prices, which can lead to a decline if earnings aren&amp;#39;t growing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, there is a way you can hedge against this risk. During periods of rising interest rates and inflation, &amp;quot;Value&amp;quot; stocks usually outperform &amp;quot;growth&amp;quot; stocks. This is because earnings are discounted based on current interest rates. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because interest rates are at historical lows, companies like Tesla, Roblox, Rivian, Lucid Motors are valued at extremely high valuations. This is because when you use a discount rate of 1-2%,  future earnings are worth very close to present earnings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a discount rate of 2%, earnings in 30 years are worth 55% of present earnings. However, if you raise that discount rate to 7% due to higher treasury yields, earnings 30 years from now are worth just 11% of present earnings!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the contrary, value stocks like Intel are currently very cheap. In this market, no one wants to own &amp;quot;Dinosaur&amp;quot; companies that aren&amp;#39;t growing. They would rather own the companies they expect to be bigger in 30 years, like AMD, Nvidia, etc. And with a 1-2% discount rate, the math checks out. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When interest rates rise substantially, if they do, growth stocks that depend on low rates to justify their valuation will get hit HARD, with as much as 80% downside. Value stocks will be hit as well as their future earnings are discounted further, but not nearly to the same extent that growth stocks do, since they have high present earnings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally, my portfolio is tilted very high towards value stocks and profitable stocks. I hold Fidelity Large Cap Value and Fidelity Small Cap value, and Fidelity Real Estate, as well as VYM and VIG as an indirect way to factor tilt towards profitable stocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, stocks always carry market risk. A recession can drive a crash due to lower earnings, as it did in 2009, and in 2020. If you are investing for the short term, it may be smart to avoid having too much in equities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[S&amp;P 500 closes at an all-time high for the 66th time this year. Needs 12 more to break the record set in 1995 (77). $SPX https://t.co/501H6FFAUF]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461439307638525954</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461439307638525954</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 21:35:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amazon is going up steadily after the last earning report and it is currently up 3% today]]></title><description><![CDATA[For the past month amazon has been going up steadily. Many retailers reported
amazing quarterly reports and guidance, and Amazon should be the one to benefit
as the upcoming holidays there will be robust spending from consumers. Amazon
should be able to absorbs the inflation from material and labor…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwtr0f/amazon_is_going_up_steadily_after_the_last/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwtr0f/amazon_is_going_up_steadily_after_the_last/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 21:19:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the past month amazon has been going up steadily. Many retailers reported amazing quarterly reports and guidance, and Amazon should be the one to benefit as the upcoming holidays there will be robust spending from consumers. Amazon should be able to absorbs the inflation from material and labor costs easily as AWS still growing very fast and provided profit margin. Investors should be keep holding the stocks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[“iNfLaTiOn Is TrAnSiToRy”]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwu7li/inflation_is_transitory/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwu7li/inflation_is_transitory/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 21:19:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sono Group: An EV startup that managed to contract out their manufacturing to Evergrande]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sono Group ($SEV), an EV startup that went public yesterday. I decided to take a
quick look at the company. Their Vehicle is... not very impressive, no
groundbreaking range, efficiency or price improvements. Their big selling point
is solar cells plastered all over the vehicle, which many companies…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwt3jd/sono_group_an_ev_startup_that_managed_to_contract/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwt3jd/sono_group_an_ev_startup_that_managed_to_contract/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 20:35:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sono Group ($SEV), an EV startup that went public yesterday.  I decided to take a quick look at the company.  Their Vehicle is... not very impressive, no groundbreaking range, efficiency or price improvements.  Their big selling point is solar cells plastered all over the vehicle, which many companies are exploring.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can learn more about the company here:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://sonomotors.com/&quot;&gt;https://sonomotors.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, who exactly is building these cars?  Surely a startup this size can&amp;#39;t mass produce $30,000 vehicles.  The answer is National Electric Vehicle Sweden (NEVS).  They bought SAAB&amp;#39;s assets in 2012 with the intent to make a SAAB 9-3 EV.  In almost a decade, no vehicle has made it to production.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It gets worse.  NEVS is a subsidiary of China Evergrande New Energy Vehicle Group, A subsidiary of Evergrande Health Industry Group, who bought 100% of NEVS in 2020.  Evergrande Health is, of course, a subsidiary Evergrande Group.  Also of note, NEVS haven&amp;#39;t filed any reports since 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NEVS ownership structure and investor relations:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nevs.com/en/investors/owner-structure/&quot;&gt;https://www.nevs.com/en/investors/owner-structure/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This  company has managed to put their manufacturing into the hands of, ostensibly, an incompetent and unproven manufacturer, which is currently a wholly owned subsidiary of Evergrande Group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If ever there were an EV stock to avoid... this would be it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMD vs NVIDIA vs NFLX]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi there, I got some bonus 20k recently and thinking abt dumping that into one
of the above tickers, based on current PE, factoring some pull back and future
potential which stock would you recommend the most. Or shall wait a bit for some
pullback.]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwrfxd/amd_vs_nvidia_vs_nflx/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwrfxd/amd_vs_nvidia_vs_nflx/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 19:44:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi there, I got some bonus 20k recently and thinking abt dumping that into one of the above tickers, based on current PE, factoring some pull back and future potential which stock would you recommend the most. Or shall wait a bit for some pullback.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[If he invested in low-risk, government bonds yes]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwsg1s/if_he_invested_in_lowrisk_government_bonds_yes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwsg1s/if_he_invested_in_lowrisk_government_bonds_yes/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 19:19:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[100% VTI]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tell me if I’m crazy.]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qwqvj0/100_vti/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qwqvj0/100_vti/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 17:45:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tell me if I’m crazy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Stocks to Buy with 500 dollars?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey guys I was wondering what stocks would be the best to buy with 500 dollars.
I’m more of a long term holder so I wouldn’t care if the price went up or down
as I wouldn’t be looking at it too much. Any recommendations for stocks please
let me know!]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwhfgp/best_stocks_to_buy_with_500_dollars/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwhfgp/best_stocks_to_buy_with_500_dollars/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 17:31:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey guys I was wondering what stocks would be the best to buy with 500 dollars. I’m more of a long term holder so I wouldn’t care if the price went up or down as I wouldn’t be looking at it too much. Any recommendations for stocks please let me know!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[DD: $SONY is more than the sum of its parts and outpferforming 90% of US blue chips.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I bought a couple stocks in my play account when I started investing (mid 2 end
2019): SONY, MSFT, NFLX. But ended up buying a SPY Tech ETF. When I looked back
I saw that SONY at times actually outpferforms Microsoft and that for close to
10 years. Granted they were beaten to the ground prior in…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwop2h/dd_sony_is_more_than_the_sum_of_its_parts_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwop2h/dd_sony_is_more_than_the_sum_of_its_parts_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 17:05:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I bought a couple stocks in my play account when I started investing (mid 2 end 2019): SONY, MSFT, NFLX. But ended up buying a SPY Tech ETF. When I looked back I saw that SONY at times actually outpferforms Microsoft and that for close to 10 years. Granted they were beaten to the ground prior in 2010 but how their last CEO turned that business around in pretty much all areas is a masterwork. When I did more research I found out that an important factor to their success was their CFO at that time, who has become their current new CEO in just 2 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At first I was mostly interested in their Playtation devision because I see how far ahead they are in storytelling and grahpics compared to other AAA developers and publishers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But now I actually like each divison they are in:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Television/Pictures: they dont have a big streaming service but they produce like 2 or 3 of Netflix biggest hits (The Crown, Bridgerton, Cobra Kai, Better call Saul) and they did Breaking Bad. I feel their television arm is morphing more and more into another HBO quality wise. I expect Netflix, Apple, Amazon and Disney to lit. fight for this content in future and Sony television can easy profit. And well Spiderman: Now way Home is a Sony movie afterall and breaking records for that franchise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Music: Sony Music is the 2nd largest Music label in the world and they are not stopping growing. Again they dont own a streaming service, but they make equal good money by licensing and with the closer becoming fan interaction of artists and their fans --maybe in VR-- (where Sony is also big into btw.) I can see them going a more direct way to present live conerts etc. skipping Spotify, Youtube etc. They already partnered up with one of the big 3 kpop labels to get as one of the first big music labels exposure to that lucrative market, so they are in the Zeitgeist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Electronics/Sensing/Imaging: I see mostly growth in Sensing and imaging technology for the EV market(cars and other vehicles). Electronics I dont think is too hot at the moment but I see their TVs and Smartphone being in the premium segment now where margin is better. Its already worth it to have that direct 2 consumer relationship imo and they can build up from here with VR and AR devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gaming: With Tencent is Sony the best and fastest growing Gaming company imo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are quite heavily advancing with their Playstation Studios portfolio aquiring left and right and increasing their existing studio size. I am not into the metaverse talk, but when Playtation would want to one Im sure they could. They talk how they want more exposure to 1st party big multiplayer titles, whereas last generation they mostly concentrated their efforts to deliver big quality singe player games. Mulitplayer brings more profit, so thats bullish. They are also devloping Playstation VR2 for release in 2022, which would for example let you play also any non VR game with rudimentary VR support. With all the metaverse (bullshit)talk I can see that reveal create kinda a buzz.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They also own Sony Bank, one of the biggest japanese digital banks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But thats about their current divisions. In the coming years, they plan to enter semi business in corporation with TSMC and build up a new core business pillar for them as they call it: Anime. They now own the biggest box office anime hit in history with Demon Salyer. That IP is so big, it generated 8 BILLION USD in revenue (&lt;a href=&quot;https://animesweet.com/anime/demon-slayer-the-series-unstoppable-success-topped-8-billion/&quot;&gt;https://animesweet.com/anime/demon-slayer-the-series-unstoppable-success-topped-8-billion/&lt;/a&gt;).  Granted, across different companies and with Merch, (mobile/console)games etc. but when they can create one such anime hit, they have the chance for another. Netflix for example produces --while quality anime content-- but not one of that caliber of Demon Salyer. With Sony having much closer ties to many japanese anime studios I can see them creating the defacto streaming service and having a chance for that next One Piece killer. Merch is brining in the money, not the movies itself. They already own Funimation and Crunchyroll and are currently working on combining them...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;YTD performance: 36%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Market Cap: 154B&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Past 5 years: 304%&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Turkey defies warnings and cuts interest rates]]></title><description><![CDATA[The central bank cut its one-week repo rate by 1 percentage point to 15%,
marking the third straight reduction in interest rates under governor Sahap
Kavcioglu from 19% at the start of September. The bank said many factors behind
surging consumer prices were “beyond monetary policy’s control” and…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwr6np/turkey_defies_warnings_and_cuts_interest_rates/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwr6np/turkey_defies_warnings_and_cuts_interest_rates/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 17:05:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The central bank cut its one-week repo rate by 1 percentage point to 15%, marking the third straight reduction in interest rates under governor Sahap Kavcioglu from 19% at the start of September. The bank said many factors behind surging consumer prices were “beyond monetary policy’s control” and that it would “consider” ending its cycle of rate cuts this December.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the decision Turkey’s lira plummeted about 4%, hitting 11 against the US dollar for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is this a political move by Erdogan? I do not have a great understanding of Turkish politics, however, Erdogan does not seem to be well liked by Turkish people I know and this decision seems irrational. Erdogan apparently holds the view that high interest causes inflation rather than tame it. Where else has this type of thinking been seen? Is it that common at all? This is the first time I have seen that opinion on interest rates and inflation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/2db0434d-2851-4485-850d-06cfca32ff22&quot;&gt;https://www.ft.com/content/2db0434d-2851-4485-850d-06cfca32ff22&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PYPL - Dropping more?]]></title><description><![CDATA[So I’m waiting to join the party with PYPL and these guys come and downgrade the
stock. Like a coitus interruptus, don’t tell me that they weren’t waiting to
watch it start flying like it was during the past week.

220$ they say, with all their maths and analysis and knowledge. I don’t believe
them…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwfit8/pypl_dropping_more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwfit8/pypl_dropping_more/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 16:38:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I’m waiting to join the party with PYPL and these guys come and downgrade the stock. Like a coitus interruptus, don’t tell me that they weren’t waiting to watch it start flying like it was during the past week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;220$ they say, with all their maths and analysis and knowledge. I don’t believe them though. But either if it’s that or 260$ now my question is how much will this drop if it will keep dropping. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Commodity price increases over the last year...
Gasoline: +92%
Coffee: +89%
WTI Crude: +85%
Heating Oil: +85%
Brent Crude +81%
Natural Gas: +74%
Cotton: +67%
Wheat: +38%
Corn: +34%
Copper: +33%
Sugar: +32%
Aluminum: +31%
Lumber: +20%
Soybeans: +9%
Silver: +3%
Gold: -0.2%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461343191588823048</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461343191588823048</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 15:47:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Q3 Revenue Growth, YoY % Change...
Tesla $TSLA: +57%
$AMD: +54%
NVIDIA $NVDA: +50%
Shopify $SHOP: +46%
Google $GOOGL: +41%
Facebook $FB: +35%
Apple $AAPL: +29%
Salesforce $CRM: +23%
Adobe $ADBE: +22%
Microsoft $MSFT: +22%
Netflix $NFLX: +16%
Amazon $AMZN: +15%
S&amp;P 500 $SPY: +14%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461336763713081352</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461336763713081352</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 15:47:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[TESLA GAINS bought the dip at 990 and put 200k on it.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwc4hp/tesla_gains_bought_the_dip_at_990_and_put_200k_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwc4hp/tesla_gains_bought_the_dip_at_990_and_put_200k_on/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 15:47:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Isn’t the entire market nothing but the greater fool theory?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I mean, what is a stock but some piece of paper you bought with the hope that
you can find someone who’s more of a fool than you to sell it to? Sure, some pay
dividends, but they’re a tiny fraction of the value of the stock. Am I missing
something, or are we all just a bunch of suckers looking for…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwhaoj/isnt_the_entire_market_nothing_but_the_greater/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwhaoj/isnt_the_entire_market_nothing_but_the_greater/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 14:21:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I mean, what is a stock but some piece of paper you bought with the hope that you can find someone who’s more of a fool than you to sell it to? Sure, some pay dividends, but they’re a tiny fraction of the value of the stock. Am I missing something, or are we all just a bunch of suckers looking for bigger suckers?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Former New York Jets running back Zac Stacy 
https://t.co/2yo0KnFV2K]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461230505697984516</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461230505697984516</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 13:44:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Roku stock plunges after downgrade; estimates ‘are just too damn high,’ says analyst]]></title><description><![CDATA[Shares of Roku Inc. are getting pummeled Wednesday after an analyst downgraded
the stock and suggested that investors have misinterpreted the company’s story
as of late.

“When a stock goes up on a series of strong and better than expected results,
few probing questions are ever asked as the…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwdhgz/roku_stock_plunges_after_downgrade_estimates_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwdhgz/roku_stock_plunges_after_downgrade_estimates_are/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 13:31:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares of Roku Inc. are getting pummeled Wednesday after an analyst downgraded the stock and suggested that investors have misinterpreted the company’s story as of late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“When a stock goes up on a series of strong and better than expected results, few probing questions are ever asked as the outperformance is usually a confirmation of an investment thesis,” MoffettNathanson’s Michael Nathanson wrote Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Accordingly, he argues that investors may have been too upbeat about the extent that Roku’s ROKU, -11.34% advertising performance helped drive its results while understating the impact of new streaming launches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nathanson cut his rating on Roku’s stock to sell from neutral, while lowering his price target to $220 from $330. “Simply put, we think our and the Street’s long-term revenue and earnings estimates are just too damn high,” he wrote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By his math, “it appears that Roku will need to monetize an absurdly high portion of long-tail AVOD [ad-based video-on-demand] impressions to come even close to Street numbers, which we think willbe a challenge given rising competitive pressures in TV OEMs [original equipment manufacturers] and operating systems,” he continued.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roku’s stock sank 9.8% in morning trading, putting them on track to suffer the biggest one-day selloff in a year, and to close at a one-year low.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nathanson believes Roku has “especially benefited from the launch of new DTC [direct-to-consumer] services over the past year,” but he worries about how that momentum will continue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The amount of revenue allocated to remaining performance obligations from content distribution agreements has notably increased since 2Q 2020, but we believe these performance obligations should begin to moderate,” as Roku continues to lap the launches of new streaming services, Nathanson said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By Nathanson’s estimations, Roku added about $79 million in new performance obligations during the third quarter, “whether from new distribution agreements or revaluation of existing agreements.” That amount is “meaningfully lower than the estimated $450+ million added each in 1Q 2021 and 2Q 2021,” he wrote, which he sees as reflective of a “potential slowdown” in streaming purchases and promotional spending on Roku’s service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of the 28 analysts tracked by FactSet who cover Roku’s stock, 21 have buy ratings, four have hold ratings, and three have sell ratings, with an average price target of $387.96.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shares of Roku, which are headed for the lowest close since Nov. 18, 2020, are up 5.2% over the past 12 months, but have lost 30% over the past three months. The S&amp;amp;P 500 index SPX, -0.26% has rallied 30.0% over a 12-month span and gained 5.5% over a three-month span.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/roku-stock-plunges-after-downgrade-estimates-are-just-too-damn-high-says-analyst-11637166554&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/roku-stock-plunges-after-downgrade-estimates-are-just-too-damn-high-says-analyst-11637166554&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alibaba misses expectations as earnings plunge 38% in the September quarter]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alibaba missed revenue and earnings expectations for the September quarter, as
slowing economic growth in China and the country’s crackdown on its technology
companies weighed on results.

Here’s how Alibaba did in its fiscal second-quarter, versus Refinitiv consensus
estimates:

Revenue: 200.69…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwo0q3/alibaba_misses_expectations_as_earnings_plunge_38/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwo0q3/alibaba_misses_expectations_as_earnings_plunge_38/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 13:05:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alibaba missed revenue and earnings expectations for the September quarter, as slowing economic growth in China and the country’s crackdown on its technology companies weighed on results.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s how Alibaba did in its fiscal second-quarter, versus Refinitiv consensus estimates:   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revenue: 200.69 billion yuan ($31.4 billion) vs. 204.93 billion yuan estimated, a 29% year-on-year rise.&lt;br/&gt;
EPS: 11.20 yuan vs. 12.36 yuan estimated, a 38% year-on-year decline.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alibaba has been a victim of China’s crackdown on its domestic technology industry which has seen a slew of new regulation brought in from antitrust to data protection.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While China’s tech giants have grown largely unencumbered over the past few years, Beijing has looked to clean up some of the behaviors of its corporates. Alibaba was fined $2.8 billion in April as part of an anti-monopoly probe.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, China’s economy slowed down in the third quarter of the year.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expectations were low coming into the fiscal second-quarter earnings report as a result, with analysts expecting it to be one of the most challenging quarters ever for the Chinese e-commerce giant.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company is coming off the back of Singles Day, a huge shopping event in China where e-commerce platforms push heavy discounts and rack up billions of dollars of sales.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alibaba raked in gross merchandise volume during the 11-day period totaling 540.3 billion yuan ($84.54 billion). Any revenue Alibaba gets from this event will not be reflected in the September quarter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/18/alibaba-earnings-fiscal-q2-revenue-misses-earnings-plunge.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/18/alibaba-earnings-fiscal-q2-revenue-misses-earnings-plunge.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Suffering]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwk6df/suffering/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwk6df/suffering/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 11:19:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[iTs tHe nExT tEsLa bRo]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwgkk8/its_the_next_tesla_bro/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwgkk8/its_the_next_tesla_bro/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 10:26:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[🍆💦 = 🐰🚀 -- $PLBY hitting an inflection point, and will challenge OnlyFans and Instagram in early December.]]></title><description><![CDATA[tldr: You probably have no idea what PLBY is going to do, and the market
probably doesn't either. Take advantage of that. Long term potential, and big
catalyst early December. Make money with the bunny. Beware: Lots of execution
risk.

---

There's an ancient saying, probably: Can't go tits up…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw9w1b/plby_hitting_an_inflection_point_and_will/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw9w1b/plby_hitting_an_inflection_point_and_will/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 09:46:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;tldr: You probably have no idea what PLBY is going to do, and the market probably doesn&amp;#39;t either. Take advantage of that. Long term potential, and big catalyst early December. Make money with the bunny. Beware: Lots of execution risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s an ancient saying, probably: Can&amp;#39;t go tits up investing in tits out. Since the dawn of humankind, men have been willing to shell out their hard earned money in order to suspend all disbelief that, despite the reality that they are disgusting and utterly replaceable blobs of flesh engineered strictly to carry and disperse sperm, they are sexually desirable and relevant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Playboy made its name exploiting this innate male desire and also made it culturally acceptable -- they somehow convinced people that this practice of shooting swimmers all over the planet is not morally bankrupt, not entirely meaningless and pointless, but rather: it is an &lt;em&gt;aspiration&lt;/em&gt; for both men and women to be a part of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To the dismay of the sock industry Playboy also invented a second, rather high margin, use for glossy paper. By printing images of naked women (likely also seeking the feeling of sexual desirability and relevance) on those pages, Playboy was able to sell those glossy sheets of paper for an incredible mark up... every month. They were also able to build one of the world&amp;#39;s most recognizable brands. (It&amp;#39;s estimated that the brand has 97% recall. Try to name any other brand with that kind of branding valued below $2b)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/4yop9ww188081.jpg?width=1136&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=8c89c24a3a378e34a53309c2f1342860b2e2de41&quot;&gt;From the interview within: \&amp;quot;I think any man enjoys flirtations, and if he said he didn’t, he’d be lying or he’d be a politician trying to get the extra four votes. I think everybody likes knowing he’s well responded to.\&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the times changed, and so did the time honored tradition of rubbing a quick one out between some pages and hastily disposing of the evidence. Though Viagra was able to extend and harden the founder&amp;#39;s penis, it did not, unfortunately, have a similar effect on the business. First VHS, then the internet. Before too long, sock companies were once again rejoicing as hoards of mongers fixed their eyes to screens and their hands to computer peripherals and footwear. At least we&amp;#39;re saving some trees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the popularity of Playboy faded, management tried a few retarded last ditch efforts to pep up their brand, including removing the cartoons, ending full frontal nudity, and ditching the slogan &amp;quot;Entertainment for Men&amp;quot;. It was, unsurprisingly, to no avail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Playboy&amp;#39;s last physical print was February 2016, and by Hugh Hefner&amp;#39;s death in late 2017, Playboy was basically a limp dick -- left to decay as dying publishing business with no vision behind it, leaving behind only an iconic logo, brand, and story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;1. The new Playboy&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Playboy was taken private in 2010, only to resurface publicly as a SPAC earlier this year. At the helm, CEO Ben Kohn has put a significant amount of work and thought into reviving and positioning the business to fit into today&amp;#39;s world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I won&amp;#39;t get into the details of the acquisitions and pivots PLBY has made since Ben took the helm and PLBY went public. Basically, it&amp;#39;s been a year-long revamp. The main theme of the new PLBY is to focus on high-margin direct-to-consumer ecommerce, with the recent reveal of Centerfold tying it all together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/t0jb1z2388081.png?width=1023&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=b57916204f31e0b9666548515be80c0b0d396e39&quot;&gt;Pieces set in place... and beast Centerfold on the way.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A summary of the pieces they&amp;#39;ve collected:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Licensing: leveraging the brand to collect easy tendies. Improving licensing deals is basically free money, and they&amp;#39;re making progress.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Playboy.com: High margin DTC ecommerce. It&amp;#39;s clear from sales data it&amp;#39;s not boomer-centered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yandy &amp;amp; Lovers: Sexual Wellness products. Ideally, Centerfold will drive even more revenue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Honey Birdette: High quality, high margin lingerie and swimwear. Also important: talent and logistics. Think designers and supply chain capabilities. Rather than outsourcing design and manufacturing of clothes, PLBY can keep the margin to themselves. Ideally, they&amp;#39;ll be selling a lot of this stuff as they drive customers to it from Centerfold.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NFTs: A team that&amp;#39;s proven the ability to launch NFTs and print money. Several successful projects under their belt at this point. NFT transfers provide recurring revenue via OpenSea&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;royalty&amp;quot; system. Eg, each time an NFT is traded, PLBY gets 10%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Centerfold: They acquired &amp;quot;Dream.me&amp;quot; in Oct, which provides the technology and talent of which Centerfold will be built on. The team was acquired in nearly all stock, so their interests are aligned: build a kick ass platform and profit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PLBY has its fingers in a lot of pies, but what stands out to me is how everything will fit together with Centerfold. &lt;strong&gt;Centerfold will be Playboy&amp;#39;s creator platform.&lt;/strong&gt; Think Patreon, or OnlyFans... &lt;strong&gt;except not only is there massive revenue potential in and of itself, there is the potential to drive revenue through all the other channels set in place.&lt;/strong&gt; Centerfold was announced September, with a launch date of Q2 2022... but on Oct 21 was advanced to Q4 2021, and in Q3 earnings call to &amp;quot;early December&amp;quot;. More on the Centerfold story later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Q3 Inflection Point&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s not an easy task to take a dying publishing company with a fading image and come up with a cohesive strategy to revive it, and it&amp;#39;s even harder to communicate that strategy to the market... especially in such a murky industry. If you read through the various statements of what PLBY is and its direction, you&amp;#39;ll find a lot of major (and minor) pivots along the way in the past year or two. &lt;strong&gt;However, for me, Q3 marks the point at which all the pieces are set and the real execution begins in earnest.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I mean by &amp;quot;inflection point&amp;quot; here is that the strategy is solidifying, and is showing early signs of working. The Q3 call has provided the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the direction PLBY has settled on: high-margin goods, DTC, Licensing, NFTs, and Centerfold tying it all together.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how the company plans to leverage their brand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;revenues are growing, even without Centerfold&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Centerfold is indeed going to happen, and the launch of it seems promising&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically, the strategy has been set, is showing signs of working. &lt;strong&gt;PLBY is clearly transitioning from a shell of a brand into a business that will print.&lt;/strong&gt; Centerfold will kick this all into high gear:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;And then when you couple that with CENTERFOLD, and how this flywheel all works together. CENTERFOLD is not only an unbelievably lucrative financial opportunity for the company. It also provides an ongoing relationship with the talent that we have worked with for 70 plus years. We also have access now to all of those subscribers on the CENTERFOLD platform that will benefit not only the Playboy membership, but also our commerce efforts as well. And so, all of this sort of comes together in this cohesive ecosystem or flywheel. I&amp;#39;m really excited by the potential for what we can deliver moving forward on a recurring revenue basis.&amp;quot; - Ben Kohn, CEO, Q3 earnings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps more importantly, I also think that the messaging and marketing to investors has reached an inflection point as well. Starting now, when investors ask &amp;quot;what the fuck is PLBY and why should I care&amp;quot;, a clear picture can be messaged. It&amp;#39;s shifting from &amp;quot;a once-dying publishing business that is now a sexual wellness lifestyle brand, brough public via SPAC&amp;quot; -- it&amp;#39;s more like a real business with clear strategy that can print.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the picture above, it&amp;#39;s clear that Centerfold is the meat of the sandwich, so let&amp;#39;s get into it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;2. CENTERFOLD vs OnlyFans&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/fn9vs5b488081.png?width=1018&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=443883caa4eba6904ea439895730ee94575ae247&quot;&gt;OnlyFans felt like destroying their reputation. They&amp;#39;ve since reversed this, but the damage has been done.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s incredible to me that I hadn&amp;#39;t heard about Centerfold until a few weeks ago. In fact, that&amp;#39;s what got me started down this rabbit hole: A publicly listed company is going to create an OnlyFans competitor? How the fuck have I not heard of this? &lt;strong&gt;I think the potential of Centerfold is barely priced in to PLBY&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You probably heard about OnlyFans&amp;#39; ban on sexual content... but did you hear about Centerfold? That&amp;#39;s about how priced in this is.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The potential here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publicity for the stock.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability for market to gain exposure to a thriving industry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Massive amount of recurring tendies, which the market loves.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue that could easily eclipse the rest of PLBY&amp;#39;s portfolio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Putting Playboy back into the zeitgeist and ushering in the next generation of cultural relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Memeability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dig a little deeper, and you&amp;#39;ll find the timing could not possibly be better:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OnlyFans fucked up in August by announcing a ban on sexual content (they reverted this days later). Massive reputational damage, and fears payment processing might be rug pulled.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The revelation that the OnlyFans owner is a piece of shit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stories about how OnlyFans does not vet creators properly, allowing a 14yo on the platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content creators want to ditch OnlyFans&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cultural push towards female empowerment and entrepreneurship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can you think of a better company to do this than Playboy?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retarded market offering crazy valuations for anything remotely technology or WFH based&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Launch date pushed up to early December&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Understanding the content creation business&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know the first thing you retards are going to think is &amp;quot;durr... Mixer couldn&amp;#39;t get market share from Twitch... so Centerfold gonna fail too!!&amp;quot; Ok, fuckheads, try to wrap your head around this: &lt;strong&gt;There are major differences between the Twitch/Mixer business and the OnlyFans/Centerfold business&lt;/strong&gt;. Yes, they both involve content creators and viewers. Yes, they both take a cut of subscriptions. But use your fucking wrinkles and you&amp;#39;ll see some key differences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There&amp;#39;s a reason that &amp;quot;hey whats your OF&amp;quot; is a meme, and &amp;quot;hey whats your twitch&amp;quot; isn&amp;#39;t.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Twitch/Mixer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What creators want: exposure to as wide an audience as possible. More viewers = more ad revenue, subscriptions, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What viewers want: a wide array of content. Discoverability. Time wasting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Network effect: &lt;strong&gt;MASSIVE&lt;/strong&gt;. More creators = more audience. More audience = more creators.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Structure: basically like a TV with various channels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Summary: audience draws in creators, creators draw in more viewers, a virtuous cycle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OnlyFans/Centerfold:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What creators want: a platform to handle the hosting and monetization of their content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What viewers want: a place to &amp;quot;consume content&amp;quot; of very particular creator(s)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Network effect: &lt;strong&gt;LOW&lt;/strong&gt;.  Subscriptions are driven by creators hustling their OF link. Discoverability is not required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Structure: basically separate &amp;quot;blogs&amp;quot; for each content creator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Summary: creators draw in their own audience, eg: &amp;quot;What&amp;#39;s your OF link?&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short: Twitch/Mixer business relies on both viewers and content creators joining their platform -- the more of each, the better. Massive network effect, massive moat for Twitch. &lt;strong&gt;OnlyFans/Centerfold relies, almost soley, on content creators joining their platform.&lt;/strong&gt; This is all made evident by how the sites are structured (channels vs blogs), and how they are used (think of how you&amp;#39;d find a twitch streamer vs how you&amp;#39;d find an OF creator).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;How PLBY steals market share from OnlyFans&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key question is: &lt;strong&gt;if you were a content creator trying to sell your feet pics, how do you choose which platform to use?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Reputation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#39;d probably want to choose a platform that will pay you, that will allow your content, and that is not owned by a scumbag. Let&amp;#39;s compare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OnlyFans:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In August, said they were having trouble raising money and with payment processing. As a result, &lt;strong&gt;said they would no longer allow sexual content, effective within weeks&lt;/strong&gt;. (They reversed this decision days later.) Imagine having all of your revenue suddenly pulled out from under you. Well, first imagine you made money to begin with. &lt;strong&gt;Massive, irrecoverable reputation damage.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Founder is a shithead. He made his money creating websites that would claim to have links to pedophilia and bestiality. Thankfully, it was a scam: those links went to legit porn sites and produced affiliate revenue. Imagine a person that the world is thankful is a scammer. That&amp;#39;s this guy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allowed under-18s on the platform. Google it. Not a good look, not investable, either.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overall, for better or worse, a somewhat trashy reputation to say you&amp;#39;re on OnlyFans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Playboy:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Decades long reputation of free speech, sex positivity, and sophistication.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publicly traded revenue generating company; high confidence they will keep paying your bills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not much shame in saying you were a playmate. Lots of bunny tattoos.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short... would you rather tattoo your ankle with an OnlyFans logo, or a Playboy bunny logo? And which company would you trust to pay you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Economics and the 80/20 rule&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While there are countless creators on OnlyFans, the vast majority of revenue comes from a tiny minority of creators. PLBY just needs to win those creators over. It&amp;#39;s not as monstrous of a task as you might think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;More than 300 OnlyFans creators reportedly earn at least $1 million annually, while 16,000 creators make at least $50,000 a year.&amp;quot; -CNBC article&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PLBY can offer creators more revenue, and more revenue streams:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Offer a higher rev share&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow creators to sell merchandise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow creators to sell NFTs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;3. CENTERFOLD vs Instagram&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/t7ya5hz588081.png?width=946&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=0c7c3392c43b7d2ca4a3ddd6be784c0f18b5d6de&quot;&gt;Instagram is not a fan of tits and will slam the banhammer.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With regards to Centerfold, less talked about is how it can function as a nudity friendly version of Instagram, and the potential there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instagram has a pretty strict content policy, and models are finding their accounts randomly get deleted due to TOS violations. Tens to hundreds of thousands of followers can vanish in an instant. Tumblr is gone, too -- so where&amp;#39;s a girl to go to post her new fake tits?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There is huge potential in a nudity friendly Instagram clone.&lt;/strong&gt; Playboy&amp;#39;s motto? &amp;quot;nudity is normal&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Playboy won&amp;#39;t have to rely on ads to generate revenue from Centerfold -- they can simply drive traffic to their existing assets. Lingerie. Sex toys. Centerfold subscriptions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Easy win, here, and if you go around reading DDs about PLBY and Centerfold, you&amp;#39;ll find it overlooked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;4. Centerfold Launch Progress&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Centerfold was initially announced in September, shortly after OnlyFans made their retarded announcement that they would not allow sexual content. The initial launch date was planned for Q2 2022. Google &amp;quot;playboy centerfold medium&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Oct 21, Centerfold announced the acquisition of Dream.me, a creator-driven/social media platform. Basically, a clone of Instagram. This acquisition was in all stock, and provided a skeleton for the platform, but more importantly a strongly incentivized team willing to bust their ass to get this thing out there. Launch date was move up to Q4 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then, the stock has been marching upwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q3 earnings, as hoped, provided some guidance on how things are going with Centerfold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;In general, the platform is in place and we think what we have assembled today is truly a competitive differentiator moving forward as we think about membership and CENTERFOLD. What we can offer the creative community is something that no one else can offer. And I think that&amp;#39;s referenced by the founding creators that we have signed up to launch with that represent in excess of 300 million social media followers.&amp;quot; - Q3 earnings call&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, there&amp;#39;s this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Founding creators on CENTERFOLD will bring in ~300 million social media followers, and hundreds of millions in existing GMV&amp;quot; -whossayn on theideafund&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this, in response to &amp;quot;And one super quick follow up for these early CENTERFOLD launch partners, what kinds of creators are in there?&amp;quot;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;So they are huge music stars, to former playmates, to adult stars, to artists, to other influencers, actors, celebrities. It&amp;#39;s really -- we&amp;#39;ve really been overwhelmed by the response from the creator community, and also by the diversity of the creators that we brought in. And I think it&amp;#39;s going to truly be something that&amp;#39;s unique&amp;quot; -Ben Kohn&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;5. NFTs&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ni0dz7l788081.png?width=294&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=5e06ef1abd961abf6630b7621443b13ea27d0dcd&quot;&gt; \&amp;quot;Rabbitar\&amp;quot; NFTs will grant special membership and perks to various things. What, exactly, is TBA.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t personally give a shit about NFTs, but PLBY is interesting in this regard. I&amp;#39;ll keep this brief:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Their run up to $60 was due to an NFT they launched.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They&amp;#39;ve since launched a much larger, and more interesting NFT series: Rabbitars. Sold out quickly, produced $9M in revenue, and will produce recurring revenue (10% on each transfer). No run up this time, though&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rabbitar NFT will have an IRL use: it&amp;#39;s planned to serve as &amp;quot;membership&amp;quot; to various Playboy/Centerfold things. Perks, discounts, live events... a lot of possibilities here, especially if each Rabbitar has different perks. AFAIK, no other public company has tied NFTs to real life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;6. Additional considerations&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t think PLBY has reach anywhere near its peak in terms of potential market interest, both retail and institutional. It has a lot of solid followers and believers of the stock, though:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GME O.G. and banana aficionado &lt;a href=&quot;/u/uberkikz11&quot;&gt;/u/uberkikz11&lt;/a&gt; is quite vocally bullish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google &amp;quot;hedgeye PLBY&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Just google the damn ticker and do some DD for yourself&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PLBY might represent the best ticker in the market to invest in men jerking off and women whoring themselves.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;7. ⚠️⚠️⚠️⚠️ THE BEAR CASES ⚠️⚠️⚠️⚠️&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s important to understand Centerfold is not a sure fire thing. There is &lt;strong&gt;considerable execution risk&lt;/strong&gt;. I&amp;#39;ll lay out what I think are the big &amp;quot;ifs&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Product&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flaccid launch&lt;/strong&gt;: It&amp;#39;s possible Centerfold, when launched, just sucks. It can come off as a shitty clone of Instagram or OnlyFans, and the market&amp;#39;s confidence can be shaken.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Delayed launch&lt;/strong&gt;: It&amp;#39;s a tech product, and subject to feature creep, bugs, etc. The deadline is extremely aggressive, and it&amp;#39;s possible it gets pushed back. However, guidance on release was given days ago, so it&amp;#39;s likely. But, still possible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exposure concerns&lt;/strong&gt;: investability / payment processor / etc. Despite what you might think, PLBY has a strong E.S.G. vibe to it, so I think it should be OK. They are &amp;gt;50% female employees (I think), and for better or worse, they&amp;#39;re very vocally woke. I think Ben Kohn does a great job walking the line between investable and &amp;quot;proper&amp;quot;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Policies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The biggest risks, in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shitty creators&lt;/strong&gt;: Though the pool of initial creators has been talked up by management, but not defined.  It&amp;#39;s possible they actually suck. Imagine a line-up of &amp;quot;unconventional beauty&amp;quot;. Eg, &amp;quot;body positive&amp;quot; woke bullshit that is attempted to be marketed as the new wave of sexual wellness. While this is possible, I think it&amp;#39;s unlikely. Ben Kohn knows what&amp;#39;s up.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content policy&lt;/strong&gt;. On a recent interview on FOX, where the host was an asshole, Ben Kohn stated there will be no &amp;quot;porn&amp;quot;.. or orgies on their airplane. However, the term &amp;quot;porn&amp;quot; was never defined... and he was talking with FOX, so he had to be careful what he said. In my opinion, if they allow nudity but no masturbation, that could be bad. If there&amp;#39;s no scat, probably less of a concern.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m somewhat worried about these given the amount of woke-speak of this company, but I&amp;#39;m confident management knows where the dollars are:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/skj0dm4988081.png?width=1353&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=dd4cabddc5d8399212e098288ab8e8399a68e93c&quot;&gt;Content policy is up in the air. Requires faith.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each notch up on the &amp;quot;debauchery&amp;quot; scale of porn likely captures less and less revenue. For fun, that scale might look like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;See through clothes, costumes, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frontal Nudity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pussy close-ups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Light bondage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sucking on dildos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Insertion of dildos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Butthole stuff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Penises&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Penises inside of things&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aggressive BDSM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cum&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A lot of cum all over and inside of various things&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pee-pee and poo-poo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I don&amp;#39;t even know. Feel free to comment!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The risk is they land somewhere too low on the scale to capture significant revenue and interest from OnlyFans-esque creators. Again, I trust their judgement... but I&amp;#39;d feel much more comfortable knowing the exact policy before launch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the plus side, there&amp;#39;s likely an 80/20 rule here. Going up the the scale will uncapture less and less revenue. So, even if they go pretty light, there&amp;#39;s plenty of opportunity. And, it should be noted that even if they go very light, the Centerfold vs. Instagram thesis would still hold quite strong. Creators need a home to post nudes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Insider Selling&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This last one you might have heard about if you follow the stock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some people made a big deal about a recent filing where the CEO and other insiders were granted a bunch of shares to sell. Rumors went flying that a ton of shares were about to get sold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s my understanding this is a nothingburger and par for the course. Yes, they got their shares... per their employment agreements or whatever. No, there is nothing there that is saying they will sell.  They &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; sell, but management has been clear they are in this for the long run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;8. Technicals&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Historical IV&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/rl85o1ca88081.png?width=706&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=95310a4d17798ac12f268f3947529968bace9ff3&quot;&gt;IV far lower than it was due to NFTs, despite PLBY having more catalysts right now.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given an advertised massive catalyst coming in early December, the IV30 sits at around 95%. I believe this is a massive mispricing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Price Action&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/csr85xqb88081.png?width=1817&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c3099ef24563c813f6405421dbf46fca09104990&quot;&gt;Annotated events of interest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s summary of price action this year. Notice the creep up after Centerfold was announced. I personally think this is bullish and the start of an upwards channel as we approach early December, but what the fuck do I know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Gamma&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/76uf800d88081.png?width=1194&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=b661e18dac8583348a92644e0a3e0c0aaf084f9b&quot;&gt;Modest gamma&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gamma on this one is nothing too crazy, though as a percentage of daily volume it is significant. A rush into options would likely push the price up somewhat, but I doubt a squeeze is in play.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;9. Positions and Price Target&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Positions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/36zeksle88081.png?width=643&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=ad0d3855d682b58c9a264248afbcdc888fb3b296&quot;&gt;Shares and calls. This is the way.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2000 x Shares: Safest bet. I&amp;#39;m happy locking these away and looking at them a year from now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;60 x Jan $35 calls: Anticipating a run up towards Centerfold launch (early December), giving a little extra time for bumps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;80 x Jan $40 calls: More aggressive, and hoping to capture some IV gain here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Targets&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m selling if IV30 runs above 200. Not worth that much risk. I&amp;#39;m trimming at $50, much more aggressively at $60, and out if hits $70. This is my personal preference, based on my personal risk tolerance and what I hope to gain, and is not investment advice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Other Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read the bear case, please. And do your own DD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;10. TLDR: 🍆💦 = 🐰🚀&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PLBY has loaded a lot of fuel into a rocket. OnlyFans, by being fuck-ups, also contributed some fuel to the rocket. So has Instagram. When Centerfold launches, PLBY will be igniting that rocket. If you are unaware of the company turnaround, and that Centerfold is launching soon, then it is likely not yet priced in. Despite all this... IV30 sits at 94%. I like the stock, and I&amp;#39;m jacked to the tits with shares and Jan $35 and $40. Also, afaik, so is the GME banana guy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How much longer can the market keep going up under the premise of "it's because of the low interest rate environment"?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I can't think of any good reason for the market to pullback in some kind of
"fiery crash" 15%, but I also don't understand why the market is up 37% from
it's pre-covid highs and why it continues to keep climbing at the rate it's
climbing.

I know there's a ton of people with a lot of money (in my…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwfn97/how_much_longer_can_the_market_keep_going_up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwfn97/how_much_longer_can_the_market_keep_going_up/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 07:13:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;#39;t think of any good reason for the market to pullback in some kind of &amp;quot;fiery crash&amp;quot; 15%, but I also don&amp;#39;t understand why the market is up 37% from it&amp;#39;s pre-covid highs and why it continues to keep climbing at the rate it&amp;#39;s climbing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know there&amp;#39;s a ton of people with a lot of money (in my mind, this group that people vaguely allude to all of the time as pent up money on the sidelines has to be typically families making $250k/yr+, no?) chasing returns. There&amp;#39;s nowhere else to park money, I get it. I&amp;#39;m just asking... when is that going to stop being the answer? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When are people going to run out of cash to deploy? How many people are really buying in at these levels weekly with any sizable volume? I get it, everybody here is dollar-cost-averaging $500/mo into their 401k irregardless and they want a badge of honor on how they ignore the market and are sticking to their great 30 year long investment plan. Amazing. Congratulations. My question is... is that&amp;#39;s what is driving the market up 40% in 14 months? Regular John Smith&amp;#39;s 401k on his $120k/yr salary? I doubt it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought on a good year, when earnings beat estimates and forecasts were positive and not revised downward, we could reliably expect companies to grow so much that overall the market averages 10% of growth before inflation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How the heck are we up 39% from August 2020 to now? Are the 505 companies inside of the S&amp;amp;P 39% more profitable/forward looking than they were then? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The money the Fed printed for stimulus + CoVID relief... has it left the &amp;quot;banking&amp;quot; system? It went fed -&amp;gt; banks. Are the banks lending it out? If not... I know that money &amp;quot;exists&amp;quot; on paper but... is it really in circulation? Who got it and who spent it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[EV Bubble]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rivian's IPO really opened my eyes to the bubble that is the EV market.

Let's think logically: How can general motors stock be 90b and Tesla's stock be
1T.

Let's say they eventually sell as many cars as Toyota (400b Market cap), their
current valuation is still 2x this, and they aren't even close…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvxw3l/ev_bubble/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvxw3l/ev_bubble/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 06:15:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rivian&amp;#39;s IPO really opened my eyes to the bubble that is the EV market. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s think logically: How can general motors stock be 90b and Tesla&amp;#39;s stock be 1T. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s say they eventually sell as many cars as Toyota (400b Market cap), their current valuation is still 2x this, and they aren&amp;#39;t even close to Toyota&amp;#39;s production level and probably won&amp;#39;t be for the next 5+ years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toyota&amp;#39;s production for 2021: 10 million cars &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tesla&amp;#39;s production for 2021: 627,350&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That means Toyota will produce 16x more cars this year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So my question is: 
If you were me would you dump Tesla stock?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR: Toyota will make 16x more cars this year, but its market cap is only 40% of Tesla&amp;#39;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit/Additional Note: I feel like many people are not considering the fact that all major vehicle companies will eventually adapt to fully electric vehicles on par with Telsa. Some car companies may go broke and be replaced with new EV based companies, however the big dogs like Toyota and GM will eventually catch up to Tesla. This is basic common sense. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Telsa, Nio, and Rivian are first movers but they dont have as big of a moat as people think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What do bogleheads think of investing money in the savings account in stablecoins and earning interest ?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I follow the three fund portfolio in both my 401k and Roth IRA accounts. I came
across stablecoins recently and was wondering if it is better to invest the
amount lying in my savings account ( earning 0.03% interest ) into stablecoins
and earn upto 10% by lending them ?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw28f8/what_do_bogleheads_think_of_investing_money_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw28f8/what_do_bogleheads_think_of_investing_money_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 05:27:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I follow the three fund portfolio in both my 401k and Roth IRA accounts. I came across stablecoins recently and was wondering if it is better to invest the amount lying in my savings account ( earning 0.03% interest ) into stablecoins and earn upto 10% by lending them ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Evergrande starts to liquidate assets to pay debts???]]></title><description><![CDATA[As of the press time, ChinaEvergrande falls 1.79%.

China Evergrande announced on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange that on November 17,
2021, a wholly-owned subsidiary of the company entered into an agreement with
United Resources Investment Holdings Co., Ltd., pursuant to which the seller
agreed to…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwfr5w/evergrande_starts_to_liquidate_assets_to_pay_debts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwfr5w/evergrande_starts_to_liquidate_assets_to_pay_debts/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 04:50:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As of the press time, ChinaEvergrande falls 1.79%.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;China Evergrande announced on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange that on November 17, 2021, a wholly-owned subsidiary of the company entered into an agreement with United Resources Investment Holdings Co., Ltd., pursuant to which the seller agreed to sell and sell the house and agreed to purchase Hengteng Network Group Co., Ltd. &lt;strong&gt;16.62 million issued shares&lt;/strong&gt; with a par value of &lt;strong&gt;HK$0.02 is HK$1.28 per share&lt;/strong&gt; (approximately &lt;strong&gt;24.26% discount&lt;/strong&gt; to Hengteng’s closing price of &lt;strong&gt;HK$1.69&lt;/strong&gt; per share on November 17, 2021), and the total consideration is &lt;strong&gt;HK$2.13 billion&lt;/strong&gt;. After the transaction is completed, the company will no longer hold any shares of Hanging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does this mean Evergrande already started to liquidate its assets to pay off debts???&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Housing starts slip nearly 1%, falling short of expectations]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. home builders started construction on homes at a seasonally-adjusted annual
rate of 1.52 million in October, representing a 0.7% decrease from the previous
month, the U.S. Census Bureau reported Wednesday. Compared with October 2020,
housing starts were up 0.4%. The pace of permitting for new…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qw066s/housing_starts_slip_nearly_1_falling_short_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qw066s/housing_starts_slip_nearly_1_falling_short_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 04:24:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. home builders started construction on homes at a seasonally-adjusted annual rate of 1.52 million in October, representing a 0.7% decrease from the previous month, the U.S. Census Bureau reported Wednesday. Compared with October 2020, housing starts were up 0.4%. The pace of permitting for new housing units increased in October, however. Permitting for new homes occurred at a seasonally-adjusted annual rate of 1.65 million, up 4% from September and 3.4% from a year ago. Economists polled by MarketWatch had expected housing starts to occur at a median pace of 1.63 million and building permits to come in at a median pace of 1.58 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/housing-starts-slip-nearly-1-falling-short-of-expectations-2021-11-17&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/housing-starts-slip-nearly-1-falling-short-of-expectations-2021-11-17&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Debating Non-Bogleheads]]></title><description><![CDATA[As we have heard plenty times, everybody is a genius in a bull market. This
sentiment holds especially true in the current age of crypto mania, meme stocks,
and Robinhood retail investors. Here’s my question for my fellow Bogleheads: How
do you approach discussions/debates with people who insist…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw98g3/debating_nonbogleheads/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw98g3/debating_nonbogleheads/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 03:24:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we have heard plenty times, everybody is a genius in a bull market. This sentiment holds especially true in the current age of crypto mania, meme stocks, and Robinhood retail investors. Here’s my question for my fellow Bogleheads: How do you approach discussions/debates with people who insist that they are great stock pickers and/or day traders?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Generally speaking, I find it better to not engage at all, especially since everybody has a different “investment” goal and is free to spend their money however they want. However, I do find it difficult to not engage with folks who are clearly full of crap (e.g. someone who claims they are making 10% weekly returns) or folks who are offering stock tips/advice to people you are close to (e.g. a sibling’s friend convincing him to trade options). In other words, what’s a polite way to tell these “geniuses” that they they’re not as smart as they think they are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Senate Amendment 4722: five subsidized microchip companies can bring 150,000 jobs back to America from overseas for +$53 billion in 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Senate Amendment 4722: five subsidized microchip companies currently receiving
$6 billion (deficit spending) can bring 150,000 jobs back to America from
overseas for $53 billion to be paid in 2022. In exchange, these companies issue
stock warrants worth that amount plus interest.

The specific…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwczt5/senate_amendment_4722_five_subsidized_microchip/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwczt5/senate_amendment_4722_five_subsidized_microchip/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 02:46:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senate Amendment 4722: five subsidized microchip companies currently receiving $6 billion (deficit spending) can bring 150,000 jobs back to America from overseas for $53 billion to be paid in 2022. In exchange, these companies issue stock warrants worth that amount plus interest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific companies receiving the $53 billion of taxpayer subsidies are Intel, Texas Instruments, Micron, Analog Devices, and NVIDIA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: The source is CSPAN-2 live from about 3 hours ago. This is from the SENATE not the house.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Here is a Market Recap for today Wed, November 17, 2021. Please enjoy!]]></title><description><![CDATA[PsychoMarket Recap - Wednesday, November 17, 2021

Stocks mostly drifted lower to hover below record levels, as market participants
further digested yesterday’s US retail sales report and new corporate earning
results from major retailers, which provide further data into consumer spending
patterns…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwa0xn/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_wed_november_17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwa0xn/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_wed_november_17/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 02:18:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Wednesday, November 17, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks mostly drifted lower to hover below record levels, as market participants further digested yesterday’s US retail sales report and new corporate earning results from major retailers, which provide further data into consumer spending patterns amid supply-chain disruptions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here are some key numbers for today&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY): -0.25%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nasdaq (QQQ): +0.05%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dow Jones (DIA): -0.58%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Russell 2000 (IWM): -1.27%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple (AAPL): +1.75%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Target (TGT): -4.73%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Department of Commerce released their monthly Retail Sales Report, which showed better than expected consumer spending trends as the holiday season, by far the busiest in the year, continues to play out. Here are the numbers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retail Sales: 1.7% increase vs 1.4% expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core Retail Sales: +1.6%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manufacturing Production: +1.2%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The solid report suggests that high inflation is not dampening consumer spending. Rising household wealth, thanks to a strong stock market, house prices, and rising wages appear to be cushioning consumers against the highest annual pace of inflation in roughly thirty years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Steven Wieting, Citigroup’s Global Wealth Chief Investment Strategist said, “The markets generally are looking at it [the pace of inflation], benignly - they are not discounting some longer-term inflation of more than 2.5%. You can see this in the pricing out on the yield curve of Treasuries. You can see this in the composition of the market with growth stocks not really being beaten down by any concerns about some lurch higher, tightening of monetary policy. We think that story is largely correct – it’s benign for markets. It doesn’t mean we get to repeat the returns from the past year, however.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, Target (TGT) and Lowe’s (LOW), two major retailers in the US, both reported better than expected earnings. This comes on the heels of both Walmart (WMT) and Home Depot (HD) both reporting strong earnings results earlier in the week. Here are the numbers (second number were analyst expectation):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Target (TGT)&lt;/strong&gt;: “With a strong inventory position heading into the peak of the holiday season, our team and our business are ready to serve our guests and poised to deliver continued, strong growth, through the holiday season and beyond,&amp;quot; said Target Chairman and CEO Brian Cornell in a statement. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue: $25.7 billion vs. $24.20 billion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comparable Store Sales: +12.7% vs. +8.3%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gross Margin: 28% vs. 29.80%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Operating Margin: 7.8% vs. 7.68%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diluted EPS: $3.03 vs. $2.84&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lowe’s (LOW):&lt;/strong&gt; “Our momentum continued this quarter, with U.S. sales comps up nearly 34% on a two-year basis, as our Total Home strategy is resonating with the Pro and DIY customer alike. In the quarter, we drove over 16% growth in Pro and 25% on Lowes.com. We also delivered operating margin expansion by driving productivity through disciplined operational execution and cost management”, said Lowe Chairman, President, and CEO Marvin Ellisoln. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue: $22.92 billion vs. $22.06 billion &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earnings per share: $2.73 vs. $2.36&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$1.90 billion in profits vs $692 million Q3 2020&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Same Store Sales: +2.2% vs -1.5%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The party seems over… after a blockbuster IPO, shares of EV startup Rivian (RIVN), which had a market cap of $150 billion on essentially 0 revenue, fell 15% today. In my humble opinion, I’d get out if I had profits (not playing this at all). Shares of Lucid Motors (LCID) were also down roughly 5% in sympathy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CME Group (CME) the world&amp;#39;s largest financial derivatives exchange in the world, trading everything from agricultural products, currencies, energy, interest rates, metals, stock indexes to digital currency futures, announced it was planning to move core trading systems Google Clouds, a massive move in financial markets. Until very recently, it was assumed that cloud computing was ill suited for high frequency trading, forcing these companies to build and develop complicated systems geared for time sensitive markets. If this works, it could reduce the cost of operations by a lot. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fisker (FSR), another EV startup in the market, announced an electric SUV with higher driving range than Tesla’s (TSLA) Model Y. Fisker announced the OCean Ultra SUV, which is planned to begin production next November, has a range of 340 miles and costs $50,000 compared to 300 miles and a cost of $60,000 with the Model Y&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple said Wednesday that it has created a self-service repair program that would allow customers to repair their own devices using genuine Apple parts and tools. The iPhone and Mac maker said Self Service Repair would begin in early 2022 with a focus on the most common serviced modules, including phone display, battery and camera, with additional repair options to be added later in the year. The right to repair has been a big controversy surrounding technology sold by companies. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;According to recent filings, Elon Musk is roughly halfway done with his pledge to sell 10% of his stake in Tesla (TSLA). You can see it here &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nasdaq.com/market-activity/stocks/tsla/insider-activity&quot;&gt;https://www.nasdaq.com/market-activity/stocks/tsla/insider-activity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Waymo, which is a subsidiary of Google’s parent company Alphabet, said on Wednesday it is expanding its partnership with United Parcel Service (UPS) to move freight using autonomous trucks between two of the parcel delivery company&amp;#39;s Texas facilities during the holiday season. This comes amid a shortage of delivery drivers in the US. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current price target are written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance Auto Parts (AAP) with two target raises. Stock currently around $232

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Raymond James from $265 to $275 at Strong-Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jefferies Financial from $240 to $268 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AutoDesk (ADSK) with two target raise. Stock currently around $330

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stifel Nicolaus from $340 to $365 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robert W Baird from $370 to $380 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DR Horton (DHI) target raised by Raymond James from $110 to $120 at Strong-Buy. Stock currently around $101&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enphase Energy (ENPH) with a host of target raises. Average price target $290 at Buy. Stock currently around $255&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Home Depot (HD) with a host of target raises after beating earnings. Average price target $440 at Buy. Stock currently around $394&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intuit (INTU) target raised by Wells Fargo from $625 to $710 at Overweight. Stock currently around $635&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IQVIA (IQV) with four price target raises. Stock currently around $265

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Citigroup from $300 to $320 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;KeyCorp from }$270 to $290 at Overweight&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UBS Group from $298 to $310 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jefferies Financial from $300 to $309 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lululemon (LULU) target raised by B. Riley from $466 to $548 at Buy. Stock currently around $465&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NetEase (NTES) target raised by Bank of America from $128 to $145 at Buy. Stock currently around $112&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Palo Alto Networks (PANW) target raised by Jefferies Financial from $550 to $615 at Buy. Stock currently around $514&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plug Power (PLUG) target raised by Citigroup from $35 to $56 at Buy. Stock currently around $42&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ferrari (RACE) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $265 to $350 at Overweight. Stock currently around $266&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sea Limited (SE) target raised by UBS Group from $350 to $380 at Buy. Stock currently around $315&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Square (SQ) target raised by Tigress Financial from $295 to $310 at Buy. Stock currently around $231&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Live as if you were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever.” - Mahatma Gandhi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just a thank you]]></title><description><![CDATA[Back in January 2020, I started lurking this place and listening to several
personal finance podcasts because I became interested in investing. I was such a
beginner, I had to watch a step-by-step yt video on how to use the Vanguard
website. I was worried that I had waited too long to invest, but I…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qwegy8/just_a_thank_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qwegy8/just_a_thank_you/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 02:18:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back in January 2020, I started lurking this place and listening to several personal finance podcasts because I became interested in investing. I was such a beginner, I had to watch a step-by-step yt video on how to use the Vanguard website. I was worried that I had waited too long to invest, but I persisted and set up my account so I would dollar cost average and start investing in ETFs. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the pandemic I got married and moved to a new city so I really kinda forgot about my investments until my husband said he wanted to start investing too, but was wary about doing so because he didn&amp;#39;t know what the right timing was. Because of this place, I was able to explain to him why it&amp;#39;s time IN the market not timing the market, and help him understand investment language, set up his account, and choose his portfolio. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically, thank you for helping me help another investor. Without this place, I would still be thinking investing was only for wallstreet bros and rich people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vanguard ETFs on Fidelity]]></title><description><![CDATA[I already have a Fidelity account and just getting into setting up a 4 fund
portfolio. Can I buy and manage Vanguard ETFs? What is so good about ETFs
anyway?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw6oq4/vanguard_etfs_on_fidelity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw6oq4/vanguard_etfs_on_fidelity/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 02:18:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I already have a Fidelity account and just getting into setting up a 4 fund portfolio. Can I buy and manage Vanguard ETFs? What is so good about ETFs anyway?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What % of your bonds allocation are I bonds (or EE bonds)?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I just found out about series I Bonds from a recent post here on r/Bogleheads
[/r/Bogleheads]. Thanks! 🙏

Up until now, bond allocation was 70% of the Vanguard total bond fund and 30% of
the Vanguard total international bond fund. But, yesterday I bought my first I
bonds from treasury direct.

I’m…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw1k6t/what_of_your_bonds_allocation_are_i_bonds_or_ee/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw1k6t/what_of_your_bonds_allocation_are_i_bonds_or_ee/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 02:18:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just found out about series I Bonds from a recent post here on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/Bogleheads&quot;&gt;r/Bogleheads&lt;/a&gt;. Thanks! 🙏  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Up until now, bond allocation was 70% of the Vanguard total bond fund and 30% of the Vanguard total international bond fund. But, yesterday I bought my first I bonds from treasury direct. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m wondering, what percentage of your bond allocation is in I Bonds (or EE bonds)?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stocks that people said were "Too overvalued" that just kept going up for years and years?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Off this year alone, I could count 90% of analysts saying to wait till AFTER
earnings to buy Costco bc they always fell, and of course for the first time
they actually went up after earnings and never went back down. Never got in a
position in it and kicking myself.

Same with NVDA. But I have a…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwb82k/stocks_that_people_said_were_too_overvalued_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwb82k/stocks_that_people_said_were_too_overvalued_that/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 01:44:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Off this year alone, I could count 90% of analysts saying to wait till AFTER earnings to buy Costco bc they always fell, and of course for the first time they actually went up after earnings and never went back down. Never got in a position in it and kicking myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Same with NVDA. But I have a huge stake on it but again people said it would probably tank after earnings, was a meme stock is massively overvalued and is up 3% AH after beating on everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What others historically were like this? Apple? Amazon?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[https://t.co/Tgrg5MCHDL]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461076309728280580</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461076309728280580</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 23:40:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>