<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 14:37:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[The GME Files. Take Two]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r00yce/the_gme_files_take_two/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r00yce/the_gme_files_take_two/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 13:31:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This paper has been going around investing subreddits and it is complete BS - here's why]]></title><description><![CDATA[You may have seen this paper
(https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2741701) floating around
various investment subreddits over the past week. It usually comes with the
title How to 3x the S&P CAGR with less risk | Leverage for the Long Run with
people praising it as an amazing new…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r03dsd/this_paper_has_been_going_around_investing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r03dsd/this_paper_has_been_going_around_investing/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 13:05:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;You may have seen this paper (&lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2741701&quot;&gt;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2741701&lt;/a&gt;) floating around various investment subreddits over the past week. It usually comes with the title &lt;strong&gt;How to 3x the S&amp;amp;P CAGR with less risk | Leverage for the Long Run&lt;/strong&gt; with people praising it as an amazing new strategy that requires little effort, provides a high degree of safety, and allows you to experience only the good side of leveraged ETFs. Here&amp;#39;s why it&amp;#39;s complete bullshit. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve seen the 200 SMA argument posted hundreds of times before in &lt;a href=&quot;/r/LETFs&quot;&gt;r/LETFs&lt;/a&gt;. I&amp;#39;m glad this one at least comes with a paper, but the paper is still falling for the same mistakes other believers fall for. The author is correct that volatility increases below any significant moving average (20/50/100/200), however, avoiding volatility should not be your main concern when holding unhedged leveraged ETFs. Your main concern should be flash crashes like in 1987 where the market fell 22% in one day. The author says this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chart 6 shows that historically, the worst 1% of trading days have occurred far more often than not below the Moving Average. Included in this list are the two worst days in market history: October 19th in 1987 and October 28th in 1929&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wow look at that, moving averages helped avoid the worst two days... but why? The answer is partially due to the fact that both the best and worst days will be in periods of high volatility, but it&amp;#39;s also heavily influenced by pure chance. A day like Black Monday could happen at anytime and if there wasn&amp;#39;t a choppy market leading up to it you will miss it with moving averages. An unleveraged 22% drop would be a 66% drop for the portfolio suggested in the paper. The market would then likely dip below the 200 SMA and the person would sell! Missing the entire ride back up, even if there was more to fall you&amp;#39;re not going to be left in a good place. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no macroeconomic reason that moving averages have any form of predictive power. The closest thing would be the concept of a self fulfilling prophecy which would require a massive audience of believers to have an impact (there are not nearly enough). People always use 200 SMA, but if you try to test other SMAs nearby you sometimes get significantly worse results. The 200 SMA just happens to get you out before the Dot Com crash as well as the GFC. When your entire reasoning is based on &lt;em&gt;well it did good in the past&lt;/em&gt; you&amp;#39;re overfitting by definition. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s look at another strategy that &lt;strong&gt;has&lt;/strong&gt; an economic backing - HFEA. Holding stocks and bonds together isn&amp;#39;t something that &lt;em&gt;just happens to work&lt;/em&gt; when you test it. When stocks experience uncertainty large investors move their money into the safety of bonds which forces them in the opposite direction to the stock. Stocks and bonds are slightly, but not perfectly inversely correlated &lt;strong&gt;and&lt;/strong&gt; both of them have positive expected returns. This is why they are the ideal hedge. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also want to point out that &lt;strong&gt;this is not an academic paper that came from a university&lt;/strong&gt;. It was published by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.leadlagreport.com/&quot;&gt;https://www.leadlagreport.com/&lt;/a&gt; which says on its homepage &amp;quot;Consistently win in the stock market and minimize risk regardless of market conditions&amp;quot; followed by a subscribe button. This is called bullshit and I encourage anyone who cares about honesty to call it out when shit like this is posted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Here’s to another term]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzp0b7/heres_to_another_term/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzp0b7/heres_to_another_term/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 12:37:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why are small-caps doing so bad compared to large caps ?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know they had their run at the start of the year but most of them lost 60% or
more of their value since then. Some as close as -80% and are trading under cash
value. Meanwhile large caps keep breaking record after record every few weeks.
You'd think money would flow to the undervalued small-caps…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzukbc/why_are_smallcaps_doing_so_bad_compared_to_large/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzukbc/why_are_smallcaps_doing_so_bad_compared_to_large/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 11:19:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know they had their run at the start of the year but most of them lost 60% or more of their value since then. Some as close as -80% and are trading under cash value. Meanwhile large caps keep breaking record after record every few weeks. You&amp;#39;d think money would flow to the undervalued small-caps again but it isn&amp;#39;t happening yet for some reason.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At some point high inflation/interest rates has to be priced in right ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$NYT buries yesterday’s terrorist attack, 5 Dead, 40 Injured https://t.co/F6ls3tk9p3]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462976976134754306</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462976976134754306</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 10:44:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Biden Will Tap Jerome Powell for New Term as Fed Chairman]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzm3mv/biden_will_tap_jerome_powell_for_new_term_as_fed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzm3mv/biden_will_tap_jerome_powell_for_new_term_as_fed/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 09:47:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SPY being held up by Apple and Tesla today]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzqq63/spy_being_held_up_by_apple_and_tesla_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzqq63/spy_being_held_up_by_apple_and_tesla_today/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 08:21:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[After careful consideration, fuck you.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzrqcn/after_careful_consideration_fuck_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzrqcn/after_careful_consideration_fuck_you/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 07:41:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pfizer says vaccine is 100 percent effective in adolescents *

What about the one’s it killed?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462973474952126472</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462973474952126472</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 06:51:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$138K GameStop (GME) Gain]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r036vr/138k_gamestop_gme_gain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r036vr/138k_gamestop_gme_gain/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 06:30:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[When will this sub un-ban meme stocks?]]></title><description><![CDATA[It's been nearly 11 months since meme stocks ramped in January. It's interesting
to follow and observe developments on some of those stocks, without the squeeze
talk. But it's a shame this can't be discussed in this sub, due to the sub's
strict rules on 'meme' stocks.

One of those companies appear…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r05jg5/when_will_this_sub_unban_meme_stocks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r05jg5/when_will_this_sub_unban_meme_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 06:30:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s been nearly 11 months since meme stocks ramped in January. It&amp;#39;s interesting to follow and observe developments on some of those stocks, without the squeeze talk. But it&amp;#39;s a shame this can&amp;#39;t be discussed in this sub, due to the sub&amp;#39;s strict rules on &amp;#39;meme&amp;#39; stocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of those companies appear to have an interesting developing story - sound balance sheet and poaching talent from other tech giants. Recently a senior director from Apple was also poached.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will &lt;a href=&quot;/r/stocks&quot;&gt;r/stocks&lt;/a&gt; ever denounce the ban and meme labelling of these companies?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What exactly makes a meme stock a meme? Tesla and other EV stocks have some insane valuations currently, Elon is practically a meme lord. There are cult like investor groups behind these companies. Why arent these stocks also memes?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I don't know if my portfolio can do this again...]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzxm2j/i_dont_know_if_my_portfolio_can_do_this_again/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzxm2j/i_dont_know_if_my_portfolio_can_do_this_again/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 06:00:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Disney Goes MOBA In New “Disney Melee Mania” Game]]></title><description><![CDATA[Source
[https://www.piratesandprincesses.net/disney-goes-moba-in-new-disney-melee-mania-game/]:

> A brand new 3v3 MOBA game where teams take control of various Disney & Pixar
> characters behind developed by Mighty Bear Games.

It will be offered on Apple Arcade and goal is to keep it simple…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzhy5y/disney_goes_moba_in_new_disney_melee_mania_game/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzhy5y/disney_goes_moba_in_new_disney_melee_mania_game/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 05:22:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.piratesandprincesses.net/disney-goes-moba-in-new-disney-melee-mania-game/&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A brand new 3v3 MOBA game where teams take control of various Disney &amp;amp; Pixar characters behind developed by Mighty Bear Games. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It will be offered on Apple Arcade and goal is to keep it simple (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.techradar.com/features/how-to-make-a-league-of-legends-kids-can-play-according-to-disney-melee-manias-developers&quot;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MOBA veterans may be aghast that Disney Melee Mania has no lanes, towers, computer-controlled minions, or even skill progression, but the result is the leanest version of the game type we’ve ever seen – which could be a perfect onramp for brand-new players to learn the genre.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My question isn&amp;#39;t so much specific to this game. My main question is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you think Disney will do a good job of expanding into gaming&lt;/strong&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel like Disney generally has been perhaps too cautious. Years ago they had chances to deepen their relationship with Riot Games, but they let that slip through their fingers. Now Riot has a hit on Netflix which could&amp;#39;ve been Disney&amp;#39;s. This is a big shame since Riot has an incredible universe of character and worlds that would be as good as a mini Marvel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disney has so much great IP if they can crack the gaming code, add that to their ESPN and merchandising expertise it will be huge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[85K to 850K, 10X in 2 Months & I'M NOT SELLING]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzngtn/85k_to_850k_10x_in_2_months_im_not_selling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzngtn/85k_to_850k_10x_in_2_months_im_not_selling/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 05:00:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Today "big tech" moves after Powell's nomination announcement.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I followed the market today and right after Powell got nominated by Biden some
stocks skyrocketed, NVDA hit up to $346 a share for example, while others
plummeted. Granted, the ones that skyrocketed followed the ones that went down
soon after.

Powell in the chair seems to be, as far as I seem to…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzwojf/today_big_tech_moves_after_powells_nomination/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzwojf/today_big_tech_moves_after_powells_nomination/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 04:43:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I followed the market today and right after Powell got nominated by Biden some stocks skyrocketed, NVDA hit up to $346 a share for example, while others plummeted. Granted, the ones that skyrocketed followed the ones that went down soon after.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Powell in the chair seems to be, as far as I seem to understand, &amp;quot;good for stocks&amp;quot; because of easy money and whatnot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m going to assume I either miss some event or are just failing to grasp some very basic concepts, what happened today that turned a supposedly very green day into an all-red one?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean the NASDAQ started pretty high and ended up like -1.4% when the closing bell hit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WSB discussion so far today]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzv0rx/wsb_discussion_so_far_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzv0rx/wsb_discussion_so_far_today/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 04:43:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Not stock related.. but here's a photo of me and the wall street bull. If you kiss his balls it's 5 years of good luck, and a lifetime of herpes!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzoqdd/not_stock_related_but_heres_a_photo_of_me_and_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzoqdd/not_stock_related_but_heres_a_photo_of_me_and_the/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 04:12:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Some words of advice for those who are entering stock market for the first time.]]></title><description><![CDATA[If you are a first time investor, especially a young investor, it is very easy
to fall in the trap of buying the stock that your friend, relative, or a
stranger on internet recommended. Just because someone made 1000% gains on
something doesn't mean you are going to make that.

Remember, that the…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r029h7/some_words_of_advice_for_those_who_are_entering/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r029h7/some_words_of_advice_for_those_who_are_entering/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 04:12:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are a first time investor, especially a young investor, it is very easy to fall in the trap of buying the stock that your friend, relative, or a stranger on internet recommended. Just because someone made 1000% gains on something doesn&amp;#39;t mean you are going to make that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember, that the faster any asset climbs up the faster it comes down like a house of cards. If it had no resistance going up, there is no support going down and when such stocks crack, they fall through the roof in a matter of hours, not even days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nowadays, you get ads on YouTube every 2 seconds with someone shouting in your face with so called their magic formula where their students make $500-$2000 every trade. Don&amp;#39;t fall for these snake oil salesman. If making money were that easy, nobody would work their ass off for years just to buy a house or a car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pick up a book and learn the basics of Finance. Fundamentals will help you get a handle of how to start valuing a company. While Technical charts play a role in short to medium term movements of the stock, long term is always going to be based on Fundamentals. Watch Peter Lynch&amp;#39;s videos on YouTube, he is an old school investor just like Warren Buffett, but has some really good food for thoughts in his videos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Needless to say, if you are investing in Crpto be extremely conservative. 10% of your portfolio is too much. Anything more than that, and you lose your hard earned savings very quickly if things go south.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand there is a Euphoria when you make quick money, but derivatives like Futures and Options are sure shot way of getting screwed if you don&amp;#39;t know what you are doing. Everyone has an itch to make a lot of money in a short period of time, but trust me, losing your original investment is one the worst feeling you can ever have if you earned that money by working hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don&amp;#39;t know anything at all about investing and want to start putting some money into an investment account, buy a broad market based ETF like SPY or QQQ on a regular basis. Think $100-$200-$500/month. Time in the market is always going to beat timing the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, as Warren Buffett said - Rule 1: Never lose money and Rule 2: Never forget Rule 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: Don&amp;#39;t invest blindly in Stocks that some friend/stranger recommended you. Efforts to make money quickly on Stocks, Crpto, or Derivatives (Futures and Options) without understanding the fundamentals and risks, will make you lose your hard earned money and your shirt. If you don&amp;#39;t know anything about investing, buy broad market based ETF like SPY and QQQ on a regular basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[r/Stocks Daily Discussion Monday - Nov 22, 2021]]></title><description><![CDATA[These daily discussions run from Monday to Friday including during our themed
posts.

Some helpful links:

 * Finviz [https://finviz.com/quote.ashx?t=spy] for charts, fundamentals, and
   aggregated news on individual stocks
 * Bloomberg market news [https://www.bloomberg.com/markets]
 *…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzij09/rstocks_daily_discussion_monday_nov_22_2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzij09/rstocks_daily_discussion_monday_nov_22_2021/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 04:12:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;These daily discussions run from Monday to Friday including during our themed posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some helpful links:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finviz.com/quote.ashx?t=spy&quot;&gt;Finviz&lt;/a&gt; for charts, fundamentals, and aggregated news on individual stocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/markets&quot;&gt;Bloomberg market news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;StreetInsider news:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Market+Check&quot;&gt;Market Check&lt;/a&gt; - Possibly why the market is doing what it&amp;#39;s doing including sudden spikes/dips&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Reuters&quot;&gt;Reuters aggregated&lt;/a&gt; - Global news&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a basic question, for example &amp;quot;what is EPS,&amp;quot; then google &amp;quot;investopedia EPS&amp;quot; and click the investopedia article on it; do this for everything until you have a more in depth question or just want to share what you learned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please discuss your portfolios in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?sort=new&amp;amp;q=Rate+My+Portfolio+-+r%2FStocks+Quarterly+Thread&amp;amp;t=all&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&quot;&gt;Rate My Portfolio sticky.&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See our past &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+%22r%2Fstocks+daily+discussion%22&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;daily discussions here.&lt;/a&gt;  Also links for:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Atechnicals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Technicals&lt;/a&gt; Tuesday, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Aoptions&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Options Trading&lt;/a&gt; Thursday, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Afundamentals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Fundamentals&lt;/a&gt; Friday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How Warren Protects His Pumps]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzv30q/how_warren_protects_his_pumps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzv30q/how_warren_protects_his_pumps/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 03:21:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is AMD not a good buy?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I had people on another sub jokingly make comments that buying AMD was like
“gambling”. I don’t see how this can be as it is fairly cheap compared to NVDA
and demand with the chip shortage and rise of EV’s. Am I missing something?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzqwgh/is_amd_not_a_good_buy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzqwgh/is_amd_not_a_good_buy/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 02:41:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had people on another sub jokingly make comments that buying AMD was like “gambling”. I don’t see how this can be as it is fairly cheap compared to NVDA and demand with the chip shortage and rise of EV’s. Am I missing something?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[FOR YOUR SAFETY , NETHERLANDS
https://t.co/x3yQQLST9g]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462936742965698566</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462936742965698566</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 02:07:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Here is a Market Recap for today Monday, Nov 22, 2021. Please enjoy!]]></title><description><![CDATA[PsychoMarket Recap - Monday, November 22, 2021

After trading mostly even throughout the day, the Nasdaq (QQQ) and S&P 500 (SPY)
sold off sharply in the last hour. Early in the morning, President Biden
announced this morning that Jerome Powell was renominated to lead the Federal
Reserve for another…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzxu26/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_nov_22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzxu26/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_nov_22/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 02:07:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Monday, November 22, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After trading mostly even throughout the day, the Nasdaq (QQQ) and S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) sold off sharply in the last hour. Early in the morning, President Biden announced this morning that Jerome Powell was renominated to lead the Federal Reserve for another four years. Federal Reserve Governor Lael Brainard, who was Powell’s main competitor, was nominated as the Vice-Chair. Looking ahead, market participants are waiting for more inflation data set to be released later this week. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Monday, President Biden announced he was nominating Jerome Powell for a second, four-year term as the Chair of the Federal Reserve and Fed Governor Lael Brainard as the Vice-Chair, ending weeks of speculation who would be tapped to run the nation’s Central Bank. Biden was expected to select either Powell or current Fed Governor Lael Brainard as Fed chair. Following the nomination, Powell will go before the Senate Banking Committee for approval, and if confirmed, will serve another four-year term. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eric Browne, Managing Director and Portfolio Manager at Pimco, said “I think this was largely expected by markets. Certainly there were some conversations in markets over the last couple of weeks about Brainard potentially being elevated to the Fed chair position. But by and large the expectation was for consistency. You may see a little bit of a rally on the back of this with the expectation that policy is going to remain in place and intact, and everything that’s been articulated already by the Fed is likely to continue into 2022 and beyond.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, more inflation data is set to be released later this week, which will provide further insight into the pace of inflation and any potential reactions by the Federal Reserve. The Core Personal Consumptions Expenditure (PCE) , which is Fed’s preferred measure for inflation, is set to be released Wednesday and expected to show a 4.1% year-over-year increase. This would be the biggest annual jump in roughly three decades. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Constellation Brands (STZ), the maker of Corona beer, is reportedly exploring for a deal to merge with Monster Beverage, according to a report by Bloomberg&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Private Equity Firm KKR made a $12 billion bid to bring Telecom Italia private, sending shares of the Italian telecommunication company higher.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sales of previously owned homes in the US unexpectedly jumped to their highest level in nine months in October, signaling that housing demand is picking up against a backdrop of low mortgage rates and strengthening labor markets. Existing home sales rose by 0.8% month-over-month in October, reaching an annualized rate of 6.34 million, according to data from the National Association of Realtors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General Motors (GM) bought a 25% stake in electric boat startup Pure Watercraft for $150 million. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Netflix (NFLX) said it is acquiring special effects company Scanline VFX, which is behind the effects of “Stranger Things” and “Game of Thrones”. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tesla Inc is planning to spend more than $1 billion on its new vehicle factory in Austin, Texas, and plans to complete construction by the end of this year, public filings with a Texas state agency showed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NVIDIA (NVDA) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zdnet.com/article/the-absurd-beauty-of-hacking-nvidias-gaugan-2-ai-image-machine/&quot;&gt;today detailed an AI system called GauGAN2,&lt;/a&gt; the successor to its GauGAN model, that lets users create lifelike landscape images that don’t exist using text. The program was developed by feeding 10 million high quality images into NVIDIA’s Selene supercomputer. This makes it faster and easier to turn an artist&amp;#39;s vision into a high-quality AI-generated image. The practical benefi is that one can use a few words to get a basic image together without any drawing at all and then tweak details to refine the final output. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In other news, NVIDIA is fast tracking development of its “&lt;a href=&quot;https://venturebeat.com/2021/11/22/how-nvidia-aims-to-demystify-zero-trust-security/&quot;&gt;Zero-Trust” cybersecurity platform built using their data processing units and Morpheus AI&lt;/a&gt;, citing vulnerabilities in it’s clients&amp;#39; datacenters. Very basically, traditional cybersecurity relies on a perimeter or firewall that prevents viruses and hacks from getting into your computer. Zero-trust is an architecture that also constantly monitors all the data in the system and is able to enforce strict control on what each user can do on the network. Manuvir Das, Head of Enterprise Computing at NVIDIA said, “You cannot just rely on the firewall on the outside, you have to assume that any application or any user inside your data center is a bad actor,” and “It is not our intention to be a direct provider of cybersecurity solutions. We have built the platform for cybersecurity companies to integrate into their solutions.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Options trading is poised to overtake the stock market]]></title><description><![CDATA[The average daily notional value of traded single-stock options has risen to
more than $450 billion this year, compared with about $405 billion for stocks,
according to Cboe Global Markets data

Date Options Shares 03/01/19 1.18684E+11 2.42142E+11 06/01/19 1.3115E+11
2.31267E+11 09/01/19 1.30488E+11…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzxtrh/options_trading_is_poised_to_overtake_the_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzxtrh/options_trading_is_poised_to_overtake_the_stock/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 02:07:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The average daily notional value of traded single-stock options has risen to more than $450 billion this year, compared with about $405 billion for stocks, according to Cboe Global Markets data&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Options&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Shares&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;03/01/19&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;1.18684E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2.42142E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;06/01/19&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;1.3115E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2.31267E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;09/01/19&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;1.30488E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2.21954E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;12/01/19&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;1.45258E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2.22308E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;03/01/20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2.11938E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;3.34016E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;06/01/20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2.24996E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;3.30627E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;09/01/20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;3.58914E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;3.40936E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;12/01/20&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;3.45747E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;3.57159E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;03/01/21&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;4.20737E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;4.57704E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;06/01/21&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4.10667E+11&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;3.91616E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;09/01/21&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4.68007E+11&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;3.67582E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;12/01/21&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5.88844E+11&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;4.00913E+11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nasdaq 100 ($QQQ) Breakdown...
-11% in 1 stock: $AAPL
-30% in 3 stocks: $AAPL, $MSFT, $GOOGL.
-52% in 7 stocks: $AAPL, $MSFT, $GOOGL, $AMZN, $TSLA, $NVDA, $FB.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462909283016888325</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462909283016888325</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 01:13:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The top 5 holdings in the S&amp;P 500 are now 23.5% of the index. With data going back to 1980, that's the highest we've seen. $SPX https://t.co/J9IjbzIEAH]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462904226280087562</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462904226280087562</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 01:13:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[INTEL (INTC)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lots of posts on here about INTEL, and most are bullish, however it has had a
huge fall, and it's really not far off its 52 week low ($45)

Apparently they are getting their chips back to being competitive with AMD.

AMD is over 100% up, over it's 52 week low, and touching it's highs...

WHO is…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzmj56/intel_intc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzmj56/intel_intc/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 01:12:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lots of posts on here about INTEL, and most are bullish, however it has had a huge fall, and it&amp;#39;s really not far off its 52 week low ($45)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apparently they are getting their chips back to being competitive with AMD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AMD is over 100% up, over it&amp;#39;s 52 week low, and touching it&amp;#39;s highs...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WHO is expecting INTC to fall through its 52 week low, and where is it&amp;#39;s support level, is there one, even yet?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are their still skeletons in the cupboard to worry about with INTC...?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am NOT holding any INTC or AMD...yet..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TIA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What are some common strategies of newbies that simply just doesn't work?]]></title><description><![CDATA[When I was younger, I used to hunt for stocks that dropped significantly from
its highs because I viewed them as "cheap" and those that were setting record
highs were "overpriced" and it was too late to get in. This, of course, is silly
thinking and not at all a good strategy.

What are some other…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzpv6b/what_are_some_common_strategies_of_newbies_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzpv6b/what_are_some_common_strategies_of_newbies_that/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 22:52:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I was younger, I used to hunt for stocks that dropped significantly from its highs because I viewed them as &amp;quot;cheap&amp;quot; and those that were setting record highs were &amp;quot;overpriced&amp;quot; and it was too late to get in.  This, of course, is silly thinking and not at all a good strategy.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are some other pitfalls that newbies get trapped in?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Australian Army Begins Transferring COVID-Positive Cases, Contacts To Quarantine Camps *

And people did nothing]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462896016861052928</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462896016861052928</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 22:40:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Revenue growth over the last year (TTM)...
AMC: -40%
Zoom: +100%

Net Income over the last year (TTM)...
AMC: -$2.08 billion
Zoom: +$1.14 billion

Stock price over the last year...
$AMC: +1,131%
$ZM: -45%

Data via @ycharts]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462895085440356359</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462895085440356359</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 22:40:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Brace yourselves! 😎]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzsito/brace_yourselves/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzsito/brace_yourselves/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 22:40:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[pp]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzu7sx/pp/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzu7sx/pp/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 22:24:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is your moat stock?]]></title><description><![CDATA[This refers to a company that has an economic “moat” or an advantage a company
has over its competitors which allows it to protect its market share and
profitability. Usually you’ll have to pay a premium for these companies due to
their security. I’ll go first, my moat is MSFT.]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzp6g2/what_is_your_moat_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzp6g2/what_is_your_moat_stock/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 21:17:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This refers to a company that has an economic “moat” or an advantage a company has over its competitors which allows it to protect its market share and profitability. Usually you’ll have to pay a premium for these companies due to their security. I’ll go first, my moat is MSFT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Did I miss any bad news on SOFI technologies?]]></title><description><![CDATA[SOFI reported $272 million revenue in Q3, over the consensus estimate of $251.6
million, and way over the same period in 2020 which was $201 million.

I don’t understand the reason for the share price drop. What am I missing?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzpcca/did_i_miss_any_bad_news_on_sofi_technologies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzpcca/did_i_miss_any_bad_news_on_sofi_technologies/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 20:55:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOFI reported $272 million revenue in Q3, over the consensus estimate of $251.6 million, and way over the same period in 2020 which was $201 million. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t understand the reason for the share price drop. What am I missing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The party doesn’t stop]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qznd5y/the_party_doesnt_stop/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qznd5y/the_party_doesnt_stop/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 20:42:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[/r/bogleheads enters TOP 5000 subreddits]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qzshca/rbogleheads_enters_top_5000_subreddits/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qzshca/rbogleheads_enters_top_5000_subreddits/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 20:27:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Need help: Trying to find a 7-10 page article that has been posted here a few times about the power of investing, compound investing, DCA, etc. It's a great introductory article for non-finance people.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sorry for being so vague, but I'm at a loss for details. But I remember it being
a great, digestible article for people interested in saving for their future,
but not too heavy-handed. Very approachable article.

edit: Found it, thanks /ujwqwert

http://efficientfrontier.com/ef/0adhoc/ifyoucan.pdf]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qzmoy8/need_help_trying_to_find_a_710_page_article_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qzmoy8/need_help_trying_to_find_a_710_page_article_that/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 20:01:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sorry for being so vague, but I&amp;#39;m at a loss for details.  But I remember it being a great, digestible article for people interested in saving for their future, but not too heavy-handed.  Very approachable article.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: Found it, thanks /ujwqwert&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://efficientfrontier.com/ef/0adhoc/ifyoucan.pdf&quot;&gt;http://efficientfrontier.com/ef/0adhoc/ifyoucan.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[750 -> 73k 3 week]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzoo3t/750_73k_3_week/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzoo3t/750_73k_3_week/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 19:48:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cathie Wood’s Genomics Fund Is Down 27% and Outflows Are Growing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bloomberg) -- Investors appear to be losing patience with Ark Investment
Management’s genomics fund.

The Ark Genomic Revolution ETF (ticker ARKG) has seen roughly $520 million of
outflows in November amid sinking returns. The fund is down 27% year-to-date as
investors shun health-care stocks in…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzqye4/cathie_woods_genomics_fund_is_down_27_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzqye4/cathie_woods_genomics_fund_is_down_27_and/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 19:36:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bloomberg) -- Investors appear to be losing patience with Ark Investment Management’s genomics fund.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ark Genomic Revolution ETF (ticker ARKG) has seen roughly $520 million of outflows in November amid sinking returns. The fund is down 27% year-to-date as investors shun health-care stocks in favor for more cyclical names that perform well during an economic recovery. Even so, the ETF is faring far worse than the broader biotech sector, with the Nasdaq Biotechnology Index up 10.49% this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ARKG is currently trading at $66.38 a share, lower than its level a year ago, before a steep rally that crested early in 2021. The genomics fund has also seen the largest outflows among Ark’s ETFs this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s interesting that typically loyal Ark investors have been bailing on the ETF,” said Nate Geraci, president of The ETF Store, an advisory firm. “The fund’s assets have been chopped in half since February. While I don’t believe the ETF is experiencing some of sort of ‘doom loop,’ clearly the outflows are putting downward price pressure on the underlying holdings and testing the will of remaining fund owners.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ETF’s two top holdings, Teladoc Health Inc. and Exact Sciences Corp., have weighed on its performance, with drops of some 45% and 37% this year, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The recent outflows may be due to investors looking for shorter-term opportunities into the year-end and freeing up cash, said Sylvia Jablonski, chief investment officer at Defiance ETFs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ark Chief Executive Officer Cathie Wood is well-known for prioritizing longer term investments over short-term gains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This is a 5-10 year hold. AI in health care is going to change the way that we can predict, treat and manage the most difficult diseases like cancer, and the Ark fund gives investors access to the companies who are on the cutting edge of that research,” said Jablonski.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/cathie-wood-s-genomics-fund-is-down-27-and-outflows-are-growing-1.1685602&quot;&gt;https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/cathie-wood-s-genomics-fund-is-down-27-and-outflows-are-growing-1.1685602&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WSJ: JPMorgan sues Tesla, Musk responds]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzr8i6/wsj_jpmorgan_sues_tesla_musk_responds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzr8i6/wsj_jpmorgan_sues_tesla_musk_responds/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 19:36:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why is Square trading down sharply today and underperforming recently]]></title><description><![CDATA[My Square cost basis is around $230, Cash App is very widely used by many people
and square has been expanding rapidly. But the stock just keep trading lower
everyday and now it is trading closing to 52 week low from May 2020. Does anyone
know is this a payment sector issue or reasons from Square…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzpkxg/why_is_square_trading_down_sharply_today_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzpkxg/why_is_square_trading_down_sharply_today_and/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 19:23:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My Square cost basis is around $230, Cash App is very widely used by many people and square has been expanding rapidly. But the stock just keep trading lower everyday and now it is trading closing to 52 week low from May 2020. Does anyone know is this a payment sector issue or reasons from Square itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Switching from Robinhood?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm still a young guy, but started taking investing kinda seriously after the
GameStop debacle. After making no money, I decided to start doing what I said
I'd be doing for years and make regular contributions to an ETF. I currently use
Robinhood as my brokerage and wonder if it would be better to…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qzait2/switching_from_robinhood/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qzait2/switching_from_robinhood/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 18:50:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m still a young guy, but started taking investing kinda seriously after the GameStop debacle. After making no money, I decided to start doing what I said I&amp;#39;d be doing for years and make regular contributions to an ETF. I currently use Robinhood as my brokerage and wonder if it would be better to switch to a different one or not worry about it. I only have fractional shares (&amp;gt;$1000) in a few stocks, but about $2k in VOO. Any benefit to switching, assuming I just want to regularly contribute to safer investments?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Gonna be switching to fidelity and eating the taxes from RH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[At $5.3 trillion, the market cap of Apple &amp; Microsoft is now $1.5 trillion higher than the combined market value of all the companies in the Russell 2000 ($3.8 trillion). 

$AAPL $MSFT

Data/Charting via @ycharts https://t.co/3JaSeLkmpO]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462826581550936065</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462826581550936065</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 18:35:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GoDaddy discloses recent security breach that exposed 1.2 million accounts]]></title><description><![CDATA[According to the latest SEC filing, this is what they say about the breach:

 1. Up to 1.2 million active and inactive Managed WordPress customers had their
    email address and customer number exposed. The exposure of email addresses
    presents risk of phishing attacks.
 2. The original…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qzp7gn/godaddy_discloses_recent_security_breach_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qzp7gn/godaddy_discloses_recent_security_breach_that/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 17:49:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the latest SEC filing, this is what they say about the breach:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up to 1.2 million active and inactive Managed WordPress customers had their email address and customer number exposed. The exposure of email addresses presents risk of phishing attacks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The original WordPress Admin password that was set at the time of provisioning was exposed. If those credentials were still in use, we reset those passwords.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For active customers, sFTP and database usernames and passwords were exposed. We reset both passwords.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For a subset of active customers, the SSL private key was exposed. We are in the process of issuing and installing new certificates for those customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blue Chips Can Be Your Bangers]]></title><description><![CDATA[Old news for the seasoned investors, but there are always new folks here. Just
wanted to use a real life example of how you can make steady gains without
needing to chase new stocks.

On a one year time horizon, I’m currently up around 25% in AAPL, and close to
400% in NET. However, my dollar gains…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qzp37a/blue_chips_can_be_your_bangers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qzp37a/blue_chips_can_be_your_bangers/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 17:33:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Old news for the seasoned investors, but there are always new folks here. Just wanted to use a real life example of how you can make steady gains without needing to chase new stocks. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a one year time horizon, I’m currently up around 25% in AAPL, and close to 400% in NET. However, my dollar gains in both stocks are less than 10% apart. While I may not have exploded on AAPL, DCA’ing in over a year has allowed to me to net the same dollar gains as a bet on growth stock. Just something to consider for newer investors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Fed's balance sheet hit another record high last week at $8.675 trillion.

Charting via @ycharts https://t.co/YaJbeDp0j7]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462775948110139403</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462775948110139403</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 17:04:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$115 billion mkt cap Rivian aims to sell 54,000 EVs by 2023. $77 billion mkt cap Ford aims to sell 600,000 by 2023.]]></title><description><![CDATA["As of October 31, 2021, we had approximately 55,400 R1T and R1S preorders in
the United States and Canada from customers who each paid a cancellable and
fully refundable deposit of $1,000. Based on our current production forecast, we
expect to fill our preorder backlog of approximately 55,400 by…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzftqa/115_billion_mkt_cap_rivian_aims_to_sell_54000_evs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzftqa/115_billion_mkt_cap_rivian_aims_to_sell_54000_evs/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 16:26:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;As of October 31, 2021, we had approximately 55,400 R1T and R1S preorders in the United States and Canada from customers who each paid a cancellable and fully refundable deposit of $1,000. Based on our current production forecast, we expect to fill our preorder backlog of approximately 55,400 by the end of 2023.&amp;quot; Rivian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;We are now expecting to produce 600,000 electric vehicles per year globally by end of 2023.&amp;quot;. Ford.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ford is already selling Mach-E&amp;#39;s and adding F150 Lightnings in volume next year (75K+ pre-orders already).  Oh it might just sell  5 million other vehicles a year at profit too (having made $5.7 billion net income YTD 3Q 2021, whilst Rivian revealed a $1 billion dollar loss in its IPO).  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry but the figures speak for themselves. US EV start-ups are trading at absurd valuations vs existing legacy EV producers like Ford who are already in the market selling EV&amp;#39;s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Biden picks Jerome Powell to lead the Fed for a second term as the U.S. battles Covid and inflation]]></title><description><![CDATA[Jerome Powell, who guided the Federal Reserve and the nation’s economy through
the staggering and sudden Covid-19 recession by implementing unprecedented
monetary stimulus, has been nominated for a second term as chairman of the U.S.
central bank.

President Joe Biden made the announcement Monday…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzm7ni/biden_picks_jerome_powell_to_lead_the_fed_for_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzm7ni/biden_picks_jerome_powell_to_lead_the_fed_for_a/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 15:20:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jerome Powell, who guided the Federal Reserve and the nation’s economy through the staggering and sudden Covid-19 recession by implementing unprecedented monetary stimulus, has been nominated for a second term as chairman of the U.S. central bank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;President Joe Biden made the announcement Monday morning following weeks of speculation that a push from progressives might see Fed Governor Lael Brainard get the spot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brainard instead will be vice chair of the board of governors; she had been widely expected to get a separate vice chair for supervision post, which oversees the nation’s banking system. As vice chair, she would succeed Richard Clarida, whose term expires Jan. 31, 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“As I’ve said before, we can’t just return to where we were before the pandemic, we need to build our economy back better, and I’m confident that Chair Powell and Dr. Brainard’s focus on keeping inflation low, prices stable, and delivering full employment will make our economy stronger than ever before,” Biden said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The nominations next head to the Senate for confirmation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In making the decision, Biden praised the Powell Fed for its “decisive” action in the early days of the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fed rolled out an unprecedented array of lending programs while also cutting interest rates back to near zero and instituting a monthly bond-buying program that would increase the central bank’s holdings of Treasurys and mortgage-backed securities by more than $4 trillion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Chair Powell has provided steady leadership during an unprecedently challenging period, including the biggest economic downturn in modern history and attacks on the independence of the Federal Reserve,” a White House statement said. “During that time, Lael Brainard – one of our country’s leading macroeconomists – has played a key leadership role at the Federal Reserve, working with Powell to help power our country’s robust economic recovery.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Powell carried the day, it was not without controversy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fed has been under fire lately following an ethics scandal in which multiple officials engaged in trading stocks at a time when the institution was implementing policies aimed at boosting markets. Powell disclosed that he owned municipal bonds, which the Fed also was buying, and he also bought and sold funds tied to the broad stock market indexes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the same time, the Fed has been hit with inflation running faster than it had anticipated – in fact, at the sharpest pace in 30 years. Official Fed policy since September 2020 has been to let inflation run somewhat hotter than the standard 2% target if it allows for full and inclusive employment, but prices have been rising well above that level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Powell has held to the line that inflation will cool off once factors associated with the pandemic return to normal. But the recent readings have raised questions about the so-called average inflation targeting that signaled a historic turn in central bank monetary policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The inflation also has come with a rapid economic recovery and a decline in the unemployment rate from a pandemic peak of 14.8% to its current 4.6%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The White House statement said the recovery is “a testament to the success of the President’s economic agenda, and it is a testament to decisive action by Chair Powell and the Federal Reserve to cushion the impact of the pandemic and get America’s economy back on track.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brainard emerged as a key force in the race over who would carry the Fed through the next four years. She has taken point on several issues important to the Biden administration, particularly the need for the Fed to brace the banking system against disruptive climate change events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A former undersecretary of the Treasury during the Obama administration, Brainard also has been a strong proponent of a digital dollar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The White House statement stressed the importance of progressive for the Fed in the years to come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biden said that Powell and Brainard “also share my deep belief that urgent action is needed to address the economic risks posed by climate change, and stay ahead of emerging risks in our financial system.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Fundamentally, if we want to continue to build on the economic success of this year we need stability and independence at the Federal Reserve – and I have full confidence after their trial by fire over the last 20 months that Chair Powell and Dr. Brainard will provide the strong leadership our country needs,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Political pressure, and a Covid struggle
President Donald Trump appointed Powell to the position in 2018 in somewhat of a surprise. Trump chose to pass over then-Chair Janet Yellen, an unusual move in that Fed leaders are rarely removed after just one term. Former President Barack Obama initially appointed Powell to a 14-year term as governor in 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Trump nominated Powell, he later fired withering criticism at the Fed chief when the central bank raised interest rates seven times in 2017 and 2018. The former president went as far as to call the Fed policymakers “boneheads” for trying to normalize policy as the economy recovered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for Brainard, she is now widely expected to be named vice chair of supervision, a key Fed post to oversee the nation’s banking system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fed is empowered by Congress to fulfill two mandates: Maximize U.S. employment and keep inflation stable. Its leaders, known as governors, are nominated by the president and vote on how to adjust interest rates, regulate the nation’s largest banks and monitor the health of the economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To combat the spike in unemployment and recession that began in the spring of 2020, the central bank slashed interest rates and began buying some $120 billion in Treasury bonds and mortgage-backed securities every month. It also instituted a variety of lending programs aimed at keeping fixed income markets functioning after they endured significant stress at the beginning of the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Economists credit that quick and sizable response for stabilizing financial markets and later repressing long-term interest rates. Lower interest rates make it easier for corporations to take on loans to build new factories, or for individuals to buy homes or cars. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Under Powell the Fed has placed more emphasis on having the economy operate at maximum employment,” Mike Feroli, chief U.S. economist at JPMorgan, said via email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This is a goal progressive economists have long advocated and a goal which is presumably consistent with Biden’s agenda.”  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen, one of Biden’s top economic advisors and a counselor on his Fed nominations, told CNBC earlier this month that she is happy with the Fed chief’s work. Yellen was the first woman to serve as the Fed’s chair and is the country’s first female Treasury secretary. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I talked to him about candidates and advised him to pick somebody who is experienced and credible,” Yellen said. “I think that Chair Powell has certainly done a good job.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Powell is also popular on Capitol Hill, where lawmakers on both sides of the aisle have praised his leadership and amiability since he took over for Yellen in February 2018. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The news is likely a disappointment to progressives including Sen. Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., who said in September that the Fed’s role in relaxing banking regulations in recent years makes Powell a “dangerous man” and that she would oppose his renomination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["I'm a true Boglehead, but it's time for me to be reminded... why isn't real estate better?" [BH Thread]]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qzccrf/im_a_true_boglehead_but_its_time_for_me_to_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qzccrf/im_a_true_boglehead_but_its_time_for_me_to_be/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 14:55:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rule 1: “It’s not a loss until you sell.”]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qziter/rule_1_its_not_a_loss_until_you_sell/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qziter/rule_1_its_not_a_loss_until_you_sell/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 14:12:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>