<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 15:15:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Isn’t the entire market nothing but the greater fool theory?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I mean, what is a stock but some piece of paper you bought with the hope that
you can find someone who’s more of a fool than you to sell it to? Sure, some pay
dividends, but they’re a tiny fraction of the value of the stock. Am I missing
something, or are we all just a bunch of suckers looking for…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwhaoj/isnt_the_entire_market_nothing_but_the_greater/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwhaoj/isnt_the_entire_market_nothing_but_the_greater/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 14:21:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I mean, what is a stock but some piece of paper you bought with the hope that you can find someone who’s more of a fool than you to sell it to? Sure, some pay dividends, but they’re a tiny fraction of the value of the stock. Am I missing something, or are we all just a bunch of suckers looking for bigger suckers?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Former New York Jets running back Zac Stacy 
https://t.co/2yo0KnFV2K]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461230505697984516</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461230505697984516</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 13:44:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Roku stock plunges after downgrade; estimates ‘are just too damn high,’ says analyst]]></title><description><![CDATA[Shares of Roku Inc. are getting pummeled Wednesday after an analyst downgraded
the stock and suggested that investors have misinterpreted the company’s story
as of late.

“When a stock goes up on a series of strong and better than expected results,
few probing questions are ever asked as the…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwdhgz/roku_stock_plunges_after_downgrade_estimates_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwdhgz/roku_stock_plunges_after_downgrade_estimates_are/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 13:31:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares of Roku Inc. are getting pummeled Wednesday after an analyst downgraded the stock and suggested that investors have misinterpreted the company’s story as of late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“When a stock goes up on a series of strong and better than expected results, few probing questions are ever asked as the outperformance is usually a confirmation of an investment thesis,” MoffettNathanson’s Michael Nathanson wrote Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Accordingly, he argues that investors may have been too upbeat about the extent that Roku’s ROKU, -11.34% advertising performance helped drive its results while understating the impact of new streaming launches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nathanson cut his rating on Roku’s stock to sell from neutral, while lowering his price target to $220 from $330. “Simply put, we think our and the Street’s long-term revenue and earnings estimates are just too damn high,” he wrote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By his math, “it appears that Roku will need to monetize an absurdly high portion of long-tail AVOD [ad-based video-on-demand] impressions to come even close to Street numbers, which we think willbe a challenge given rising competitive pressures in TV OEMs [original equipment manufacturers] and operating systems,” he continued.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roku’s stock sank 9.8% in morning trading, putting them on track to suffer the biggest one-day selloff in a year, and to close at a one-year low.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nathanson believes Roku has “especially benefited from the launch of new DTC [direct-to-consumer] services over the past year,” but he worries about how that momentum will continue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The amount of revenue allocated to remaining performance obligations from content distribution agreements has notably increased since 2Q 2020, but we believe these performance obligations should begin to moderate,” as Roku continues to lap the launches of new streaming services, Nathanson said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By Nathanson’s estimations, Roku added about $79 million in new performance obligations during the third quarter, “whether from new distribution agreements or revaluation of existing agreements.” That amount is “meaningfully lower than the estimated $450+ million added each in 1Q 2021 and 2Q 2021,” he wrote, which he sees as reflective of a “potential slowdown” in streaming purchases and promotional spending on Roku’s service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of the 28 analysts tracked by FactSet who cover Roku’s stock, 21 have buy ratings, four have hold ratings, and three have sell ratings, with an average price target of $387.96.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shares of Roku, which are headed for the lowest close since Nov. 18, 2020, are up 5.2% over the past 12 months, but have lost 30% over the past three months. The S&amp;amp;P 500 index SPX, -0.26% has rallied 30.0% over a 12-month span and gained 5.5% over a three-month span.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/roku-stock-plunges-after-downgrade-estimates-are-just-too-damn-high-says-analyst-11637166554&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/roku-stock-plunges-after-downgrade-estimates-are-just-too-damn-high-says-analyst-11637166554&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alibaba misses expectations as earnings plunge 38% in the September quarter]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alibaba missed revenue and earnings expectations for the September quarter, as
slowing economic growth in China and the country’s crackdown on its technology
companies weighed on results.

Here’s how Alibaba did in its fiscal second-quarter, versus Refinitiv consensus
estimates:

Revenue: 200.69…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwo0q3/alibaba_misses_expectations_as_earnings_plunge_38/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwo0q3/alibaba_misses_expectations_as_earnings_plunge_38/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 13:05:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alibaba missed revenue and earnings expectations for the September quarter, as slowing economic growth in China and the country’s crackdown on its technology companies weighed on results.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s how Alibaba did in its fiscal second-quarter, versus Refinitiv consensus estimates:   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revenue: 200.69 billion yuan ($31.4 billion) vs. 204.93 billion yuan estimated, a 29% year-on-year rise.&lt;br/&gt;
EPS: 11.20 yuan vs. 12.36 yuan estimated, a 38% year-on-year decline.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alibaba has been a victim of China’s crackdown on its domestic technology industry which has seen a slew of new regulation brought in from antitrust to data protection.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While China’s tech giants have grown largely unencumbered over the past few years, Beijing has looked to clean up some of the behaviors of its corporates. Alibaba was fined $2.8 billion in April as part of an anti-monopoly probe.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, China’s economy slowed down in the third quarter of the year.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expectations were low coming into the fiscal second-quarter earnings report as a result, with analysts expecting it to be one of the most challenging quarters ever for the Chinese e-commerce giant.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company is coming off the back of Singles Day, a huge shopping event in China where e-commerce platforms push heavy discounts and rack up billions of dollars of sales.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alibaba raked in gross merchandise volume during the 11-day period totaling 540.3 billion yuan ($84.54 billion). Any revenue Alibaba gets from this event will not be reflected in the September quarter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/18/alibaba-earnings-fiscal-q2-revenue-misses-earnings-plunge.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/18/alibaba-earnings-fiscal-q2-revenue-misses-earnings-plunge.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Suffering]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwk6df/suffering/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwk6df/suffering/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 11:19:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[iTs tHe nExT tEsLa bRo]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwgkk8/its_the_next_tesla_bro/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwgkk8/its_the_next_tesla_bro/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 10:26:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[🍆💦 = 🐰🚀 -- $PLBY hitting an inflection point, and will challenge OnlyFans and Instagram in early December.]]></title><description><![CDATA[tldr: You probably have no idea what PLBY is going to do, and the market
probably doesn't either. Take advantage of that. Long term potential, and big
catalyst early December. Make money with the bunny. Beware: Lots of execution
risk.

---

There's an ancient saying, probably: Can't go tits up…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw9w1b/plby_hitting_an_inflection_point_and_will/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw9w1b/plby_hitting_an_inflection_point_and_will/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 09:46:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;tldr: You probably have no idea what PLBY is going to do, and the market probably doesn&amp;#39;t either. Take advantage of that. Long term potential, and big catalyst early December. Make money with the bunny. Beware: Lots of execution risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s an ancient saying, probably: Can&amp;#39;t go tits up investing in tits out. Since the dawn of humankind, men have been willing to shell out their hard earned money in order to suspend all disbelief that, despite the reality that they are disgusting and utterly replaceable blobs of flesh engineered strictly to carry and disperse sperm, they are sexually desirable and relevant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Playboy made its name exploiting this innate male desire and also made it culturally acceptable -- they somehow convinced people that this practice of shooting swimmers all over the planet is not morally bankrupt, not entirely meaningless and pointless, but rather: it is an &lt;em&gt;aspiration&lt;/em&gt; for both men and women to be a part of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To the dismay of the sock industry Playboy also invented a second, rather high margin, use for glossy paper. By printing images of naked women (likely also seeking the feeling of sexual desirability and relevance) on those pages, Playboy was able to sell those glossy sheets of paper for an incredible mark up... every month. They were also able to build one of the world&amp;#39;s most recognizable brands. (It&amp;#39;s estimated that the brand has 97% recall. Try to name any other brand with that kind of branding valued below $2b)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/4yop9ww188081.jpg?width=1136&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=8c89c24a3a378e34a53309c2f1342860b2e2de41&quot;&gt;From the interview within: \&amp;quot;I think any man enjoys flirtations, and if he said he didn’t, he’d be lying or he’d be a politician trying to get the extra four votes. I think everybody likes knowing he’s well responded to.\&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the times changed, and so did the time honored tradition of rubbing a quick one out between some pages and hastily disposing of the evidence. Though Viagra was able to extend and harden the founder&amp;#39;s penis, it did not, unfortunately, have a similar effect on the business. First VHS, then the internet. Before too long, sock companies were once again rejoicing as hoards of mongers fixed their eyes to screens and their hands to computer peripherals and footwear. At least we&amp;#39;re saving some trees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the popularity of Playboy faded, management tried a few retarded last ditch efforts to pep up their brand, including removing the cartoons, ending full frontal nudity, and ditching the slogan &amp;quot;Entertainment for Men&amp;quot;. It was, unsurprisingly, to no avail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Playboy&amp;#39;s last physical print was February 2016, and by Hugh Hefner&amp;#39;s death in late 2017, Playboy was basically a limp dick -- left to decay as dying publishing business with no vision behind it, leaving behind only an iconic logo, brand, and story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;1. The new Playboy&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Playboy was taken private in 2010, only to resurface publicly as a SPAC earlier this year. At the helm, CEO Ben Kohn has put a significant amount of work and thought into reviving and positioning the business to fit into today&amp;#39;s world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I won&amp;#39;t get into the details of the acquisitions and pivots PLBY has made since Ben took the helm and PLBY went public. Basically, it&amp;#39;s been a year-long revamp. The main theme of the new PLBY is to focus on high-margin direct-to-consumer ecommerce, with the recent reveal of Centerfold tying it all together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/t0jb1z2388081.png?width=1023&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=b57916204f31e0b9666548515be80c0b0d396e39&quot;&gt;Pieces set in place... and beast Centerfold on the way.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A summary of the pieces they&amp;#39;ve collected:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Licensing: leveraging the brand to collect easy tendies. Improving licensing deals is basically free money, and they&amp;#39;re making progress.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Playboy.com: High margin DTC ecommerce. It&amp;#39;s clear from sales data it&amp;#39;s not boomer-centered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yandy &amp;amp; Lovers: Sexual Wellness products. Ideally, Centerfold will drive even more revenue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Honey Birdette: High quality, high margin lingerie and swimwear. Also important: talent and logistics. Think designers and supply chain capabilities. Rather than outsourcing design and manufacturing of clothes, PLBY can keep the margin to themselves. Ideally, they&amp;#39;ll be selling a lot of this stuff as they drive customers to it from Centerfold.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NFTs: A team that&amp;#39;s proven the ability to launch NFTs and print money. Several successful projects under their belt at this point. NFT transfers provide recurring revenue via OpenSea&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;royalty&amp;quot; system. Eg, each time an NFT is traded, PLBY gets 10%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Centerfold: They acquired &amp;quot;Dream.me&amp;quot; in Oct, which provides the technology and talent of which Centerfold will be built on. The team was acquired in nearly all stock, so their interests are aligned: build a kick ass platform and profit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PLBY has its fingers in a lot of pies, but what stands out to me is how everything will fit together with Centerfold. &lt;strong&gt;Centerfold will be Playboy&amp;#39;s creator platform.&lt;/strong&gt; Think Patreon, or OnlyFans... &lt;strong&gt;except not only is there massive revenue potential in and of itself, there is the potential to drive revenue through all the other channels set in place.&lt;/strong&gt; Centerfold was announced September, with a launch date of Q2 2022... but on Oct 21 was advanced to Q4 2021, and in Q3 earnings call to &amp;quot;early December&amp;quot;. More on the Centerfold story later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Q3 Inflection Point&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s not an easy task to take a dying publishing company with a fading image and come up with a cohesive strategy to revive it, and it&amp;#39;s even harder to communicate that strategy to the market... especially in such a murky industry. If you read through the various statements of what PLBY is and its direction, you&amp;#39;ll find a lot of major (and minor) pivots along the way in the past year or two. &lt;strong&gt;However, for me, Q3 marks the point at which all the pieces are set and the real execution begins in earnest.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I mean by &amp;quot;inflection point&amp;quot; here is that the strategy is solidifying, and is showing early signs of working. The Q3 call has provided the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the direction PLBY has settled on: high-margin goods, DTC, Licensing, NFTs, and Centerfold tying it all together.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how the company plans to leverage their brand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;revenues are growing, even without Centerfold&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Centerfold is indeed going to happen, and the launch of it seems promising&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically, the strategy has been set, is showing signs of working. &lt;strong&gt;PLBY is clearly transitioning from a shell of a brand into a business that will print.&lt;/strong&gt; Centerfold will kick this all into high gear:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;And then when you couple that with CENTERFOLD, and how this flywheel all works together. CENTERFOLD is not only an unbelievably lucrative financial opportunity for the company. It also provides an ongoing relationship with the talent that we have worked with for 70 plus years. We also have access now to all of those subscribers on the CENTERFOLD platform that will benefit not only the Playboy membership, but also our commerce efforts as well. And so, all of this sort of comes together in this cohesive ecosystem or flywheel. I&amp;#39;m really excited by the potential for what we can deliver moving forward on a recurring revenue basis.&amp;quot; - Ben Kohn, CEO, Q3 earnings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps more importantly, I also think that the messaging and marketing to investors has reached an inflection point as well. Starting now, when investors ask &amp;quot;what the fuck is PLBY and why should I care&amp;quot;, a clear picture can be messaged. It&amp;#39;s shifting from &amp;quot;a once-dying publishing business that is now a sexual wellness lifestyle brand, brough public via SPAC&amp;quot; -- it&amp;#39;s more like a real business with clear strategy that can print.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the picture above, it&amp;#39;s clear that Centerfold is the meat of the sandwich, so let&amp;#39;s get into it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;2. CENTERFOLD vs OnlyFans&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/fn9vs5b488081.png?width=1018&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=443883caa4eba6904ea439895730ee94575ae247&quot;&gt;OnlyFans felt like destroying their reputation. They&amp;#39;ve since reversed this, but the damage has been done.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s incredible to me that I hadn&amp;#39;t heard about Centerfold until a few weeks ago. In fact, that&amp;#39;s what got me started down this rabbit hole: A publicly listed company is going to create an OnlyFans competitor? How the fuck have I not heard of this? &lt;strong&gt;I think the potential of Centerfold is barely priced in to PLBY&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You probably heard about OnlyFans&amp;#39; ban on sexual content... but did you hear about Centerfold? That&amp;#39;s about how priced in this is.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The potential here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publicity for the stock.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability for market to gain exposure to a thriving industry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Massive amount of recurring tendies, which the market loves.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue that could easily eclipse the rest of PLBY&amp;#39;s portfolio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Putting Playboy back into the zeitgeist and ushering in the next generation of cultural relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Memeability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dig a little deeper, and you&amp;#39;ll find the timing could not possibly be better:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OnlyFans fucked up in August by announcing a ban on sexual content (they reverted this days later). Massive reputational damage, and fears payment processing might be rug pulled.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The revelation that the OnlyFans owner is a piece of shit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stories about how OnlyFans does not vet creators properly, allowing a 14yo on the platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content creators want to ditch OnlyFans&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cultural push towards female empowerment and entrepreneurship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can you think of a better company to do this than Playboy?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retarded market offering crazy valuations for anything remotely technology or WFH based&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Launch date pushed up to early December&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Understanding the content creation business&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know the first thing you retards are going to think is &amp;quot;durr... Mixer couldn&amp;#39;t get market share from Twitch... so Centerfold gonna fail too!!&amp;quot; Ok, fuckheads, try to wrap your head around this: &lt;strong&gt;There are major differences between the Twitch/Mixer business and the OnlyFans/Centerfold business&lt;/strong&gt;. Yes, they both involve content creators and viewers. Yes, they both take a cut of subscriptions. But use your fucking wrinkles and you&amp;#39;ll see some key differences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There&amp;#39;s a reason that &amp;quot;hey whats your OF&amp;quot; is a meme, and &amp;quot;hey whats your twitch&amp;quot; isn&amp;#39;t.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Twitch/Mixer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What creators want: exposure to as wide an audience as possible. More viewers = more ad revenue, subscriptions, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What viewers want: a wide array of content. Discoverability. Time wasting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Network effect: &lt;strong&gt;MASSIVE&lt;/strong&gt;. More creators = more audience. More audience = more creators.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Structure: basically like a TV with various channels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Summary: audience draws in creators, creators draw in more viewers, a virtuous cycle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OnlyFans/Centerfold:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What creators want: a platform to handle the hosting and monetization of their content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What viewers want: a place to &amp;quot;consume content&amp;quot; of very particular creator(s)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Network effect: &lt;strong&gt;LOW&lt;/strong&gt;.  Subscriptions are driven by creators hustling their OF link. Discoverability is not required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Structure: basically separate &amp;quot;blogs&amp;quot; for each content creator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Summary: creators draw in their own audience, eg: &amp;quot;What&amp;#39;s your OF link?&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short: Twitch/Mixer business relies on both viewers and content creators joining their platform -- the more of each, the better. Massive network effect, massive moat for Twitch. &lt;strong&gt;OnlyFans/Centerfold relies, almost soley, on content creators joining their platform.&lt;/strong&gt; This is all made evident by how the sites are structured (channels vs blogs), and how they are used (think of how you&amp;#39;d find a twitch streamer vs how you&amp;#39;d find an OF creator).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;How PLBY steals market share from OnlyFans&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key question is: &lt;strong&gt;if you were a content creator trying to sell your feet pics, how do you choose which platform to use?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Reputation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#39;d probably want to choose a platform that will pay you, that will allow your content, and that is not owned by a scumbag. Let&amp;#39;s compare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OnlyFans:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In August, said they were having trouble raising money and with payment processing. As a result, &lt;strong&gt;said they would no longer allow sexual content, effective within weeks&lt;/strong&gt;. (They reversed this decision days later.) Imagine having all of your revenue suddenly pulled out from under you. Well, first imagine you made money to begin with. &lt;strong&gt;Massive, irrecoverable reputation damage.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Founder is a shithead. He made his money creating websites that would claim to have links to pedophilia and bestiality. Thankfully, it was a scam: those links went to legit porn sites and produced affiliate revenue. Imagine a person that the world is thankful is a scammer. That&amp;#39;s this guy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allowed under-18s on the platform. Google it. Not a good look, not investable, either.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overall, for better or worse, a somewhat trashy reputation to say you&amp;#39;re on OnlyFans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Playboy:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Decades long reputation of free speech, sex positivity, and sophistication.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publicly traded revenue generating company; high confidence they will keep paying your bills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not much shame in saying you were a playmate. Lots of bunny tattoos.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short... would you rather tattoo your ankle with an OnlyFans logo, or a Playboy bunny logo? And which company would you trust to pay you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Economics and the 80/20 rule&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While there are countless creators on OnlyFans, the vast majority of revenue comes from a tiny minority of creators. PLBY just needs to win those creators over. It&amp;#39;s not as monstrous of a task as you might think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;More than 300 OnlyFans creators reportedly earn at least $1 million annually, while 16,000 creators make at least $50,000 a year.&amp;quot; -CNBC article&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PLBY can offer creators more revenue, and more revenue streams:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Offer a higher rev share&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow creators to sell merchandise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow creators to sell NFTs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;3. CENTERFOLD vs Instagram&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/t7ya5hz588081.png?width=946&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=0c7c3392c43b7d2ca4a3ddd6be784c0f18b5d6de&quot;&gt;Instagram is not a fan of tits and will slam the banhammer.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With regards to Centerfold, less talked about is how it can function as a nudity friendly version of Instagram, and the potential there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instagram has a pretty strict content policy, and models are finding their accounts randomly get deleted due to TOS violations. Tens to hundreds of thousands of followers can vanish in an instant. Tumblr is gone, too -- so where&amp;#39;s a girl to go to post her new fake tits?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There is huge potential in a nudity friendly Instagram clone.&lt;/strong&gt; Playboy&amp;#39;s motto? &amp;quot;nudity is normal&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Playboy won&amp;#39;t have to rely on ads to generate revenue from Centerfold -- they can simply drive traffic to their existing assets. Lingerie. Sex toys. Centerfold subscriptions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Easy win, here, and if you go around reading DDs about PLBY and Centerfold, you&amp;#39;ll find it overlooked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;4. Centerfold Launch Progress&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Centerfold was initially announced in September, shortly after OnlyFans made their retarded announcement that they would not allow sexual content. The initial launch date was planned for Q2 2022. Google &amp;quot;playboy centerfold medium&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Oct 21, Centerfold announced the acquisition of Dream.me, a creator-driven/social media platform. Basically, a clone of Instagram. This acquisition was in all stock, and provided a skeleton for the platform, but more importantly a strongly incentivized team willing to bust their ass to get this thing out there. Launch date was move up to Q4 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then, the stock has been marching upwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q3 earnings, as hoped, provided some guidance on how things are going with Centerfold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;In general, the platform is in place and we think what we have assembled today is truly a competitive differentiator moving forward as we think about membership and CENTERFOLD. What we can offer the creative community is something that no one else can offer. And I think that&amp;#39;s referenced by the founding creators that we have signed up to launch with that represent in excess of 300 million social media followers.&amp;quot; - Q3 earnings call&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, there&amp;#39;s this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Founding creators on CENTERFOLD will bring in ~300 million social media followers, and hundreds of millions in existing GMV&amp;quot; -whossayn on theideafund&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this, in response to &amp;quot;And one super quick follow up for these early CENTERFOLD launch partners, what kinds of creators are in there?&amp;quot;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;So they are huge music stars, to former playmates, to adult stars, to artists, to other influencers, actors, celebrities. It&amp;#39;s really -- we&amp;#39;ve really been overwhelmed by the response from the creator community, and also by the diversity of the creators that we brought in. And I think it&amp;#39;s going to truly be something that&amp;#39;s unique&amp;quot; -Ben Kohn&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;5. NFTs&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ni0dz7l788081.png?width=294&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=5e06ef1abd961abf6630b7621443b13ea27d0dcd&quot;&gt; \&amp;quot;Rabbitar\&amp;quot; NFTs will grant special membership and perks to various things. What, exactly, is TBA.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t personally give a shit about NFTs, but PLBY is interesting in this regard. I&amp;#39;ll keep this brief:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Their run up to $60 was due to an NFT they launched.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They&amp;#39;ve since launched a much larger, and more interesting NFT series: Rabbitars. Sold out quickly, produced $9M in revenue, and will produce recurring revenue (10% on each transfer). No run up this time, though&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rabbitar NFT will have an IRL use: it&amp;#39;s planned to serve as &amp;quot;membership&amp;quot; to various Playboy/Centerfold things. Perks, discounts, live events... a lot of possibilities here, especially if each Rabbitar has different perks. AFAIK, no other public company has tied NFTs to real life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;6. Additional considerations&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t think PLBY has reach anywhere near its peak in terms of potential market interest, both retail and institutional. It has a lot of solid followers and believers of the stock, though:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GME O.G. and banana aficionado &lt;a href=&quot;/u/uberkikz11&quot;&gt;/u/uberkikz11&lt;/a&gt; is quite vocally bullish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google &amp;quot;hedgeye PLBY&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Just google the damn ticker and do some DD for yourself&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PLBY might represent the best ticker in the market to invest in men jerking off and women whoring themselves.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;7. ⚠️⚠️⚠️⚠️ THE BEAR CASES ⚠️⚠️⚠️⚠️&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s important to understand Centerfold is not a sure fire thing. There is &lt;strong&gt;considerable execution risk&lt;/strong&gt;. I&amp;#39;ll lay out what I think are the big &amp;quot;ifs&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Product&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flaccid launch&lt;/strong&gt;: It&amp;#39;s possible Centerfold, when launched, just sucks. It can come off as a shitty clone of Instagram or OnlyFans, and the market&amp;#39;s confidence can be shaken.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Delayed launch&lt;/strong&gt;: It&amp;#39;s a tech product, and subject to feature creep, bugs, etc. The deadline is extremely aggressive, and it&amp;#39;s possible it gets pushed back. However, guidance on release was given days ago, so it&amp;#39;s likely. But, still possible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exposure concerns&lt;/strong&gt;: investability / payment processor / etc. Despite what you might think, PLBY has a strong E.S.G. vibe to it, so I think it should be OK. They are &amp;gt;50% female employees (I think), and for better or worse, they&amp;#39;re very vocally woke. I think Ben Kohn does a great job walking the line between investable and &amp;quot;proper&amp;quot;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Policies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The biggest risks, in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shitty creators&lt;/strong&gt;: Though the pool of initial creators has been talked up by management, but not defined.  It&amp;#39;s possible they actually suck. Imagine a line-up of &amp;quot;unconventional beauty&amp;quot;. Eg, &amp;quot;body positive&amp;quot; woke bullshit that is attempted to be marketed as the new wave of sexual wellness. While this is possible, I think it&amp;#39;s unlikely. Ben Kohn knows what&amp;#39;s up.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content policy&lt;/strong&gt;. On a recent interview on FOX, where the host was an asshole, Ben Kohn stated there will be no &amp;quot;porn&amp;quot;.. or orgies on their airplane. However, the term &amp;quot;porn&amp;quot; was never defined... and he was talking with FOX, so he had to be careful what he said. In my opinion, if they allow nudity but no masturbation, that could be bad. If there&amp;#39;s no scat, probably less of a concern.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m somewhat worried about these given the amount of woke-speak of this company, but I&amp;#39;m confident management knows where the dollars are:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/skj0dm4988081.png?width=1353&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=dd4cabddc5d8399212e098288ab8e8399a68e93c&quot;&gt;Content policy is up in the air. Requires faith.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each notch up on the &amp;quot;debauchery&amp;quot; scale of porn likely captures less and less revenue. For fun, that scale might look like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;See through clothes, costumes, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frontal Nudity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pussy close-ups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Light bondage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sucking on dildos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Insertion of dildos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Butthole stuff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Penises&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Penises inside of things&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aggressive BDSM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cum&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A lot of cum all over and inside of various things&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pee-pee and poo-poo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I don&amp;#39;t even know. Feel free to comment!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The risk is they land somewhere too low on the scale to capture significant revenue and interest from OnlyFans-esque creators. Again, I trust their judgement... but I&amp;#39;d feel much more comfortable knowing the exact policy before launch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the plus side, there&amp;#39;s likely an 80/20 rule here. Going up the the scale will uncapture less and less revenue. So, even if they go pretty light, there&amp;#39;s plenty of opportunity. And, it should be noted that even if they go very light, the Centerfold vs. Instagram thesis would still hold quite strong. Creators need a home to post nudes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Insider Selling&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This last one you might have heard about if you follow the stock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some people made a big deal about a recent filing where the CEO and other insiders were granted a bunch of shares to sell. Rumors went flying that a ton of shares were about to get sold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s my understanding this is a nothingburger and par for the course. Yes, they got their shares... per their employment agreements or whatever. No, there is nothing there that is saying they will sell.  They &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; sell, but management has been clear they are in this for the long run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;8. Technicals&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Historical IV&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/rl85o1ca88081.png?width=706&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=95310a4d17798ac12f268f3947529968bace9ff3&quot;&gt;IV far lower than it was due to NFTs, despite PLBY having more catalysts right now.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given an advertised massive catalyst coming in early December, the IV30 sits at around 95%. I believe this is a massive mispricing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Price Action&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/csr85xqb88081.png?width=1817&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c3099ef24563c813f6405421dbf46fca09104990&quot;&gt;Annotated events of interest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s summary of price action this year. Notice the creep up after Centerfold was announced. I personally think this is bullish and the start of an upwards channel as we approach early December, but what the fuck do I know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Gamma&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/76uf800d88081.png?width=1194&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=b661e18dac8583348a92644e0a3e0c0aaf084f9b&quot;&gt;Modest gamma&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gamma on this one is nothing too crazy, though as a percentage of daily volume it is significant. A rush into options would likely push the price up somewhat, but I doubt a squeeze is in play.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;9. Positions and Price Target&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Positions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/36zeksle88081.png?width=643&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=ad0d3855d682b58c9a264248afbcdc888fb3b296&quot;&gt;Shares and calls. This is the way.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2000 x Shares: Safest bet. I&amp;#39;m happy locking these away and looking at them a year from now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;60 x Jan $35 calls: Anticipating a run up towards Centerfold launch (early December), giving a little extra time for bumps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;80 x Jan $40 calls: More aggressive, and hoping to capture some IV gain here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Targets&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m selling if IV30 runs above 200. Not worth that much risk. I&amp;#39;m trimming at $50, much more aggressively at $60, and out if hits $70. This is my personal preference, based on my personal risk tolerance and what I hope to gain, and is not investment advice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Other Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read the bear case, please. And do your own DD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;10. TLDR: 🍆💦 = 🐰🚀&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PLBY has loaded a lot of fuel into a rocket. OnlyFans, by being fuck-ups, also contributed some fuel to the rocket. So has Instagram. When Centerfold launches, PLBY will be igniting that rocket. If you are unaware of the company turnaround, and that Centerfold is launching soon, then it is likely not yet priced in. Despite all this... IV30 sits at 94%. I like the stock, and I&amp;#39;m jacked to the tits with shares and Jan $35 and $40. Also, afaik, so is the GME banana guy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How much longer can the market keep going up under the premise of "it's because of the low interest rate environment"?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I can't think of any good reason for the market to pullback in some kind of
"fiery crash" 15%, but I also don't understand why the market is up 37% from
it's pre-covid highs and why it continues to keep climbing at the rate it's
climbing.

I know there's a ton of people with a lot of money (in my…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwfn97/how_much_longer_can_the_market_keep_going_up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwfn97/how_much_longer_can_the_market_keep_going_up/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 07:13:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;#39;t think of any good reason for the market to pullback in some kind of &amp;quot;fiery crash&amp;quot; 15%, but I also don&amp;#39;t understand why the market is up 37% from it&amp;#39;s pre-covid highs and why it continues to keep climbing at the rate it&amp;#39;s climbing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know there&amp;#39;s a ton of people with a lot of money (in my mind, this group that people vaguely allude to all of the time as pent up money on the sidelines has to be typically families making $250k/yr+, no?) chasing returns. There&amp;#39;s nowhere else to park money, I get it. I&amp;#39;m just asking... when is that going to stop being the answer? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When are people going to run out of cash to deploy? How many people are really buying in at these levels weekly with any sizable volume? I get it, everybody here is dollar-cost-averaging $500/mo into their 401k irregardless and they want a badge of honor on how they ignore the market and are sticking to their great 30 year long investment plan. Amazing. Congratulations. My question is... is that&amp;#39;s what is driving the market up 40% in 14 months? Regular John Smith&amp;#39;s 401k on his $120k/yr salary? I doubt it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought on a good year, when earnings beat estimates and forecasts were positive and not revised downward, we could reliably expect companies to grow so much that overall the market averages 10% of growth before inflation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How the heck are we up 39% from August 2020 to now? Are the 505 companies inside of the S&amp;amp;P 39% more profitable/forward looking than they were then? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The money the Fed printed for stimulus + CoVID relief... has it left the &amp;quot;banking&amp;quot; system? It went fed -&amp;gt; banks. Are the banks lending it out? If not... I know that money &amp;quot;exists&amp;quot; on paper but... is it really in circulation? Who got it and who spent it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[EV Bubble]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rivian's IPO really opened my eyes to the bubble that is the EV market.

Let's think logically: How can general motors stock be 90b and Tesla's stock be
1T.

Let's say they eventually sell as many cars as Toyota (400b Market cap), their
current valuation is still 2x this, and they aren't even close…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvxw3l/ev_bubble/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvxw3l/ev_bubble/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 06:15:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rivian&amp;#39;s IPO really opened my eyes to the bubble that is the EV market. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s think logically: How can general motors stock be 90b and Tesla&amp;#39;s stock be 1T. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s say they eventually sell as many cars as Toyota (400b Market cap), their current valuation is still 2x this, and they aren&amp;#39;t even close to Toyota&amp;#39;s production level and probably won&amp;#39;t be for the next 5+ years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toyota&amp;#39;s production for 2021: 10 million cars &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tesla&amp;#39;s production for 2021: 627,350&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That means Toyota will produce 16x more cars this year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So my question is: 
If you were me would you dump Tesla stock?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR: Toyota will make 16x more cars this year, but its market cap is only 40% of Tesla&amp;#39;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit/Additional Note: I feel like many people are not considering the fact that all major vehicle companies will eventually adapt to fully electric vehicles on par with Telsa. Some car companies may go broke and be replaced with new EV based companies, however the big dogs like Toyota and GM will eventually catch up to Tesla. This is basic common sense. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Telsa, Nio, and Rivian are first movers but they dont have as big of a moat as people think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What do bogleheads think of investing money in the savings account in stablecoins and earning interest ?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I follow the three fund portfolio in both my 401k and Roth IRA accounts. I came
across stablecoins recently and was wondering if it is better to invest the
amount lying in my savings account ( earning 0.03% interest ) into stablecoins
and earn upto 10% by lending them ?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw28f8/what_do_bogleheads_think_of_investing_money_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw28f8/what_do_bogleheads_think_of_investing_money_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 05:27:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I follow the three fund portfolio in both my 401k and Roth IRA accounts. I came across stablecoins recently and was wondering if it is better to invest the amount lying in my savings account ( earning 0.03% interest ) into stablecoins and earn upto 10% by lending them ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Evergrande starts to liquidate assets to pay debts???]]></title><description><![CDATA[As of the press time, ChinaEvergrande falls 1.79%.

China Evergrande announced on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange that on November 17,
2021, a wholly-owned subsidiary of the company entered into an agreement with
United Resources Investment Holdings Co., Ltd., pursuant to which the seller
agreed to…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwfr5w/evergrande_starts_to_liquidate_assets_to_pay_debts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwfr5w/evergrande_starts_to_liquidate_assets_to_pay_debts/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 04:50:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As of the press time, ChinaEvergrande falls 1.79%.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;China Evergrande announced on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange that on November 17, 2021, a wholly-owned subsidiary of the company entered into an agreement with United Resources Investment Holdings Co., Ltd., pursuant to which the seller agreed to sell and sell the house and agreed to purchase Hengteng Network Group Co., Ltd. &lt;strong&gt;16.62 million issued shares&lt;/strong&gt; with a par value of &lt;strong&gt;HK$0.02 is HK$1.28 per share&lt;/strong&gt; (approximately &lt;strong&gt;24.26% discount&lt;/strong&gt; to Hengteng’s closing price of &lt;strong&gt;HK$1.69&lt;/strong&gt; per share on November 17, 2021), and the total consideration is &lt;strong&gt;HK$2.13 billion&lt;/strong&gt;. After the transaction is completed, the company will no longer hold any shares of Hanging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does this mean Evergrande already started to liquidate its assets to pay off debts???&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Housing starts slip nearly 1%, falling short of expectations]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. home builders started construction on homes at a seasonally-adjusted annual
rate of 1.52 million in October, representing a 0.7% decrease from the previous
month, the U.S. Census Bureau reported Wednesday. Compared with October 2020,
housing starts were up 0.4%. The pace of permitting for new…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qw066s/housing_starts_slip_nearly_1_falling_short_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qw066s/housing_starts_slip_nearly_1_falling_short_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 04:24:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. home builders started construction on homes at a seasonally-adjusted annual rate of 1.52 million in October, representing a 0.7% decrease from the previous month, the U.S. Census Bureau reported Wednesday. Compared with October 2020, housing starts were up 0.4%. The pace of permitting for new housing units increased in October, however. Permitting for new homes occurred at a seasonally-adjusted annual rate of 1.65 million, up 4% from September and 3.4% from a year ago. Economists polled by MarketWatch had expected housing starts to occur at a median pace of 1.63 million and building permits to come in at a median pace of 1.58 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/housing-starts-slip-nearly-1-falling-short-of-expectations-2021-11-17&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/housing-starts-slip-nearly-1-falling-short-of-expectations-2021-11-17&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Debating Non-Bogleheads]]></title><description><![CDATA[As we have heard plenty times, everybody is a genius in a bull market. This
sentiment holds especially true in the current age of crypto mania, meme stocks,
and Robinhood retail investors. Here’s my question for my fellow Bogleheads: How
do you approach discussions/debates with people who insist…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw98g3/debating_nonbogleheads/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw98g3/debating_nonbogleheads/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 03:24:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we have heard plenty times, everybody is a genius in a bull market. This sentiment holds especially true in the current age of crypto mania, meme stocks, and Robinhood retail investors. Here’s my question for my fellow Bogleheads: How do you approach discussions/debates with people who insist that they are great stock pickers and/or day traders?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Generally speaking, I find it better to not engage at all, especially since everybody has a different “investment” goal and is free to spend their money however they want. However, I do find it difficult to not engage with folks who are clearly full of crap (e.g. someone who claims they are making 10% weekly returns) or folks who are offering stock tips/advice to people you are close to (e.g. a sibling’s friend convincing him to trade options). In other words, what’s a polite way to tell these “geniuses” that they they’re not as smart as they think they are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Senate Amendment 4722: five subsidized microchip companies can bring 150,000 jobs back to America from overseas for +$53 billion in 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[Senate Amendment 4722: five subsidized microchip companies currently receiving
$6 billion (deficit spending) can bring 150,000 jobs back to America from
overseas for $53 billion to be paid in 2022. In exchange, these companies issue
stock warrants worth that amount plus interest.

The specific…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwczt5/senate_amendment_4722_five_subsidized_microchip/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwczt5/senate_amendment_4722_five_subsidized_microchip/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 02:46:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senate Amendment 4722: five subsidized microchip companies currently receiving $6 billion (deficit spending) can bring 150,000 jobs back to America from overseas for $53 billion to be paid in 2022. In exchange, these companies issue stock warrants worth that amount plus interest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific companies receiving the $53 billion of taxpayer subsidies are Intel, Texas Instruments, Micron, Analog Devices, and NVIDIA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: The source is CSPAN-2 live from about 3 hours ago. This is from the SENATE not the house.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Here is a Market Recap for today Wed, November 17, 2021. Please enjoy!]]></title><description><![CDATA[PsychoMarket Recap - Wednesday, November 17, 2021

Stocks mostly drifted lower to hover below record levels, as market participants
further digested yesterday’s US retail sales report and new corporate earning
results from major retailers, which provide further data into consumer spending
patterns…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwa0xn/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_wed_november_17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwa0xn/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_wed_november_17/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 02:18:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Wednesday, November 17, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks mostly drifted lower to hover below record levels, as market participants further digested yesterday’s US retail sales report and new corporate earning results from major retailers, which provide further data into consumer spending patterns amid supply-chain disruptions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here are some key numbers for today&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY): -0.25%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nasdaq (QQQ): +0.05%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dow Jones (DIA): -0.58%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Russell 2000 (IWM): -1.27%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple (AAPL): +1.75%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Target (TGT): -4.73%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Department of Commerce released their monthly Retail Sales Report, which showed better than expected consumer spending trends as the holiday season, by far the busiest in the year, continues to play out. Here are the numbers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retail Sales: 1.7% increase vs 1.4% expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core Retail Sales: +1.6%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manufacturing Production: +1.2%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The solid report suggests that high inflation is not dampening consumer spending. Rising household wealth, thanks to a strong stock market, house prices, and rising wages appear to be cushioning consumers against the highest annual pace of inflation in roughly thirty years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Steven Wieting, Citigroup’s Global Wealth Chief Investment Strategist said, “The markets generally are looking at it [the pace of inflation], benignly - they are not discounting some longer-term inflation of more than 2.5%. You can see this in the pricing out on the yield curve of Treasuries. You can see this in the composition of the market with growth stocks not really being beaten down by any concerns about some lurch higher, tightening of monetary policy. We think that story is largely correct – it’s benign for markets. It doesn’t mean we get to repeat the returns from the past year, however.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, Target (TGT) and Lowe’s (LOW), two major retailers in the US, both reported better than expected earnings. This comes on the heels of both Walmart (WMT) and Home Depot (HD) both reporting strong earnings results earlier in the week. Here are the numbers (second number were analyst expectation):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Target (TGT)&lt;/strong&gt;: “With a strong inventory position heading into the peak of the holiday season, our team and our business are ready to serve our guests and poised to deliver continued, strong growth, through the holiday season and beyond,&amp;quot; said Target Chairman and CEO Brian Cornell in a statement. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue: $25.7 billion vs. $24.20 billion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comparable Store Sales: +12.7% vs. +8.3%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gross Margin: 28% vs. 29.80%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Operating Margin: 7.8% vs. 7.68%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diluted EPS: $3.03 vs. $2.84&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lowe’s (LOW):&lt;/strong&gt; “Our momentum continued this quarter, with U.S. sales comps up nearly 34% on a two-year basis, as our Total Home strategy is resonating with the Pro and DIY customer alike. In the quarter, we drove over 16% growth in Pro and 25% on Lowes.com. We also delivered operating margin expansion by driving productivity through disciplined operational execution and cost management”, said Lowe Chairman, President, and CEO Marvin Ellisoln. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue: $22.92 billion vs. $22.06 billion &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earnings per share: $2.73 vs. $2.36&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$1.90 billion in profits vs $692 million Q3 2020&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Same Store Sales: +2.2% vs -1.5%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The party seems over… after a blockbuster IPO, shares of EV startup Rivian (RIVN), which had a market cap of $150 billion on essentially 0 revenue, fell 15% today. In my humble opinion, I’d get out if I had profits (not playing this at all). Shares of Lucid Motors (LCID) were also down roughly 5% in sympathy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CME Group (CME) the world&amp;#39;s largest financial derivatives exchange in the world, trading everything from agricultural products, currencies, energy, interest rates, metals, stock indexes to digital currency futures, announced it was planning to move core trading systems Google Clouds, a massive move in financial markets. Until very recently, it was assumed that cloud computing was ill suited for high frequency trading, forcing these companies to build and develop complicated systems geared for time sensitive markets. If this works, it could reduce the cost of operations by a lot. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fisker (FSR), another EV startup in the market, announced an electric SUV with higher driving range than Tesla’s (TSLA) Model Y. Fisker announced the OCean Ultra SUV, which is planned to begin production next November, has a range of 340 miles and costs $50,000 compared to 300 miles and a cost of $60,000 with the Model Y&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple said Wednesday that it has created a self-service repair program that would allow customers to repair their own devices using genuine Apple parts and tools. The iPhone and Mac maker said Self Service Repair would begin in early 2022 with a focus on the most common serviced modules, including phone display, battery and camera, with additional repair options to be added later in the year. The right to repair has been a big controversy surrounding technology sold by companies. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;According to recent filings, Elon Musk is roughly halfway done with his pledge to sell 10% of his stake in Tesla (TSLA). You can see it here &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nasdaq.com/market-activity/stocks/tsla/insider-activity&quot;&gt;https://www.nasdaq.com/market-activity/stocks/tsla/insider-activity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Waymo, which is a subsidiary of Google’s parent company Alphabet, said on Wednesday it is expanding its partnership with United Parcel Service (UPS) to move freight using autonomous trucks between two of the parcel delivery company&amp;#39;s Texas facilities during the holiday season. This comes amid a shortage of delivery drivers in the US. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current price target are written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance Auto Parts (AAP) with two target raises. Stock currently around $232

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Raymond James from $265 to $275 at Strong-Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jefferies Financial from $240 to $268 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AutoDesk (ADSK) with two target raise. Stock currently around $330

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stifel Nicolaus from $340 to $365 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robert W Baird from $370 to $380 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DR Horton (DHI) target raised by Raymond James from $110 to $120 at Strong-Buy. Stock currently around $101&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enphase Energy (ENPH) with a host of target raises. Average price target $290 at Buy. Stock currently around $255&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Home Depot (HD) with a host of target raises after beating earnings. Average price target $440 at Buy. Stock currently around $394&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intuit (INTU) target raised by Wells Fargo from $625 to $710 at Overweight. Stock currently around $635&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IQVIA (IQV) with four price target raises. Stock currently around $265

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Citigroup from $300 to $320 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;KeyCorp from }$270 to $290 at Overweight&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UBS Group from $298 to $310 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jefferies Financial from $300 to $309 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lululemon (LULU) target raised by B. Riley from $466 to $548 at Buy. Stock currently around $465&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NetEase (NTES) target raised by Bank of America from $128 to $145 at Buy. Stock currently around $112&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Palo Alto Networks (PANW) target raised by Jefferies Financial from $550 to $615 at Buy. Stock currently around $514&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plug Power (PLUG) target raised by Citigroup from $35 to $56 at Buy. Stock currently around $42&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ferrari (RACE) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $265 to $350 at Overweight. Stock currently around $266&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sea Limited (SE) target raised by UBS Group from $350 to $380 at Buy. Stock currently around $315&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Square (SQ) target raised by Tigress Financial from $295 to $310 at Buy. Stock currently around $231&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Live as if you were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever.” - Mahatma Gandhi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just a thank you]]></title><description><![CDATA[Back in January 2020, I started lurking this place and listening to several
personal finance podcasts because I became interested in investing. I was such a
beginner, I had to watch a step-by-step yt video on how to use the Vanguard
website. I was worried that I had waited too long to invest, but I…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qwegy8/just_a_thank_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qwegy8/just_a_thank_you/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 02:18:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back in January 2020, I started lurking this place and listening to several personal finance podcasts because I became interested in investing. I was such a beginner, I had to watch a step-by-step yt video on how to use the Vanguard website. I was worried that I had waited too long to invest, but I persisted and set up my account so I would dollar cost average and start investing in ETFs. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the pandemic I got married and moved to a new city so I really kinda forgot about my investments until my husband said he wanted to start investing too, but was wary about doing so because he didn&amp;#39;t know what the right timing was. Because of this place, I was able to explain to him why it&amp;#39;s time IN the market not timing the market, and help him understand investment language, set up his account, and choose his portfolio. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically, thank you for helping me help another investor. Without this place, I would still be thinking investing was only for wallstreet bros and rich people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vanguard ETFs on Fidelity]]></title><description><![CDATA[I already have a Fidelity account and just getting into setting up a 4 fund
portfolio. Can I buy and manage Vanguard ETFs? What is so good about ETFs
anyway?]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw6oq4/vanguard_etfs_on_fidelity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw6oq4/vanguard_etfs_on_fidelity/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 02:18:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I already have a Fidelity account and just getting into setting up a 4 fund portfolio. Can I buy and manage Vanguard ETFs? What is so good about ETFs anyway?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What % of your bonds allocation are I bonds (or EE bonds)?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I just found out about series I Bonds from a recent post here on r/Bogleheads
[/r/Bogleheads]. Thanks! 🙏

Up until now, bond allocation was 70% of the Vanguard total bond fund and 30% of
the Vanguard total international bond fund. But, yesterday I bought my first I
bonds from treasury direct.

I’m…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw1k6t/what_of_your_bonds_allocation_are_i_bonds_or_ee/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw1k6t/what_of_your_bonds_allocation_are_i_bonds_or_ee/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 02:18:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just found out about series I Bonds from a recent post here on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/Bogleheads&quot;&gt;r/Bogleheads&lt;/a&gt;. Thanks! 🙏  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Up until now, bond allocation was 70% of the Vanguard total bond fund and 30% of the Vanguard total international bond fund. But, yesterday I bought my first I bonds from treasury direct. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m wondering, what percentage of your bond allocation is in I Bonds (or EE bonds)?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stocks that people said were "Too overvalued" that just kept going up for years and years?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Off this year alone, I could count 90% of analysts saying to wait till AFTER
earnings to buy Costco bc they always fell, and of course for the first time
they actually went up after earnings and never went back down. Never got in a
position in it and kicking myself.

Same with NVDA. But I have a…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwb82k/stocks_that_people_said_were_too_overvalued_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwb82k/stocks_that_people_said_were_too_overvalued_that/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 01:44:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Off this year alone, I could count 90% of analysts saying to wait till AFTER earnings to buy Costco bc they always fell, and of course for the first time they actually went up after earnings and never went back down. Never got in a position in it and kicking myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Same with NVDA. But I have a huge stake on it but again people said it would probably tank after earnings, was a meme stock is massively overvalued and is up 3% AH after beating on everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What others historically were like this? Apple? Amazon?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[https://t.co/Tgrg5MCHDL]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461076309728280580</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461076309728280580</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 23:40:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Asset manager at Wells Fargo trades daily but underperforms the indexes]]></title><description><![CDATA[A friend left about $1M over a bit more than a year with an asset manager at
Wells Fargo. The activity on the account shows shares bought and sold in various
companies and ETFs, almost daily (and several transactions in a day). I forgot
the exact performance numbers, but account growth was under 20%…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw8ghp/asset_manager_at_wells_fargo_trades_daily_but/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw8ghp/asset_manager_at_wells_fargo_trades_daily_but/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 22:35:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A friend left about $1M over a bit more than a year with an asset manager at Wells Fargo. The activity on the account shows shares bought and sold in various companies and ETFs, almost daily (and several transactions in a day). I forgot the exact performance numbers, but account growth was under 20% compared to 23% in QQQ during the same period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The asset manager claims that the account has much less risk so it&amp;#39;s all good etc. Also, he said there is no fee on the trades - they&amp;#39;re all fee-free. He claims the performance is already in the ballpark and will only get better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder of course about a number of things about all this, but mainly it&amp;#39;s the frequent trades. What advantage does the asset manager get from trading frequently assuming they are fee-free? Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I'll just add a little more air to the bubble, it won't pop...]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw3wyn/ill_just_add_a_little_more_air_to_the_bubble_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw3wyn/ill_just_add_a_little_more_air_to_the_bubble_it/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 22:18:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nvidia easily beats earnings expectations on strong gaming and data center sales]]></title><description><![CDATA[Revenue: $7.1 billion versus $6.81 billion expected.

Earnings per share: $1.17 versus $1.11 expected.

Gaming revenue: $3.22 billion versus $3.18 billion expected.

Data Center revenue: $2.94 billion versus $2.69 billion expected.

The company's stock was up more than 3% following the report.

"The…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qw9gzs/nvidia_easily_beats_earnings_expectations_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qw9gzs/nvidia_easily_beats_earnings_expectations_on/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 22:18:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revenue&lt;/strong&gt;: $7.1 billion versus $6.81 billion expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Earnings per share&lt;/strong&gt;: $1.17 versus $1.11 expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gaming revenue&lt;/strong&gt;: $3.22 billion versus $3.18 billion expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Center revenue&lt;/strong&gt;: $2.94 billion versus $2.69 billion expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company&amp;#39;s stock was up more than 3% following the report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;The third quarter was outstanding, with record revenue,” Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang said in a statement. “Demand for NVIDIA AI is surging, driven by hyperscale and cloud scale-out, and broadening adoption by more than 25,000 companies. NVIDIA RTX has reinvented computer graphics with ray tracing and AI, and is the ideal upgrade for the large, growing market of gamers and creators, as well as designers and professionals building home workstations.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company also issued a bullish forecast for revenue in the current quarter ending in January.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nvidia said it expects to report around $7.4 billion in the current quarter, ending in January, higher than analyst expectations of $6.86 billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-q-3-earnings-2022-203256956.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-q-3-earnings-2022-203256956.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/nvidia-nvda-earnings-q3-2022.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/nvidia-nvda-earnings-q3-2022.html&lt;/a&gt; (I took the guidance from here)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is the next "cloud computing"?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Investing in cloud computing 5-10 years ago would've made you multiple baggers.

I don't literally mean what will replace cloud computing next, but in your
opinion, what is the next niche area like this that will explode over the next
5-10 years?

Electric vehicles are obviously the hot topic right…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw71tf/what_is_the_next_cloud_computing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw71tf/what_is_the_next_cloud_computing/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 21:29:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investing in cloud computing 5-10 years ago would&amp;#39;ve made you multiple baggers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t literally mean what will replace cloud computing next, but in your opinion, what is the next niche area like this that will explode over the next 5-10 years?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Electric vehicles are obviously the hot topic right now but I am just not in on that bandwagon, so I&amp;#39;m curious to hear what y&amp;#39;all think could be next?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not even looking to hear about specific stocks just the industry but feel free to share those as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[sold AMC today - this hurts.]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is really more of a rant/lament, so if you don't want to hear it, feel free
to keep scrolling.

Anyhow, I put $500 into AMC back in 2020 hoping for a 6-7x return in 1 - 2 yrs.
As luck would have it, this became one of the meme stocks and it shot up to $70.
Excited to be part of the movement, I…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qw5q85/sold_amc_today_this_hurts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qw5q85/sold_amc_today_this_hurts/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 21:13:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is really more of a rant/lament, so if you don&amp;#39;t want to hear it, feel free to keep scrolling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyhow, I put $500 into AMC back in 2020 hoping for a 6-7x return in 1 - 2 yrs. As luck would have it, this became one of the meme stocks and it shot up to $70. Excited to be part of the movement, I hung on, joined the AMC stock forum and stayed in as it dipped back down and down. But it&amp;#39;s just gotten to a point where it doesn&amp;#39;t make responsible sense for me to keep it anymore in hopes of another price surge up to $60 and beyond, when the last few months&amp;#39; price surges only go up ~$40 and I&amp;#39;m sitting on ~14x and have real life bills to pay, including a major medical bill. So, I bit today&amp;#39;s price surge past $40 and sold, I know it was the responsible thing to do - but damn this hurts. Really wanted to be a part of the next a-p-e nation win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: so i posted here bc i figured the other forums would hate on me for selling.  I know this was the responsible thing to do, but it would&amp;#39;ve been nice to hang in there with the rest of a-p-e nation - but don&amp;#39;t have the extra $$ to be doing that right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit 2: want to add, despite my decision to sell, i think this whole memestock phenomenon is so cool and when i&amp;#39;m old with grandkids, it&amp;#39;ll be cool to look back and say that I was a part of it even for a little bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How will the influx of Covid investors affect the next big market downturn?]]></title><description><![CDATA[It's no secret that the number of retail investors has increased immensely since
the start of Covid, when everyone wanted on the money printing train. The
question now becomes, how will all of these investors (who have only ever been
around during one of the greatest bull markets in history) react…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw3asn/how_will_the_influx_of_covid_investors_affect_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw3asn/how_will_the_influx_of_covid_investors_affect_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 20:53:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s no secret that the number of retail investors has increased immensely since the start of Covid, when everyone wanted on the money printing train. The question now becomes, how will all of these investors (who have only ever been around during one of the greatest bull markets in history) react to the next major downturn?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It could be tomorrow, it could be in 5 years, but I believe there&amp;#39;s going to be substantially more panic than usual when it arrives. Could be an excellent opportunity for more seasoned, rational investors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hopefully they get back to me before the market closes.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw5eog/hopefully_they_get_back_to_me_before_the_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw5eog/hopefully_they_get_back_to_me_before_the_market/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 20:40:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ford's shares in Rivian, that's sells no cars, now worth $17.5 billion vs its own $79 billion mkt cap, despite it selling 1.4 million cars to 3Q 2021]]></title><description><![CDATA[So at close Ford's mkt cap was only $79 billion, despite it selling 1.4 million
cars in the first three quarters of 2021. It also has over 150,000 pre-orders
for its F150 Lightening for 2022 and had sold 21,700 Mach-E's at the end of
October.

Ford owns 102 million shares (it should sell them…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvybd6/fords_shares_in_rivian_thats_sells_no_cars_now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvybd6/fords_shares_in_rivian_thats_sells_no_cars_now/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 20:25:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So at close Ford&amp;#39;s mkt cap was only $79 billion, despite it selling 1.4 million cars in the first three quarters of 2021.  It also has over 150,000 pre-orders for its F150 Lightening for 2022 and had sold 21,700 Mach-E&amp;#39;s at the end of October.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ford owns 102 million shares (it should sell them sharpish at this price) worth an incredible $17.5 billion in Rivian that has sold a couple of hundred cars to employees to date. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s not absurd at all. I mean Rivian had a massive 13,000 orders at end of 3Q (giggle).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I seriously wonder how many Rivian investors know that Ford has a massive stake.  I hope it sells it very soon as a Ford shareholder.  Those funds can quickly be put to use massively outselling Rivian in BEV&amp;#39;s by even larger multiples in 2022, 2023, 2024....(basically forever).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The US stock market has genuinely lost its marbles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nvidia Reports Earnings Today. Here’s What to Expect]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nvidia is set to report third-quarter earnings results after the market closes
on Wednesday. With shares hovering around record highs, it will take a
blockbuster report to move the needle for investors. Nvidia stock rose 0.6% to
$302.03 in Tuesday trading. Shares surged earlier this month as…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvw3t4/nvidia_reports_earnings_today_heres_what_to_expect/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvw3t4/nvidia_reports_earnings_today_heres_what_to_expect/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 20:25:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nvidia is set to report third-quarter earnings results after the market closes on Wednesday. With shares hovering around record highs, it will take a blockbuster report to move the needle for investors. Nvidia stock rose 0.6% to $302.03 in Tuesday trading. Shares surged earlier this month as investors bought in on hype surrounding Nvidia’s financial prospects amid billions in investment, most notably from Facebook ‘s newly rebranded parent Meta Platforms (FB), to build a theorized next phase of the internet called the metaverse. Not even renewed scrutiny in the U.K. related to its proposed acquisition of chip designer Arm could stop the graphics card stock’s 131% year-to-date run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the third quarter, analysts polled by FactSet forecast adjusted earnings of $1.11 a share and sales of $6.82 billion. The earnings report or outlook may need to be a blowout for the stock to continue rising. Though 34 of the 43 analysts listed by FactSet have Buy or equivalent ratings, the stock’s mean price target is $280.70. Bullish analysts will either need to raise their targets or downgrade the stock if shares hold above their targets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/articles/nvidia-stock-earnings-preview-51637101805?mod=mw_latestnews&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/articles/nvidia-stock-earnings-preview-51637101805?mod=mw_latestnews&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Canoo and rumored Walmart deal]]></title><description><![CDATA[Canoo ($GOEV) is up 23% this morning due to rumors that it has landed Walmart as
a partner. This rumor started because Canoo moved its headquarter to
Bentonville, the home of Walmart headquarters. Canoo also teased during its
earnings call that it will be building some prototypes for an unnamed…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvy3j9/canoo_and_rumored_walmart_deal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvy3j9/canoo_and_rumored_walmart_deal/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 19:44:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canoo ($GOEV) is up 23% this morning due to rumors that it has landed Walmart as a partner. This rumor started because Canoo moved its headquarter to Bentonville, the home of Walmart headquarters. Canoo also teased during its earnings call that it will be building some prototypes for an unnamed partner, which of course the internet jumped on the idea that it must be Walmart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m a little skeptical of this, since Walmart already has other car partners like Ford and Gatik. Does it make sense to add Canoo?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My thesis is that Canoo is a decent speculative stock even if it doesn&amp;#39;t have this Walmart deal. There&amp;#39;s lots of other tailwinds such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The infrastructure bill.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Canoo fills a niche that&amp;#39;s not directly competitive against Rivian or Tesla (and definitely not Lucid). For example Canoo would be great for local governments and schools which will be forced to go green and would like vehicles with low maintenance costs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The market is hungry for EV stock right now. And at sub $20 this is something people can feel good throwing a few bucks in and hold for years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Possible cons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worried that Canoo doesn&amp;#39;t manufacture it&amp;#39;s own vehicles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Canoo already had one hyped up story with the acquisition talks with Apple. If this Walmart thing go south investors will &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; hate Canoo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Possible discussion topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are there &lt;em&gt;other&lt;/em&gt; possible reasons to move to Bentonville? Perhaps that city offer huge incentives not seen elsewhere, or maybe it&amp;#39;s actually a great hub of manufacturing. Anyone in that area know?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;How does Canoo stack up against other EV &amp;quot;hype&amp;quot; stocks right now?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclosure: I bought some Canoo this morning, and I kinda like their aesthetic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Metaverse ??]]></title><description><![CDATA[Is the industry at large grossly overestimating people's appetite to spend X
amount of time in a video game?

I actually watched facebook's entire presentation on meta. I've also been in
what other companies are referring to as "metaverses" currently such as Roblox,
second life etc.



Am I missing…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvta30/metaverse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvta30/metaverse/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 18:46:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is the industry at large grossly overestimating people&amp;#39;s appetite to spend X amount of time in a video game?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I actually watched facebook&amp;#39;s entire presentation on meta. I&amp;#39;ve also been in what other companies are referring to as &amp;quot;metaverses&amp;quot; currently such as Roblox, second life etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Am I missing something here? I used to be an avid gamer myself. But my current age I dont have the mental or physical will power to play a game when I get home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m just tired as hell. Its been a drag for my significant other, since we were both avid gamers together.  But its just the reality.. I&amp;#39;m way too tired to play anything on the weekends. Luckily, I just spectate whatever she&amp;#39;s playing and I guess I get my gaming fix there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question remains though. I know my anecdotal experience isnt going to be very useful but I&amp;#39;m just wondering how everybody else feels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I saw the FB meta video, all +1 hour of it, and I just thought.. wow. Who would want to be logged into a video game with that shit on your face for multiple hours??&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it just me? Am I just an old fart?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also vaguely reminds me of the 3d movies phase as well. Everybody thought we&amp;#39;d be lining up to see these 3d movies forever but people quickly got tired of that too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amazon to stop accepting Visa credit cards issued in the UK, citing high fees]]></title><description><![CDATA[> KEY POINTS
> 
> Amazon has told some customers that, from Jan. 19 onward, the company will no
> longer accept Visa credit cards issued in Britain.
> 
> The e-commerce giant cited high fees charged by the payment processor.
> 
> Visa said it was “very disappointed that Amazon is threatening to…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw4ca8/amazon_to_stop_accepting_visa_credit_cards_issued/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw4ca8/amazon_to_stop_accepting_visa_credit_cards_issued/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 18:33:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KEY POINTS&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon has told some customers that, from Jan. 19 onward, the company will no longer accept Visa credit cards issued in Britain.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The e-commerce giant cited high fees charged by the payment processor.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visa said it was “very disappointed that Amazon is threatening to restrict consumer choice in the future.”&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LONDON — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AMZN&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; plans to stop accepting payments made via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/V&quot;&gt;Visa&lt;/a&gt; credit cards issued in the U.K. starting next year.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The e-commerce giant has told some customers that, from Jan. 19 onward, the company will no longer accept Visa credit cards issued in Britain ” due to the high fees Visa charges for processing credit card transactions.”&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Visa shares fell 2.5% in U.S. premarket trading.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visa earlier this year hiked the interchange fees it charges merchants for processing digital transactions between the U.K. and the European Union.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After Brexit, an EU cap on interchange fees no longer applies in the U.K., allowing card networks to raise their charges.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/MA&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mastercard&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;has also increased its U.K.-EU interchange fees.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon customers were told they will still be able to use debit cards — including those issued by Visa — and non-Visa credit cards like Mastercard and&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AXP&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;American Express&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;. Users are being encouraged to update their default payment method ahead of the changes.&lt;/strong&gt; The news was first reported by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-17/amazon-will-stop-accepting-visa-credit-cards-issued-in-the-u-k?srnd=technology-vp&quot;&gt;Bloomberg&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Visa said it was “very disappointed that Amazon is threatening to restrict consumer choice in the future.”  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“U.K. shoppers can use their Visa debit and credit cards at Amazon U.K. today and throughout the holiday season,” a Visa spokesperson told CNBC.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We have a long-standing relationship with Amazon, and we continue to work toward a resolution, so our cardholders can use their preferred Visa credit cards at Amazon U.K. without Amazon-imposed restrictions come January 2022.”  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon blasted Visa for its high card charges. “The cost of accepting card payments continues to be an obstacle for businesses striving to provide the best prices for customers,” a spokesperson for the company told CNBC.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“These costs should be going down over time with technological advancements, but instead they continue to stay high or even rise.”&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The move could be viewed as a way for Amazon to get some bargaining power over Visa to lower its fees. The payments firm also charges businesses scheme fees to become part of its network.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While smaller retailers aren’t in a position to negotiate, Amazon — given its size — may have better luck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/amazon-to-stop-accepting-visa-credit-cards-issued-in-the-uk.html&quot;&gt;CNBC&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/finance/quote/V:NYSE&quot;&gt;Visa is down about 5%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Still a GEM]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw1iz3/still_a_gem/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw1iz3/still_a_gem/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 17:54:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Currently at all-time highs:

-The stock mkt
-GDP
-Household net worth
-Housing prices
-Retail sales
-Jobs available

Yet consumer sentiment is crashing

Strange times

https://t.co/CCSzf8DXG3]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460752388617289731</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460752388617289731</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 17:42:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[China Evergrande founder sells mansions and private jets to cover debts]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvx70d/china_evergrande_founder_sells_mansions_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvx70d/china_evergrande_founder_sells_mansions_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 17:42:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Are you buying the dip? 

$BTC $ETH $SOL

👇]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460602142985760774</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460602142985760774</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 16:35:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Going to tell my boss to “Go fuck yourself , I own Lucid !”]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvykva/going_to_tell_my_boss_to_go_fuck_yourself_i_own/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvykva/going_to_tell_my_boss_to_go_fuck_yourself_i_own/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 16:33:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wild times we live in]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvzney/wild_times_we_live_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvzney/wild_times_we_live_in/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 16:33:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[First time with calls. Absolutely zero idea what I'm doing, am I doing it right? Also, how do I make money from this?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvo1pr/first_time_with_calls_absolutely_zero_idea_what/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvo1pr/first_time_with_calls_absolutely_zero_idea_what/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 15:26:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lucid Motors 40k Shares]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvprvj/lucid_motors_40k_shares/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvprvj/lucid_motors_40k_shares/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 15:26:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Whats worse than a bubble?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvy6j5/whats_worse_than_a_bubble/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvy6j5/whats_worse_than_a_bubble/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:59:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amazon to stop accepting Visa Credit Cards Issued in UK]]></title><description><![CDATA[Amazon (AMZN) is to cease accepting payments made by UK-issued Visa (V) credit
cards from next year, it has been revealed.

The online retail giant blamed the decision on high fees charged by Visa to
process transactions.

The changes will come into effect as early as 19 January 2022, Bloomberg…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvyppt/amazon_to_stop_accepting_visa_credit_cards_issued/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvyppt/amazon_to_stop_accepting_visa_credit_cards_issued/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:20:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon (AMZN) is to cease accepting payments made by UK-issued Visa (V) credit cards from next year, it has been revealed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The online retail giant blamed the decision on high fees charged by Visa to process transactions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The changes will come into effect as early as 19 January 2022, Bloomberg first reported, citing information that Amazon had shared with its customers this week, after they had purchased items.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$V down approx 3.25% in the pre-market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dimensional Files for US Small Cap Value ETF and International Small Cap Value ETF]]></title><description><![CDATA[Could this have the potential to solve some limitation (that I may not know
about) in the popular AVUV for small cap value tilts? I realize an SCV tilt
isn't the most Boglehead move, however I have seen its relatively recent
popularity in this sub and am quite interested in it myself. Would love to…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvxzxa/dimensional_files_for_us_small_cap_value_etf_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvxzxa/dimensional_files_for_us_small_cap_value_etf_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:20:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Could this have the potential to solve some limitation (that I may not know about) in the popular AVUV for small cap value tilts? I realize an SCV tilt isn&amp;#39;t the most Boglehead move, however I have seen its relatively recent popularity in this sub and am quite interested in it myself. Would love to hear what you guys think!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://us.dimensional.com/about-us/media-center/dimensional-lists-four-fixed-income-etfs-and-announces-further-expansion-of-etf-offering&quot;&gt;https://us.dimensional.com/about-us/media-center/dimensional-lists-four-fixed-income-etfs-and-announces-further-expansion-of-etf-offering&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Elon still has more than 50% of shares to sell in Tesla from Tweet]]></title><description><![CDATA[Arguably closer to 60% if you allow for the near $1 billion stock that he was
already due to sell from September SEC filings, that preceded his tweet:

https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.marketwatch.com/amp/story/another-day-another-tesla-stock-sale-for-elon-musk-8-8-billion-over-past-7-days…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvxlci/elon_still_has_more_than_50_of_shares_to_sell_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvxlci/elon_still_has_more_than_50_of_shares_to_sell_in/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:20:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arguably closer to 60% if you allow for the near $1 billion stock that he was already due to sell from September SEC filings, that preceded his tweet:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.marketwatch.com/amp/story/another-day-another-tesla-stock-sale-for-elon-musk-8-8-billion-over-past-7-days-11637116058&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.marketwatch.com/amp/story/another-day-another-tesla-stock-sale-for-elon-musk-8-8-billion-over-past-7-days-11637116058&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course if Sanders would just respond to his damned tweets, he could be a great scapegoat for offloading far more shares on the highs.  And who would blame Musk if he did.  He did afterall think Tesla &amp;#39;insanely&amp;#39; over valued at $50 billion:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.vanityfair.com/news/2017/05/even-elon-musk-thinks-teslas-stock-is-insanely-overvalued/amp&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.vanityfair.com/news/2017/05/even-elon-musk-thinks-teslas-stock-is-insanely-overvalued/amp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Target tops earnings estimates, but shares fall as retailer focuses on keeping customer prices low]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/target-tgt-q3-2021earnings.html

Earnings per share: $3.03 adjusted vs. $2.83, expected

Revenue: $25.65 billion vs. $24.78 billion

Target topped earnings for the fiscal third quarter, as seasonal moments like
Halloween and back-to-school boosted sales.

The retailer…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvydgi/target_tops_earnings_estimates_but_shares_fall_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvydgi/target_tops_earnings_estimates_but_shares_fall_as/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:20:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/target-tgt-q3-2021earnings.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/target-tgt-q3-2021earnings.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earnings per share: $3.03 adjusted vs. $2.83, expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revenue: $25.65 billion vs. $24.78 billion&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Target topped earnings for the fiscal third quarter, as seasonal moments like Halloween and back-to-school boosted sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The retailer raised its forecast, saying that comparable sales could rise at between a high-single digit and low double-digit pace in the holiday period. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CEO Brian Cornell said the company is focused on value as prices of food, gas and more rise and consumers face sticker shock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is another non tech stock that always outperform. The e-commerce operations have been improved and getting competitive advantages against Walmart and Amazon. The management teams are dealing with inflations perfectly and will be able to pass those to customers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Xu Jiayin sold personal assets and invest over RMB7 billion life-saving funds into Evergrande]]></title><description><![CDATA[Xu Jiayin, chairman of the board of directors of China Evergrande, who promised
to ensure the interests of investors and promise the resumption of work and
guarantee the delivery of buildings, is selling his personal assets to save
Evergrande. Since July 1st, in order to maintain the liquidity of…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvomsc/xu_jiayin_sold_personal_assets_and_invest_over/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvomsc/xu_jiayin_sold_personal_assets_and_invest_over/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:43:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xu Jiayin, chairman of the board of directors of China Evergrande, who promised to ensure the interests of investors and promise the resumption of work and guarantee the delivery of buildings, &lt;strong&gt;is selling his personal assets to save Evergrande&lt;/strong&gt;. Since July 1st, in order to maintain the liquidity of the group, Xu has raised funds through the &lt;strong&gt;sale of personal assets&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;pledged equity&lt;/strong&gt; and has invested more than &lt;strong&gt;RMB7 billion&lt;/strong&gt; in the group to maintain the basic operations of the huge Evergrande empire. During this period, Evergrande did not have financing and sales suspension, but it must ensure the monthly payment of &lt;strong&gt;10%&lt;/strong&gt;, the salary of headquarters employees, and the payment of interest on domestic and foreign bonds, so as to promote the resumption of work and production of projects across the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you think this action can save Evergrande?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[During a gold rush, sell shovels]]></title><description><![CDATA[During a chip rush (due to EV, mining, metaverse), what are the relevant chip
suppliers companies?

I know TSM is a big one but they are a Taiwan company. I'm looking for a US one.
I know Intel and Qorvo have their own in house fab and as an IC designer I had
my designs fab at Qorvo and Global…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvspcz/during_a_gold_rush_sell_shovels/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvspcz/during_a_gold_rush_sell_shovels/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:30:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;During a chip rush (due to EV, mining, metaverse), what are the relevant chip suppliers companies?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know TSM is a big one but they are a Taiwan company. I&amp;#39;m looking for a US one. I know Intel and Qorvo have their own in house fab and as an IC designer I had my designs fab at Qorvo and Global Foundries too. But which companies are the main suppliers for this chip rush?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ford at a recent high price of $19.79 does it still have room to move upward]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know that Ford has a big investment in Rivian. What will the upside be for
Ford if they hold onto that investment or decide to liquidate it. Personally I
think there’s still a lot of growth potential sister vehicles especially their
EV 150 has a tremendous amount of future orders. Do you think…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvp7du/ford_at_a_recent_high_price_of_1979_does_it_still/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvp7du/ford_at_a_recent_high_price_of_1979_does_it_still/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:30:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know that Ford has a big investment in Rivian.  What will the upside be for Ford if they hold onto that investment or decide to liquidate it. Personally I think there’s still a lot of growth potential sister vehicles especially their EV 150 has a tremendous amount of future orders. Do you think will see a move up towards $30 per share during 2022?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is investing in junior mining stocks worth it?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’ve been investing since early this year and while I have placed some money on
bigger stocks like FCX and BHP, I am planning to invest in some juniors too. I
don’t plan on placing a lot on them though, since I am aware of the risks that
come with investing in it.

I am looking into three stocks…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvx11z/is_investing_in_junior_mining_stocks_worth_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvx11z/is_investing_in_junior_mining_stocks_worth_it/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:30:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been investing since early this year and while I have placed some money on bigger stocks like FCX and BHP, I am planning to invest in some juniors too. I don’t plan on placing a lot on them though, since I am aware of the risks that come with investing in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am looking into three stocks which includes &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fortitudegold.com/&quot;&gt;Fortitude Gold&lt;/a&gt; (FTCO). They are a small producer but a good thing about them is that they have no debts. They recently increased their dividend by 14%, and reported positive results in their Golden Mile property.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I included &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.threevalleycopper.com/&quot;&gt;Three Valley Copper&lt;/a&gt; (TVC) since they’re showing great potential too. They announced a financing with a deal brought about by investor demand, financing the company with $16 million dollars. They are expected to start mining early 2022 and will potentially produce 13-16 thousand tonnes of copper cathodes in a few years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m still looking into other juniors to add to my bigger mining stocks but some peers have been encouraging me to hold physical metals as well. I’m not really sure about this though. It would help me a lot if you guys share your thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NVDA tomorrow... your thoughts?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm not currently in NVDA right now, and I'm probably just going to watch
earnings from the sidelines, but it'll certainly be interesting to see how the
stock performs during the day tomorrow, and then obviously what's going to
happen in afterhours.

Normally, I'd think that anything even remotely…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvo2a3/nvda_tomorrow_your_thoughts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvo2a3/nvda_tomorrow_your_thoughts/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:03:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not currently in NVDA right now, and I&amp;#39;m probably just going to watch earnings from the sidelines, but it&amp;#39;ll certainly be interesting to see how the stock performs during the day tomorrow, and then obviously what&amp;#39;s going to happen in afterhours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Normally, I&amp;#39;d think that anything even remotely good has already been priced into this stock, so I don&amp;#39;t see how it could possibly explode to the upside after earnings. I&amp;#39;m sure they&amp;#39;re hurting in getting parts from their suppliers like anybody else. So, I&amp;#39;d think the forward guidance would be very cautious. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course anything is possible. The thing could hit $350 in AH or maybe $270&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>