<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 06:10:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[The Profitability of Technical Analysis: A Review [Research paper]]]></title><description><![CDATA[Read full paper…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ovcjjt/the_profitability_of_technical_analysis_a_review/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ovcjjt/the_profitability_of_technical_analysis_a_review/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 22:14:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read &lt;a href=&quot;https://poseidon01.ssrn.com/delivery.php?ID=126024068112004090070125064117102098039053020046074058007069112088085114006090003108037124118022010007121006117112102074097040048054065011084089116092127015036046038120079117088108110066097076124001007019110123106024098067119106013098003098083&amp;amp;EXT=pdf&amp;amp;INDEX=TRUE&quot;&gt;full paper here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shortened quotes version;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The purpose of this report is to review the evidence on the profitability of technical analysis. To achieve this purpose, the report comprehensively reviews survey, theoretical and empirical studies regarding technical trading strategies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The survey literature indicates that technical analysis has been widely used by market participants in futures markets and foreign exchange markets, and that about 30% to 40% of practitioners appear to believe that technical analysis is an important factor in determining price movement at shorter time horizons up to 6 months.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We provide an overview of theoretical models that include implications about the profitability of technical analysis. Conventional efficient market theories, such as the martingale model and random walk models, rule out the possibility of technical trading profits in speculative markets, while relatively recent models such as noisy rational expectation models or behavioral models suggest that technical trading strategies may be profitable due to noise in the market or investors’ irrational behavior&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Early studies indicated that technical trading strategies were profitable in foreign exchange markets and futures markets, but not in stock markets before the 1980s. Modern studies indicated that technical trading strategies consistently generated economic profits in a variety of speculative markets at least until the early 1990s. Among a total of 92 modern studies, 58 studies found positive results regarding technical trading strategies, while 24 studies obtained negative results. Ten studies indicated mixed results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Despite the positive evidence on the profitability of technical trading strategies, it appears that most empirical studies are subject to various problems in their testing procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technical analysis is a forecasting method of price movements using past prices, volume, and open interest.2 Pring (2002), a leading technical analyst, provides a more specific definition:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The technical approach to investment is essentially a reflection of the idea that prices move in trends that are determined by the changing attitudes of investors toward a variety of economic, monetary, political, and psychological forces. The art of technical analysis, for it is an art, is to identify a trend reversal at a relatively early stage and ride on that trend until the weight of the evidence shows or proves that the trend has reversed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical analysis includes a variety of forecasting techniques ... However, academic research on technical analysis is generally limited to techniques that can be expressed in mathematical forms, namely technical trading systems, although some recent studies attempt to test.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Since Charles H. Dow first introduced the Dow theory in the late 1800s, technical analysis has been extensively used among market participants such as brokers, dealers, fund managers, speculators, and individual investors in the financial industry. 3 Numerous surveys indicate that practitioners attribute a significant role to technical analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For example, futures fund managers rely heavily on computer-guided technical trading systems (Irwin and Brorsen 1985; Brorsen and Irwin 1987; Billingsley and Chance 1996), and about 30% to 40% of foreign exchange traders around the world believe that technical analysis is the major factor determining exchange rates in the short-run up to six months (e.g., Menkhoff 1997; Cheung and Wong 2000; Cheung, Chinn, and Marsh 2000; Cheung and Chinn 2001).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In contrast to the views of many practitioners, most academics are skeptical about technical analysis. Rather, they tend to believe that markets are informationally efficient and hence all available information is impounded in current prices (Fama 1970). In efficient markets, therefore, any attempts to make profits by exploiting currently available information are futile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nevertheless, in recent decades rigorous theoretical explanations for the widespread use of technical analysis have been developed based on noisy rational expectation models (Treynor and Ferguson 1985; Brown and Jennings 1989; Grundy and McNichols 1989; Blume, Easley, and O’Hara 1994), behavioral (or feedback) models (De Long et al. 1990a, 1991; Shleifer and Summers 1990), disequilibrium models (Beja and Goldman 1980), herding models (Froot, Scharfstein, and Stein 1992), agent-based models (Schmidt 2002), and chaos theory (Clyde and Osler 1997). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Survey Studies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The oldest survey study regarding technical analysis dates back to Stewart (1949), who analyzed the trading behavior of customers of a large Chicago futures commission firm over the 1924-1932 period. The result indicated that in general traders were unsuccessful in their grain futures trading, regardless of their scale and knowledge of the commodity traded&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amateur speculators were more likely to be long than short in futures markets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Smidt (1965a) surveyed trading activities of amateur traders in the US commodity futures markets in 1961.4 In this survey, about 53% of respondents claimed that they used charts either exclusively or moderately in order to identify trends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There was a slight tendency for chartists to pyramid more frequently than other traders.5 It is interesting to note that only 10% of the chartists, compared to 29% of the non-chartists, nearly always took long positions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Group of Thirty (1985) surveyed the views of market participants on the functioning of the foreign exchange market in 1985. The respondents were composed of 40 large banks and 15 securities houses in 12 countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;97% of bank respondents and 87% of the securities houses believed that the use of technical analysis had a significant impact on the market.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brorsen and Irwin (1987) carried out a survey of large public futures funds’ advisory groups in 1986. In their survey, more than half of the advisors responded that they relied heavily on computer-guided technical trading systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Since technically traded public and private futures funds were estimated to control an average of 23% of the open interest in ten important futures markets, the funds seemed large enough to move prices if they traded in unison ( &amp;lt;&amp;lt; Interesting point)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frankel and Froot (1990) showed that switching a forecasting method for another over time may explain changes in the demand for dollars in foreign exchange markets. The evidence provided was the survey results of Euromoney magazine for foreign exchange forecasting firms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In 1978, nineteen forecasting firms exclusively used fundamental analysis and only three firms technical analysis. After 1983, however, the distribution had been reversed. In 1983, only one firm reported using fundamental analysis, and eight technical analysis. In 1988, seven firms appeared to rely on fundamental analysis while eighteen firms employed technical analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cheung, Chinn, and Marsh (2000) surveyed the views of UK-based foreign exchange dealers on technical anaysis in 1998. In this survey, 33% of the respondents described themselves as technical analysts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Moreover, 26% of the dealers responded that technical trading is the most important factor that determines exchange rate movements over the medium run.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cheung and Chinn (2001) published survey results for US-based foreign exchange traders conducted in 1998. In the survey, about 30% of the traders indicated that technical trading best describes their trading strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;About 31% of the traders responded that technical trading was the primary factor determining exchange rate movements up to 6 months.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Quite a lot more in this survey section but will leave it at that to keep this somewhat brief)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In sum, survey studies indicate that technical analysis has been widely used by practitioners in futures markets and foreign exchange markets, and regarded as an important factor in determining price movements at shorter time horizons. However, no survey evidence for stock market traders was found.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Theory&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Efficient Markets Hypothesis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The efficient markets hypothesis has long been a dominant paradigm in describing the behavior of prices in speculative markets. Working (1949, p. 160) provided an early version of the hypothesis:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If it is possible under any given combination of circumstances to predict future price changes and have the predictions fulfilled, it follows that the market expectations must have been defective ; ideal market expectations would have taken full account of the information which permitted successful prediction of the price changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revised his definition of a perfect futures market to “… one in which the market price would constitute at all times the best estimate that could be made, from currently available information, of what the price would be at the delivery date of the futures contracts (Working, 1962, p. 446).”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identical to the famous definition of an efficient market given by Fama (1970, p. 383): “A market in which prices always ‘fully reflect’ available information is called ‘efficient’.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thus, technical analysis provides a weak form test of market efficiency because it heavily uses past price history&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(I&amp;#39;m going to skip some section now but the full table of content is at the bottom of the post)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chart Pattern Studies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chang and Osler evaluated the performance of the head-and-shoulders pattern using daily spot rates for 6 currencies (mark, yen, pound, franc, Swiss franc, and Canadian dollar) during the entire floating rate period, 1973-1994.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;head-and-shoulders rule s generated statistically significant returns of about 13% and 19% per year for the mark and yen, respectively, but not for the other exchange rates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Returns from the exogenous exit rule appeared to be insignificant in most cases. The trading profits from the endogenous exit rules were substantially higher than either the annual buy-and-hold returns of 2.5% for the mark and 4.4% for the yen or annual average stock yield of 6.8% measured on the S&amp;amp;P 500 index.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chang and Osler further investigated the performance of moving average rules and momentum rules and compared the results with the observed performance of the head-and shoulders rule. Returns from the simple technical trading systems appeared statistically significant for all six currencies and the simpler rules easily outperformed the head-and shoulders rules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hence, Chang and Osler concluded that, although the head-and-shoulders patterns had some predictive power for the mark and yen during the period of floating exchange rates, the use of the head-and-shoulders rule did not seem to be rational, because they were easily dominated by simple moving average rules and momentum rules (&amp;lt;&amp;lt; This is actually a really good point. The way a trend forms means the head and shoulders pattern produces one of the most common false signals and usually a strong counter move when breaking, but the ones that work are important).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Caginalp and Laurent (1998) reported that candlestick reversal patterns generated substantial profits in comparison to an average gain for the same holding period. For the S&amp;amp;P 500 stocks over the 1992-1996 period&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In general, the results of chart pattern studies varied depending on patterns, markets, and sample periods tested, but suggested that some chart patterns might have been profitable in stock markets and foreign exchange markets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary and Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Most survey studies indicate that technical analysis has been widely used by market participants in futures markets and foreign exchange markets, and that at least 30% to 50 40% of practitioners regard technical analysis as an important factor in determining price movement at shorter time horizons up to 6 months.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the theoretical literature, the conventional efficient markets models, such as the martingale and random walk models, rule out the existence of profitable technical trading (&amp;lt;&amp;lt; All the efficient market stuff is just a theory. It&amp;#39;s so often stated as if it is fact)... On the other hand, several other models, such as noisy rational expectations models, feedback models, disequilibrium models, herding models, agent-based models, and chaos theory, suggest that technical trading strategies may be profitable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In these models, thus, there exist profitable trading opportunities that are not being exploited.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other chapters not mentioned;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Martingale Model&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Random Walk Models&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Noisy Rational Expectations Models&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Noise Traders and Feedback Models&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other Models&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13 Summary of Theory&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Empirical Studies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technical Trading Systems&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dual Moving Average Crossover&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside Price Channel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Relative Strength Index&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alexander’s Filter Rule&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Early Empirical Studies (1960-1987)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overview&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Representative Early Studies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Summary of Early Studies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Modern Empirical Studies (1988-2004)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overview&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Representative Modern Studies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Standard Studies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Model-Based Bootstrap Studies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Genetic Programming Studies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reality Check Studies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chart Pattern Studies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nonlinear Studies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other Studies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Summary of Modern Studies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Summary and Conclusion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is VTI market cap diversity a mirage?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/ovd25i/is_vti_market_cap_diversity_a_mirage/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/ovd25i/is_vti_market_cap_diversity_a_mirage/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 21:41:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What do the ultra rich do beforehand to prepare for a suspected upcoming recession and/or inflation to be able to profit when things go bad?]]></title><description><![CDATA[“The rich get richer and the poor get poorer”

What kind of investments do they do to win and profit off an UPCOMING economic
downturn? Thinking of 2008 and the Great Depression specifically, or any time
the rich got richer and the poor got poorer. I’m wondering how…

Do they hoard on gold first?…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ovdc9m/what_do_the_ultra_rich_do_beforehand_to_prepare/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ovdc9m/what_do_the_ultra_rich_do_beforehand_to_prepare/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 21:02:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The rich get richer and the poor get poorer”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What kind of investments do they do to win and profit off an UPCOMING economic downturn? Thinking of 2008 and the Great Depression specifically, or any time the rich got richer and the poor got poorer. I’m wondering how…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do they hoard on gold first? Buy real estate? Buy competing businesses? Increase their debt as leverage?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I watched a few videos on this subject, seems to be all over the place. Not looking for a secret formula, but maybe an explanation of what you think and why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I read about debt. Some of the “winners” bought a bunch of properties to amass as much debt as they could, so that when a recession would hit, they’d end-up paying so much less. But then my question is, if before a crash properties are super inflated at the start, does that mean they purchase huge amount of over valued properties on debt hoping for it to crash? How does that even make sense / work if you can’t even pay the mortgages?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My gut says I should be doing at least one of the above in the coming months…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[‎About to start my 401K with Fidelity. Is there a better robo-investment option like Betterment that can use pre-tax income?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I just moved to the US so just wanted to make sure I do it right the first time.

I used to use Betterment five years ago, but it was straight from my earnings
after tax deduction but I made a good 4-7% annual off of it.

Now that I'm married, and having moved to the US, my position is offering me…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/outsbk/about_to_start_my_401k_with_fidelity_is_there_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/outsbk/about_to_start_my_401k_with_fidelity_is_there_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 21:02:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just moved to the US so just wanted to make sure I do it right the first time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used to use Betterment five years ago, but it was straight from my earnings after tax deduction but I made a good 4-7% annual off of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that I&amp;#39;m married, and having moved to the US, my position is offering me an option to start a 401K with Fidelity. But postpandemic, I feel that now is a good time to start with a robo investing pension plan instead, so long as it has access to my pre-tax income. Is that even possible?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wall Street Week Ahead for the trading week beginning August 2nd, 2021]]></title><description><![CDATA[Good Friday evening to all of you here on r/stocks [/r/stocks]. I hope everyone
on this sub made out pretty nicely in the market this past week, and is ready
for the new trading week & month ahead.

Here is everything you need to know to get you ready for the trading week
beginning August 2nd,…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ouykv9/wall_street_week_ahead_for_the_trading_week/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ouykv9/wall_street_week_ahead_for_the_trading_week/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 20:36:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good Friday evening to all of you here on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/stocks&quot;&gt;r/stocks&lt;/a&gt;. I hope everyone on this sub made out pretty nicely in the market this past week, and is ready for the new trading week &amp;amp; month ahead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is everything you need to know to get you ready for the trading week beginning August 2nd, 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;July jobs report could be what gives the market its next big jolt in the week ahead - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/30/july-jobs-report-could-be-what-gives-the-market-its-next-big-jolt-in-the-week-ahead.html&quot;&gt;(Source)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friday’s jobs report could be a catalyst that helps determine whether markets are volatile or will trade like it’s the quiet dog days of August.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More than a quarter of the S&amp;amp;P 500 report earnings in the coming week. The calendar includes companies in sectors such as consumer staples, insurance, pharma, travel and media. From Booking Holdings to ViacomCBS, Wayfair and Kellogg, investors will be watching to see what companies say about reopening activity, supply chain disruptions and rising costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I think as much as 85% of the companies which are reporting earnings mentioned inflation on their earnings calls,” Franklin Templeton Fixed Income chief investment officer Sonal Desai said. “Inflation may not be a problem to policymakers and financial markets, which seem not to be concerned at all. It does seem to bother the people who have to buy stuff or people who produce stuff.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;The jobs factor&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Federal Reserve has said the sharp jump in inflation is just temporary, and many investors appear to be taking it in stride for now. The market is intensely focused on the central bank’s other mandate: the labor market. Fed Chairman Jerome Powell said Wednesday he would like to see strong jobs reports before winding down the central bank’s $120 billion a month bond-buying program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics will release the July employment report on the morning of Friday, Aug. 6. It’s expected to show 788,000 nonfarm payrolls, down from 850,000 in June, according to Dow Jones. The unemployment rate is expected to dip to 5.7% from 5.9%. Average hourly wages are expected to rise 3.9% year over year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ironsides Macroeconomics director of research Barry Knapp said he expects the next two monthly jobs reports will be strong, and the Fed should then be ready to announce in September that it is ready to start the slow unwind of its bond purchasing program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is an important step since it would be the first real move away from the central bank’s easy policies that were put in place in the pandemic. It would also mean the Fed would be open to raising interest rates once the tapering is completed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Game changer for markets&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Friday could be a game changer,” Knapp said of the employment report. Before that, he expects stocks to trade in a narrow range.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the number of jobs added in July is much higher than expected, at more than 1 million, Knapp said the market could immediately sell off on the idea the Fed would be ready to pare back its bond purchases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the number is weaker than expected, the market could rally. “We are in a dead period after earnings, with concerns about the pace of the reopening. It’s still a bit of a question mark. The bias would be higher after a weak number. ... Bad is good. Good is bad,” said Knapp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like some other strategists, he expects to see a stock market correction, possibly later this summer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’m in the camp where I think we’re going to have our first major correction.” Knapp said. “What we’re likely to get is at least 10% or more. ... It could really happen when they [Fed officials] make the announcement in September.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wilmington Trust chief economist Luke Tilley said he expects just 350,000 jobs, based on the high frequency data he watches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We think the run rate is about 500,000 jobs. Last month seems a little bit overcooked,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Reflation trade&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The S&amp;amp;P 500 was down 0.4% in the past week, finishing at 4,395, while the Nasdaq lost even more , down 1.1% at 14,672.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cyclical stocks were among the best performers. Materials jumped 2.8% in the week, and energy shares were up 1.6%. Financials gained 0.7%. But tech fell 0.7%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Knapp said it now makes sense to hold stocks that are in the reflation trade, such as energy, industrials or materials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The surge in the delta variant of the coronavirus has become a worry among investors and has been a factor holding down interest rates. The 10-year yield, which moves opposite price, has held at low levels and was at 1.23% on Friday, amid concern that the delta variant of the coronavirus could slow growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Investors will be watching other important data in the coming week, including the Institute for Supply Management’s manufacturing data Monday, and jobless claims and trade data Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;The China trade&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;China was also a dominant market story in the past week and could continue to be. Hong Kong’s Hang Seng Index fell 5% for the week. Chinese regulators continued their crackdown on internet companies, publicly traded education companies and other industries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Strategists say Beijing is trying to reclaim its biggest companies as its own and turn them away from listings in foreign markets. Officials were particularly upset with Didi Global which reportedly went public even after being warned not to by Beijing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chinese regulators reportedly spoke with international banks after their actions sparked a wave of selling in internet stocks and the broader Chinese stock market. The regulators said companies could continue to go public in the U.S. if they met listing requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We will continue to see regulators try to calm the waters. I would say this was a communications misstep,” said Franklin Templeton’s Desai. “You don’t have massive swings without having negative impact.” She added it sent ripples through emerging markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This is China trying to gain control, and they tried to do it in a very heavy way, and they were surprised at the backlash,” Desai said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The KraneShares CSI China Internet ETF has lost about half its value from its peak in February, and was down another 2.6% Friday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Internet retailer Alibaba is one of the ETF’s top holdings. The company is expected to announce earnings on Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This past week saw the following moves in the S&amp;amp;P:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/eQ4pMub.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE FULL S&amp;amp;P TREE MAP FOR THE PAST WEEK!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;S&amp;amp;P Sectors for this past week:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/vhlrMce.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE S&amp;amp;P SECTORS FOR THE PAST WEEK!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Major Indices for this past week:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/RRSF7cS.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE MAJOR INDICES FOR THE PAST WEEK!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Major Futures Markets as of Friday&amp;#39;s close:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/hTKiEb3.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE MAJOR FUTURES INDICES AS OF FRIDAY!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Economic Calendar for the Week Ahead:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/YrCuf8W.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE FULL ECONOMIC CALENDAR FOR THE WEEK AHEAD!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Percentage Changes for the Major Indices, WTD, MTD, QTD, YTD as of Friday&amp;#39;s close:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/fZKzJfU.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE CHART!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;S&amp;amp;P Sectors for the Past Week:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/59nY5gO.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE CHART!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Major Indices Pullback/Correction Levels as of Friday&amp;#39;s close:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/flIRmSl.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE CHART!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Major Indices Rally Levels as of Friday&amp;#39;s close:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ZpaVwYn.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE CHART!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Most Anticipated Earnings Releases for this week:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/GB7yn3W.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE CHART!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here are the upcoming IPO&amp;#39;s for this week:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/5r4Hlqm.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE CHART!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Friday&amp;#39;s Stock Analyst Upgrades &amp;amp; Downgrades:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/L68F4GF.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE CHART LINK #1!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/VocjXSz.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE CHART LINK #2!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/oDsO8vO.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE CHART LINK #3!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;August has been a dangerous month for the market&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;August is the worst DJIA, S&amp;amp;P 500, Russell 1000 and Russell 2000 month over the last 33 years, 1988-2020 with average declines ranging from 0.4% by Russell 2000 to 0.8% by DJIA. For NASDAQ August ranks second worst over the same period with an average gain of 0.2%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contributing to this poor performance since 1987; the second shortest bear market in history (45 days) caused by turmoil in Russia, the Asian currency crisis and the Long-Term Capital Management hedge fund debacle ending August 31, 1998 with the DJIA shedding 6.4% that day. DJIA dropped a record 1344.22 points for the month, off 15.1%—which is the second worst monthly percentage DJIA loss since 1950. Saddam Hussein triggered a 10.0% slide in August 1990. Sizeable losses in 2010, 2011, 2013 and 2015 of over 4% on DJIA have widened Augusts’ average decline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In post-election years, Augusts’ rankings are little changed. August is the worst month for DJIA and Russell 1000 and second worst for S&amp;amp;P 500, NASDAQ and Russell 2000. Average declines in post-election year Augusts swell to 0.8% by Russell 2000 to 1.7% by DJIA. Each index has also seen more declining post-election year Augusts than positive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://64.media.tumblr.com/78fd9b0e8110b9d2e779ce650c18cd79/3293cb0a1c43f61d-02/s400x600/92f8c448cdafe2c1f033ccdad8bd7b3461f26a66.jpg&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE CHART!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Modern 4-Year Cycle Theory Approaching Near Term High&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://64.media.tumblr.com/e7c3175df9fa85b593af70440d79c62f/b5c96d0e540e1659-24/s500x750/5c976a9f3f233c0795ead0a363cd399469eab8e2.jpg&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE CHART!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the recent uptick in volatility and today’s drop the S&amp;amp;P 500% is up 17.2% year-to-date. This is right in line with our 2021 Annual Forecast best case scenario made last December. Our updated outlook is for S&amp;amp;P 500 to finish the year in the 4300-4500 range or even higher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, as you can see in the chart of the Modern 4-Year Presidential Election Cycle we are due for a pause over the next couple of months before the rally resumes in the September/October timeframe. This illustration of the average 4-year cycle uses the S&amp;amp;P 500 back to 1949, which is the first full cycle post-WWII vs. other comparisons that use the Dow back 125 years to 1896.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We feel the more recent dataset is a better representation of the modern cycle where post-election years have been better and election years weaker – impacted by the undecided election in 2000 and the financial crisis of 2008. Midterm years are still lackluster with propensity for the significant bottoms and pre-election years are still the tops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This creates the sweet spot of the 4-year cycle from Q4 in the midterm year through Q2 in the pre-election year. From the midterm low to the pre-election year high DJIA averages a 45% gain since 1950 and NASDAQ averages a 70% gain since 1974.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Neutral Sentiment Surge Continues&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AAII&amp;#39;s weekly sentiment survey saw an equal percentage (30.6%) of respondents report as bullish and bearish last week. This week saw a much more optimistic pivot as 36.2% of respondents reported bullish sentiment. While higher, bullish sentiment is still at one of the lowest levels since last fall. At 36.2%, bullish sentiment is also now just below the historical average of 38%. While the AAII reading on bullish sentiment was higher but still muted, the Investors Intelligence survey of newsletter writers showed bullish sentiment fall 8.1 percentage points to 53.1%. While that is not a particularly low reading (the lowest since only the end of May), it was the largest one week decline since October 2019. In other words, bullish sentiment is not necessarily collapsing, but it has lost some footing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://media.bespokepremium.com/uploads/2021/07/072921-AAII-Bull.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE CHART!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With more bulls in the AAII survey, fewer respondents reported bearish sentiment. In fact, less than a quarter of investors reported bearish sentiment this week. That is down 6.5 percentage points from the prior week; the largest one-week decline since a 6.6 percentage point decline in the first week of June.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://media.bespokepremium.com/uploads/2021/07/072921-AAII-Bear.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE CHART!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The inverse moves in bullish and bearish sentiment resulted in the bull-bear spread to rise 12.1 points. While off the lows, it is still not as strong of a reading as has been seen for most of this year. In fact, the current reading is 5.5 points below the average since the start of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://media.bespokepremium.com/uploads/2021/07/072921-AAII-Spread.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE CHART!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most impressive sentiment reading this week was neutral sentiment. Over the past four weeks, neutral sentiment has risen 10.5 percentage points without a single decline in that time. That is the biggest four-week rise since mid-May when it had risen 14.9 percentage points. Now as the predominant sentiment with just below 40% of respondents reporting as such, neutral sentiment is at the highest level since the first week of 2020 when this reading was 1.2 percentage points higher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://media.bespokepremium.com/uploads/2021/07/072921-AAII-Neutral.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE CHART!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Services Consumption Lifts GDP Growth&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lofty expectations for second quarter gross domestic product (GDP) growth were left somewhat wanting as a decent headline number fell short of expectations. Peering under the hood, though, we think this is still a fairly solid report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bureau of Economic Analysis released its preliminary estimate for second quarter GDP this morning, showing the U.S. economy grew at a 6.5% annualized pace against the Bloomberg median forecast for 8.4%. While this represented a small acceleration from the first quarter’s 6.3% pace, investors viewed the headline number as a mild disappointment in light of the heightened expectations. The composition of the growth, though, largely reinforces the prevailing narratives of a strong consumer juxtaposed with supply chain bottlenecks, restricting growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The positive takeaway from today’s report is that we are clearly seeing a rebound in the in-person consumption of services,” said LPL Financial Chief Investment Strategist Ryan Detrick. “This indicates a confidence by consumers to reengage with the parts of the economy beaten down most by COVID, and continued momentum here will be key if we are to see the consumer continue to power overall growth.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As seen in the LPL Chart of the day, the US consumer continued to do the heavy lifting, offsetting weakness in most other major GDP components.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i0.wp.com/lplresearch.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/7.29.21-Blog-1-Chart-1.png?ssl=1&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE CHART!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Business fixed investment came in strong and demonstrated business’ attempts to ramp up output to meet surging demand. Residential investment had a more predictable decline, as well-documented labor shortages and high materials costs are restricting new projects. The volatile inventory components, though, did represent a drag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking forward, we expect continued growth in the third quarter but with a different composition. Consumer spending should still be respectable, but likely will recede a bit due to the fading impact of past government transfer payments. New momentum in services as in-person commerce picks up should continue under the hood. Picking up the slack; though, business investment should continue to recover, and net exports may improve as the rest of the world plays catch-up to the U.S. in their recoveries, consuming more of our goods and services. Government spending and inventories also both have favorable outlooks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Delta variant of COVID-19 presents a risk to the outlook, but we see strong reason to remain optimistic. The U.S. is lagging the U.K. in its exposure to the Delta variant, and if we model our trajectory after theirs, which obviously is an imperfect comparison, we expect to see a peak in cases in the coming weeks. In fact, the U.K. is already on a strong path to recovery despite doomsday headlines. Domestically, COVID-19 cases are spiking in areas with the lowest vaccination rates. But, there is evidence that these are also the states experiencing the highest uptick in new vaccinations, which should help self-correct the trends. Positivity rates can be thought of as the fastest-twitch indicator, with hospitalization trends following in the ensuing weeks. Through that lens we see that some of the hardest hit states may have already seen their positivity rates peak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We upgraded our 2021 forecast for U.S. real GDP growth earlier this year from 5–5.5% to 6.25–6.75%, and while there are sure to be bumps along the way, we expect to see the economy continue growing at a strong pace as activity further normalizes over the course of the year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the most notable companies (tickers) reporting earnings in this upcoming trading week ahead-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(&lt;strong&gt;T.B.A. THIS WEEKEND.&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/GB7yn3W.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR NEXT WEEK&amp;#39;S MOST NOTABLE EARNINGS RELEASES!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/TQmsBSu.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR NEXT WEEK&amp;#39;S HIGHEST VOLATILITY EARNINGS RELEASES!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Gzq3pvf.jpg&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE MOST ANTICIPATED EARNINGS RELEASES FOR THE NEXT 2 WEEKS!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/6Fs8mPV.jpg&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE MOST ANTICIPATED EARNINGS RELEASES BEFORE MONDAY&amp;#39;S MARKET OPEN!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below are some of the notable companies coming out with earnings releases this upcoming trading week ahead which includes the date/time of release &amp;amp; consensus estimates courtesy of Earnings Whispers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monday 8.2.21 Before Market Open:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ZWp8OaE.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR MONDAY&amp;#39;S PRE-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monday 8.2.21 After Market Close:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ohdyr9p.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR MONDAY&amp;#39;S AFTER-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #1!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/slHJD4Q.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR MONDAY&amp;#39;S AFTER-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #2!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tuesday  8.3.21 Before Market Open:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/1zkKsVE.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR TUESDAY&amp;#39;S PRE-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #1!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/WAATOMk.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR TUESDAY&amp;#39;S PRE-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #2!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/xh7l5Zv.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR TUESDAY&amp;#39;S PRE-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #3!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tuesday 8.3.21 After Market Close:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/e0sMEnG.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR TUESDAY&amp;#39;S AFTER-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #1!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/2IwGNKM.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR TUESDAY&amp;#39;S AFTER-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #2!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/cW7zxea.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR TUESDAY&amp;#39;S AFTER-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #3!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wednesday 8.4.21 Before Market Open:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/jqS9aXG.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR WEDNESDAY&amp;#39;S PRE-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #1!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Rp9cJXU.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR WEDNESDAY&amp;#39;S PRE-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #2!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wednesday 8.4.21 After Market Close:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/tgLqTTK.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR WEDNESDAY&amp;#39;S AFTER-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #1!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ZBTMpeg.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR WEDNESDAY&amp;#39;S AFTER-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #2!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/mt44H8d.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR WEDNESDAY&amp;#39;S AFTER-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #3!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/NzzJziN.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR WEDNESDAY&amp;#39;S AFTER-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #4!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thursday 8.5.21 Before Market Open:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/FFtYdqW.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THURSDAY&amp;#39;S PRE-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #1!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/TIbnFLG.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THURSDAY&amp;#39;S PRE-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #2!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/y2pICGr.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THURSDAY&amp;#39;S PRE-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #3!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/niaft8M.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THURSDAY&amp;#39;S PRE-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #4!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thursday 8.5.21 After Market Close:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/HzDehyM.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THURSDAY&amp;#39;S AFTER-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #1!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/IP92TD5.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THURSDAY&amp;#39;S AFTER-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #2!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/jtvNw70.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THURSDAY&amp;#39;S AFTER-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #3!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/9z7EDva.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THURSDAY&amp;#39;S AFTER-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #4!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/6VRQZfz.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THURSDAY&amp;#39;S AFTER-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #5!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Friday 8.6.21 Before Market Open:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/he9f0pH.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR FRIDAY&amp;#39;S PRE-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #1!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/PiPV8iT.png&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR FRIDAY&amp;#39;S PRE-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES LINK #2!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Friday 8.6.21 After Market Close:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;([CLICK HERE FOR FRIDAY&amp;#39;S AFTER-MARKET EARNINGS TIME &amp;amp; ESTIMATES!]())&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(NONE.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;(T.B.A. THIS WEEKEND.)&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(T.B.A. THIS WEEKEND.)&lt;/strong&gt; (T.B.A. THIS WEEKEND.).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;http://elite.finviz.com/chart.ashx?t=SPY&amp;amp;ty=c&amp;amp;ta=st_c,sch_200p,sma_50,sma_200,sma_20,sma_100,bb_20_2,rsi_b_14,macd_b_12_26_9,stofu_b_14_3_3&amp;amp;p=d&amp;amp;s=l&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE FOR THE CHART!&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;DISCUSS!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are you all watching for in this upcoming trading week?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you all have a wonderful weekend a great trading week ahead &lt;a href=&quot;/r/stocks&quot;&gt;r/stocks&lt;/a&gt;. :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMZN PUTS 900->20k in a day]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/outrw0/amzn_puts_90020k_in_a_day/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/outrw0/amzn_puts_90020k_in_a_day/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 18:51:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["The best stock market ever" - two solid opinions]]></title><description><![CDATA[Since the last 12 years have been so great for the U.S. stock market, these two
articles from the past week are must-reads, IMO.

First, from the well-known Ben Carlson - As Good As It Gets?
[https://awealthofcommonsense.com/2021/07/as-good-as-it-gets/]

And then a riff from The Best Interest - Are…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ov6wdj/the_best_stock_market_ever_two_solid_opinions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ov6wdj/the_best_stock_market_ever_two_solid_opinions/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 18:27:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the last 12 years have been so great for the U.S. stock market, these two articles from the past week are must-reads, IMO. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, from the well-known Ben Carlson - &lt;a href=&quot;https://awealthofcommonsense.com/2021/07/as-good-as-it-gets/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As Good As It Gets?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then a riff from The Best Interest - &lt;a href=&quot;https://bestinterest.blog/the-best-stock-market-period-ever/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are We In The Best Stock Market Period…Ever?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both short, succinct, worth reading. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR - markets have been very good recently...but have been even better in the past.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Should I go 10% Cash or 10% Bonds? Are buying bonds today betting that interest rates go negative?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have 45% in an international index fund (excludes US stocks), 30% in SP500,
15% in small/mid cap index.

I would like to keep 10% in bonds or cash to take advantage of rebalancing.

But I'm not sure how I feel about bonds right now. If you are buying bonds now,
isn't that kind of like betting…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ov59g0/should_i_go_10_cash_or_10_bonds_are_buying_bonds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ov59g0/should_i_go_10_cash_or_10_bonds_are_buying_bonds/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 16:57:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have 45% in an international index fund (excludes US stocks), 30% in SP500, 15% in small/mid cap index. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would like to keep 10% in bonds or cash to take advantage of rebalancing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I&amp;#39;m not sure how I feel about bonds right now. If you are buying bonds now, isn&amp;#39;t that kind of like betting interest rates will go negative? I know bonds tend to go down in value when interest rates go up. And it seems a common theme now is investors shorting bonds, which is a little scary to be honest. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Cash fund offered in my plan is &amp;quot; Invesco Stable Val Trust CF&amp;quot;, which basically tracks the &amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ftserussell.com/products/indices/3m-us-tbill&quot;&gt;FTSE 3 Month US T-Bill Index Series&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;. It has a 0.35% expense ratio, which is kind of high for a cash fund imo. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bond Index offered is  State Steet US Bond Index NL, which basically tracks the  &amp;quot;Bloomberg Barclays U.S. Aggregate Bond Index&amp;quot;. It only has a 0.06% expense ratio. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your time&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The 6 stages of a market bubble]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ouvz3d/the_6_stages_of_a_market_bubble/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ouvz3d/the_6_stages_of_a_market_bubble/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 16:57:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What could possible mass rental evictions mean for the economy]]></title><description><![CDATA[It seems like we’re coming up on evictions in the US resuming after being put on
hold for covid. I’m trying to read up on this more.

My main questions are could the hold on evictions could of been contributing to
the raise in housing prices we have been seeing? Even if it’s just a small
piece.

And…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ov1fhm/what_could_possible_mass_rental_evictions_mean/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ov1fhm/what_could_possible_mass_rental_evictions_mean/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 15:53:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seems like we’re coming up on evictions in the US resuming after being put on hold for covid. I’m trying to read up on this more. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My main questions are could the hold on evictions could of been contributing to the raise in housing prices we have been seeing? Even if it’s just a small piece. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And if evictions suddenly start happening at once in large numbers what effects could this have? Would this effect the real estate area of the economy negatively? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry for being a very uninformed question. I’ve gotten good at reading charts and understand options but the underlying cause and effect of the economy is not something I understand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Twitter Suspends Science Writer After He Posts Results Of Pfizer Clinical Test https://t.co/yAm1hiNDdM]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1421491996217286662</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1421491996217286662</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 15:38:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The combined revenue of the 4 largest US companies hit a record $1.15 trillion over last 12 months...
Apple $AAPL: $347 billion
Microsoft $MSFT: $168 billion
Google $GOOGL: $197 billion
Amazon $AMZN: $443 billion

That's larger than the GDP of all but 14 countries.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1421462805866233860</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1421462805866233860</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 15:38:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Microvast ~ MVST]]></title><description><![CDATA[Microvast - MVST

Microvast - Leader in the fast charging batteries. Full charge in 20minutes !

New interview w/ Microvast COO Shane Smith

Some key quotes:

The primary reason that we even went to the public markets was to raise enough
capital to support the orders we already have in place. We won…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ov6yx9/microvast_mvst/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ov6yx9/microvast_mvst/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 15:38:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microvast - MVST&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microvast - Leader in the fast charging batteries. Full charge in 20minutes !&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New interview w/ Microvast COO Shane Smith&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some key quotes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The primary reason that we even went to the public markets was to raise enough capital to support the orders we already have in place. We won more business then we have capacity for&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Solid State Battery
-Lithium Metal battery
-High Temperature Cells (Sports Car Application)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vertically integrated &amp;amp; proprietary
- $1.5B contracted revenue thru 2027
- $100M+ revenue 2020 / $2.3B 2025E revenue
- 550+ patents
- 3.8B+ miles with ZERO operational accidents
- 28K+ battery systems in operation in 19 countries &amp;amp; 160 cities&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1800+ total employees (500+ R&amp;amp;D personnel)
- Full Range of Energy Densities: 85 – 265 Wh / Kg
- Long cycle lives: 2,500+ – 20,000+
- Best-in-Class Charging Performance: 10-30 mins
- Products for all classes of commercial vehicles, passenger vehicles &amp;amp; energy storage solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Product specs vs. closest competitor &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Range per charge: 370 miles vs. 300 miles
Speed of charge: 12 mins for 70% vs. 30 mins for 60%
Lifespan: 3000 cycles vs. 1000 cycles 
Lifetime Throughput Mileage: 1M miles vs. 270K miles&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2025 Adjacent TAM = ~ $45B&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;55% CAGR 2020-2025E&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microvast’s batteries are now integrated in ~30K vehicles, running in 160 cities, 19 countries, for a total of over 3.8 billion miles traveled on its batteries to date w/ 0 accidents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the Board of Directors at Microvast is Dr. M. Stanley Whittingham, who was recently awarded the Nobel Prize in Chemistry for his ground-breaking work on lithium-ion batteries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will Support OshkoshDefense in future progress which includes the USPS Contract&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microvast&amp;#39;s marquee customer partnerships w/ industry leaders, including Gaussin, FPT Industrial, Oshkosh and a &amp;quot;leading German luxury sports car company&amp;quot;, this is due to be announced shortly as well as R&amp;amp;D partnerships w/ BMW &amp;amp; Ford&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Could the luxury OEM partner be Mercedes?
1 year ago Mercedes-Benz&amp;#39;s decided to build the new generation of the eSprinter electric van in Ludwigsfelde which coincidentally is the same proximity of Microvast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microvast is light years ahead of $QS QuantumScapeCo in every aspect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want a piece of the EV Battery sector, this is it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These batteries are also FIRE PROOF&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What companies no matter how good of an investment they’re that you absolutely refuse to invest with?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I stay away from Social media stocks primarily because I hate what they do with
user data and the scandals they’ve been apart of. I’m Weary of big tech like
google and Apple for similar reasons.

I don’t invest in pharma unless it’s in a diversified ETF. Not a big fan of
Pharmaceuticals cause of…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ouvysd/what_companies_no_matter_how_good_of_an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ouvysd/what_companies_no_matter_how_good_of_an/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 15:38:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I stay away from Social media stocks primarily because I hate what they do with user data and the scandals they’ve been apart of. I’m Weary of big tech like google and Apple for similar reasons. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t invest in pharma unless it’s in a diversified ETF. Not a big fan of Pharmaceuticals cause of controversial things that happen with medical trials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t invest In China anymore cause of the shadiness of the Chinese government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t invest in Weed stocks cause I’m really not educated enough on it and it’s a polarizing topic for the most part.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gotta love the Deus ex machina saving my portfolio]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ov5y5f/gotta_love_the_deus_ex_machina_saving_my_portfolio/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ov5y5f/gotta_love_the_deus_ex_machina_saving_my_portfolio/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 15:13:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does anyone else have a moral obligation not to invest in certain stocks?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I would consider myself a very moral person, I invest but I'd still rather money
go to the average person than a corporation. Like if a large company i have
money in gets slapped with a deserved fine or lawsuit im happy even though I
will lose money

I could never invest in tobacco, oil, defence,…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ov6n59/does_anyone_else_have_a_moral_obligation_not_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ov6n59/does_anyone_else_have_a_moral_obligation_not_to/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 14:29:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I would consider myself a very moral person, I invest but I&amp;#39;d still rather money go to the average person than a corporation. Like if a large company i have money in gets slapped with a deserved fine or lawsuit im happy even though I will lose money&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could never invest in tobacco, oil, defence, MLM stocks like herbalife, diamond mines, huge shady banks like goldman, or just morally abhorrent companies like nestle and Monsanto &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know you could make the argument that every company is actually morally abhorrent because they exist solely to make money and I&amp;#39;d agree with you, but in a late capitalist world where the wealth gap is higher than ever and social climbing is at the lowest it has ever been you have to make bread in some way or another &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I absolutely loathe war profiteers, I loathe tobacco companies because my grandad died of lung cancer, I loathe mlm stocks because they trap average working people in debt, I loathe diamond mines for creating artificial scarcity and for hiring mercanries to murder striking diamond workers. So why would I give my money to any of them and contribute to helping them reach their goals? How would it be moral to profit off these bloodsucking leeches?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know wallstreet is sociopath/psychopath central, I mean they collapsed the global economy in 2008 because they were making so much money fucking over the average person but I really hate that attitude that you should leave morals at the door when investing. With that attitude these companies will continue to exploit and hurt people, &amp;quot;someone has to profit why not it be you?&amp;quot; why does anyone need to profit off it? I have seen a few comments on reddit saying that they would invest in a company even if it used slavery which I find sickening &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Does anyone else not invest in certain companies/industries out of their moral beliefs or do you leave morals at the door?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Finally paying off mortgage.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Finally going to pay off my mortgage. I’m 43 and will have the option to retire
at 50. Now I’ll be able to max out my retirement accounts.I’m a government
worker and will receive a nice pension. More than enough to cover my living
expenses. Please critique my investment strategy. Thank you!

457…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/ov6i8f/finally_paying_off_mortgage/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/ov6i8f/finally_paying_off_mortgage/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 14:29:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally going to pay off my mortgage. I’m 43 and will have the option to retire at 50. Now I’ll be able to max out my retirement accounts.I’m a government worker and will receive a nice pension. More than enough to cover my living expenses. Please critique my investment strategy. Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;457 (traditional) currently in a SP 500 index fund but thinking of switching to Schwab Target 2045 Index Fund for diversification. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roth 401K: SWTSX&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roth IRA: FSKAX&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coroners rule death of 21 yr old University of Cincinnati student was not caused by vaccine, but natural causes **

John Foley died of acute heart failure one day after taking vaccine. He had no underlying health issues]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1421224103139217418</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1421224103139217418</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 13:40:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amazon faces more than slowing sales growth: it needs more warehouses]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-faces-more-than-slowing-sales-growth-it-needs-more-warehouses-2021-07-30/

Amazon plans to add 517 facilities to its global distribution infrastructure in
the coming years, according to logistics consultancy MWPVL International. That
is 176…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/out3du/amazon_faces_more_than_slowing_sales_growth_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/out3du/amazon_faces_more_than_slowing_sales_growth_it/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 11:44:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-faces-more-than-slowing-sales-growth-it-needs-more-warehouses-2021-07-30/&quot;&gt;https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-faces-more-than-slowing-sales-growth-it-needs-more-warehouses-2021-07-30/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amazon plans to add 517 facilities to its global distribution infrastructure in the coming years, according to logistics consultancy MWPVL International. That is 176 million square feet on top of the 402 million it already has.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amazon did not comment on the accuracy of those estimates, but said its infrastructure rollout already is ramping up. Over the past 12 months, capital expenditures and equipment leases jumped 74% to $54.5 billion, almost double the growth rate a year ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amazon is still investing the profit, expanding the warehouses and logistic infrastructures. AWS and advertisement revenue growth also reaccelerated. Investors need to be patience as the investment short term period for amazon will pay off for the long term benefit of shareholders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Adobe vs Netflix compared (and faang debate)]]></title><description><![CDATA[I picked these to compare since they both run a subscription based model and
have similar marketcaps (250 billion or so), and pe (54 or so) As of right now
im leaning towards adobe, the reason is because they have few competitors,
diverse products range. I believe they have better growth potential…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ov1ml8/adobe_vs_netflix_compared_and_faang_debate/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ov1ml8/adobe_vs_netflix_compared_and_faang_debate/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 07:34:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I picked these to compare since they both run a subscription based model and have similar marketcaps (250 billion or so), and pe (54 or so) As of right now im leaning towards adobe, the reason is because they have few competitors, diverse products range. I believe they have better growth potential thanks to better pricing power and more user growth potential. (us&amp;amp;international growth vs netflix primarily international) higher margins (40% vs 16%), stock buybacks (-1% vs +1% dilution), high switching costs better moat, much better balance sheet for adobe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a forward pe, adobe is about 10% more expensive (fwd pe of 44 vs 40) and marketcap wise it is about 25% higher. (adobe makes about 15% more profit) The main benefit for netflix is improving margins over time but I only see net profit margins going to 25% max.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing I want to add for adobe has over 100 products with 60% being creative cloud and that alone has 20-30 famous products like photoshop, primer pro, the stuff you know adobe for. document cloud and digital experience no one knows but that segment is growing like crazy whereas netflix makes 99% of revenue from one main product. the two segments for adobe is mostly business to business like digital marketing, digital signatures, data analytics, ai, ecommerce sales, publishing, and much more and makes 40% of sales and growing in a fast market where things are going more digital (think youtube, shopify, docusign). I just dont see much growth for netflix where pretty much in the us more than 70 million users out of 120 million households have it already.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But i put up an poll on whats better and everyone said netflix, but no one really explained why? is adobe underrated and should it replace netflix in faang, or is netflix still king and explain why it is better because i dont get the hype and why everyone still use faang for big tech synonym when they are several other growth tech companies like adobe that have much higher marketcap than netflix. anyways, what is your pick on whats the better company&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My Robinhood Charger Has Been Acting Weird Since the IPO]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ouypzd/my_robinhood_charger_has_been_acting_weird_since/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ouypzd/my_robinhood_charger_has_been_acting_weird_since/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 07:22:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Maxed out my ROTH IRA, now what?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I maxed out my roth earlier this month since I had extra money that was just
sitting, but now i'm wondering what is the best next move for me? I'm not in a
position right now to contribute to a 401k yet, but I was thinking of opening a
brokerage account to invest into ETFs like VTI/VOO just like my…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/ouxbfv/maxed_out_my_roth_ira_now_what/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/ouxbfv/maxed_out_my_roth_ira_now_what/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 04:55:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I maxed out my roth earlier this month since I had extra money that was just sitting, but now i&amp;#39;m wondering what is the best next move for me? I&amp;#39;m not in a position right now to contribute to a 401k yet, but I was thinking of opening a brokerage account to invest into ETFs like VTI/VOO just like my roth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[First time back in NYC in a year and a half 

I definitely missed this city https://t.co/LL7hhEoGxp]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1421226226606383106</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1421226226606383106</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 04:35:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What are peoples’ thoughts on Fidelity’s Zero Fees index funds?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Are there hidden downsides? I’m still learning the in’s and out’s, so having
more experienced input on these would be helpful! I’m trying to help my sister
(24 years old) set up her retirement account since her company does not offer a
401k. Looking at doing a Roth IRA at Fidelity for her. She has…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/oumaqp/what_are_peoples_thoughts_on_fidelitys_zero_fees/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/oumaqp/what_are_peoples_thoughts_on_fidelitys_zero_fees/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 03:08:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are there hidden downsides? I’m still learning the in’s and out’s, so having more experienced input on these would be helpful! I’m trying to help my sister (24 years old) set up her retirement account since her company does not offer a 401k. Looking at doing a Roth IRA at Fidelity for her. She has ZERO interest in this stuff, so a lazy-type portfolio is best for her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Story: I almost lost $802K today and I did it for $4100 in options premium. Don't do that.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I thought I had a brilliant, fool proof strategy that the market didn't know and
I was first to discover but I was wrong.

The strategy: Find weekly options deep out of the money that yield at least 0.5%
of the capital requirement. The shot strike price must be below the 200 moving
day average and…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ouuhev/story_i_almost_lost_802k_today_and_i_did_it_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ouuhev/story_i_almost_lost_802k_today_and_i_did_it_for/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 02:32:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I thought I had a brilliant, fool proof strategy that the market didn&amp;#39;t know and I was first to discover but I was wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The strategy:  Find weekly options deep out of the money that yield at least 0.5% of the capital requirement. The shot strike price must be below the 200 moving day average and you leverage up to get decent premiums.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started this in May 2021 selling deep out of the money TSLA naked puts. Then I realized this uses too much margin, so I learnt about credit spreads but I didn&amp;#39;t act on it. Then came big tech earnings week and I decided to lay low and not trade at all, but then my tool scanned and found the AMZN deep out of the money puts are yielding similar returns to TSLA, which is basically almost impossible to find in the market unless it&amp;#39;s something like AMC or other meme stocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I decided to pull the trigger, so I sold 3280 shot, and bought 3200 long on 7/28 expiring 7/30. AMZN was trading north of 3650. I was certain it wouldn&amp;#39;t drop 10% or even get close.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well after hours happened and I paniced, my life flashed before me, I had levered up $525000 in my account, and I also had levered up my wife&amp;#39;s account for $280,000 for a total of $800,000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This wasn&amp;#39;t a YOLO, it wasn&amp;#39;t a double my money scheme. I was thinking I could do this 52 weeks in a year, collect 0.5% yield on $800,000 of collateral and move to Hawaii.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It didn&amp;#39;t work out like that. When the markets opened, I got out of the position with $76K of damage, and wiped out all my gains and then some, but I&amp;#39;m thankful to everyone who helped me here on reddit (elsewhere) and WSB discord, and of course my wife who when she found out we&amp;#39;d lose $800,000 just said, don&amp;#39;t worry at least we&amp;#39;ll be together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So cautionary tale for those selling levered up bull put credit spreads and/or naked TSLA puts, those black swan events you don&amp;#39;t think you can get close to ... well you can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: I lost $76K closing the position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT 2: I had all my margin used up, so I needed to wire in more cash, which thankfully my broker makes available immediately, so that&amp;#39;s how I actually closed the trade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT 3: Please note, this was not a YOLO, I was not considering this as a gambling thing, but of course I know how it is now, but I&amp;#39;m not a YOLOer is what I wanted to say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT 4: I have hundreds of DMs asking me how I found the spread, I will buy a new domain, host my app on that and you can all have at it for free. But I mean I hope you know it&amp;#39;s not as good as it sounds given my post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT 5: Proof: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/HK0D5Yp&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/a/HK0D5Yp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[July...
Moderna $MRNA: +50%
Bitcoin $BTC: +17%
Ethereum $ETH: +7%
20+Yr Treasury $TLT: +4%
Nasdaq 100 $QQQ: +3%
S&amp;P $SPY: +2%
EM $EEM: -6%
SPACs $SPAK: -11%
China $FXI: -13%
Dogecoin $DOGE: -19%
GameStop $GME: -25%
China Tech $KWEB: -28%
AMC $AMC: -35%
TAL Education $TAL: -76%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1421229920768909317</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1421229920768909317</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 01:56:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fuck, my wife’s boyfriend is gunna be pissed… no money for date night this weekend…]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ouujdd/fuck_my_wifes_boyfriend_is_gunna_be_pissed_no/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ouujdd/fuck_my_wifes_boyfriend_is_gunna_be_pissed_no/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 00:53:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Here is a Market Recap for today Friday, July 30, 2021]]></title><description><![CDATA[PsychoMarket Recap - Friday, July 30, 2021

Stocks fell Friday, reversing after yesterday’s gains to cap off one of the
choppier weeks we’ve had in the market all year. The choppiness largely seems to
stem from very erratic movements after-hours after companies report earnings. In
my humble opinion,…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/outna8/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_friday_july_30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/outna8/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_friday_july_30/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 23:41:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Friday, July 30, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks fell Friday, reversing after yesterday’s gains to cap off one of the choppier weeks we’ve had in the market all year. The choppiness largely seems to stem from very erratic movements after-hours after companies report earnings. In my humble opinion, a lot of these movements seem like overreactions to me and represent nice opportunities. Moreover, this week market participants digested a weaker-than-expected print in GDP growth and the Federal Reserve’s July Monetary Policy Report. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the volatility, all three major indexes closed the month higher, capping the six consecutive month of gains. As of today’s close, the S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) is up 18.04% year-to-date. Absolutely insane. On the other hand, the Russell 2000 (IWM), which tracks the performance of small-caps, continued it’s streak of underperformance, closing the month 3.77% lower. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Core personal consumption expenditures (PCE) grew at a faster year-on-year rate in June than in May, reflecting ongoing upward price pressures as demand surges during the recovery. The Bureau of Economic Analysis reported that core PCE grew 3.5% in June over last year, topping May&amp;#39;s 3.4% rate. Still, however, this was less hot than the 3.7% pace consensus economists expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, the US Bureau of Economic Analysis released its advanced estimate of second-quarter gross-domestic-product (GDP) growth. Despite accelerating from the first-quarter, economists were largely expecting a higher jump, despite consumer spending, the largest component of US economic activity, beating expectations. However, it seems market participants were not fazed. Here are the numbers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q2 GDP, seasonally adjusted annualized quarter-over-quarter:&lt;/strong&gt; 6.5% vs. 8.4% expected and a downwardly revised 6.3% in Q1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personal consumption:&lt;/strong&gt; 11.8% vs. 10.5% expected and 11.4% in Q1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Core personal consumption expenditures, quarter-over-quarter:&lt;/strong&gt; 6.0% vs. 6.1% expected and an upwardly revised 2.7% in Q1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The July Monetary Policy Report was largely reiterated the same thing it has been for the last 3-4 months, but did include did include some new language hinting that the economic recovery is getting closer to the Fed’s stated goals. The statement read, “Last December, the Committee indicated that it would continue to increase its holdings of Treasury securities by at least $80 billion per month and of agency mortgage‑backed securities by at least $40 billion per month until substantial further progress has been made toward its maximum employment and price stability goals. Since then, the economy has made progress toward these goals, and the Committee will continue to assess progress in coming meetings.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, the Fed athe report did acknowledge potential risks and stated the Fed was ready to act if “appropriate risks arise”. The statement read, “In assessing the appropriate stance of monetary policy, the Committee will continue to monitor the implications of incoming information for the economic outlook. The Committee would be prepared to adjust the stance of monetary policy as appropriate if risks emerge that could impede the attainment of the Committee&amp;#39;s goals. The Committee&amp;#39;s assessments will take into account a wide range of information, including readings on public health, labor market conditions, inflation pressures and inflation expectations, and financial and international developments.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read the entire July FOMC statement here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/pressreleases/monetary20210728a.htm&quot;&gt;https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/pressreleases/monetary20210728a.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week, the five largest companies in the market, Apple (AAPL), Amazon (AMZN), Microsoft (MSFT), Alphabet (GOOG, GOOGL), and Facebook (FB) all reported earnings. Despite all of them handily beating top-line estimates, a lot of them actually pulled back. Let’s recap the numbers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microsoft (MSFT)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revenue:&lt;/strong&gt; $46.15 billion versus $44.25 billion expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Earnings per share:&lt;/strong&gt; $2.17 versus $1.92 expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Productivity and Business Processes:&lt;/strong&gt; $14.69 billion versus $13.9 billion expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intelligent Cloud:&lt;/strong&gt; $17.38 billion versus $16.4 billion expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More Personal Computing:&lt;/strong&gt; $14.09 billion versus $13.8 billion expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alphabet (GOOG, GOOGL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Earnings per share (EPS):&lt;/strong&gt; $27.26 vs $19.34 per share&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revenue:&lt;/strong&gt; $61.88 billion vs $56.16 billion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YouTube advertising revenue:&lt;/strong&gt; $7.00 billion vs $6.37 billion expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google Cloud revenue:&lt;/strong&gt; $4.63 billion vs $4.40 billion expected, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traffic acquisition costs (TAC):&lt;/strong&gt; $10.93 billion vs $9.74 billion expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apple (AAPL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EPS&lt;/strong&gt;: $1.30 vs. $1.01 estimated &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revenue&lt;/strong&gt;: $81.41 billion vs. $73.30 billion estimated, up 36% year-over-year &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;iPhone revenue&lt;/strong&gt;: $39.57 billion vs. $34.01 billion estimated, up 49.78% year-over-year &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Services revenue&lt;/strong&gt;: $17.48 billion vs. $16.33 billion estimated, up 33% year-over-year &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Products revenue&lt;/strong&gt;: $8.76 billion vs. $7.80 billion estimated, up 40% year-over-year &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mac revenue&lt;/strong&gt;:$8.24 billion vs. $8.07 billion estimated, up 16% year-over-year &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;iPad revenue&lt;/strong&gt;: $7.37 billion vs. $7.15 billion estimated, up 12% year-over-year &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gross margin&lt;/strong&gt;: 43.3% vs. 41.9% estimated &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook (FB)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Earnings:&lt;/strong&gt; $3.61 per share, adjusted, vs. $3.03 per share expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revenue:&lt;/strong&gt; $29.08 billion, vs. $27.89 billion expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily active users (DAUs):&lt;/strong&gt; 1.91 billion, vs. 1.91 billion expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monthly active users (MAUs):&lt;/strong&gt; 2.90 billion, vs. 2.91 billion expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Average revenue per user (ARPU):&lt;/strong&gt; $10.12, vs. $9.66 expected &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon (AMZN)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revenue:&lt;/strong&gt; $113.08 billion versus $115.06 billion expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EPS:&lt;/strong&gt; $15.12 versus $12.22 expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AWS revenue:&lt;/strong&gt; $14.81 billion versus $14.18 billion expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This earning season is shaping to be another record-breaking quarter. As of Friday, 88% of S&amp;amp;P 500 companies topped consensus earnings per share estimates, according to FactSet data. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As many as 125,000 people reported suffering Snapchat outages Thursday evening, as per industry tracker Downdetector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yesterday, was the highly anticipated IPO of Robinhood (HOOD), popular brokerage that has garnered a horrendous reputation among many retail traders, particularly those who invest in “meme stocks”. Probably not the IPO they were hoping for, with the stock down almost 7% since it began trading&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal income rose 0.1% in June month-on-month, according to the Bureau of Economic Analysis&amp;#39; monthly report. Consensus economists were looking for a 0.3% monthly decline, according to Bloomberg data. In May, personal income fell 2.2%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Boeing (BA) target raised by Wells Fargo from $244 to $254 at Equal-Weight. Stock currently around $226&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bio-Rad Laboratories (BIO) target raised by Wells Fargo from $735 to $930 at Overweight. Stock currently around $740&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comcast (CMCSA) with a host of target raises. Consensus price target $70 at Buy. Stock currently around $59&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deckers Outdoor (DECK) with a host of target raises. Consensus price target $500 at Buy. Stock currently around $411&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gilead Sciences (GILD) with two target raises. Stock currently around $68

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SVB Leerink from $74 to $77 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Royal bank of Canada from $81 to $84 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intercontinental Exchange (ICE) target raised by Raymond James from $136 to $140 at Buy. Stock currently around $120&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LPL Financial (LPLA) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $195 to $202 at Overweight. Stock currently around $141&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MasterCard (MA) with a host of target raises. Consensus price target $450 at Buy. Stock currently around $385&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ArcelorMittal (MT) target raised by Deutsche Bank from $43 to $47 at Buy. Stock currently around $35&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;O’Reilly Automotive (ORLY) target raised by Oppenheimer from $590 to $690 at Outperform. Stock currently around $603&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;STMicroelectronics (STM) target raised by Cowen from $49 to $52 at Outperform. Stock currently around $41&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skyworks Solutions (SWKS) with two target raises. Stock currently around $184

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B. Riley from $235 to $245 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Needham &amp;amp; Co. from $245 to $255&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“In my view, the biggest investment risk is not the volatility of prices, but whether you will suffer a permanent loss of capital. Not only is the mere drop in stock prices not risk, but it is an opportunity. Where else do you look for cheap stocks?” - Li Lu&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Once Upon a Time on Wall Street]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ound3f/once_upon_a_time_on_wall_street/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ound3f/once_upon_a_time_on_wall_street/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 22:50:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Good read by former Vanguard CEO Jack Brennan. Has anyone else read it yet?]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/ouej9c/good_read_by_former_vanguard_ceo_jack_brennan_has/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/ouej9c/good_read_by_former_vanguard_ceo_jack_brennan_has/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 21:30:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amazon drops 137 billion in marketcap - a record.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Amazon drops 7.5% today after earnings, losing 137.25 billion in one day. This
is the biggest marketcap drop in one day. To put in perspective, if markets were
flat, amazon alone would contribute 0.15% drop in VT (all equities worldwide)
0.3% in VOO (sp500) and 0.63% in QQQ The drop is enough, in…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/out55s/amazon_drops_137_billion_in_marketcap_a_record/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/out55s/amazon_drops_137_billion_in_marketcap_a_record/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 21:09:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon drops 7.5% today after earnings, losing 137.25 billion in one day. This is the biggest marketcap drop in one day. To put in perspective, if markets were flat, amazon alone would contribute 0.15% drop in VT (all equities worldwide) 0.3% in VOO (sp500) and 0.63% in QQQ The drop is enough, in theory, to send 1100 dollars to every us household. In terms of marketcap leaders, apple is 2.4 trillion, microsoft is 2.15 trillion, saudi aramco is at 1.85 trillion, google is 1.8 trillion, amazon is 1.67 trillion. google surpasses amazon in marketcap due to strong surge as earnings beat expectations by more than 40%. amazon missed revenue and guidance was below expectations. this is one of the few times amazon misses earnings, and one of the worst % drops for amazon not including 2000,2008 crash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my opinion, this drop is exaggerated. most of the drop is because of sales dropping and bad guidance, but most of revenue comes from retail. But most of the profit comes from aws and ads, and both of the business has accelerated this year. Retail is low margin business, usually 2-3% whereas 20-30% for ads and aws. so aws and ads revenue is 10 times more valuable. People pay attention to revenue as a whole instead of the segments making the profits. I would consider to buy this stock but im more of an etf guy, so i dont have a position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;sources: companiesmarketcap, vanguard/nasdaq site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Daily Reverse Repo Hits Historic High - Over 1 Trillion]]></title><description><![CDATA[In 2019, highest was $2.306B.

In 2020, highest was $307M.

And now in 2021, we have hit a whopping $1,039.394B.

For a short definition of what a reverse repo is, it is a short-term agreement
to purchase securities in order to sell them back at a slightly higher price.
Currently it seems banks have…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ourri0/daily_reverse_repo_hits_historic_high_over_1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ourri0/daily_reverse_repo_hits_historic_high_over_1/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 20:25:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2019, highest was $2.306B.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2020, highest was $307M.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now in 2021, we have hit a whopping $1,039.394B. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a short definition of what a reverse repo is, it is a short-term agreement to purchase securities in order to sell them back at a slightly higher price. Currently it seems banks have too much liquidity (which is too much liability), causing these ridiculous RRP spikes. This is a pretty bad sign for the economy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I spend too much time on Reddit]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ounupk/i_spend_too_much_time_on_reddit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ounupk/i_spend_too_much_time_on_reddit/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 20:25:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Microvast ~ MVST 🚀🚀🚀🚀]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ok guys. The mods have assured me the auto bot won’t delete the post now. So we
should be good to go.

Microvast - MVST🚀🚀

Listen up retards. This is a x5 play. 60% Short volume too!!! Let’s squeeze
them!

Microvast - Leader in the fast charging batteries. Full charge in 20minutes !

New interview…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ouiyx9/microvast_mvst/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ouiyx9/microvast_mvst/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 20:25:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok guys. The mods have assured me the auto bot won’t delete the post now. So we should be good to go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microvast - MVST🚀🚀&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listen up retards. This is a x5 play. 
60% Short volume too!!! Let’s squeeze them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microvast - Leader in the fast charging batteries. Full charge in 20minutes !&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New interview w/ Microvast COO Shane Smith&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cheddar.com/media/microvast-goes-public-on-nasdaq-via-spac&quot;&gt;https://cheddar.com/media/microvast-goes-public-on-nasdaq-via-spac&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some key quotes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The primary reason that we even went to the public markets was to raise enough capital to support the orders we already have in place. We won more business then we have capacity for&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Solid State Battery
-Lithium Metal battery
-High Temperature Cells (Sports Car Application)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vertically integrated &amp;amp; proprietary
- $1.5B contracted revenue thru 2027
- $100M+ revenue 2020 / $2.3B 2025E revenue
- 550+ patents
- 3.8B+ miles with ZERO operational accidents
- 28K+ battery systems in operation in 19 countries &amp;amp; 160 cities&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1800+ total employees (500+ R&amp;amp;D personnel)
- Full Range of Energy Densities: 85 – 265 Wh / Kg
- Long cycle lives: 2,500+ – 20,000+
- Best-in-Class Charging Performance: 10-30 mins
- Products for all classes of commercial vehicles, passenger vehicles &amp;amp; energy storage solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Product specs vs. closest competitor &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Range per charge: 370 miles vs. 300 miles
Speed of charge: 12 mins for 70% vs. 30 mins for 60%
Lifespan: 3000 cycles vs. 1000 cycles 
Lifetime Throughput Mileage: 1M miles vs. 270K miles&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2025 Adjacent TAM = ~ $45B&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;55% CAGR 2020-2025E&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microvast’s batteries are now integrated in ~30K vehicles, running in 160 cities, 19 countries, for a total of over 3.8 billion miles traveled on its batteries to date w/ 0 accidents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the Board of Directors at Microvast is Dr. M. Stanley Whittingham, who was recently awarded the Nobel Prize in Chemistry for his ground-breaking work on lithium-ion batteries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will Support OshkoshDefense in future progress which includes the USPS Contract&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microvast&amp;#39;s marquee customer partnerships w/ industry leaders, including Gaussin, FPT Industrial, Oshkosh and a &amp;quot;leading German luxury sports car company&amp;quot;, this is due to be announced shortly as well as R&amp;amp;D partnerships w/ BMW &amp;amp; Ford&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Could the luxury OEM partner be Mercedes?
1 year ago Mercedes-Benz&amp;#39;s decided to build the new generation of the eSprinter electric van in Ludwigsfelde which coincidentally is the same proximity of Microvast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microvast is light years ahead of $QS QuantumScapeCo in every aspect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want a piece of the EV Battery sector, this is it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These batteries are also FIRE PROOF&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MSFT long-term vs FAANG, growth-rate, ai, and tablets]]></title><description><![CDATA[Another MSFT post, i know.

Comparing MSFT's growth rate, P/S and P/E to Google's and Facebooks, I can't
help but notice both Google and Facebook have significantly higher sales growth
and lower P/E's and P/S's.

MSFT has a strong position in cloud, desktop/laptop OS and…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ouikh2/msft_longterm_vs_faang_growthrate_ai_and_tablets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ouikh2/msft_longterm_vs_faang_growthrate_ai_and_tablets/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 18:52:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another MSFT post, i know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Comparing MSFT&amp;#39;s growth rate, P/S and P/E to Google&amp;#39;s and Facebooks, I can&amp;#39;t help but notice both Google and Facebook have significantly higher sales growth and lower P/E&amp;#39;s and P/S&amp;#39;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MSFT has a strong position in cloud, desktop/laptop OS and business/educational software, but in terms of long-term growth with growing markets like tablets, AI, and advertising, is MSFT a player in those or other new growth markets?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both Google and Facebook are building products to high-growth markets like Android/AI/Instagram/WhatsAPP,  and I was wondering if MSFT was in any similar high-growth markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to share your thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMZN yolo. Some spank bank material for you degenerates while you’re bored this weekend while the market is closed.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oulhms/amzn_yolo_some_spank_bank_material_for_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oulhms/amzn_yolo_some_spank_bank_material_for_you/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 18:31:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[US SEC OF DEFENSE — FULLY VAXXED — GIGANTIC PUSSY
 https://t.co/4utQ7eaGcO]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1421000051611078659</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1421000051611078659</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 17:35:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Commodity prices over last year...
Natural Gas: +118%
Gasoline: +88%
WTI Crude: +79%
Coffee: +79%
Heating Oil: +75%
Brent Crude +74%
Corn: +69%
Soybeans: +55%
Copper: +55%
Sugar: +52%
Cotton: +48%
Wheat: +35%
Lumber: +21%
Palladium: +12%
Platinum: +8%
Silver: +6%
Gold: -6%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1421128997086371849</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1421128997086371849</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 16:39:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[If you’re fully vaxxed and get COVID and spread it to others — that means the vaccine is working]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1420943642114527232</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1420943642114527232</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 14:43:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[RANSOM: AUSTRALIA TO REMAIN LOCKED DOWN UNTIL 80% OF POPULATION IS JABB’d **

Presently just 14% are vaccinated, 2 deaths YTD]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1421095877217767428</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1421095877217767428</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 14:43:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ark Innovation ETF bought $45 million worth of Robinhood on first day of trade]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Ark Innovation ETF ARKK, +0.21%, the flagship fund of Cathie Wood's Ark
Investment Management, purchased nearly 1.3 million shares of Robinhood Markets
HOOD, -8.37% during its first day of trade, worth roughly $45 million. Robinhood
shares slumped 8% as the initial public offering, targeted to…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ouk7fb/ark_innovation_etf_bought_45_million_worth_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ouk7fb/ark_innovation_etf_bought_45_million_worth_of/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 14:18:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ark Innovation ETF ARKK, +0.21%, the flagship fund of Cathie Wood&amp;#39;s Ark Investment Management, purchased nearly 1.3 million shares of Robinhood Markets HOOD, -8.37% during its first day of trade, worth roughly $45 million. Robinhood shares slumped 8% as the initial public offering, targeted to Robinhood&amp;#39;s own retail base, was greeted with tepid demand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/ark-innovation-etf-bought-45-million-worth-of-robinhood-on-first-day-of-trade-2021-07-30&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/ark-innovation-etf-bought-45-million-worth-of-robinhood-on-first-day-of-trade-2021-07-30&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is everyone’s thoughts, opinions, and takes on this move by Cathie Wood and Ark?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Global Coronavirus (COVID-19) Vaccine Market Research Report 2021: Market is Expected to Grow at a Robust Rate to Reach $91.3 Billion]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dublin, July 30, 2021 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- The "Global Coronavirus Vaccine
Market, By Infection Type (SARS-CoV-2, SARS-CoV, MERS-CoV), By Vaccine Type, By
Product Type, By Route of Administration, By Patient Type, By End User, By
Region, Competition Forecast & Opportunities, 2026" report has been…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ouj7jl/global_coronavirus_covid19_vaccine_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ouj7jl/global_coronavirus_covid19_vaccine_market/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 14:18:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dublin, July 30, 2021 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- The &amp;quot;Global Coronavirus Vaccine Market, By Infection Type (SARS-CoV-2, SARS-CoV, MERS-CoV), By Vaccine Type, By Product Type, By Route of Administration, By Patient Type, By End User, By Region, Competition Forecast &amp;amp; Opportunities, 2026&amp;quot; report has been added to &lt;strong&gt;ResearchAndMarkets.com&amp;#39;s&lt;/strong&gt; offering.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Global Coronavirus Vaccine Market is expected to grow at a robust rate in value terms to reach USD 91325.46 million by the end of 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ongoing pandemic novel coronavirus disease (COVID-19) is caused due to SARS-COV-2 and generally spreads from animals to humans and then from humans to humans.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Global Coronavirus Vaccine Market is expected to grow at a robust rate during the forecast period. The Global Coronavirus Vaccine Market is driven by the increasing prevalence of this disease across different parts of the globe. This has increased the need to protect the world from the virus, thereby increased sales of coronavirus vaccine through 2026.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, increasing research and development activities by various pharmaceutical &amp;amp; biotechnology players for the development of potential vaccines is anticipated to foster the market growth. According to WHO, there are more than 70 coronavirus vaccines under development by different companies and organizations.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently, mRNA-based vaccine named Moderna COVID-19 Vaccine (mRNA-1273), adenovirus-based vaccine named COVID-19 Vaccine AstraZeneca (AZD1222) also known as Covishield in India and Sputnik V which constitutes recombinant adenovirus vaccine which is developed by Gamaleya Research Institute, Russia are being used for vaccination among adults.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The vaccine developed by Moderna, Inc., Pfizer Inc., AstraZeneca PLC are leading the race and is currently administered to entire population. T-COVIDTM, AdCOVID and COVI-VAC are intranasal COVID-19 vaccines which are under pre-clinical and phase 1 trials.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Global Coronavirus Vaccine Market is segmented based on infection type, vaccine type, product type, route of administration, patient type, end-user, company, and region. Based on infection type, the market can be categorized into SARS-CoV-2, SARS-CoV and MERS-CoV. The SARS-CoV-2 segment is expected to dominate the market since this infection or virus is the primary cause of the pandemic.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regionally, the Global Coronavirus Vaccine Market has been segmented into Asia-Pacific, North America, South America, Europe, and Middle East &amp;amp; Africa. Among these, Asia-Pacific is expected to witness significant growth during the forecast period in the overall coronavirus vaccine market.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Major companies are developing advanced technologies and launching new services to stay competitive in the market. Other competitive strategies include mergers &amp;amp; acquisitions and new product developments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Major players include&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Moderna, Inc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pfizer Inc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson SA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sinopharm Group Company Ltd&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AstraZeneca PLC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serum Institute of India Pvt Ltd&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bharat Biotech International Ltd&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sinovac Biotech Ltd&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sanofi SA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GlaxoSmithKline PLC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Novavax, Inc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Airway Therapeutics, Inc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cadila Healthcare Ltd&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CanSino Biologics Inc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mitsubishi Chemical Holdings Corporation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eubiologics Co Ltd&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;United Biomedical Inc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Merck &amp;amp; Co, Inc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CureVac NV&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inovio Pharmaceuticals, Inc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Report Scope:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Years considered for this report:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Base Year: 2020&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Estimated Year: 2021&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Forecast Period: 2022-2026&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Coronavirus Vaccine Market, By Infection Type:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SARS-CoV-2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SARS-CoV&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MERS-CoV&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Coronavirus Vaccine Market, By Vaccine Type:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Virus Vaccine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Viral Vector Vaccine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nucleic Acid Vaccine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protein Based Vaccine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Coronavirus Vaccine Market, By Product Type:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monovalent Vaccine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multivariant Vaccine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Coronavirus Vaccine Market, By Route of Administration:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intramuscular&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oral&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intranasal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Coronavirus Vaccine Market, By Patient Type:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adult&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pediatric&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Coronavirus Vaccine Market, By End-User:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hospitals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clinics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research Institutes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Coronavirus Vaccine Market, By Region:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;North America&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;United States&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mexico&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Canada&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Europe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;United Kingdom&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Germany&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;France&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Italy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spain&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Asia-Pacific&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;China&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;India&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Singapore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Japan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;South Korea&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hong Kong&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Australia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thailand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;South America&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brazil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Argentina&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colombia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Middle East &amp;amp; Africa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UAE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Saudi Arabia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kuwait&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;South Africa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ceo.ca/@nasdaq/global-coronavirus-covid-19-vaccine-market-research&quot;&gt;https://ceo.ca/@nasdaq/global-coronavirus-covid-19-vaccine-market-research&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NYC IS BACK!
 https://t.co/OfbaIAgDWU]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1420918305284632581</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1420918305284632581</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 13:43:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[U.S. GDP (6.5%) Trails Forecast (8.4%) Even as Consumer Spending Surges]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-gdp-trails-forecast-even-123834932.html


U.S. GDP TRAILS FORECAST EVEN AS CONSUMER SPENDING SURGES

(Bloomberg) -- U.S. growth missed forecasts in the second quarter as the effects
of supply-chain constraints reverberated through the economy and took the shine
off…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/otx4g6/us_gdp_65_trails_forecast_84_even_as_consumer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/otx4g6/us_gdp_65_trails_forecast_84_even_as_consumer/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 13:05:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-gdp-trails-forecast-even-123834932.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-gdp-trails-forecast-even-123834932.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;U.S. GDP Trails Forecast Even as Consumer Spending Surges&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Bloomberg)  -- U.S. growth missed forecasts in the second quarter as the effects of  supply-chain constraints reverberated through the economy and took the  shine off one of the biggest gains in consumer spending in decades.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gross  domestic product expanded at a 6.5% annualized rate following a revised  6.3% pace in the first quarter, the Commerce Department’s preliminary  estimate showed Thursday. Federal government outlays, residential  investment and inventories weighed on the figure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personal consumption, the biggest part of the economy, advanced an annualized 11.8%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The  inflation-adjusted value of domestically produced goods and services  climbed to an annualized $19.36 trillion, eclipsing its pre-pandemic  peak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The median forecast in a Bloomberg survey of economists  called for an 8.4% increase in second-quarter GDP. Stock-index futures  climbed after the report, the yield on the 10-year Treasury note rose  and the dollar weakened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Emboldened by vaccinations, federal  financial relief and a broader reopening of the economy, Americans had  both the wherewithal and the opportunity to ramp up spending on services  such as dining out. The extra cash paired with robust hiring helped  sustain outlays for merchandise as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, economic  growth will be challenged by waning government support and lingering  supply and labor constraints. At the same time, the rapidly spreading  delta variant of Covid-19 present risks to the spending outlook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More stories like this are available on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/&quot;&gt;bloomberg.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/subscriptions/67obqkd5zdp5lj8/?utm_source=yahoo_usn&quot;&gt;Subscribe now&lt;/a&gt; to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;©2021 Bloomberg L.P.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Charles Schwab UK boss: 'FOMO and HODL are not investment strategies']]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/ouihbi/charles_schwab_uk_boss_fomo_and_hodl_are_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/ouihbi/charles_schwab_uk_boss_fomo_and_hodl_are_not/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 12:33:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Robinhood has Worst IPO Ever]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oud6vs/robinhood_has_worst_ipo_ever/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oud6vs/robinhood_has_worst_ipo_ever/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 08:53:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Had to buy it]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oucpbs/had_to_buy_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oucpbs/had_to_buy_it/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 08:41:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Let’s tell them to get another shot after the first two don’t work” https://t.co/B7zVlm4O1L]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1420952743188049923</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1420952743188049923</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 05:35:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pinterest plunges after missing on user growth expectations]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/29/pinterest-pins-earnings-q2-2021.html

Adjusted earnings per share: 25 cents vs. 13 cents forecast by Refinitiv

Revenue: $613 million vs. $562.1 million forecast by Refinitiv

Monthly active users: 454 million vs. 482 million forecast by StreetAccount

Average revenue…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ou5s6q/pinterest_plunges_after_missing_on_user_growth/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ou5s6q/pinterest_plunges_after_missing_on_user_growth/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 05:21:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/29/pinterest-pins-earnings-q2-2021.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/29/pinterest-pins-earnings-q2-2021.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adjusted earnings per share: 25 cents vs. 13 cents forecast by Refinitiv&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revenue: $613 million vs. $562.1 million forecast by Refinitiv&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monthly active users: 454 million vs. 482 million forecast by StreetAccount&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Average revenue per user: $1.32 vs. $1.17 forecast by StreetAccount&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stock is down 14% after the earning release and down more than 19% after hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Looking for a new investment idea...high risk appetite]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi all,

I just secured some profits from SPRT and Biogen. While those were insanely
risky bets I want to reduce risks, however my risk appetite is still high as I
want to grow my assets fairly fast.

 * I am ok with loosing 25% , aiming for 50%+ profit.
 * Short investment horizon of 3-6 months
 *…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/otwan0/looking_for_a_new_investment_ideahigh_risk/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/otwan0/looking_for_a_new_investment_ideahigh_risk/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 05:00:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi all,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just secured some profits from SPRT and Biogen. While those were insanely risky bets I want to reduce risks, however my risk appetite is still high as I want to grow my assets fairly fast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am ok with loosing 25% , aiming for  50%+ profit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short investment horizon of 3-6 months&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stocks only. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like Cannabis and Lab Meat, but this is long term. I think that cruise liners are overvalued. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Appreciate any ideas. Thank you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>