<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 03:41:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[在目前的市场条件下，是否有可能出现调整？]]></title><description><![CDATA[真正的问题。在目前的市场条件下，广泛的、交叉的指数修正是否可能？
的市场条件下，是否有可能出现广泛的、交叉的指数调整？老实说，我认为不可能。我认为由于QE和美联储的支持
有如此多的现金到处乱晃，寻找一个家，以至于任何有回报前景的东西都被立即投资。
哪怕是回报前景渺茫的东西，都会被立即投资进去。

听着...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvgi4h/is_a_correction_even_possible_under_current/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvgi4h/is_a_correction_even_possible_under_current/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 02:51:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Genuine question. Is a broad, cross-index correction possible given the current market conditions? I honestly think not. I think due to QE and Fed bolstering there is so much cash sloshing around looking for a home that anything with an even remote prospect of return is instantly invested in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hear me out. I really think this is a new paradigm, not as in oh market goes up forever and this time is different, and more as in this amount of QE and stimulus mixed with bare bones low interest rate has never been achieved before. We have never had a market with the combination of those 2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here&amp;#39;s how I see things going forward:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dumb money is here to stay. There&amp;#39;s just too damn much of it flooding the market looking for a home. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Retail investor sentiment has changed. No one is risk-adverse on a broad scale anymore. Investors are willing to hold through dips and plunge more cash into them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interest rates are rock bottom, and there&amp;#39;s the possibility they stay that way or go negative due to debt implications if they&amp;#39;re raised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s going to change? Is retail suddenly going to become risk adverse? Is the amount of capital flooding the system going to be reigned in? Are interest rates going to drastically rise, if at all?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t think so. I quite literally think that given market conditions and sentiment a correction is not even possible. Do all the remind me&amp;#39;s you want. The market is unable to correct.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉有价值的唯一原因是超级充电网络，而Rivian和Lucid没有这个网络。]]></title><description><![CDATA[两年前，我以开玩笑的方式试驾了一辆特斯拉3型车，结果当天就买了一辆。
同一天。它们实际上是非常酷的车，而且快得要命......但你知道为什么我和其他有钱的正常人（又不是你们这些没钱的弱智）都要买。
但你知道为什么我和其他有钱的正常人（又称不是你们这些在RH账户里有500美元的破产弱智）会买这些车。
500美元在你的RH账户）买它们？

超级充电器网络....]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvelvp/the_only_reason_tesla_is_worth_anything_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvelvp/the_only_reason_tesla_is_worth_anything_is/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 02:29:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I test drove a Tesla model 3 two years ago as a joke and ended up buying one that same day. They&amp;#39;re actually really cool cars and fast as shit... but you know why I, and other normal people with money (aka not you broke retards with $500 in your RH accounts) buy them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE SUPER CHARGER NETWORK. This is basically a system of electric gas stations that charge your car in 30-40 minutes, and allows you to drive ANYWHERE in America and Canada. You can drive from San Diego to NYC with this network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know what you can&amp;#39;t do with a Rivian or Lucid? Drive anywhere you don&amp;#39;t normally drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you try to charge your car at a charge port or whatever, it&amp;#39;ll take you 8 hours for a full charge. The only reason Tesla is worth anything is because of their phenomenal super charger network. How the fuck are lucid and rivian going to compete with that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;edit: looks like the truth has triggered some fuckin’ noobs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[财政部长珍妮特-耶伦警告说，拜登的基础设施法案中的要求可能加速美国的债务违约。]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 财政部长珍妮特-耶伦周二警告国会领导层说
> 如果联邦政府不采取行动，它可能在下个月出现债务违约。
> 采取行动提高债务上限。
> 
> 耶伦女士在给高层立法者的一封信中预计，在12月15日之后，将有
> 有一些情况在...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvlndx/treasury_secretary_janet_yellen_warns_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvlndx/treasury_secretary_janet_yellen_warns_that/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 02:29:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen warned congressional leadership Tuesday that the federal government could default on its debt next month if they don’t take action to raise the debt ceiling.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a letter to top lawmakers, Ms. Yellen projected that after Dec. 15, there are scenarios in which the Treasury could have “insufficient resources to continue to finance the operation of the U.S. government.”  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ms. Yellen added that she has “a high degree of confidence” in the Treasury’s ability to make debt payments through Dec. 15. That’s two weeks longer than her initial forecast of Dec. 3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More money coming in? More pump?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[还有人讨厌新的Vanguard应用程序吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我讨厌那些试图成为超时尚和极简主义的应用程序。我不知道什么是
哪些地方，而且感觉功能都被拿走了。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvj98f/anybody_else_hate_the_new_vanguard_app/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvj98f/anybody_else_hate_the_new_vanguard_app/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 01:53:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I hate apps that try to be ultra sleek and minimalist. I don&amp;#39;t know where anything is, and it feels like features have been taken away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cloudflare缓解了来自15,000台设备的近2 Tbps DDoS发射]]></title><description><![CDATA["Cloudflare表示，它缓解了一次分布式拒绝服务（DDoS）攻击，该攻击的峰值略低于2 Tbps带宽。
由于使用了大约1.5万台被攻击的设备，该攻击的带宽峰值略低于2 Tbps。
15,000台被破坏的设备。

该公司表示，这是它迄今为止所目睹的最大的DDoS攻击。它
据称，它使用了一种混合型的 "网络"。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvhk2a/cloudflare_mitigated_nearly_2_tbps_ddos_launched/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvhk2a/cloudflare_mitigated_nearly_2_tbps_ddos_launched/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:51:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Cloudflare says it mitigated a distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack that peaked at just under 2 Tbps of bandwidth thanks to its use of approximately 15,000 compromised devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company says this was the largest DDoS attack it had witnessed to date. It was said to have used a mix of Mirai-infected Internet of Things devices, which are commonly used to launch massive DDoS attacks, as well as unpatched instances of the GitLab developer tool.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source, PCMag: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pcmag.com/news/cloudflare-mitigates-nearly-2-tbps-ddos-attack&quot;&gt;https://www.pcmag.com/news/cloudflare-mitigates-nearly-2-tbps-ddos-attack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是今天（2021年11月16日，星期二）的市场回顾。请欣赏!]]></title><description><![CDATA[心理市场回顾 - 2021年11月16日，星期二

今天股市上涨，市场参与者松了一口气，因为新的
市场参与者松了一口气，因为新的经济数据显示消费者需求仍然强劲，尽管持续的供应链
供应链中断和劳动力短缺的情况下，消费需求仍然强劲，市场参与者松了一口气。此外，沃尔玛（WMT）等主要零售商。
Target...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjo3j/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_tuesday_nov_16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjo3j/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_tuesday_nov_16/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:51:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Tuesday, November 16, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks gained today, with market participants releasing a sigh of relief as new economic data showed consumer demand remains strong despite ongoing supply-chain disruptions and labor shortages. Moreover, major retailers like Walmart (WMT), Target (TGT), Lowe’s (LOW), and Home Depot (HD) are set to release quarterly earnings this week, giving us more information into the state of consumer spending in the US. As a reminder, consumer spending accounts for roughly 70% of US GDP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Department of Commerce released their monthly Retail Sales Report, which showed better than expected consumer spending trends as the holiday season, by far the busiest in the year, continues to play out. Here are the numbers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retail Sales: 1.7% increase vs 1.4% expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core Retail Sales: +1.6%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manufacturing Production: +1.2%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The solid report suggests that high inflation is not dampening consumer spending. Rising household wealth, thanks to a strong stock market, house prices, and rising wages appear to be cushioning consumers against the highest annual pace of inflation in roughly thirty years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matthew Shay, President of the National Retail Federation, said of the report, “Today’s numbers show that consumers are getting a jump on their holiday shopping. We continue to urge consumers to shop early and shop safely, and we fully expect this holiday season to be one for the record books”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, two of the largest retailers in the US, Walmart (WMT) and Home Depot (HD), reported earnings today, with both companies demolishing earnings (though WMT stock did not react positively). Here are the numbers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Walmart (WMT)&lt;/strong&gt; 

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue: $140.53 billion vs $135.60 billion expected &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earnings per Share (EPS): $1.45 vs $1.40 expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sames Store Sales: +9.2% vs +6.9% expected &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;eCommerce Sales: +8% vs +1.9% expected &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Home Depot (HD)&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue: $36.82 billion vs $35.01 billion expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earnings per Share (EPS): $3.92 vs $3.40 expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Same Store Sales: +6.1% vs 1.9% expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These reports came at the tail end of what has already been an exceptionally strong earnings season. As of Friday, 92% of S&amp;amp;P 500 companies had reported actual results, and of these, 81% of them had reported better-than-expected earnings results, according to FactSet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_111221.pdf&quot;&gt;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_111221.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Somehow, someway, shares of Rivian (RIVN) keep rising after its blockbuster IPO, with the company now being the third largest auto manufacturer by market cap at roughly $150 billion despite barely completing any deliveries. This is, by far, the craziest valuation I’ve ever seen. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Commerce Department reported Tuesday that import prices rose 1.2% on a monthly basis in October, coming in well above the 0.4% rise for September. This was also above the 1.0% increase consensus economists expected for October, according to Bloomberg data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Qualcomm (QCOM) are on fire after the company projected that its chipset business will average “midteens” revenue growth through its fiscal year 2024. That’s well above the 8% average contemplated by Wall Street’s current estimates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Netflix (NFLX) is set to release the highly anticipated sequel to Tiger King tomorrow. It seems like Netflix has been on an amazing roll as of late and now has a higher market cap than Disney (DIS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lucid Motors (LCID) has now overtaken Ford Motors (F) in market cap&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple (AAPL) is reportedly working to make its own in-house modem chip that allows wireless connection for iPhones by 2023. Qualcomm (QCOM), which currently supplies modem chips for all Apple devices, estimates Apple will self-supply 80% of modem chips by 2023. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current stock price was written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance Auto Parts (AAP) with four target raises. Stock currently around $235

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Citigroup from $282 to $290 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wedbush from $250 to $270 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Credit Suisse from $250 to $255 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bank of America from $256 to $282 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Datadog (DDOG) target raised by Jefferies Financial from $210 to $230 at Buy. Stock currently around $194&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lucid Motors (LCID) price target raised by Citigroup from $28 to $57 at Buy. Stock currently around $57 after gapping up 25%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lattice Semiconductor (LSCC) target raised by Benchmark from $81 to $96 at Buy. Stock currently around $85&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NVIDIA (NVDA) target raised by Credit Suisse from $225 to $400 at Outperform. Stock currently around $300.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tyson Foods (TSN) with a host of target raises. Average price target $95 at Buy. Stock currently aroun d$84&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UnitedHealth Group (UNH) target raised by Deutsche Bank from $421 to $477 at Buy. Stock currently around $450&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Workday (WDAY) target raised by Jefferies Financial from $320 to $350 at Buy. Stock currently around $299&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Turn your wounds into wisdom.” — Oprah Winfrey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这也是磨练的一部分]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvfd4d/its_part_of_the_grind/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvfd4d/its_part_of_the_grind/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 23:53:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我们是否已经进入了一个新的时代，长期的股票市场崩溃已经成为过去？]]></title><description><![CDATA[看起来鲍威尔的说法起了作用，股市在2020年3月的暴跌后只用了3个月就恢复了。
个月就恢复了。美联储是否已经成功地
从市场上消除了所有真正的风险？如果是这样，这将是未来几十年的现状吗？
未来几十年的现状吗？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvcaii/have_we_entered_a_new_era_where_prolonged_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvcaii/have_we_entered_a_new_era_where_prolonged_stock/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 23:41:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seems like the Powell put has worked and it only took the stock market 3 months to recover after the crash in March of 2020. Has the fed managed to remove all real risk from the market? If so will this be the status quo for the next few decades?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储为什么不加息？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我听到很多关于美联储只是打开闸门以取悦华尔街并保持经济增长的论点。
讨好华尔街并保持经济增长，但这种说法在历史上的任何时候都有可能出现。
但这种说法在历史上的任何时候都有可能出现；但在过去，美联储的行为是负责任的。

当然，这种不计后果的通货膨胀推动与...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvi2d8/why_is_the_fed_not_raising_rates/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvi2d8/why_is_the_fed_not_raising_rates/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 22:35:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I hear a lot of arguments about the fed simply opening the floodgates to please Wall St and keep the economy rising, but that argument could have been made at any point in history; yet in the past the fed have acted responsibly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Surely this reckless inflatory push has something to do with competition between the US and China/Russia? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether its the fact China will overtake it quicker now or a potential conflict with either one. Could it be an experiment in whether having the “global currency” can allow a country to buy growth without insane amounts of inflation? Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta使用面部识别 "视频自拍 "寻找 "可疑账户"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[看一下Meta公司的发展方向。

我在我的IG上遇到了问题，因为现在几乎每天我都不得不
发送视频自拍进行 "验证"。似乎他们希望每个IG
帐户完全公开，而不仅仅是为了那些想浏览IG的人
匿名的人。

它直接...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv20ol/meta_using_facial_recognition_video_selfies_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv20ol/meta_using_facial_recognition_video_selfies_for/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 22:18:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A look at where Meta is heading as a company. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve bene having issues on my IG because nearly every day now I am having to send in a video selfie for &amp;quot;verification&amp;quot;. It seems like they want every IG account totally public and not simply for people who want to browse IG anonymously. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It directly says: &amp;quot;The video will never be visible on Instagram and will be deleted within 30 days. This won&amp;#39;t use ice recognition or collect biometric data&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Instagram/comments/qt15br/this_is_just_creepy/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/Instagram/comments/qt15br/this_is_just_creepy/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But given the new &amp;quot;Meta&amp;quot; name so focused on the meta verse, it&amp;#39;s extremely difficult to trust they aren&amp;#39;t using biometric data. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Captchas and &amp;quot;image puzzles&amp;quot; have been used for years to confirm human users and reduce bot activity, and are far less intrusive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The level of privacy is getting insane at this point and I just wonder where this is leading to for Meta. They say the data will be deleted within 30 days.. but I just don&amp;#39;t believe that and they are using it for some future Metaverse data. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I frankly wish this was a bigger news story already, because if they actually got backlash I think they would have to at least respond about it. Very interesting that I suddenly started getting these messages too around the same time Meta was announced as the name.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME的净累积保费不断增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[GME的净累积保费不断增加，这表明有大量的
大量的催款正在积累。这些设置是挤压的完美选择，因为
这些被MM们持有的看涨期权，可以用长线来对冲...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvbkwn/gme_net_cumulative_premiums_keep_increasing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvbkwn/gme_net_cumulative_premiums_keep_increasing/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 21:42:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The net cumulative premiums on GME keep increasing, suggesting that a large amount of calls is being accumulated. Those setups are perfect for a squeeze, as these calls, held short by MMs, net to be hedged with long shares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/srnqtpergzz71.png?width=1332&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=05053ef1adf33bb2305b4ed9db3ec184adb9d4c4&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/srnqtpergzz71.png?width=1332&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=05053ef1adf33bb2305b4ed9db3ec184adb9d4c4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the past few weeks, it&amp;#39;s obvious that the calls have been leading, as you can see on the chart below. The green and purple bars at the bottom are not volume bars, they represent premiums. As you can see, recent sessions have been overwhelmingly biased towards the call side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/2urndniugzz71.png?width=1522&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=a9ab1581d51afd41c637615aec3b0c6c47ca8846&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/2urndniugzz71.png?width=1522&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=a9ab1581d51afd41c637615aec3b0c6c47ca8846&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The volume has also been skewed to the call side MTD, with the majority of large trades being for calls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/bhq044dchzz71.jpg?width=1605&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=65bdfebff36b78ac9df8c7a69c2689ad1645989b&quot;&gt;stockgrid.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[动视首席执行官鲍比-科蒂克多年来对视频游戏巨头的性行为指控知情不报]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.wsj.com/articles/activision-videogames-bobby-kotick-sexual-misconduct-allegations-11637075680?st=2l46k41g4se9lc8&amp;amp;reflink=share_mobilewebshare

> 多年来，科蒂克先生本人也被几位女性指控在工作场所内外有
> 在工作场所内外的虐待行为，并在...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qve7ya/activision_ceo_bobby_kotick_knew_for_years_about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qve7ya/activision_ceo_bobby_kotick_knew_for_years_about/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 21:28:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/activision-videogames-bobby-kotick-sexual-misconduct-allegations-11637075680?st=2l46k41g4se9lc8&amp;amp;amp;amp;reflink=share_mobilewebshare&quot;&gt;https://www.wsj.com/articles/activision-videogames-bobby-kotick-sexual-misconduct-allegations-11637075680?st=2l46k41g4se9lc8&amp;amp;amp;amp;reflink=share_mobilewebshare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the years, Mr. Kotick himself has been accused by several women of mistreatment both inside and outside the workplace, and in some instances has worked to settle the complaints quickly and quietly, according to people familiar with the incidents and documents reviewed by the Journal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2006, one of his assistants complained that he had harassed her, including by threatening in a voice mail to have her killed, according to people familiar with the matter. He settled the matter out of court, the people said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: &lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.md/2021.11.16-160822/https://www.wsj.com/articles/activision-videogames-bobby-kotick-sexual-misconduct-allegations-11637075680&quot;&gt;Non-paywall link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我的投资组合中有1/3投资于VXUS。]]></title><description><![CDATA[另外2/3是在VTI。我是在一个半月前才开始这个冒险的。
但我不禁注意到，到目前为止，VTI的表现要好两倍。I
在一个有钱的熟人的建议下，我买了VXUS，但我读到一些东西
表明VXUS多年来一直表现不佳。是否...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv7joe/i_have_13_of_my_portfolio_invested_in_vxus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv7joe/i_have_13_of_my_portfolio_invested_in_vxus/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 20:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other 2/3 is in VTI.  I just started this adventure about a month and a half ago, but I can&amp;#39;t help but to notice that VTI performs twice as well to date.  I picked up VXUS on advice from a rich acquaintance, but I&amp;#39;ve read some things indicating that VXUS has underperformed for many years now.  Does anyone have experience with this?  I&amp;#39;m contemplating dumping everything into VTI.  This port is worth around 136k for reference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么马斯克要卖掉任何东西来支付他的税收？]]></title><description><![CDATA[像他这样的亿万富翁不是以他们的股票价值为抵押进行借款吗？如果他
如果他相信他的股票会升值，那么很明显，以1%的利息获得贷款比出售他的股票更便宜。
以1%的利息获得贷款比出售他的股票更便宜。

银行不可能不愿意借钱给世界上最富有的人。
最低限度...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv6u5w/why_does_musk_have_to_sell_anything_to_pay_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv6u5w/why_does_musk_have_to_sell_anything_to_pay_for/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 20:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t billionaires like him borrow against the value of their shares? If he believes in the value of his shares to appreciate then obviously it&amp;#39;s cheaper to get a loan at 1% interest than to sell his shares. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s no way banks aren&amp;#39;t willing to lend money to the world&amp;#39;s richest man at a minimal interest rate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[福布斯》。南希-梅斯议员提出了结束联邦大麻禁令的法案。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvbyxa/forbes_representative_nancy_mace_introduces_bill/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvbyxa/forbes_representative_nancy_mace_introduces_bill/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:56:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian公司的IPO让我思考。很明显，美国股市被高估了。然而，它却一直在走高。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在698家价值超过100亿美元的美国企业中，你有25%的企业以10倍的价格销售。
销售额。因此，如果你只有10亿美元的销售额，你的价值是100亿美元。

在接下来的13年里，你的销售额必须每年增长20%才能达到1倍的销售额。

在价值超过100亿美元的公司中，只有约4%的公司的销售额增长达到或超过了1倍。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvacjm/the_rivian_ipo_got_me_thinking_clearly_the_us/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvacjm/the_rivian_ipo_got_me_thinking_clearly_the_us/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:56:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Out of 698 US businesses worth over $10b, you&amp;#39;ve got 25% of those selling at 10x sales. So, if you have only $1b in sales, you&amp;#39;re worth $10b.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#39;d have to grow sales 20% per year for the next 13 years to get to 1x sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only about 4% of companies worth over $10b have grown sales at, or above, 20% over the last 10 years. This figure drops to 2% if you include all US SEC reporting businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That means, roughly, about 20% of your stock market valuations are insanely overpriced. Rivian being one of them. That paired with the Shiller P/E being close to all-time highs, and inflation spiking well above expectation, signals potential disaster on the horizon. Be careful out there peeps. If the FED starts talking rate hikes, expect a sell-off. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/pressreleases/monetary20211103a.htm&quot;&gt;https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/pressreleases/monetary20211103a.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian（收入0美元，净收入-16亿美元）现在的市值高于星巴克（收入290亿美元，净收入42亿美元）和Target（收入1000亿美元，净收入63亿美元）。

$rivn $sbux $tgt

数据来自@ycharts https://t.co/hv4gEyxqDt]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460622351582773250</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460622351582773250</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:43:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[您对伯恩斯坦有什么经验？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我刚刚和我妻子的家人通了电话......我不知道该怎么称呼他们。
他们......财富管理人？伯恩斯坦。听起来他们是一家巨大的公司，对客户的最低要求很高。
他们与我交谈的唯一原因是我岳父的身份。
因为我的岳父是谁。我想知道是否有一个...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvc66l/what_is_your_experience_with_bernstein/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvc66l/what_is_your_experience_with_bernstein/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:18:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just got off the phone with my wife&amp;#39;s family&amp;#39;s...I don&amp;#39;t know what to call them...Wealth management people? Bernstein. Sounds like they&amp;#39;re a huge firm with high minimums for clients, and the only reason they&amp;#39;re talking to me is because of who my father in law is. I&amp;#39;m wondering whether there&amp;#39;s an advantage to going with a group like this and what sort of benefit I&amp;#39;d see over SPY all the way. They told me in their sales pitch they determine asset allocation and they have great research blah blah etc, then have what sound like their own mini funds and at a higher level REITs available only to high net worth clients. No crypto exposure, no nft&amp;#39;s. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This all seems extremely old school and outdated. Am I missing something? They have my wife 30% bonds in her early 30&amp;#39;s, which seems...short sighted. They couldn&amp;#39;t give me a straight answer on how they do compared with a passive index fund&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[谁能给我解释一下，为什么伯克希尔公司的市值仍然比里维安公司大？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460668037032562703</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460668037032562703</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 18:45:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[请告诉我，不要理会所有的噪音，坚持走下去。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想把钱投到特斯拉、加密货币或其他一些我的朋友们都很喜欢的热门股票上。
我的朋友们都在大肆宣传。请劝说我不要这样做，并告诉我坚持到底。
并告诉我继续投资于VTI。谢谢你的服务。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvb5wx/please_tell_me_to_ignore_all_the_noise_and_stay/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvb5wx/please_tell_me_to_ignore_all_the_noise_and_stay/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 18:25:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to throw money into Tesla, crypto, or some of the other hot stocks all my friends are raving about. Please talk me out of this, and tell me to stay the course and just invest in VTI instead. Thank you for your service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[家得宝收益高于预期，因消费者修缮房屋，销售量猛增9.8%。]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/16/home-depot-hd-q3-2021-earnings.html

每股收益。3.92美元，预期3.40美元

收入：368.2亿美元，预期350.1亿美元

家得宝第三季度的盈利和收入超过了华尔街的预期。
收入。

该季度的同店销售攀升了6.1%，...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv7hil/home_depot_earnings_top_estimates_fueled_by_98/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv7hil/home_depot_earnings_top_estimates_fueled_by_98/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 17:59:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/16/home-depot-hd-q3-2021-earnings.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/16/home-depot-hd-q3-2021-earnings.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earnings per share: $3.92 vs. $3.40 expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revenue: $36.82 billion vs. $35.01 billion expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Home Depot topped Wall Street’s estimates for its third-quarter earnings and revenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Same-store sales climbed 6.1% in the quarter, beating StreetAccount estimates of 2.2%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consumers were spending more when they visited, raising the average ticket by 12.9% to $82.38.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Home Depot is one of the non tech stock that keep outperform. This is one of the portfolio must have stock due to the loyalty of the customers. Every time you visit there you will see a never ending long line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天达到了巨大的个人里程碑! 下一步是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我已经正式达到我的个人储蓄目标，即5万现金。我今年29岁，为了达到这个目标
为了达到这个目标，我牺牲了很多，花了近十年时间才达到这个目标。

税前和扣除前的工资是6万。

学生贷款还剩2万，2022年1月开始还款。

401(a)为16,230 - Vanguard Target...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvbw93/big_personal_milestone_reached_today_what_next/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvbw93/big_personal_milestone_reached_today_what_next/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 17:47:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have officially reached my personal savings goal of 50k cash. I&amp;#39;m 29 and have sacrificed a lot to meet this goal, it&amp;#39;s taken me almost a decade to get here. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salary is 60k before taxes and deductions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;20k left on student loans, payments start up again Jan 2022. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;401(a) at 16,230 - Vanguard Target Retire 2055 11.1% Vanguard Target Retire 2060 88.9%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;457(b) at 8,340 - Vanguard Target Retire 2055 11.1% Vanguard Target Retire 2060 88.9%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: I did not select these Target funds or allocations. It was selected automatically through my employers retirement servicer.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taxable Ally brokerage account worth: $642.52. Crypto account worth about: $600 ($400 btc). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personal note: my family is poor/working class so I pay the lion&amp;#39;s share of my family&amp;#39;s bills (mom and brother). Mom is overcoming cancer and will likely be out of work till 2022, had surgery to remove cancer and will be going through radiation sessions soon (hopefully no chemo). Fortunately (or unfortunately) she makes so little money that she&amp;#39;s always qualified for medicaid and all her treatments have been covered. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;#39;t crunched the numbers but I think all the bills (personal, communal, her personal) will likely run between 4-5k till February 2022... fingers crossed she can get back to work sooner. Brother makes about 30-35k but does not routinely contribute to communal bills, mom doesn&amp;#39;t force him and that&amp;#39;s just the way it is, it&amp;#39;s fruitless to argue about it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any advice on what my next move should be?  I feel like I stalk this sub enough to know the basics: open a Roth and split funds between an US index, international index, and bond right? I guess I need that echo chamber to confirm. I&amp;#39;m very much a serial saver. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to make this money work in my favor. Growing up in poverty I&amp;#39;ve gained a serious emergency mindset. I&amp;#39;m obsessed with preparing for the worst because bad news is the only consant. That&amp;#39;s how my family existed; constantly stressed about money, the next bill, and next big financial disaster etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry for the long post, ANY advice is GREATLY appreciated!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国零售销售再创历史新高，而消费者情绪却处于10年来的最低水平。

看他们做什么，而不是看他们说什么。https://t.co/x2Md4zFAj0]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460632395086974981</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460632395086974981</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:54:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[里维安是现代的Pets.con]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rvian在世界的Pets.com中获得了传奇的地位，它有能力获得1300亿以上的市值。
它能够在几乎没有销售的情况下获得1300多亿美元的市值。甚至银行
里维安将能够交付其所有的预购订单（这是从来没有保证过的
他们的成功有很多障碍和风险；他们...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qv3tyt/rivian_is_the_modern_day_petscon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qv3tyt/rivian_is_the_modern_day_petscon/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:30:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rvian has obtained legendary status among the Pets.com of the world with its ability to command a market cap of 130B+ on virtually 0 sales. Even banking Rivian will be able to deliver on all of its pre-orders (which are never guaranteed) there are so many obstacles and risks to their success; they should not command a massive multiple. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently their biggest competitor Tesla is trading at 25x revenue and has traded from 15-30x revenue over the last 1-2 years. Today Rivian is trading at 150–200–even 250x Price to Revenue. While comparing Tesla ( a well known, huge company with multiple production plants, battery tech, great engineers, market dominance,  Elon, a huge following, massive assets, full AI self driving and a proven production / delivery method) is like comparing apples to apes, let do it. Lets use Price to Revenue as the model and compare Rivian revenue to Tesla revenue. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be fair we should take the anticipated cars being made this year (Rivian says they hope 1k)* average cost of each car (67.5k base + extras = ~75k lets say) = 75mm in sales. To make it a better comparison lets make this a yearly number. Also lets make a great case for Rivian with great production efficiently, no problems, continued refinement, and growth from current cars per day(CPD) (current pace is ~3 CPD or ~320 by EOY but they hope to deliver 1k cars by EOY 2021 which is goal of 1k/108 days since 9/14/21 production start = CPD of 9.25) and lets double it next year. That would give us 9.25 x 2 x 365 x 75k = 506mm per year in revenue and make today’s valuation (at 131B) 258x FY 2022 revenue only after assuming a myriad of extremely positive assumptions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For fun lets triple 9.25 and even then at 760mm in revenue that is 172x FY2022 revenue. Said another way, in order for Rivian to have the same Price/Revenue as Tesla’s average of 22 they would have to produce 5.95Billion in revenue or 79.4k cars per year or ~218 CPD aka 72x their current CPD rate or 23.5x their 2021 target CPD rate. So lets reverse engineer that to find a reasonable stock price — FY2022 best case sales 760m*30 (highest Tesla P/R)=22.8B or ~21$ per share which is still ~8x what Amazon paid about a year ago. Anyone else smell this shitty bubble and going to short this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[家庭成员对加密货币有妄想。我怎样才能唤醒他？]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好，我有个家人快到40岁了，他
一心想要把他的每一美元都投到以太坊里。他是那种
他是那种喝多了，太吵了，而且一般来说对钱很糟糕的人。I
我在金融行业实习，从事实际交易，但他似乎...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv6ml5/family_member_is_delusional_about_crypto_how_can/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv6ml5/family_member_is_delusional_about_crypto_how_can/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:57:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello all, I have a family member who is approaching his 40’s and he is hell-bent on throwing every dollar he has into Ethereum. He is one of those people who drinks too much, is too loud, and is generally terrible with money. I intern in the financial industry, in actual trading, but he just seems to ignore me completely. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He has this idea that he missed out on getting rich through bitcoin, so he thinks buying Ethereum at all time highs is equivalent to buying bitcoin at 4K. He’s not understanding that price means nothing and market cap is a more relevant indicator of your timing. Ethereum already has an enormous market cap and the upside is limited. He is also one of those who don’t understand that there is no thing as getting rich quick. I’ve tried telling him about just holding a diversified portfolio and making monthly/yearly contributions but of course it falls on deaf ears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m worried that if/when we see another 50% drop overnight, he’s going to be wiped out. He has kids who will feel it too.  And i get it, a lot of Americans are feeling insecure about retirement and they feel like they must make last ditch efforts to make up for years of poor finances. But this is reality, I know for certain that this guy is going to get burned chasing the next big thing. He got lucky and bought GME, which he then blew the proceeds on luxury rentals and alcohol. Now I think he’a chasing that high again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do I not feel responsible? How do I wake him up? Should I not care?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[应该如何评价像戈尔斯-古根海姆（Polestar SPAC）这样的SPAC？]]></title><description><![CDATA[你们好。

Polestar是一家在欧洲销售电动车的电动车公司，想通过与Gores Guggenheim的SPAC合并上市。
通过与Gores Guggenheim的SPAC合并。

在我看来，Polestar本身的价值绝对超过15亿美元。
如果你把它与其他电动车股票，如Lucid、Rivian
或...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qunnan/how_should_one_value_a_spac_like_gores_guggenheim/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qunnan/how_should_one_value_a_spac_like_gores_guggenheim/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:57:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Polestar, an EV company that sells electric cars in Europe, wants to go public through a SPAC merger with Gores Guggenheim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Polestar  itself is, in my opinion, definitely worth more than 1.5 Billion  dollars in Market Cap if you compare it to other EV stocks, like Lucid,  Rivian or Fisker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Gores  Guggenheim has a market cap of only 1.5 Billion dollars. Surely, I&amp;#39;m  missing something here? I&amp;#39;m quite certain that I&amp;#39;m missing something. If  the merger goes through, what happens to the market cap and stock price  of Gores Guggenheim?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will the MC  just go to a few billion while the stock price stays the same? Will the  stock disappear? I really don&amp;#39;t know how this works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么CRSP跌得这么厉害？CRISPR Therapeutics]]></title><description><![CDATA[通常情况下，像这样的公司，我认为他们会疯狂地亏损。
但他们的PE是16.17。他们的EPS是5.26。他们有一个令人难以置信的光明
从现在开始的3或4年内，他们有一个令人难以置信的光明的未来。为什么他们的股票跌得这么厉害？是雅虎
财经的PE和EPS信息不正确吗？该股的低...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quw1p1/why_is_crsp_falling_so_much_crispr_therapeutics/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quw1p1/why_is_crsp_falling_so_much_crispr_therapeutics/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:57:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Normally, with a company like this, I&amp;#39;d expect them to be losing money like crazy, but their PE is 16.17. Their EPS is 5.26. They have an incredibly bright future like 3 or 4 years from now. Why is the stock tanking so hard? Is Yahoo Finance&amp;#39;s information incorrect on the PE and EPS? The stocks low today was $84.31. It&amp;#39;s starting to look juicy, but man, who knows...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian的市值刚刚超过花旗集团的市值。

是的，那个花旗集团。
成立于1812年
2亿个客户账户
4,600家分支机构
世界上最大的信用卡发行商
204,000名员工
720亿美元的收入
230亿美元的净收入
2.3万亿美元的总资产

$RIVN $C https://t.co/7X3zafMB3I]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460618711707140109</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460618711707140109</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:45:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sportradar公布第三季度财报（11月17日）]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://sportshandle.com/on-tap-111521/


11月17日，星期三

总部设在瑞士的体育博彩数据供应商Sportradar将报告
季度收益，这是自9月完成IPO以来的第一次。
Sportradar在2020年获得了4.78亿美元的收入，净收入为1800万美元。超过...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv6q19/sportradar_reports_thirdquarter_earnings_nov_17th/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv6q19/sportradar_reports_thirdquarter_earnings_nov_17th/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:27:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sportshandle.com/on-tap-111521/&quot;&gt;https://sportshandle.com/on-tap-111521/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Wednesday, November 17&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sportradar, the Switzerland-based sports betting data provider, will report quarterly earnings for the first time since completing its IPO in September. Sportradar earned $478 million in 2020, with $18 million in net income. Over the first half of 2021, Sportradar &lt;a href=&quot;https://frontofficesports.com/sportradar-looks-to-acquire-tech-companies-after-ipo/&quot;&gt;increased revenue 42%&lt;/a&gt; on a year-over-year basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Sportradar went public in September, the company indicated that it plans to pursue acquisitions of tech and artificial intelligence companies as a way of furthering its growth plans. Earlier this month, Sportradar secured an exclusive betting data rights agreement with UEFA’s portfolio of competitions, including the UEFA European Championships in soccer. Also during the quarter, Michael Jordan assumed an advisory role with Sportradar’s board while increasing his &lt;a href=&quot;https://investors.sportradar.com/news-releases/news-release-details/michael-jordan-assumes-advisory-role-sportradar&quot;&gt;investment in the company&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Preview already posted in the subreddit by &lt;a href=&quot;/u/deepdivestocks&quot;&gt;u/deepdivestocks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Sportradar/comments/qv3ba3/srad_earnings_released_on_17th_november/&quot;&gt;$SRAD Earnings Released on 17th November&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;View: $SRAD has been on a small uptick the last few weeks after reaching a low. With gambling stocks down across the board, could this be the exception?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any views on EPS and revenue targets?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么RIVIAN还在涨价？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道每个人都希望它是下一个特斯拉，并且对每一个电动车都有恐惧感，但一个几乎没有任何交付的公司，其市值是第三高的。
但一个几乎没有交付任何产品的公司，却拥有汽车行业第三高的市值（1400亿美元以上），这对我来说太荒谬了。
但一个几乎没有任何交付的公司，却拥有汽车行业第三高的市值（1400亿以上），对我来说是非常荒谬的...... 而且我不关心
亚马逊的传言。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv7y8j/why_on_earth_is_rivian_still_going_up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv7y8j/why_on_earth_is_rivian_still_going_up/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:27:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know everyone is hoping it&amp;#39;s the next tesla and is FOMOing on every EV, but a company that barely made ANY deliveries , having the 3rd highest market cap in the car industry (140B+) , is plain ridiculous for me... And I don&amp;#39;t care about the Amazon rumors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通称特斯拉欠银行1.62亿美元]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quy6j8/jpmorgan_says_tesla_owes_the_bank_162_million/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quy6j8/jpmorgan_says_tesla_owes_the_bank_162_million/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 14:47:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[预测市场崩溃的时间线（罗恩-保罗著）]]></title><description><![CDATA[2014年--市场必须修正，在它发生之前，谁会说这是一次崩溃？
发生之前，谁还会说是崩盘呢？我认为，我们将迎来一次重大的修正。我认为我们非常、非常
脆弱
[http://www.cnbc.com/2014/07/29/ron-paul-stocks-are-in-a-bubble-and-will-crash.html]

2015年--仍有很多不稳定因素存在......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv79af/timeline_of_predicting_a_market_crash_by_ron_paul/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv79af/timeline_of_predicting_a_market_crash_by_ron_paul/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 14:47:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnbc.com/2014/07/29/ron-paul-stocks-are-in-a-bubble-and-will-crash.html&quot;&gt;2014 -  The market has to correct, and who&amp;#39;s going to call it a crash until it  happens? We&amp;#39;re in for a major correction, I think. I think we&amp;#39;re very,  very vulnerable&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnbc.com/2015/06/19/ron-paul-stock-market-day-of-reckoning-is-near.html&quot;&gt;2015 -  There&amp;#39;s a lot of instability still out there, and this hasn&amp;#39;t been  corrected yet. I don&amp;#39;t think it&amp;#39;s going to correct easily, I don&amp;#39;t think  it&amp;#39;s going to be just a correction.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnbc.com/2017/07/02/ron-paul-not-a-shock-if-stocks-fall-25-percent-and-gold-soars-50-percent-by-oct.html&quot;&gt;2017 -  &amp;quot;If our markets are down 25 percent and gold is up 50 percent it wouldn&amp;#39;t be a total shock to me&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/14/ron-paul-market-meltdown-could-spark-depression-like-conditions.html&quot;&gt;2018 -  A 50% correction will spark depression-like conditions that may be ‘worse than 1929’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/the-dollar-is-going-to-self-destruct-talking-bitcoin-with-ron-paul&quot;&gt;2019 - The Dollar is going to self destruct&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_gbZlnyuQ6g&quot;&gt;2020 - The end result is an overinflated stock market that could see a “violent correction”, as well as a monetary system on the brink of collapse. I happen to believe it’s the biggest financial bubble in the history of monetary policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VCj-m08qPd4&quot;&gt;On the next economic crash in 2021&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[HSA账户，你有什么想法？]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以，我想知道人们对HSA账户的看法。我读了一篇文章
说这是一个很好的工具，可以把钱放进去，这样将来当你
老年人时，你可以支付医疗费用。

它还可以降低你的应税收入。

我唯一的问题是，我并不年轻...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qv5mv6/hsa_accounts_what_are_your_thoughts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qv5mv6/hsa_accounts_what_are_your_thoughts/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 14:35:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, I was trying to find out peoples thoughts on HSA accounts.  I read an article that said it is a great vehicle to put money into so that in the future when you are elderly you can pay for medical expenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also can lower your taxable income.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My only issue with this, is that I am not young anymore and have started having health problems.  A high deductible plan would suck out the cash from me.  I am guessing this is a good option for people in their early 20s since they are probably less likely to have health problems.  Not sure if the Boglehead community has thoughts on this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[还有谁在考虑做空Rivian？]]></title><description><![CDATA[不瞒你说，我甚至从未想过做空一家公司，但这是
太疯狂了。前期市场高达157美元，没有理由被估价为1370亿美元。
作为参考，特斯拉，最著名的是被高估，但股价仍然上升
涨，其交易价格仅为RIVN估值的7.3倍。然而，RIVN有0...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv44ti/who_else_is_thinking_of_shorting_rivian/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv44ti/who_else_is_thinking_of_shorting_rivian/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 13:31:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not going to lie, I’ve never even thought of shorting a company, but this is insane. Up to $157 in pre market with no reason to be valued at $137 billion. 
For reference, Tesla, most famous for being overvalued and the stock still goes up is trading at only 7.3x the valuation of RIVN. Yet RIVN has 0 sales, 0 revenue, 0 profit. 
This thing is going to fall hard. Just a matter of how long these buyers can hold the price this high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国通胀预期的激增有增无减，上升到了有史以来的最高水平（5年的盈亏平衡点为3.17%）。https://t.co/faPSer3Q4F]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460406986785411073</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460406986785411073</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 11:44:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[20M失业 - 我的父母给了我2000美元的投资，我做的这些选择好吗...？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我刚刚在Fidelity开了一个账户，准备买这些指数基金/债券。
但我只是想从你们那里得到一些验证，如果这些是我最好的
选择。

 * 国内股票。FSKAX（总市场 - 0.015%）。

 *国际股票。FSPSX (国际 - 0.035%)

 *新兴市场：...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qupyu7/20m_unemployed_i_have_been_given_2000_dollars_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qupyu7/20m_unemployed_i_have_been_given_2000_dollars_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 09:57:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just opened an account with fidelity and about to buy these index funds/bonds, but I just want some verification from you people whether if these are my best options.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;domestic stocks:            FSKAX (total market - 0.015%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;international stocks:     FSPSX (international - 0.035%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;emerging markets:         FPADX (emerging markets - 0.075%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. treasury bonds:      FUAMX (treasury bonds - 0.03%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. TIPS:                    FIPDX (inflation protected bonds - 0.05%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;real estate:                   FSRNX (real estate index fund - 0.07%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;and this will be the % split I am doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;30% domestic equity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% international equity &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;10% emerging market equity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% U.S. Treasury bonds&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% TIPS (inflation protected bonds)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% Real estate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不知道伊隆爸爸的最终目的是什么，但他最近一直有一些超级大坏蛋的感觉。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quyhqs/not_sure_what_papa_elons_endgame_is_but_hes_been/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quyhqs/not_sure_what_papa_elons_endgame_is_but_hes_been/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 08:35:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tilray To the Moon DD里面。]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党人南希-梅斯将在今天的大麻法案会议上提出她的大麻法案，时间是
美国东部时间下午2:00在国会山举行。
https://twitter.com/RepNancyMace/status/1459565180585656325?s=20

德国新的联合政府正在讨论大麻合法化问题。Tilray
已经在德国销售医用大麻，并已...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qukdev/tilray_to_the_moon_dd_inside/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qukdev/tilray_to_the_moon_dd_inside/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 08:10:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican Nancy Mace is presenting her Marijuana bill conference today at 2:00pm EDT at Capitol Hill.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/RepNancyMace/status/1459565180585656325?s=20&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/RepNancyMace/status/1459565180585656325?s=20&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Germany&amp;#39;s new coalition government in talks of legalizing Marijuana. Tilray sells medical marijuana already in Germany and has license. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-10/germany-s-next-coalition-close-to-deal-on-legalizing-cannabis&quot;&gt;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-10/germany-s-next-coalition-close-to-deal-on-legalizing-cannabis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s go my precious little Diamond hands. Tilray currently up over 6%. This is not financial Advice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我25岁了，这是我的罗斯。我在这里能做得更好吗？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qungve/im_25_and_this_is_my_roth_what_can_i_do_better/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qungve/im_25_and_this_is_my_roth_what_can_i_do_better/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 07:50:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在富达的VTSAX相当于什么？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qulqnk/what_is_the_vtsax_equivalent_at_fidelity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qulqnk/what_is_the_vtsax_equivalent_at_fidelity/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 06:49:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利发布其2022年市场展望，并认为会出现下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利认为，在利率上升的背景下，美国股市未来一年将面临更大的挑战。
在利率上升、增长放缓和供应链中断的背景下，美国股市将面临更多挑战。

这家华尔街公司最近将明年的标准普尔500指数目标定为4,400点。
这意味着比目前的水平下降了5%。负面的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quo6jl/morgan_stanley_is_out_with_its_2022_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quo6jl/morgan_stanley_is_out_with_its_2022_market/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 05:22:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morgan Stanley sees a more challenging year ahead for U.S. equities against a backdrop of higher interest rates, slowing growth and supply chain disruptions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Wall Street firm recently set its S&amp;amp;P 500 target for next year at 4,400, implying a 5% decline from current levels. The negative projection followed a blockbuster year for stocks that has seen the &lt;a href=&quot;https://link.cnbc.com/click/25708849.282877/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuY25iYy5jb20vcXVvdGVzLy5TUFg_X19zb3VyY2U9bmV3c2xldHRlciU3Q21hcmtldGluZw/5ba060792ddf9c38dd023063Bd6668e6e&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/a&gt; rallying 25% and raking in more than 60 record highs despite fears of persistent inflation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[从历史上看，在收市时投资比在开市时投资要好得多，大多数收益是在一夜之间发生的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[早在2018年就有一篇有趣的文章说

> 如果你在每个工作日交易的最后一秒钟买入SPY
> 自1993年以来，并在第二天开市时卖出 - 捕获所有的净
> 小时后的收益--你的累计价格收益将是571%。
> 
> 在另一方面...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quxd2t/historically_its_way_better_to_invest_at_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quxd2t/historically_its_way_better_to_invest_at_market/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 04:11:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is an interesting article back from 2018 that says&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you had bought the SPY at the last second of trading on each business day since 1993 and sold at the market open the next day — capturing all of the net after-hour gains — your cumulative price gain would be 571%  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, if you had done the reverse, buying the ETF at the first second of regular trading every morning at 9:30 a.m. and selling at the 4 p.m. close, you would be down 4.4%&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have backtested the same for 2020 and 2021, see the results below. Every day I was buying/selling just 1 share of $SPY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Buy at open, sell at close&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Buy at close, sell at open&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2020&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-$4.88&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$45.42&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2021&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-$38.05&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$53.92&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: all calculations made using BreakingEquity&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是2021年11月15日星期一的市场回顾。请欣赏!]]></title><description><![CDATA[心理市场回顾--2021年11月15日，星期一

股市收盘时涨跌互现，道琼斯指数（DIA）和科技股密集的纳斯达克指数（QQQ）
收盘小幅下跌，因为市场参与者消化了来自中国的乐观经济数据
市场参与者消化了来自中国的乐观经济数据，并等待着稍后的美国零售销售的关键报告。
本周晚些时候美国零售销售的关键报告。罗素指数...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qushen/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_nov_15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qushen/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_nov_15/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:51:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Monday, November 15, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks finished mixed, with the Dow Jones (DIA) and tech-heavy Nasdaq (QQQ) closing modestly lower, as market participants digested upbeat economic data coming from China and await for a key report on retail sales in the US later this week. The Russell 2000 (IWM), which tracks the performance of small-caps, underperformed on the day, closing 0.44% lower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stronger than expected economic data coming out of China helped lift the sentiments of market participants following last week’s inflation report. The world&amp;#39;s second-largest economy saw both retail sales and industrial production unexpectedly rise in October in a year-over-year period, suggesting that China’s economy is holding up better than expected amid new stay-in-place restrictions and ongoing power shortages. However, prices of new homes dropped 0.25% in October versus September, marking the biggest drop in more than six years as the nation’s real estate market remains under pressure from the Evergrande situation. Here are the numbers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retail Sales: +4.9% YoY vs +3.5 expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Industrial Production: +3.5% YoY vs +3% expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow, market participants will receive the Commerce Department’s monthly Retail Sales report, which is expected to show a 1.3% year-over-year rise in retail sales, improving from September’s disappointing 0.7% rise. Moreover, major retailers like Walmart (WMT), Target (TGT), Home Depot (HD), and Lowe’s (LOW) are set to report Q3 earnings, which will offer additional data regarding the state of consumer demand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week, markets were spooked by the pace of inflation, with the recent Consumer Price Index (CPI) showing the fastest pace of increase in roughly 30 years. which showed prices soared 6.2% in a year-on-year period, accelerating from September’s 5.4% YoY rate, and higher than the 5.9% expected. The staying power and magnitude of inflationary pressures has, perhaps, become the central question for market participants, with companies across the board reporting rising input costs and price hikes passed on to the consumers to preserve margins. While Q3 earning results have robustly demonstrated that companies in the SPY were largely able to navigate these cost pressures, the possibility remains that if inflation runs hotter than expected for longer than expected, it could begin to hamper consumer demand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ian Shepherdson, Chief Economist at Pantheon Macroeconomics, wrote in a note to clients, “The surge in core inflation in October marks the start of a run of big gains, thanks to surging used auto prices, rebounding airline fares, and faster increases in housing costs. We think core inflation will peak at almost 7% in March, which will pose a serious challenge to the Fed&amp;#39;s benign medium-term view. Chair [Jerome] Powell will have to convince markets that the combination of rocketing payrolls and soaring inflation does not threaten the transitory story, to which he appears still to be committed. We remain of the view that the Fed will start to hike in September, but a June hike can&amp;#39;t be ruled out. If labor participation shows no sign of life by the March FOMC meeting, we expect the Fed to accelerate the taper and then hike in June. This would play badly across all asset markets.” As always, it is important to acknowledge and understand the risks present in the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Boeing (BA) surged after the company said it was “hopeful” China would resume order of the 737 Max two years after its grounding.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;U.S. crude oil output from the Permian Basin of West Texas and New Mexico is set to jump to a record 4.95 million barrels per day in December, a new government forecast showed on Monday. This would bring production in the key U.S. shale patch well above its pre-pandemic average from March 2020.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of oat-milk maker Oatly (OTLY) fell more than 20% after missing earnings expectations and cutting guidance. The stock is down roughly 50% since IPO back in late-May.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Snap (SNAP) were up after the company reached a deal with Sony Music Entertainment to allow the company to use its artist and sounds on the Snapchat App.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Twitter Inc said on Monday it will expand free access to the social networking site&amp;#39;s data to help software developers create tools and products that could promote safer online conversations or curate content. The move is part of Twitter&amp;#39;s growing effort over the past year to decentralize the company, a vision that aims to give users more control over what content they see in their Twitter feed or have new ways of sharing content on the site, Amir Shevat, Twitter&amp;#39;s head of product for the developer platform, said in an interview.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amazon.com Inc has reached a deal to sell virtual medical services to Hilton Hotels in the United States, one of the first major customers for the company’s burgeoning healthcare business. Amazon Care is an on-demand health offering that lets users message or video-chat clinicians and receive home visits in some cities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UK ministers are expected to order an in-depth investigation of Nvidia Corp&amp;#39;s planned $40 billion acquisition of British chip designer ARM over antitrust and national security concerns. As a huge NVDA bull, hope all goes well!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Finance Tech (SOFI) announced an offering of 50 million shares. The stock is down as a result. Not surprising for management to take advantage of this massive runup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of oat-meal maker Oatly (OTLY) gapped down -20% after missing earnings expectations and cutting guidance moving forward. After a promising start, the stock is now roughly -50% since its IPO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current stock price was written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AutoDesk (ADSK) target raised by Mizuho from $350 to $380 at Buy. Stock currently around $326&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Broadcom (AVGO) target raised by Argus from $560 to $620 at Buy. Stoick currently around $565&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coupang (CPNG) target raised by Mizuho from $32 to $40 at Overweight. Stock currently around $28&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salesforce (CRM) target raised by Mizuho from $320 to $360 at Buy. Stock currently around $305&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crowdstrike (CRWD) target raised by Mizuho from $330 to $360 at Buy. Stock was also downgraded by Morgan Stanley to $250, so there are competing perspectives here&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intuit (INTU) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $615 to $715 at Overweight. Stock currently around $626&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MasterCard (MA) target raised by Mizuho from $50 to $465 at Buy. Stock currently around $360&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Netflix (NFLX) target raised by KeyCorp from $690 to $725 at Overweight. Stock currently around $680&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NVIDIA (NVDA) with three target raises. Stock currently around $300

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Citigroup from $223 to $350 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robert W Baird from $240 to $360 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UBS Group from $230 to $350 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Palo Alto Networks (PANW) with three target raises. Stock currently around $518

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mizuho from $560 to $625 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deutsche Bank from $560 to $605 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Royal Bank of Canada from $560 to $590 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roblox (RBLX) target raised by BTIG Research from $98 to $133 at Buy. Stock currently around $108&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Signature Bank (SBNY) target raised by Raymond James from $360 at $400 at Outperform. Stock currently around $321&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snowflake (SNOW) target raised by Mizuho from  $340 to $450 at Buy. Stock currently around $393&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Finance Tech (SOFI) target raised by Mizuho from $28 to $30 at Buy. Stock currently around $22&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Valero Energy (VLO) target raised by Wells Fargo from $102 to $106 at Overweight. Stock currently around $77&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Don&amp;#39;t judge each day by the harvest you reap but by the seeds that you plant.&amp;quot; -Robert Louis Stevenson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Metaverse: 下一个最大的机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是90年代末的互联网，2000年代的社交媒体，以及数字媒体。
2010年代的数字货币（加密货币）。Facebook的Metaverse可能是其中的一个。
2020年代最大的投资机会之一。如果你正在关注Facebook的
Connect 2021会议，你会意识到Facebook现在有多深...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quvg93/metaverse_next_biggest_opportunity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quvg93/metaverse_next_biggest_opportunity/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the internet in the late ’90s, social media in the 2000s, and digital currency (crypto) in the 2010s. Facebook’s Metaverse might be one of the greatest investment opportunities in the 2020s. If you are following Facebook’s Connect 2021 conference you will realize how much deep Facebook now Meta has invested in the platform. They own Oculus which is the first step towards VR/AR metaverse. The application of Metaverse based platforms is immense and beyond gaming and virtually every aspect of our lives. Here are some of the potential companies to benefit from:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unity Software: Virtually all applications will be developed either on Unity or Unreal Engine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Autodesk: They own 3D Max and Maya which again might be used to develop VR/AR applications. Plus they have various Building Information Modelling tools like Revit and Navisworks which might be useful in creating Metaverse beyond gaming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Matterport: 3D scanning &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trimble: Again they have Sketchup and various 3D scanning tools&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shopify and Amazon: They might be the first ones to create virtual stores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft: They own Minecraft and have developed ‘Hololens’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roblox: The platform already works with Oculus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me know if there are any other key players which I have missed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我令人沮丧的投资故事。今天我把大部分的东西都拿出来了，90天的禁令，我有一段时间不会回来了。Gg市场。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qul0k6/my_depressing_investment_story_today_i_took_most/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qul0k6/my_depressing_investment_story_today_i_took_most/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[火箭实验室（RKLB）将收购行星系统公司。]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation

看起来火箭实验室正在继续尝试纵向创新。这听起来
对投资者来说是个好消息，特别是在他们已经购买了Advanced
解决方案公司之后...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qurofj/rocket_lab_rklb_to_acquire_planetary_systems_corp/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qurofj/rocket_lab_rklb_to_acquire_planetary_systems_corp/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation&quot;&gt;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like Rocket Lab is continuing to try to vertically innovate. This sounds like good news for investors especially after they already bought Advanced Solutions Inc earlier this year. These two acquisitions along with recent talks of selling rocket hardware to other companies look promising.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[管理是一个公司最重要的部分之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看到很多新的投资者都在关注FCF的内在价值、利润或创新。
这些都很重要，但其中一个最重要的因素却被忽略了。
往往被忽略了。

强大的管理将是你的大部分回报。如果首席执行官做出错误的决定
特别是在市场上......。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/queyas/management_is_one_of_the_most_important_parts_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/queyas/management_is_one_of_the_most_important_parts_of/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I see a lot of new investors looking at FCF intrisnic value, profits or innovation. which is all important but one of the most important factors is mostly overlooked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;strong management is going to be most of ur returns. If the CEO makes bad decisions u will become a bagholder. especialy in market downturns Reits or commodity&amp;#39;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best Example is Elon Musk is able to sell almost a million cars withour spending money on ads without Elon Musk tesla would be at 10/20% of their market cap max. If the company didnt go bankrupt. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ivanhoe has a legendairy CEO in mining and the company preforms well and has amazing assets. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes its better to sit on the sideline even if a stock is dirt cheap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;wereldhave has been cheap for years with an 10% dividend and even 20% for a while with a lot of intrisic value but did cut the dividend time and time again took huge losses and still holds bad assets. -80% of their peak and it use to be a large cap stock on the AEX/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intel was unable to preform with the rest of the market but when a new ceo comes he invest billions and claims the company holds a lot of tech which shows how weak management was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IBM used to be a leader but focussed on share buybacks insted of innovating. sold assets and tech cheap and the best parts. use to be one of the biggest tech companys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are countless examples of weak managment destroying share value in a small company 1 or 2 bad decisions can bankrupt the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;when looking at a stock look at management experience look at the board and insider ownership before u even touch the stock&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[挑选个别股票的理由]]></title><description><![CDATA[你挑选个人股票的理由是什么？

除了试图战胜市场，还有其他原因吗？

所有的研究表明，这真的很难做到，而那么多人仍然选择手工挑选股票。
选择手工挑选股票，我真的想知道原因是什么。

这是一个真实的问题，我并不是想...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quh9ag/reasons_to_pick_individual_stocks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quh9ag/reasons_to_pick_individual_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 02:08:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What are your reasons to pick individual stocks? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is there any other reason then to try to beat the market?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With all the research showing it’s really hard to do and so many people still choosing to hand pick stocks I was really wondering what are the reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a real question I am not trying to dismiss any market strategy. I am just curious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[火箭实验室（RKLB）将收购行星系统公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation

看起来火箭实验室正在继续尝试纵向创新。这听起来
对投资者来说是个好消息，特别是在他们已经购买了Advanced
解决方案公司之后...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qurnf4/rocket_lab_rklb_to_acquire_planetary_systems/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qurnf4/rocket_lab_rklb_to_acquire_planetary_systems/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 02:08:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation&quot;&gt;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like Rocket Lab is continuing to try to vertically innovate. This sounds like good news for investors especially after they already bought Advanced Solutions Inc earlier this year. These two acquisitions along with recent talks of selling rocket hardware to other companies look promising.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[多少才算够？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qurk7o/how_much_is_enough/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qurk7o/how_much_is_enough/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 01:14:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>