<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 06:00:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[bogleheads认为将储蓄账户中的钱投资于稳定币并赚取利息的做法如何？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在我的401k和Roth IRA账户中都遵循三个基金组合。我最近发现
我最近遇到了稳定币，我想知道，如果把放在银行里的钱用于投资稳定币是否更好？
躺在我的储蓄账户中的金额（赚取0.03%的利息）投资到稳定币中。
并通过借给他们赚取高达10%的利息？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw28f8/what_do_bogleheads_think_of_investing_money_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw28f8/what_do_bogleheads_think_of_investing_money_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 05:27:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I follow the three fund portfolio in both my 401k and Roth IRA accounts. I came across stablecoins recently and was wondering if it is better to invest the amount lying in my savings account ( earning 0.03% interest ) into stablecoins and earn upto 10% by lending them ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[恒大开始变卖资产还债？]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至记者发稿时，中国恒大下跌1.79%。

中国恒大在香港证券交易所宣布，11月17日。
2021年，该公司的一家全资子公司与
联合资源投资控股有限公司，据此，卖方
同意...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwfr5w/evergrande_starts_to_liquidate_assets_to_pay_debts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwfr5w/evergrande_starts_to_liquidate_assets_to_pay_debts/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 04:50:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As of the press time, ChinaEvergrande falls 1.79%.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;China Evergrande announced on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange that on November 17, 2021, a wholly-owned subsidiary of the company entered into an agreement with United Resources Investment Holdings Co., Ltd., pursuant to which the seller agreed to sell and sell the house and agreed to purchase Hengteng Network Group Co., Ltd. &lt;strong&gt;16.62 million issued shares&lt;/strong&gt; with a par value of &lt;strong&gt;HK$0.02 is HK$1.28 per share&lt;/strong&gt; (approximately &lt;strong&gt;24.26% discount&lt;/strong&gt; to Hengteng’s closing price of &lt;strong&gt;HK$1.69&lt;/strong&gt; per share on November 17, 2021), and the total consideration is &lt;strong&gt;HK$2.13 billion&lt;/strong&gt;. After the transaction is completed, the company will no longer hold any shares of Hanging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does this mean Evergrande already started to liquidate its assets to pay off debts???&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[房屋开工率下滑近1%，未达预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国房屋建筑商在10月份开始建造房屋，经季节性调整后的年增长率为152万。
10月份的年增长率为152万，比前一个月下降了0.7%。
美国人口普查局周三报告称，10月份的房屋开工率经季节性调整为152万套，比前一个月下降了0.7%。与2020年10月相比。
房屋开工率上升了0.4%。新建房屋的许可速度...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qw066s/housing_starts_slip_nearly_1_falling_short_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qw066s/housing_starts_slip_nearly_1_falling_short_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 04:24:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. home builders started construction on homes at a seasonally-adjusted annual rate of 1.52 million in October, representing a 0.7% decrease from the previous month, the U.S. Census Bureau reported Wednesday. Compared with October 2020, housing starts were up 0.4%. The pace of permitting for new housing units increased in October, however. Permitting for new homes occurred at a seasonally-adjusted annual rate of 1.65 million, up 4% from September and 3.4% from a year ago. Economists polled by MarketWatch had expected housing starts to occur at a median pace of 1.63 million and building permits to come in at a median pace of 1.58 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/housing-starts-slip-nearly-1-falling-short-of-expectations-2021-11-17&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/housing-starts-slip-nearly-1-falling-short-of-expectations-2021-11-17&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[辩论非博格莱特人]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们已经听过很多次，在牛市中每个人都是天才。这种
这种观点在当前的加密货币狂热、备忘录股票、Robinhood散户投资者的时代尤其正确。
和Robinhood的散户投资者。以下是我对我的Bogleheads同伴的问题。你如何
你如何对待与那些坚持要与他们讨论/辩论的人...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw98g3/debating_nonbogleheads/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw98g3/debating_nonbogleheads/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 03:24:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we have heard plenty times, everybody is a genius in a bull market. This sentiment holds especially true in the current age of crypto mania, meme stocks, and Robinhood retail investors. Here’s my question for my fellow Bogleheads: How do you approach discussions/debates with people who insist that they are great stock pickers and/or day traders?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Generally speaking, I find it better to not engage at all, especially since everybody has a different “investment” goal and is free to spend their money however they want. However, I do find it difficult to not engage with folks who are clearly full of crap (e.g. someone who claims they are making 10% weekly returns) or folks who are offering stock tips/advice to people you are close to (e.g. a sibling’s friend convincing him to trade options). In other words, what’s a polite way to tell these “geniuses” that they they’re not as smart as they think they are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议院第4722号修正案：五家受补贴的微芯片公司可以在2022年以+530亿美元的价格将15万个工作岗位从海外带回美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[参议院第4722号修正案：五家受补贴的微芯片公司目前获得了
60亿美元（赤字开支），可以将15万个工作岗位从海外带回美国，并分20年支付530亿美元。
带来15万个工作岗位，并在2022年支付530亿美元。作为交换，这些公司发行
价值该金额的股票认股权证及利息。

具体的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwczt5/senate_amendment_4722_five_subsidized_microchip/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwczt5/senate_amendment_4722_five_subsidized_microchip/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 02:46:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senate Amendment 4722: five subsidized microchip companies currently receiving $6 billion (deficit spending) can bring 150,000 jobs back to America from overseas for $53 billion to be paid in 2022. In exchange, these companies issue stock warrants worth that amount plus interest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific companies receiving the $53 billion of taxpayer subsidies are Intel, Texas Instruments, Micron, Analog Devices, and NVIDIA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: The source is CSPAN-2 live from about 3 hours ago. This is from the SENATE not the house.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是今天（星期三，2021年11月17日）的市场回顾。请欣赏!]]></title><description><![CDATA[心理市场回顾 - 2021年11月17日，星期三

股市大多走低，在纪录水平以下徘徊，因为市场参与者
市场参与者进一步消化了昨天的美国零售销售报告和新的企业盈利报告。
市场参与者进一步消化了昨天的美国零售销售报告和主要零售商的新的企业盈利结果，这些数据为消费者支出模式提供了进一步的数据
模式的进一步数据...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwa0xn/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_wed_november_17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwa0xn/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_wed_november_17/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 02:18:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Wednesday, November 17, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks mostly drifted lower to hover below record levels, as market participants further digested yesterday’s US retail sales report and new corporate earning results from major retailers, which provide further data into consumer spending patterns amid supply-chain disruptions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here are some key numbers for today&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY): -0.25%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nasdaq (QQQ): +0.05%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dow Jones (DIA): -0.58%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Russell 2000 (IWM): -1.27%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple (AAPL): +1.75%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Target (TGT): -4.73%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Department of Commerce released their monthly Retail Sales Report, which showed better than expected consumer spending trends as the holiday season, by far the busiest in the year, continues to play out. Here are the numbers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retail Sales: 1.7% increase vs 1.4% expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core Retail Sales: +1.6%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manufacturing Production: +1.2%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The solid report suggests that high inflation is not dampening consumer spending. Rising household wealth, thanks to a strong stock market, house prices, and rising wages appear to be cushioning consumers against the highest annual pace of inflation in roughly thirty years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Steven Wieting, Citigroup’s Global Wealth Chief Investment Strategist said, “The markets generally are looking at it [the pace of inflation], benignly - they are not discounting some longer-term inflation of more than 2.5%. You can see this in the pricing out on the yield curve of Treasuries. You can see this in the composition of the market with growth stocks not really being beaten down by any concerns about some lurch higher, tightening of monetary policy. We think that story is largely correct – it’s benign for markets. It doesn’t mean we get to repeat the returns from the past year, however.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, Target (TGT) and Lowe’s (LOW), two major retailers in the US, both reported better than expected earnings. This comes on the heels of both Walmart (WMT) and Home Depot (HD) both reporting strong earnings results earlier in the week. Here are the numbers (second number were analyst expectation):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Target (TGT)&lt;/strong&gt;: “With a strong inventory position heading into the peak of the holiday season, our team and our business are ready to serve our guests and poised to deliver continued, strong growth, through the holiday season and beyond,&amp;quot; said Target Chairman and CEO Brian Cornell in a statement. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue: $25.7 billion vs. $24.20 billion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comparable Store Sales: +12.7% vs. +8.3%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gross Margin: 28% vs. 29.80%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Operating Margin: 7.8% vs. 7.68%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diluted EPS: $3.03 vs. $2.84&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lowe’s (LOW):&lt;/strong&gt; “Our momentum continued this quarter, with U.S. sales comps up nearly 34% on a two-year basis, as our Total Home strategy is resonating with the Pro and DIY customer alike. In the quarter, we drove over 16% growth in Pro and 25% on Lowes.com. We also delivered operating margin expansion by driving productivity through disciplined operational execution and cost management”, said Lowe Chairman, President, and CEO Marvin Ellisoln. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue: $22.92 billion vs. $22.06 billion &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earnings per share: $2.73 vs. $2.36&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$1.90 billion in profits vs $692 million Q3 2020&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Same Store Sales: +2.2% vs -1.5%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The party seems over… after a blockbuster IPO, shares of EV startup Rivian (RIVN), which had a market cap of $150 billion on essentially 0 revenue, fell 15% today. In my humble opinion, I’d get out if I had profits (not playing this at all). Shares of Lucid Motors (LCID) were also down roughly 5% in sympathy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CME Group (CME) the world&amp;#39;s largest financial derivatives exchange in the world, trading everything from agricultural products, currencies, energy, interest rates, metals, stock indexes to digital currency futures, announced it was planning to move core trading systems Google Clouds, a massive move in financial markets. Until very recently, it was assumed that cloud computing was ill suited for high frequency trading, forcing these companies to build and develop complicated systems geared for time sensitive markets. If this works, it could reduce the cost of operations by a lot. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fisker (FSR), another EV startup in the market, announced an electric SUV with higher driving range than Tesla’s (TSLA) Model Y. Fisker announced the OCean Ultra SUV, which is planned to begin production next November, has a range of 340 miles and costs $50,000 compared to 300 miles and a cost of $60,000 with the Model Y&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple said Wednesday that it has created a self-service repair program that would allow customers to repair their own devices using genuine Apple parts and tools. The iPhone and Mac maker said Self Service Repair would begin in early 2022 with a focus on the most common serviced modules, including phone display, battery and camera, with additional repair options to be added later in the year. The right to repair has been a big controversy surrounding technology sold by companies. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;According to recent filings, Elon Musk is roughly halfway done with his pledge to sell 10% of his stake in Tesla (TSLA). You can see it here &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nasdaq.com/market-activity/stocks/tsla/insider-activity&quot;&gt;https://www.nasdaq.com/market-activity/stocks/tsla/insider-activity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Waymo, which is a subsidiary of Google’s parent company Alphabet, said on Wednesday it is expanding its partnership with United Parcel Service (UPS) to move freight using autonomous trucks between two of the parcel delivery company&amp;#39;s Texas facilities during the holiday season. This comes amid a shortage of delivery drivers in the US. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current price target are written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance Auto Parts (AAP) with two target raises. Stock currently around $232

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Raymond James from $265 to $275 at Strong-Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jefferies Financial from $240 to $268 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AutoDesk (ADSK) with two target raise. Stock currently around $330

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stifel Nicolaus from $340 to $365 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robert W Baird from $370 to $380 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DR Horton (DHI) target raised by Raymond James from $110 to $120 at Strong-Buy. Stock currently around $101&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enphase Energy (ENPH) with a host of target raises. Average price target $290 at Buy. Stock currently around $255&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Home Depot (HD) with a host of target raises after beating earnings. Average price target $440 at Buy. Stock currently around $394&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intuit (INTU) target raised by Wells Fargo from $625 to $710 at Overweight. Stock currently around $635&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IQVIA (IQV) with four price target raises. Stock currently around $265

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Citigroup from $300 to $320 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;KeyCorp from }$270 to $290 at Overweight&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UBS Group from $298 to $310 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jefferies Financial from $300 to $309 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lululemon (LULU) target raised by B. Riley from $466 to $548 at Buy. Stock currently around $465&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NetEase (NTES) target raised by Bank of America from $128 to $145 at Buy. Stock currently around $112&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Palo Alto Networks (PANW) target raised by Jefferies Financial from $550 to $615 at Buy. Stock currently around $514&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plug Power (PLUG) target raised by Citigroup from $35 to $56 at Buy. Stock currently around $42&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ferrari (RACE) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $265 to $350 at Overweight. Stock currently around $266&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sea Limited (SE) target raised by UBS Group from $350 to $380 at Buy. Stock currently around $315&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Square (SQ) target raised by Tigress Financial from $295 to $310 at Buy. Stock currently around $231&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Live as if you were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever.” - Mahatma Gandhi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[只是感谢你]]></title><description><![CDATA[早在2020年1月，我开始潜伏在这个地方，并听取了几个
个人理财播客，因为我开始对投资感兴趣。我是这样一个
初学者，我不得不观看一个关于如何使用Vanguard的yt视频。
网站。我担心我等了太长时间才进行投资，但我...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qwegy8/just_a_thank_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qwegy8/just_a_thank_you/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 02:18:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back in January 2020, I started lurking this place and listening to several personal finance podcasts because I became interested in investing. I was such a beginner, I had to watch a step-by-step yt video on how to use the Vanguard website. I was worried that I had waited too long to invest, but I persisted and set up my account so I would dollar cost average and start investing in ETFs. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the pandemic I got married and moved to a new city so I really kinda forgot about my investments until my husband said he wanted to start investing too, but was wary about doing so because he didn&amp;#39;t know what the right timing was. Because of this place, I was able to explain to him why it&amp;#39;s time IN the market not timing the market, and help him understand investment language, set up his account, and choose his portfolio. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically, thank you for helping me help another investor. Without this place, I would still be thinking investing was only for wallstreet bros and rich people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[富达的Vanguard ETFs]]></title><description><![CDATA[我已经有一个富达账户，刚刚开始建立一个4个基金的投资组合。
投资组合。我可以购买和管理Vanguard ETFs吗？ETF有什么好的？
到底有什么好处？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw6oq4/vanguard_etfs_on_fidelity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw6oq4/vanguard_etfs_on_fidelity/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 02:18:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I already have a Fidelity account and just getting into setting up a 4 fund portfolio. Can I buy and manage Vanguard ETFs? What is so good about ETFs anyway?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[您的债券配置中，I型债券（或EE型债券）占多少百分比？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我刚刚从r/Bogleheads上的一个最近的帖子中发现了I系列债券的情况
[/r/Bogleheads]。谢谢! 🙏

到现在为止，债券配置是Vanguard总债券基金的70%，以及30%的
债券基金，以及30%的先锋国际债券基金。但是，昨天我买了我的第一个I
债券，从国库直接购买。

我...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw1k6t/what_of_your_bonds_allocation_are_i_bonds_or_ee/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qw1k6t/what_of_your_bonds_allocation_are_i_bonds_or_ee/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 02:18:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just found out about series I Bonds from a recent post here on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/Bogleheads&quot;&gt;r/Bogleheads&lt;/a&gt;. Thanks! 🙏  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Up until now, bond allocation was 70% of the Vanguard total bond fund and 30% of the Vanguard total international bond fund. But, yesterday I bought my first I bonds from treasury direct. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m wondering, what percentage of your bond allocation is in I Bonds (or EE bonds)?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[人们说 "估值过高 "的股票，多年来一直在上涨？]]></title><description><![CDATA[仅仅在今年，我就可以数出90%的分析师说要等到盈利之后再买好市多，因为它们总是在下跌。
买入好市多，因为他们总是下跌，当然，这是第一次
他们在财报后真的上涨了，而且再也没有回落。我从来没有进过
仓，并为自己感到自责。

NVDA也一样。但我有一个...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwb82k/stocks_that_people_said_were_too_overvalued_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwb82k/stocks_that_people_said_were_too_overvalued_that/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 01:44:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Off this year alone, I could count 90% of analysts saying to wait till AFTER earnings to buy Costco bc they always fell, and of course for the first time they actually went up after earnings and never went back down. Never got in a position in it and kicking myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Same with NVDA. But I have a huge stake on it but again people said it would probably tank after earnings, was a meme stock is massively overvalued and is up 3% AH after beating on everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What others historically were like this? Apple? Amazon?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[https://t.co/Tgrg5MCHDL]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461076309728280580</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461076309728280580</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 23:40:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行的资产经理每天都进行交易，但表现不如指数。]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个朋友在一年多的时间里把大约100万美元留给了富国银行的一个资产经理。
富国银行。该账户的活动显示，几乎每天都有各种公司和ETF的股票买入和卖出
公司和ETF的股票，几乎每天都有（一天有几笔交易）。我忘了
确切的业绩数字，但账户增长低于20%......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw8ghp/asset_manager_at_wells_fargo_trades_daily_but/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw8ghp/asset_manager_at_wells_fargo_trades_daily_but/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 22:35:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A friend left about $1M over a bit more than a year with an asset manager at Wells Fargo. The activity on the account shows shares bought and sold in various companies and ETFs, almost daily (and several transactions in a day). I forgot the exact performance numbers, but account growth was under 20% compared to 23% in QQQ during the same period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The asset manager claims that the account has much less risk so it&amp;#39;s all good etc. Also, he said there is no fee on the trades - they&amp;#39;re all fee-free. He claims the performance is already in the ballpark and will only get better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder of course about a number of things about all this, but mainly it&amp;#39;s the frequent trades. What advantage does the asset manager get from trading frequently assuming they are fee-free? Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我只是在泡沫中多加一点空气，它不会爆裂...]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw3wyn/ill_just_add_a_little_more_air_to_the_bubble_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw3wyn/ill_just_add_a_little_more_air_to_the_bubble_it/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 22:18:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[游戏和数据中心销售强劲，Nvidia轻松超越盈利预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[收入：71亿美元，而预期为68.1亿美元。

每股收益。1.17美元，而预期为1.11美元。

游戏收入：32.2亿美元，预期31.8亿美元。

数据中心收入：29.4亿美元，而预期为26.9亿美元。

该公司的股票在报告发布后上涨了3%以上。

"该...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qw9gzs/nvidia_easily_beats_earnings_expectations_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qw9gzs/nvidia_easily_beats_earnings_expectations_on/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 22:18:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revenue&lt;/strong&gt;: $7.1 billion versus $6.81 billion expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Earnings per share&lt;/strong&gt;: $1.17 versus $1.11 expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gaming revenue&lt;/strong&gt;: $3.22 billion versus $3.18 billion expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Center revenue&lt;/strong&gt;: $2.94 billion versus $2.69 billion expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company&amp;#39;s stock was up more than 3% following the report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;The third quarter was outstanding, with record revenue,” Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang said in a statement. “Demand for NVIDIA AI is surging, driven by hyperscale and cloud scale-out, and broadening adoption by more than 25,000 companies. NVIDIA RTX has reinvented computer graphics with ray tracing and AI, and is the ideal upgrade for the large, growing market of gamers and creators, as well as designers and professionals building home workstations.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company also issued a bullish forecast for revenue in the current quarter ending in January.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nvidia said it expects to report around $7.4 billion in the current quarter, ending in January, higher than analyst expectations of $6.86 billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-q-3-earnings-2022-203256956.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nvidia-q-3-earnings-2022-203256956.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/nvidia-nvda-earnings-q3-2022.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/nvidia-nvda-earnings-q3-2022.html&lt;/a&gt; (I took the guidance from here)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[下一个 "云计算 "是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[5-10年前投资于云计算会让你成为多个包子。

我的意思不是说下一步什么会取代云计算，而是在你看来
观点，下一个像这样的利基领域将在未来5-10年内爆发出来
5-10年内爆发？

电动汽车显然是热门话题，对...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw71tf/what_is_the_next_cloud_computing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw71tf/what_is_the_next_cloud_computing/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 21:29:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investing in cloud computing 5-10 years ago would&amp;#39;ve made you multiple baggers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t literally mean what will replace cloud computing next, but in your opinion, what is the next niche area like this that will explode over the next 5-10 years?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Electric vehicles are obviously the hot topic right now but I am just not in on that bandwagon, so I&amp;#39;m curious to hear what y&amp;#39;all think could be next?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not even looking to hear about specific stocks just the industry but feel free to share those as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天卖掉了AMC--这很伤人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这其实更像是一种咆哮/感叹，所以如果你不想听，请随意。
继续滚动。

总之，我在2020年向AMC投入500美元，希望在1-2年内获得6-7倍的回报。
幸运的是，这成为了纪念性的股票之一，并飙升至70美元。
我很高兴能成为运动的一部分，我...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qw5q85/sold_amc_today_this_hurts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qw5q85/sold_amc_today_this_hurts/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 21:13:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is really more of a rant/lament, so if you don&amp;#39;t want to hear it, feel free to keep scrolling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyhow, I put $500 into AMC back in 2020 hoping for a 6-7x return in 1 - 2 yrs. As luck would have it, this became one of the meme stocks and it shot up to $70. Excited to be part of the movement, I hung on, joined the AMC stock forum and stayed in as it dipped back down and down. But it&amp;#39;s just gotten to a point where it doesn&amp;#39;t make responsible sense for me to keep it anymore in hopes of another price surge up to $60 and beyond, when the last few months&amp;#39; price surges only go up ~$40 and I&amp;#39;m sitting on ~14x and have real life bills to pay, including a major medical bill. So, I bit today&amp;#39;s price surge past $40 and sold, I know it was the responsible thing to do - but damn this hurts. Really wanted to be a part of the next a-p-e nation win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: so i posted here bc i figured the other forums would hate on me for selling.  I know this was the responsible thing to do, but it would&amp;#39;ve been nice to hang in there with the rest of a-p-e nation - but don&amp;#39;t have the extra $$ to be doing that right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit 2: want to add, despite my decision to sell, i think this whole memestock phenomenon is so cool and when i&amp;#39;m old with grandkids, it&amp;#39;ll be cool to look back and say that I was a part of it even for a little bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Covid投资者的涌入将如何影响下一次大的市场衰退？]]></title><description><![CDATA[自从Covid开始以来，散户投资者的数量已经大大增加，这已经不是什么秘密了。
当每个人都想坐上印钞机的火车时，Covid开始了。现在的问题是
现在的问题是，所有这些投资者（他们只在有史以来最伟大的牛市中出现过）将如何？
这些投资者（他们只在历史上最伟大的牛市之一出现过）会如何反应？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw3asn/how_will_the_influx_of_covid_investors_affect_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw3asn/how_will_the_influx_of_covid_investors_affect_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 20:53:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s no secret that the number of retail investors has increased immensely since the start of Covid, when everyone wanted on the money printing train. The question now becomes, how will all of these investors (who have only ever been around during one of the greatest bull markets in history) react to the next major downturn?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It could be tomorrow, it could be in 5 years, but I believe there&amp;#39;s going to be substantially more panic than usual when it arrives. Could be an excellent opportunity for more seasoned, rational investors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[希望他们能在市场关闭前给我答复。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw5eog/hopefully_they_get_back_to_me_before_the_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw5eog/hopefully_they_get_back_to_me_before_the_market/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 20:40:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特在Rivian的股份，没有销售任何汽车，现在价值175亿美元，而它自己的市值为790亿美元，尽管它到2021年第三季度销售了140万辆汽车。]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，在收盘时，福特的市值只有790亿美元，尽管它在2021年前三季度卖出140万辆
2021年前三个季度的汽车。它还拥有超过150,000份2022年F150 Lightening的预订单
其2022年的F150 Lightening的预订单，并且在10月底已经售出21,700辆Mach-E汽车。
10月份。

福特拥有1.02亿股股票（它应该卖掉它们...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvybd6/fords_shares_in_rivian_thats_sells_no_cars_now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvybd6/fords_shares_in_rivian_thats_sells_no_cars_now/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 20:25:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So at close Ford&amp;#39;s mkt cap was only $79 billion, despite it selling 1.4 million cars in the first three quarters of 2021.  It also has over 150,000 pre-orders for its F150 Lightening for 2022 and had sold 21,700 Mach-E&amp;#39;s at the end of October.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ford owns 102 million shares (it should sell them sharpish at this price) worth an incredible $17.5 billion in Rivian that has sold a couple of hundred cars to employees to date. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s not absurd at all. I mean Rivian had a massive 13,000 orders at end of 3Q (giggle).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I seriously wonder how many Rivian investors know that Ford has a massive stake.  I hope it sells it very soon as a Ford shareholder.  Those funds can quickly be put to use massively outselling Rivian in BEV&amp;#39;s by even larger multiples in 2022, 2023, 2024....(basically forever).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The US stock market has genuinely lost its marbles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nvidia今天公布盈利情况。以下是期待的内容]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nvidia将在周三收盘后公布第三季度财报。
周三。随着股价在历史高点附近徘徊，它将需要一个巨大的报告来感动投资者。
巨大的报告才能打动投资者的心。Nvidia股价在周二的交易中上涨0.6%至
周二交易中的302.03美元。本月早些时候股价飙升，因为...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvw3t4/nvidia_reports_earnings_today_heres_what_to_expect/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvw3t4/nvidia_reports_earnings_today_heres_what_to_expect/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 20:25:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nvidia is set to report third-quarter earnings results after the market closes on Wednesday. With shares hovering around record highs, it will take a blockbuster report to move the needle for investors. Nvidia stock rose 0.6% to $302.03 in Tuesday trading. Shares surged earlier this month as investors bought in on hype surrounding Nvidia’s financial prospects amid billions in investment, most notably from Facebook ‘s newly rebranded parent Meta Platforms (FB), to build a theorized next phase of the internet called the metaverse. Not even renewed scrutiny in the U.K. related to its proposed acquisition of chip designer Arm could stop the graphics card stock’s 131% year-to-date run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the third quarter, analysts polled by FactSet forecast adjusted earnings of $1.11 a share and sales of $6.82 billion. The earnings report or outlook may need to be a blowout for the stock to continue rising. Though 34 of the 43 analysts listed by FactSet have Buy or equivalent ratings, the stock’s mean price target is $280.70. Bullish analysts will either need to raise their targets or downgrade the stock if shares hold above their targets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/articles/nvidia-stock-earnings-preview-51637101805?mod=mw_latestnews&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/articles/nvidia-stock-earnings-preview-51637101805?mod=mw_latestnews&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡努和传闻中的沃尔玛交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[Canoo（$GOEV）今天上午上涨了23%，因为有传言说它已经找到了沃尔玛作为
的合作伙伴。这一传言的起因是卡努公司将其总部迁至
本顿维尔，也就是沃尔玛总部所在地。卡奴还在其收益电话会议上预告
财报电话会议上，它将为一个不知名的公司建造一些原型。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvy3j9/canoo_and_rumored_walmart_deal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvy3j9/canoo_and_rumored_walmart_deal/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 19:44:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canoo ($GOEV) is up 23% this morning due to rumors that it has landed Walmart as a partner. This rumor started because Canoo moved its headquarter to Bentonville, the home of Walmart headquarters. Canoo also teased during its earnings call that it will be building some prototypes for an unnamed partner, which of course the internet jumped on the idea that it must be Walmart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m a little skeptical of this, since Walmart already has other car partners like Ford and Gatik. Does it make sense to add Canoo?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My thesis is that Canoo is a decent speculative stock even if it doesn&amp;#39;t have this Walmart deal. There&amp;#39;s lots of other tailwinds such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The infrastructure bill.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Canoo fills a niche that&amp;#39;s not directly competitive against Rivian or Tesla (and definitely not Lucid). For example Canoo would be great for local governments and schools which will be forced to go green and would like vehicles with low maintenance costs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The market is hungry for EV stock right now. And at sub $20 this is something people can feel good throwing a few bucks in and hold for years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Possible cons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worried that Canoo doesn&amp;#39;t manufacture it&amp;#39;s own vehicles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Canoo already had one hyped up story with the acquisition talks with Apple. If this Walmart thing go south investors will &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; hate Canoo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Possible discussion topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are there &lt;em&gt;other&lt;/em&gt; possible reasons to move to Bentonville? Perhaps that city offer huge incentives not seen elsewhere, or maybe it&amp;#39;s actually a great hub of manufacturing. Anyone in that area know?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;How does Canoo stack up against other EV &amp;quot;hype&amp;quot; stocks right now?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclosure: I bought some Canoo this morning, and I kinda like their aesthetic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Metaverse ?]]></title><description><![CDATA[整个行业是否严重高估了人们在视频游戏中花费X
时间的欲望？

我实际上看了facebook关于元的整个演示。我还参加了
其他公司目前所称的 "元"，如Roblox。
第二人生等等。



我是不是错过了...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvta30/metaverse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvta30/metaverse/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 18:46:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is the industry at large grossly overestimating people&amp;#39;s appetite to spend X amount of time in a video game?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I actually watched facebook&amp;#39;s entire presentation on meta. I&amp;#39;ve also been in what other companies are referring to as &amp;quot;metaverses&amp;quot; currently such as Roblox, second life etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Am I missing something here? I used to be an avid gamer myself. But my current age I dont have the mental or physical will power to play a game when I get home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m just tired as hell. Its been a drag for my significant other, since we were both avid gamers together.  But its just the reality.. I&amp;#39;m way too tired to play anything on the weekends. Luckily, I just spectate whatever she&amp;#39;s playing and I guess I get my gaming fix there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question remains though. I know my anecdotal experience isnt going to be very useful but I&amp;#39;m just wondering how everybody else feels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I saw the FB meta video, all +1 hour of it, and I just thought.. wow. Who would want to be logged into a video game with that shit on your face for multiple hours??&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it just me? Am I just an old fart?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also vaguely reminds me of the 3d movies phase as well. Everybody thought we&amp;#39;d be lining up to see these 3d movies forever but people quickly got tired of that too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊将停止接受在英国发行的Visa信用卡，理由是费用高昂]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 关键点
> 
> 亚马逊已经告诉一些客户，从1月19日起，该公司将不再接受
> 不再接受在英国发行的Visa信用卡。
> 
> 该电子商务巨头以支付处理商收取的高额费用为由。
> 
> 维萨公司表示，它 "对亚马逊威胁要在英国使用维萨信用卡感到非常失望"。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw4ca8/amazon_to_stop_accepting_visa_credit_cards_issued/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw4ca8/amazon_to_stop_accepting_visa_credit_cards_issued/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 18:33:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KEY POINTS&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon has told some customers that, from Jan. 19 onward, the company will no longer accept Visa credit cards issued in Britain.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The e-commerce giant cited high fees charged by the payment processor.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visa said it was “very disappointed that Amazon is threatening to restrict consumer choice in the future.”&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LONDON — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AMZN&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; plans to stop accepting payments made via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/V&quot;&gt;Visa&lt;/a&gt; credit cards issued in the U.K. starting next year.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The e-commerce giant has told some customers that, from Jan. 19 onward, the company will no longer accept Visa credit cards issued in Britain ” due to the high fees Visa charges for processing credit card transactions.”&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Visa shares fell 2.5% in U.S. premarket trading.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visa earlier this year hiked the interchange fees it charges merchants for processing digital transactions between the U.K. and the European Union.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After Brexit, an EU cap on interchange fees no longer applies in the U.K., allowing card networks to raise their charges.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/MA&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mastercard&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;has also increased its U.K.-EU interchange fees.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon customers were told they will still be able to use debit cards — including those issued by Visa — and non-Visa credit cards like Mastercard and&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AXP&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;American Express&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;. Users are being encouraged to update their default payment method ahead of the changes.&lt;/strong&gt; The news was first reported by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-17/amazon-will-stop-accepting-visa-credit-cards-issued-in-the-u-k?srnd=technology-vp&quot;&gt;Bloomberg&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Visa said it was “very disappointed that Amazon is threatening to restrict consumer choice in the future.”  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“U.K. shoppers can use their Visa debit and credit cards at Amazon U.K. today and throughout the holiday season,” a Visa spokesperson told CNBC.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We have a long-standing relationship with Amazon, and we continue to work toward a resolution, so our cardholders can use their preferred Visa credit cards at Amazon U.K. without Amazon-imposed restrictions come January 2022.”  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon blasted Visa for its high card charges. “The cost of accepting card payments continues to be an obstacle for businesses striving to provide the best prices for customers,” a spokesperson for the company told CNBC.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“These costs should be going down over time with technological advancements, but instead they continue to stay high or even rise.”&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The move could be viewed as a way for Amazon to get some bargaining power over Visa to lower its fees. The payments firm also charges businesses scheme fees to become part of its network.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While smaller retailers aren’t in a position to negotiate, Amazon — given its size — may have better luck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/amazon-to-stop-accepting-visa-credit-cards-issued-in-the-uk.html&quot;&gt;CNBC&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/finance/quote/V:NYSE&quot;&gt;Visa is down about 5%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[仍然是一颗宝石]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw1iz3/still_a_gem/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw1iz3/still_a_gem/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 17:54:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[目前处于历史高位。

-股票市场
-国内生产总值
-家庭净资产
-住房价格
-零售业销售
-可用的工作机会

然而，消费者的情绪正在崩溃

奇怪的时代

https://t.co/CCSzf8DXG3]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460752388617289731</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460752388617289731</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 17:42:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国恒大创始人出售豪宅和私人飞机以抵偿债务]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvx70d/china_evergrande_founder_sells_mansions_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvx70d/china_evergrande_founder_sells_mansions_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 17:42:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你是否买入跌停板？

$BTC $ETH $SOL

👇]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460602142985760774</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460602142985760774</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 16:35:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我要告诉我的老板，"去死吧，我拥有Lucid！"]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvykva/going_to_tell_my_boss_to_go_fuck_yourself_i_own/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvykva/going_to_tell_my_boss_to_go_fuck_yourself_i_own/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 16:33:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我们所处的狂野时代]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvzney/wild_times_we_live_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvzney/wild_times_we_live_in/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 16:33:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[第一次用电话。完全不知道我在做什么，我做得对吗？另外，我怎样才能从中赚钱？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvo1pr/first_time_with_calls_absolutely_zero_idea_what/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvo1pr/first_time_with_calls_absolutely_zero_idea_what/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 15:26:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lucid Motors 40k股份]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvprvj/lucid_motors_40k_shares/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvprvj/lucid_motors_40k_shares/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 15:26:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有什么比泡沫更糟糕？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvy6j5/whats_worse_than_a_bubble/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvy6j5/whats_worse_than_a_bubble/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:59:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊将停止接受在英国发行的Visa信用卡]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊（AMZN）将从明年起停止接受英国发行的Visa（V）信用卡的付款。
据透露，从明年开始，亚马逊将停止接受英国发行的Visa（V）信用卡付款。

这家在线零售巨头将这一决定归咎于Visa收取的高额交易费用。
处理交易。

彭博社称，这些变化最早将于2022年1月19日生效。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvyppt/amazon_to_stop_accepting_visa_credit_cards_issued/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvyppt/amazon_to_stop_accepting_visa_credit_cards_issued/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:20:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon (AMZN) is to cease accepting payments made by UK-issued Visa (V) credit cards from next year, it has been revealed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The online retail giant blamed the decision on high fees charged by Visa to process transactions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The changes will come into effect as early as 19 January 2022, Bloomberg first reported, citing information that Amazon had shared with its customers this week, after they had purchased items.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$V down approx 3.25% in the pre-market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[维度公司为美国小型股价值ETF和国际小型股价值ETF提交文件]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是否有可能解决流行的AVUV对小盘股价值倾斜的一些限制（我可能不知道）？
这是否有可能解决流行的AVUV小盘股价值倾斜的一些限制（我可能不知道）？我意识到小盘股的倾斜
并不是博格瑞德最擅长的动作，但是我看到它最近在这个子项目中比较流行，我自己也对它很感兴趣。
在这个子里的受欢迎程度，而且我自己也对它相当感兴趣。我很想...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvxzxa/dimensional_files_for_us_small_cap_value_etf_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvxzxa/dimensional_files_for_us_small_cap_value_etf_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:20:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Could this have the potential to solve some limitation (that I may not know about) in the popular AVUV for small cap value tilts? I realize an SCV tilt isn&amp;#39;t the most Boglehead move, however I have seen its relatively recent popularity in this sub and am quite interested in it myself. Would love to hear what you guys think!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://us.dimensional.com/about-us/media-center/dimensional-lists-four-fixed-income-etfs-and-announces-further-expansion-of-etf-offering&quot;&gt;https://us.dimensional.com/about-us/media-center/dimensional-lists-four-fixed-income-etfs-and-announces-further-expansion-of-etf-offering&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆仍有超过50%的特斯拉股份可供出售 从推特上看]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你考虑到他在9月份向美国证券交易委员会提交的近10亿美元的股票，可以说接近60%。
在他发推文之前，美国证券交易委员会（SEC）9月份的文件已经规定他要卖掉近10亿美元的股票。

https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.marketwatch.com/amp/story/another-day-another-tesla-stock-sale-for-elon-musk-8-8-billion-over-past-7-days...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvxlci/elon_still_has_more_than_50_of_shares_to_sell_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvxlci/elon_still_has_more_than_50_of_shares_to_sell_in/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:20:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arguably closer to 60% if you allow for the near $1 billion stock that he was already due to sell from September SEC filings, that preceded his tweet:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.marketwatch.com/amp/story/another-day-another-tesla-stock-sale-for-elon-musk-8-8-billion-over-past-7-days-11637116058&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.marketwatch.com/amp/story/another-day-another-tesla-stock-sale-for-elon-musk-8-8-billion-over-past-7-days-11637116058&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course if Sanders would just respond to his damned tweets, he could be a great scapegoat for offloading far more shares on the highs.  And who would blame Musk if he did.  He did afterall think Tesla &amp;#39;insanely&amp;#39; over valued at $50 billion:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.vanityfair.com/news/2017/05/even-elon-musk-thinks-teslas-stock-is-insanely-overvalued/amp&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.vanityfair.com/news/2017/05/even-elon-musk-thinks-teslas-stock-is-insanely-overvalued/amp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[塔吉特公司盈利超出预期，但股价下跌，因为零售商专注于保持客户价格低廉]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/target-tgt-q3-2021earnings.html

每股收益。调整后为3.03美元，预期为2.83美元

收入：256.5亿美元 vs. 247.8亿美元

塔吉特公司第三财季的收益名列前茅，因为万圣节和返校等季节性因素促进了销售。
万圣节和返校日等季节性因素促进了销售。

该零售商...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvydgi/target_tops_earnings_estimates_but_shares_fall_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvydgi/target_tops_earnings_estimates_but_shares_fall_as/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:20:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/target-tgt-q3-2021earnings.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/target-tgt-q3-2021earnings.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earnings per share: $3.03 adjusted vs. $2.83, expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revenue: $25.65 billion vs. $24.78 billion&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Target topped earnings for the fiscal third quarter, as seasonal moments like Halloween and back-to-school boosted sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The retailer raised its forecast, saying that comparable sales could rise at between a high-single digit and low double-digit pace in the holiday period. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CEO Brian Cornell said the company is focused on value as prices of food, gas and more rise and consumers face sticker shock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is another non tech stock that always outperform. The e-commerce operations have been improved and getting competitive advantages against Walmart and Amazon. The management teams are dealing with inflations perfectly and will be able to pass those to customers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[许家印变卖个人资产，向恒大投入超过70亿元人民币的救命资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国恒大集团董事局主席许家印承诺
许家印承诺确保投资者的利益，并承诺复工和保证交付建设。
的董事长许家印，正在出售他的个人资产以拯救恒大。
恒大。自7月1日以来，为了维持恒大的流动资金...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvomsc/xu_jiayin_sold_personal_assets_and_invest_over/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvomsc/xu_jiayin_sold_personal_assets_and_invest_over/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:43:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xu Jiayin, chairman of the board of directors of China Evergrande, who promised to ensure the interests of investors and promise the resumption of work and guarantee the delivery of buildings, &lt;strong&gt;is selling his personal assets to save Evergrande&lt;/strong&gt;. Since July 1st, in order to maintain the liquidity of the group, Xu has raised funds through the &lt;strong&gt;sale of personal assets&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;pledged equity&lt;/strong&gt; and has invested more than &lt;strong&gt;RMB7 billion&lt;/strong&gt; in the group to maintain the basic operations of the huge Evergrande empire. During this period, Evergrande did not have financing and sales suspension, but it must ensure the monthly payment of &lt;strong&gt;10%&lt;/strong&gt;, the salary of headquarters employees, and the payment of interest on domestic and foreign bonds, so as to promote the resumption of work and production of projects across the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you think this action can save Evergrande?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在淘金热中，出售铁锹]]></title><description><![CDATA[在芯片热潮中（由于电动车、采矿、元数据），相关的芯片供应商有哪些？
供应商公司？

我知道TSM是一个大公司，但他们是一家台湾公司。我正在寻找一家美国公司。
我知道英特尔和Qorvo有他们自己的内部工厂，作为一个IC设计师，我的设计是在Qorvo进行的。
我的设计是在Qorvo和Global...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvspcz/during_a_gold_rush_sell_shovels/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvspcz/during_a_gold_rush_sell_shovels/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:30:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;During a chip rush (due to EV, mining, metaverse), what are the relevant chip suppliers companies?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know TSM is a big one but they are a Taiwan company. I&amp;#39;m looking for a US one. I know Intel and Qorvo have their own in house fab and as an IC designer I had my designs fab at Qorvo and Global Foundries too. But which companies are the main suppliers for this chip rush?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特公司在最近的高价位19.79美元，是否仍有上升的空间]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道福特公司在Rivian有很大的投资。如果福特公司持有里维安公司的股份，那么他们的收益将是什么呢？
如果他们持有这项投资或决定将其清算，对福特来说会有什么好处？我个人认为
我个人认为，妹妹的车辆仍有很大的增长潜力，特别是他们的
EV150有巨大的未来订单。你是否认为...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvp7du/ford_at_a_recent_high_price_of_1979_does_it_still/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvp7du/ford_at_a_recent_high_price_of_1979_does_it_still/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:30:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know that Ford has a big investment in Rivian.  What will the upside be for Ford if they hold onto that investment or decide to liquidate it. Personally I think there’s still a lot of growth potential sister vehicles especially their EV 150 has a tremendous amount of future orders. Do you think will see a move up towards $30 per share during 2022?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资初级矿业股票是否值得？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我从今年年初开始投资，虽然我把一些钱放在了FCX和BHP等大型股票上。
较大的股票，如FCX和BHP，我也计划投资于一些小型企业。I
但我不打算在这些股票上投入大量资金，因为我知道投资的风险。
因为我知道投资这些股票的风险。

我正在研究三只股票...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvx11z/is_investing_in_junior_mining_stocks_worth_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvx11z/is_investing_in_junior_mining_stocks_worth_it/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:30:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been investing since early this year and while I have placed some money on bigger stocks like FCX and BHP, I am planning to invest in some juniors too. I don’t plan on placing a lot on them though, since I am aware of the risks that come with investing in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am looking into three stocks which includes &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fortitudegold.com/&quot;&gt;Fortitude Gold&lt;/a&gt; (FTCO). They are a small producer but a good thing about them is that they have no debts. They recently increased their dividend by 14%, and reported positive results in their Golden Mile property.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I included &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.threevalleycopper.com/&quot;&gt;Three Valley Copper&lt;/a&gt; (TVC) since they’re showing great potential too. They announced a financing with a deal brought about by investor demand, financing the company with $16 million dollars. They are expected to start mining early 2022 and will potentially produce 13-16 thousand tonnes of copper cathodes in a few years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m still looking into other juniors to add to my bigger mining stocks but some peers have been encouraging me to hold physical metals as well. I’m not really sure about this though. It would help me a lot if you guys share your thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[明天的NVDA...你的想法是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我现在不在NVDA中，我可能只是从旁观看
我可能只是从旁观者的角度看一下收益，但看看NVDA的表现肯定会很有趣。
明天白天的股价表现，然后显然是盘后的情况。
发生在盘后。

通常情况下，我认为任何事情，即使是远程...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvo2a3/nvda_tomorrow_your_thoughts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvo2a3/nvda_tomorrow_your_thoughts/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:03:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not currently in NVDA right now, and I&amp;#39;m probably just going to watch earnings from the sidelines, but it&amp;#39;ll certainly be interesting to see how the stock performs during the day tomorrow, and then obviously what&amp;#39;s going to happen in afterhours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Normally, I&amp;#39;d think that anything even remotely good has already been priced into this stock, so I don&amp;#39;t see how it could possibly explode to the upside after earnings. I&amp;#39;m sure they&amp;#39;re hurting in getting parts from their suppliers like anybody else. So, I&amp;#39;d think the forward guidance would be very cautious. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course anything is possible. The thing could hit $350 in AH or maybe $270&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian的市值目前为1450亿。在未来的几年里，有哪些市值低于1500亿的好股票是你比较看好的？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直听说Rivian在过去几天里已经超过了几家公司的市值。
我想知道什么是最好的进入。

你觉得在未来的几个月和几年里，什么是最好的？
你觉得在未来的几个月和几年里，哪些是最好的，也是市值在1500亿以下的？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjzf7/rivians_market_cap_is_currently_at_145b_what_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjzf7/rivians_market_cap_is_currently_at_145b_what_are/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 12:33:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I keep hearing Rivian has surpassed several companies market caps over the last few days and wondering what would the best ones to go into.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you feel are the best ones over the coming months and years to be holding onto that are also sub 150B market caps?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["我们不会因为担心可能出现的通货膨胀而先发制人地提高利率。我们将等待实际通货膨胀或其他不平衡的证据。" - J. 鲍威尔

过去一年的通货膨胀...
出口价格。+18.1%
进口价格。+10.7%
生产者价格指数: +8.6%
消费物价指数: +6.2%
PCE: +4.4%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460828560797667330</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460828560797667330</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:43:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你们这些人让我感到恶心，Rivian在这些水平上显然被低估了，你们没有看到整个画面。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我很震惊，人们还不明白这一点。rivian出售的T恤衫
[https://rivian.com/gear-shop]。我买了一件35美元的Rivian T恤。
我买了一件35美元的T恤，它的材料真的很好，这有助于证明+1400亿美元的
市值，如果我是诚实的。这艘船才刚刚开始，它...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvo2v1/you_people_make_me_sick_rivian_is_clearly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvo2v1/you_people_make_me_sick_rivian_is_clearly/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:43:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m shocked that people don&amp;#39;t still understand this yet. &lt;a href=&quot;https://rivian.com/gear-shop&quot;&gt;RIVIAN SELLS T-SHIRTS&lt;/a&gt;. I bought one of those $35 dollar T-shirts Rivian sells, it&amp;#39;s really good material which IMO helps justify the +$140 billion market cap if I&amp;#39;m being honest. This ship has only started &amp;amp; it won&amp;#39;t be long until more people buy these t-shirts. Rivian is not just a car company, it&amp;#39;s a clothing company too.(&lt;del&gt;Tsla is not just a car company, it&amp;#39;s a technology company too&lt;/del&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$RIVN的市值比他妈的大众汽车还要高。绝对不是泡沫。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvfn8c/rivn_has_a_higher_market_cap_than_fucking/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvfn8c/rivn_has_a_higher_market_cap_than_fucking/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:31:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车股票有什么特别之处？]]></title><description><![CDATA[今天和过去几个月以及2020年和2021年的大部分时间里，电动车股票一直是
在股价升值方面的领先行业。

我们有LCID，他今天上涨了23%。

RVN今天上涨了15%，其市值几乎达到1500亿美元。

其他如GOEV、FSR、XPEV、PTRA，他们的表现都很出色......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvilhs/what_is_so_special_about_ev_stocks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvilhs/what_is_so_special_about_ev_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:31:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today and for the past few months and most of 2020 and 2021, EV stocks have been the leading sectors in terms of stock price appreciation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have LCID who is up 23% today. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RVN who is up 15% today and with a market cap of almost $150B. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Others like GOEV, FSR, XPEV, PTRA who have been outperforming most of the market recently. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shit, TSLA is at $1T valuation and won’t stop there most likely. Yes, yes, I know Tesla is NoT jUsT aN EV cOmPaNy. But still. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Point is, what is the hype with EV stocks? I understand that it is a rapidly growing industry since mandates and adoption will allow EVs to replace ICE vehicles in the coming years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, automaker margins are freaking terrible. I just don’t see the appeal of auto maker stocks going up just because they are going EV. There will be lots of competitors (obviously), beit the new companies like Lucid, Rivian, and Tesla and the legacy makers like Volkswagen, Toyota, etc. Also, it’s not like EV is some niche field where duopolies or monopolies will thrive either. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s also not mention that EVs will cost more to make when compared to ICE. So it’s not like auto makers are going to cut major costs like when Ford introduced the assembly line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just want to start a discussion and hear people’s thoughts. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And no, I’m not shorting or buying puts. Just genuinely surprised that this EV bubble or rally - whatever you want to call it - is still going strong. Especially in times of inflation fears.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[周五鲍威尔的决定会对市场产生多大程度的影响？]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登刚刚宣布美联储将在4天内作出决定......因此，这要么是周五晚些时候
星期五晚上或星期六。因此，当市场在周末关闭时，这使得
我担心他正在更换负责人并取代鲍威尔。

比起利率、糖价飙升、通货膨胀......我最大的担忧是迄今为止的变化
在...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qviwx9/how_badly_will_the_market_be_affected_by_powell/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qviwx9/how_badly_will_the_market_be_affected_by_powell/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:18:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Biden just announced fed decision will be in 4 days… so that’s either late Friday night or Saturday. So when the market is closed on a weekend which makes me concerned he is changing the head and replacing Powell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More than rates, covid spike, inflation… my biggest concern was by far a change in Powell because the market hates change and unexpected news. I could totally see this resulting in what should have probably already happened with a correction especially with big market cap stocks. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the new chair would be Brainard who has a major supporter in Senator Warren, who opposes the FAANG stock dominance. I am very concerned and hopefully he just sticks with Powell. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The market is going so well this would really be the biggest negative that would sink things for end of year&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["我两边都在玩，这样我总能出头。"]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvqhsk/im_playing_both_sides_so_that_i_always_come_out/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvqhsk/im_playing_both_sides_so_that_i_always_come_out/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:18:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车初创公司Lucid的市值超过福特，股价暴涨，超过890亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA["我对我们的股票价格感觉很好，"豪斯在联合采访中告诉CNBC。
采访时说。"我们已经有的上升，它今天的位置，以及增长的轨迹，坦率地说，这在我们面前。
坦率地说，在我们面前的是增长的轨迹。我看到我们被认为是一家拥有平台的技术公司。
我看到我们被认为是一家技术公司，它的平台可以扩展到很多领域。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjuok/ev_startup_lucids_market_value_blows_past_ford_at/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjuok/ev_startup_lucids_market_value_blows_past_ford_at/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 10:44:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;I feel great about our stock price,&amp;quot; House told CNBC during the joint interview. &amp;quot;The runup that we&amp;#39;ve had, where it is today and also the growth trajectory, frankly, that&amp;#39;s in front of us. I see that we&amp;#39;re being regarded as a technology company with a platform that&amp;#39;s extensible across lots of vehicle variants and sustainable tech.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1980年至2021年标准普尔500指数的月度平均回报率：年底前的强劲表现？]]></title><description><![CDATA[以下是自1980年以来的平均回报率（%）。

数据是到2021年9月。资料来源。标准普尔和哈弗分析。

1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 +1.2 -0.1 +0.5 +1.5 -0.1 +0.8
+1.6 +0.7 -1.0 +0.4 +0.9 +1.3

你对2021年12月的赌注是什么？你是如何准备的？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjvni/average_monthly_sp_500_returns_from_1980_to_2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjvni/average_monthly_sp_500_returns_from_1980_to_2021/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 08:11:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below are the average return in % since 1980.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Data are through September 2021.  Source: Standard &amp;amp; Poor’s and Haver Analytics. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Jan&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Feb&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Mar&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Apr&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;May&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Jun&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Jul&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Aug&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Sep&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Oct&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Nov&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Dec&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+1.2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-0.1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+0.5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+1.5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-0.1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+0.8&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+1.6&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+0.7&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-1.0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+0.4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+0.9&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+1.3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What your bet for Dec 2021? How are you preparing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>