<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 02:18:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[涨幅最大的......已经持有多年，多年，多年了]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsthht/top_gainersbeen_holding_for_years_and_years_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsthht/top_gainersbeen_holding_for_years_and_years_and/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 01:46:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我们为你做饭，我们为你拖垃圾，我们为你接电话，我们为你开救护车! 我们在你睡觉时保护你!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qt7v2a/we_cook_your_meals_we_haul_your_trash_we_connect/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qt7v2a/we_cook_your_meals_we_haul_your_trash_we_connect/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 01:46:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[整个星期五晚上都在拉砖头。(一半会被我的长腿遮住，但我不够聪明，没能全部遮住）FUCK DASH。你们这些弱智的人说这是肯定要放的]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qt6oze/been_shitting_bricks_all_friday_night_half_will/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qt6oze/been_shitting_bricks_all_friday_night_half_will/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 22:34:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[rivian的IPO已经差不多把我卖了，这是个泡沫，很快就会破灭。不知道什么时候，但会开始对冲商品。]]></title><description><![CDATA[通货膨胀失控，印钞机超速运转，债务上限不得不提高
杠杆过高的银行和开发商在全球范围内倒闭，而现在
一家几乎没有销售过汽车的公司在纯投机的基础上拥有680亿美元的市值。
投机。钱就像糖果一样被扔来扔去，这...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qt68da/the_rivian_ipo_has_pretty_much_sold_me_this_is_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qt68da/the_rivian_ipo_has_pretty_much_sold_me_this_is_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 20:53:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inflation is running away, money printer on overdrive, debt limit having to be raised, overleveraged banks and developers collapsing around the world, and now a company that has sold almost zero vehicles has 68B in market cap based on PURE speculation. Money is being thrown around like candy, this is completely unsustainable. But as the saying goes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The market can stay irrational longer than you can stay solvent. Even burry was early by a year. It&amp;#39;s quite clear to me before the end of next year the bubble is going to pop, it&amp;#39;s just a matter of when not if. So instead of &amp;quot;lol just short then crowd&amp;quot; i think I&amp;#39;ll be moving most of my portfolio to commodities till this thing is over.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[无法说服我的嫂子开始投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的嫂子是一名27岁的特殊教育教师。她是我认识的
我认识的最好的理财者之一。例如，她花了一个多月的时间来研究要买哪辆车。
她花了一个多月的时间研究买哪辆车，并在谈判中两次抓住汽车销售员试图偷偷提高价格的行为。
她在谈判过程中被抓住。她是我心目中的完美人选。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qt5em6/cannot_convince_my_sisterinlaw_to_start_investing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qt5em6/cannot_convince_my_sisterinlaw_to_start_investing/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 20:25:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My sister in law is a 27 year old special education teacher. She is one of the best money managers I know. For example she spent over a month researching which car to buy, and caught the car salesmen twice trying to sneak higher prices past her during negotiation. She is the perfect person I would expect to be a boglehead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She is currently sitting on $60k in cold hard cash, that she has been building up for over 3 years. I knew she must have some but I didn&amp;#39;t know it was this much. I introduced her to the bogleheads philosophy, sent her a link to The Little Book of Common Sense Investing, sent her a link to the bogleheads forum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That was about 6 months ago. I have tried to engage her since then, but she just does not seem interested in the topic. Which is even more infuriating because that&amp;#39;s exactly the type of person who should be investing in low cost index funds. Someone who literally doesn&amp;#39;t care and will only check it every 5 years or so. She said she is too scared to invest, too risk adverse. I tried to tell her (and her sisters) that in fact the riskier thing by far is to not invest. But I don&amp;#39;t seem to be getting through to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She is still kind of young, so I think she thinks she still has time, but my analytical brain is on fire thinking of the compounding interest she is losing out on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has anyone else faced this issue? How do I convince her what she is doing, while it may feel safe, is actually way more dangerous?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: I should clarify that I am NOT trying to force Bogleheads philosophy on my sister-in-law. I&amp;#39;m not even really a Boglehead myself, although I do admire and desire to be a Boglehead. I have had maybe 3 conversations with her about investing, each less than 5 minutes long. This post is about my anxiety and concern for my family&amp;#39;s financial health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My mother became very ill when I was 20 years old, and was forced into early retirement. She didn&amp;#39;t have enough saved up by then to survive on her own. It has been very tough for me to witness, and I think my fears are coming out in anxiety when I see other people I love make decisions that might set them up for a similar fate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vanguard的新应用程序失败了，投资者抱怨用户体验的缺陷。也许它是一个功能，而不是一个错误 🤣]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qt5xkg/vanguards_new_app_flops_with_investors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qt5xkg/vanguards_new_app_flops_with_investors/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 19:48:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[里维安即将越过大众汽车公司的mk上限而不销售]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-12/rivian-is-now-biggest-u-s-company-with-no-sales-amid-ev-fever

因此，让我们来看看事实。

 * CEO没有成功的记录。

 * 公司没有销售。

 * 到目前为止，公司已经成功地将产量提升到每天只有一辆卡车。

 * 该...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qt5b0e/rivian_about_to_cross_vws_mk_cap_without_sales/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qt5b0e/rivian_about_to_cross_vws_mk_cap_without_sales/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 18:12:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-12/rivian-is-now-biggest-u-s-company-with-no-sales-amid-ev-fever&quot;&gt;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-12/rivian-is-now-biggest-u-s-company-with-no-sales-amid-ev-fever&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So let’s look at the facts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;CEO has no track record of success. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Company has no sales.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far the company has managed to ramp production to only one truck a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company is “targeting” a total of 1mn production rate in 2030. This includes vans, trucks, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[感谢TSLA美元，我在圣诞节买了一个新妻子。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qt5fe7/thanks_to_tsla_im_buying_a_new_wife_for_christmas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qt5fe7/thanks_to_tsla_im_buying_a_new_wife_for_christmas/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 18:12:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在你看来，什么股票是绝对的垃圾？]]></title><description><![CDATA[寻找一些可以做空的股票。做空对于散户投资者来说是相当罕见的
来做的。但它实际上使你的投资组合更加平衡，更加
准备好应对经济下滑。

我现在大约70%做多30%现金，我想用大约10%的投资组合做空。

我准备对一些股票进行研究...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qt4su4/what_stock_is_absolute_trash_in_your_opinion/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qt4su4/what_stock_is_absolute_trash_in_your_opinion/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 18:12:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking for some stocks to short. 
Shorting is pretty rare for retail investors to do. But it actually makes your portfolio a little more balanced and more ready for a downturn. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m about 70% long 30% cash and I want to short with about 10% of my portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some stocks I’m going to do research on as potential shorts are 
Ttcf,
Nikola,
Rivian,
Matterport,
And 
Zoom &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What trash companies come to mind for you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[周五快乐，弱智。单日收益10.2万。周三买了这些。昨天下跌了3万。今天兑现了7.7万的收益! 周五快乐!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qshvre/happy_friday_retards_102k_gains_in_a_single_day/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qshvre/happy_friday_retards_102k_gains_in_a_single_day/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 17:39:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你从事投资多久了，你的平均年收益率是多少？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我很好奇人们在这个子上的典型回报。

这个地方似乎是一个混合的袋子，有真正聪明的投资者，有赌博的
瘾者和18岁的年轻人在寻求帮助。

在你们的投资生涯中，你们有什么样的回报？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qt3ctu/how_long_have_you_been_investing_and_what_is_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qt3ctu/how_long_have_you_been_investing_and_what_is_your/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 17:39:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m curious about people&amp;#39;s typical returns on this sub. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This place seems to be a mixed bag of genuinely intelligent investors, gambling addicts, and 18 y/o&amp;#39;s looking for help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What kind of returns have you had in your investing careers?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[梅梅克尔币，比你想象的要笨。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果说有什么东西预示着投资界的小丑行为越来越多，那就是
当新闻媒体开始炒作一个价值4000万的迷你币时。
[https://www.express.co.uk/finance/city/1520609/shiba-inu-price-latest-crypto-news-shib-army-dogebonk-bitcoin-ethereum]
有2万名持有人。这到底是怎么一回事？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qt54cg/memecoins_dumber_than_you_think/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qt54cg/memecoins_dumber_than_you_think/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 17:39:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If anything portends the ever growing clowning of the investment world, it’s when the news media starts hyping a 40m  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.express.co.uk/finance/city/1520609/shiba-inu-price-latest-crypto-news-shib-army-dogebonk-bitcoin-ethereum&quot;&gt;micro cap memecoin&lt;/a&gt; with 20k holders. What the ever loving fuck. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what exactly is going on here? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s my theory, and I’ll preface this by saying I’m not a crypto expert, but I am the owner of a large PR firm, and I’ve seen the underbelly of how media works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s happening here is that we are witnessing the extraordinary power of meme based communities centered around highly memeable content. The power comes from two places.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The meme creates very strong in-group dynamics. Look no further than the popularity of meme based (not memecoin) based subreddits. Memes spread like wildfire even when financial incentive isn’t involved. This creates hyper active communities that build strong ties extremely quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Memes themselves are viral loops. Any community user creating memes is a potential source of new virality for the meme, or memecoin. This is an exponential flywheel and this is what most miss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As these groups ramp up, you inevitably get people with media power joining, including journalist with big audiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This seems to be happening with dogebonk and perhaps a few others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The memecoin market is an insane Wild West, and everyone should fully expect them all to potentially be scams. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That said, we already know the proliferating power of memes, so to expect memecoins to not be able to leverage that huge power, is to be blind to the clown world crypto enabled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储今年在其资产负债表上增加了1.3万亿美元，并保持利率为0，而通胀率已上升到31年的高点（年比6.2%）。

美联储的双重任务（价格稳定）的1/2被完全忽视，他们已经失去了作为通胀斗士的所有剩余的可信度。https://t.co/g1UyhyDr6U]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459535782516084737</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459535782516084737</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 16:53:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国预算赤字（财政年度，十亿美元）
2021: -$2,772
2020: -$3,132
2019: -$984
2018: -$779
2017: -$665
2016: -$585
2015: -$442
2014: -$485
2013: -$680
2012: -$1,077
2011: -$1,299
2010: -$1,295
2009: -$1,413
2008: -$459
2007: -$161
2006: -$248
2005: -$318
2004: -$413
2003年：-378美元 https://t.co/FY3BMmk6Ss]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459257660629524481</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459257660629524481</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 16:53:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[清偿学生债务与投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[我妻子有大约1万的学生贷款债务，利息为4.2%。我正准备
我即将收到一笔奖金（4万），显然可以把它还清，然后把剩下的钱投资于
但我的一部分只是想投资我所有的奖金，然后只是每月支付
她的债务，并随着时间的推移而还清。我真的没有...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsoqdy/pay_off_student_debt_vs_invest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsoqdy/pay_off_student_debt_vs_invest/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 16:53:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My wife has approx. 10k in student loan debt at 4.2% interest. I’m about to receive a bonus (40k) that would obviously pay it off and then invest the rest but part of me just wants to invest all of my bonus and then just make monthly payments on her debt and pay it off over time. I don’t really have any issues with having debt “hanging over my head” and really just want to make the decision that makes the most sense based on math. For reference, household income is 160k. I’m leaning towards investing all of it and continuing her repayment plan. Open to any ideas. TYIA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[说服我的妻子使用Bogleheads方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好。

大约两年前，我让我的妻子设立了一个ISA（相当于英国的ROTH IRA），她
她用一笔钱进行了投资，并从那时起每月向其中存入不到10%的工资。
自此以后，她每个月都会把她工资的10%左右存入该账户。目前的回报率略低于58%。
她拥有其他5家公司的直接股票（小型）。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qszfic/convince_my_wife_of_the_bogleheads_method/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qszfic/convince_my_wife_of_the_bogleheads_method/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 16:16:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi all, &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About 2 years ago I had my wife set up a ISA (UK equivalent of ROTH IRA), she invested with a lumpsum and has been contributing a little under 10% of her salary to it each month since. Currently sitting on returns of just under 58%, she owns direct equities in 5 other companies (small values under £1000) with mixed fortunes. One small cap mining has performed well the others well below the rate of inflation and 1 has negative returns. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been encouraging her to sell (no tax implications) and reinvest into her vangaurd portfolio as a lumpum but she is emotionally attached to the success of her picks and does not want to sell. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can you kind folks send me some specific article and studies on passive strategy vs direct stocks? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have tried to reason, explained compounded growth, opportunity loss but cannot get through to her. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[富裕的年轻投资者认为他们父母所依赖的财富管理公司没有用处]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 富裕的千禧一代对财务顾问。谢谢你的高尔夫邀请，但你
> 不能投资我的钱

华尔街日报》最近写了一篇关于这个问题的文章，如果你有兴趣，你可以很容易找到这篇文章。
你可以很容易地找到一篇文章，如果你有兴趣的话。

我一次又一次地听到同样的话。"任何人都可以做一个普通的财务顾问的工作
顾问"。下面是一个...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qt3c2n/wealthy_young_investors_dont_see_use_for_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qt3c2n/wealthy_young_investors_dont_see_use_for_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 16:16:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rich Millennials to Financial Advisers: Thanks for the Golf Invite, but You Can’t Invest My Money&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WSJ recently wrote an article about it, you can easily find an article if you are interested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hear the same again and again: &amp;quot;anyone can do a job of an average financial advisor&amp;quot;. Below is a story of a person from the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had a group of 5 mutual funds and our decision to decide what fund to put them in was based on one question: “on a scale of 1-5, what is your risk tolerance”. We asked every single client this and based on their answer plus their age, income and savings we put them in one of those  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought even a monkey could do my job at first but was amazed how many clients wouldn’t invest at all and just had their money sitting in cash. I wondered how even without an advisor why people couldn’t/wouldn’t pick pretty much any mutual fund and put their money there  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got paid based on how much I got people to invest and thought it would be easy money to convince people to make their assets grow but it was damn hard. Most clients had money in a CD and would refuse to move it &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever thought of going to money managers? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe you tried - what was the experience like?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么你不在目前的水平上购买支付宝？]]></title><description><![CDATA[支付宝在过去几个月里一直在挨打，然后被KO了
财报后。他们对下一季度的前瞻性指导有点低调，但该股仍然是
股价仍然稳固。分析师们已经下调了他们的PT，但他们仍然是
比目前的价格高出20-30%。与他们的venemo amzn...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qswdrr/why_would_you_not_buy_paypal_at_current_level/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qswdrr/why_would_you_not_buy_paypal_at_current_level/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 16:16:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paypal has been taking a beating for the last few months and then was KOed post-earnings. Their forward guidance for next quarter was a bit muted, but the stock IMO is still solid. Analysts have downgraded their PT, but they are still 20-30% higher than the current price. With their venemo amzn deal, Christmas around the corner, they should have a decent quarter. Just want to get some thoughts on say why even current price levels might be higher or essentially any other downsides. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[那么......特斯拉是怎么回事？是什么让人们对它如此有信心？]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，我已经在特斯拉上坐了很久，而我周围的人
我周围的人都在全力以赴。我的直觉告诉我，如果所有人都涌向一个
的东西，一定有什么猫腻。

我不能撒谎，我曾一次又一次地被诱惑着跳进去，看到我的朋友们
让...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsyjg3/so_whats_the_deal_with_tesla_what_is_it_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsyjg3/so_whats_the_deal_with_tesla_what_is_it_that/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 15:20:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;#39;ve been sitting on the sidelines for quite a while on Tesla while everyone else around me go all in. My gut feeling tells me that if everyone flocks to one thing, there must be something fishy about it all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;#39;t lie, I&amp;#39;ve been tempted time and time again to jump in, seeing my friends make 10% in a single day and what not. I guess I am only human. However, after reading the works of Buffet, Howard Marks, Munger, and those gentlemen (which i consider my teachers), Tesla just seems to go against their philosophy; especially when it comes to the margin of safety principle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now Tesla is a special case, if we look at Tesla as a company, their debt is consistently decreasing, equity and profits are growing like crazy, all of that is good. It&amp;#39;s just the valuation. Currently at a P/E of ~300 for instance, it means they have A LOT to back up for in the near future and the public obviously has high hopes in them. But my question is, what exactly is this hope? I am not very informed about Tesla, neither am I an engineer, which is why I wanna hear some of your opinions about them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- What is their specific moat when it comes to the electric cars? How will this moat be protected by other automobile dealers? (i.e the Germans, Ford, the Chinese, etc...) Is it just their brand or do they have superior technology that will actually be hard to replicate/improve by other companies in the coming 10 years?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- What other ventures are they going into besides cars? Is it A.I? What constitutes as A.I? If it is a personal robot who does the dishes for you and cleans your house, in what way will they have superior engineers compared to the other giants such as Alphabet and Microsoft? And why will they perform better than them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically, what is it that they do that makes people so confident in them, and what is it that accounts for this valuation?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[葡萄牙规定，你的老板在工作时间之外与你联系是非法的 https://t.co/2RBNwvR264]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459341980719362049</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459341980719362049</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 14:42:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你对什么股票（不经常在这里讨论）最有信心？]]></title><description><![CDATA[就像它所要求的那样，请让我知道......本周末将做dd，所以我对检查一些我可能错过的股票感兴趣。
有兴趣看看我可能错过的一些股票。

除了你的股票之外，请随时提供任何原因。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsqnak/what_stock_not_discussed_here_often_do_you_have/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsqnak/what_stock_not_discussed_here_often_do_you_have/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 13:28:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just like it asks, please let me know...will be doing dd this weekend and so am interested in checking out some stocks I may have missed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please feel free to provide any reasons why in addition to your stock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[呃......。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsru0w/uhhh/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsru0w/uhhh/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 11:19:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我被骗了

https://t.co/89XBPLUCYT]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459327267184779277</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459327267184779277</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 09:38:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[用硼砂洗衣服--不是洗身体。https://t.co/vDmqO5E8CI]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459288322749210639</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459288322749210639</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 09:38:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这是你们中的哪一个猿人？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsu5ll/which_one_of_you_apes_is_this/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsu5ll/which_one_of_you_apes_is_this/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 09:22:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么媒体对恒大的违约行为撒谎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[以下是一些文章，声称恒大确实错过了他们的债券付款。

https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.nytimes.com/2021/11/10/business/evergrande-bond-deadline.amp.html

https://www.reuters.com/business/several-bondholders-china-evergrande-receive-overdue-bond-coupon-payments-media-2021...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsping/why_is_the_media_lying_about_evergrandes_default/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsping/why_is_the_media_lying_about_evergrandes_default/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 08:43:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are some articles claiming that evergrande has did miss their bond payment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.nytimes.com/2021/11/10/business/evergrande-bond-deadline.amp.html&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.nytimes.com/2021/11/10/business/evergrande-bond-deadline.amp.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/business/several-bondholders-china-evergrande-receive-overdue-bond-coupon-payments-media-2021-11-11/&quot;&gt;https://www.reuters.com/business/several-bondholders-china-evergrande-receive-overdue-bond-coupon-payments-media-2021-11-11/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.nytimes.com/2021/10/28/business/evergrande-bond-payment.amp.html&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.nytimes.com/2021/10/28/business/evergrande-bond-payment.amp.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the articles states this which I thought was interesting:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;{Evergrande’s challenges could spread outside of China as well, as they ripple through global financial markets. On Monday, the Federal Reserve said troubles in China’s property sector could threaten the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Given the size of China’s economy and financial system as well as its extensive trade linkages with the rest of the world, financial stresses in China could strain global financial markets through a deterioration of risk sentiment, pose risks to global economic growth, and affect the United States,” the Fed said in its twice-yearly update on the American financial system.} &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EVERGRANDE DID DEFAULT:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.yahoo.com/now/evergrande-officially-defaulted-dmsa-preparing-161200818.html&quot;&gt;https://www.yahoo.com/now/evergrande-officially-defaulted-dmsa-preparing-161200818.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am seriously concerned on the reasons why evergrande’s default is being silenced, and what this means for the market as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在短短一个多月内从400美元到51000美元]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qssi74/from_400_to_51k_in_just_over_a_month/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qssi74/from_400_to_51k_in_just_over_a_month/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 07:15:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[还有人讨厌股票分析文章的点击率标题吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我正在使用M1金融系统来寻找随机的股票代码，然后我注意到了一件事。
我注意到有件事让我很不爽，那就是他们在说股票上涨或下跌时使用的整个戏剧性语言。
他们用整个戏剧性的语言来说明一只股票的涨跌。

如果一只股票上涨了一美元或5%左右，他们就会说一些愚蠢的废话，如："这只股票今天大涨。
这只股票今天大涨。"或者...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsofa3/anyone_else_hate_the_click_bait_titles_for_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsofa3/anyone_else_hate_the_click_bait_titles_for_stock/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 06:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was using M1 finance to just look around for random stocks tickers and something I noticed that really bugged me, is the whole dramatic language they use to say a stock went up or down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If a stock goes up by a dollar or around 5%, they say dumb crap like, &amp;quot;this stock has surged today.&amp;quot; or ascended, or spiked, or is sky rocketing. But like, the stock I was looking at had an ipo price of $12 and now it&amp;#39;s $4 and its apparently &amp;quot;skyrocketing.&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;like no, no it&amp;#39;s not. if I&amp;#39;m an investor from day one, and I read the phrase skyrocket, I&amp;#39;m thinking this thing is like $100 a share or something. Like the people who write these articles, I don&amp;#39;t know how they get paid for this. These analysts are paid to type nonsense every single day, but they aren&amp;#39;t paid to be accurate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was wondering if there was some enforced rules to these fancy adjectives. Because i see it with every company. They say plummet, or downward spiral, or falling when a company goes down even 1%, but jettisoned, surged, or sky rocket when it&amp;#39;s doing mildly good. I think it&amp;#39;s meant to keep people nervous and excited so people keep buying and selling and eventually make no money in the end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[戳穿通货膨胀阴谋论的漏洞，作者：Larry Swedroe]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsrov3/poking_holes_in_the_inflation_conspiracy_theory/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsrov3/poking_holes_in_the_inflation_conspiracy_theory/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 06:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[巨大的F***k Robinhood能量!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的$aapl 150看涨期权今天到期，在没有通知的情况下，他们关闭了我的
他们在下午3:02关闭了我的仓位，当时股价为149.76美元。当然，它在下午3:30之前反弹到
到下午3:30的时候，钱已经涨到了150.40美元。

我立即打电话给支持部门，在绕了一圈后，他们在收盘后给我回电说
市场关闭后，他们给我回电话说...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsllfi/big_fk_robinhood_energy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsllfi/big_fk_robinhood_energy/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 04:51:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I had $aapl 150 calls expiring today and WITHOUT notice they closed my position at 3:02pm when the stock was $149.76. And of course it rallied into the money by as much as $150.40 by 3:30pm!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I immediately called support and after a run around they called me back after the market closed saying that the risk assessment team made the decision to close. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why wouldn’t they send a notification ahead of time stating that by a certain time they would close the position? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nothing… They sold right before the stock rallied into close. The CSR offered zero condolences or any modicum of help. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this is another PSA: Fuck Robinhood!! I hope their stock burns to the ground, I’m withdrawing all my funds and moving to a better platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: Lesson learned, yes I’m retarded and don’t know how to read. More or less just venting to my fellow apes. For those who are unaware of this, we’ll now you know! Thank you for the lashing, but still fuck RH!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是今天（2021年11月12日，星期五）的市场回顾]]></title><description><![CDATA[心理市场回顾 - 2021年11月12日，星期五

周五股市稳步上扬，市场参与者继续平衡
在通胀上升的情况下，企业盈利好于预期。标准普尔500指数（SPY）
收盘上涨0.75%，科技股重仓的纳斯达克指数（QQQ）上涨1.05%，道琼斯...
琼斯...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsmfuq/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_friday_november/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsmfuq/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_friday_november/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 03:24:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Friday, November 12, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks advanced firmly on Friday, with market participants continuing to balance better-than-expected corporate earnings amid rising inflation. The S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) closed the day 0.75% higher, the tech-heavy Nasdaq (QQQ) rose 1.05%, and the Dow Jones (DIA) broke a three day losing streak to finish 0.51% higher. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of Friday’s close, the SPY closed the week 0.4% lower following volatility after the release of the October Consumer Price Index. However, after five consecutive weeks of gains, the market remains marginally below previous all-time highs. The QQQ closed the week 0.91% lower, while the DIA closed the week 0.97% lower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the Labor Department released the monthly Consumer Price Index, which showed prices soared 6.2% in a year-on-year period, accelerating from September’s 5.4% YoY rate, and higher than the 5.9% expected. This represents that fastest pace of inflationary expansion since 1990, though one has to take into account easy comparisons to last year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The staying power and magnitude of inflationary pressures has, perhaps, become the central question for market participants, with companies across the board reporting rising input costs and price hikes passed on to the consumers to preserve margins. While Q3 earning results have robustly demonstrated that companies in the SPY were largely able to navigate these cost pressures, the possibility remains that if inflation runs hotter than expected for longer than expected, it could begin to hamper consumer demand. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While a rise in inflation was expected, the pace of the increase surprised to the upside. If the pace of increase is not moderated soon, it carries meaningful implications for corporations, consumers, and the Federal Reserve. As input costs rise, companies will pass the increase in cost to consumers to preserve their bottom line, who will be forced to pay the higher prices. The Fed would then be forced to step in and rise interest rates, which will makes the cost to borrow money more expensive, which means people and companies will likely spend less, leading to a fall in demand for goods and services. A rise in interest rates would particularly hurt high P/E tech stocks that have been flying in the last two years, as these companies rely on borrowing to fund their aggressive expansion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still, the Federal Reserve and many economists have reaffirmed that the inflationary pressures are transitory, caused by pandemic-era disruptions in global trade and will eventually ease, albeit while likely settling at a higher level than had been present before the pandemic. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gabriela Santos, Global Market Strategist at JP Morgan, said “Inflation should moderate. We’re talking about settling at 2%, 2.5% over the course of the next 12 months. So we&amp;#39;re still talking about real wage gains, and that&amp;#39;s extremely supportive, certainly of people&amp;#39;s livelihoods, but also of consumption and hence the economy overall. We do expect a big re-acceleration in growth starting this quarter and throughout next year, [and] 5% average growth just over the next three quarters. So we would characterize this not as stagflation, but as reflation. And that difference is, reflation is actually quite good for earnings growth and quite good for the stock market, especially cyclical sectors.&amp;quot; So far, expectations are that the Fed will step in sometime mid-2022 to raise interest rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Rivian (RIVN), which is backed by Ford and Amazon,  continue to be on absolute fire. The company, which is expected to lose $1.28 billion on no more than $1 million in revenue this quarter, now has a market cap of more than $100 billion. For perspective, they are now the fourth largest automaker in the world by market cap. I’m not a stickler for valuation, but this is absolute insanity and unsustainable. The company has not started production and is already priced to perfection, which they are bound to hit a snag with. I don’t think this price is sustainable. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The University of Michigan’s closely monitored Consumer Sentiment survey showed the consumer sentiment index decreased to 66.8 from 71.7 in October, missing estimates of 72.5. Waning confidence reflects “ an escalating inflation rate and the growing belief among consumers that no effective policies have yet been developed to reduce the damage from surging inflation,” Richard Curtin, director of the survey, said in a statement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Snap (SNAP) investor sued the social media company alleging it downplayed how Apple’s (AAPL) change in privacy would affect revenue. Remember, the stock plummeted 25% after an earnings miss, citing Apple’s changes as hampering ad revenue. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After more than a decade of explosive growth, China&amp;#39;s Singles&amp;#39; Day, the world&amp;#39;s biggest online shopping fest, is losing its gloss and bracing for more modest growth in coming years, hurt by a slower economy and tighter regulatory scrutiny. Alibaba (BABA) said on Friday its sales - or gross merchandise value (GMV) - during the 11 day event grew 8.5%, the slowest rate ever and the first time it came under double-digits growth. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Friday said it rejected an exchange-traded fund from VanEck that would have tracked Bitc… spot prices directly. This would have stood in contrast to the ProShares ETF (BITO), which was approved and which only tracks futures rather than prices directly.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current stock price was written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Affirm (AFRM) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $140 to $185 at Overweight. Stock currently around $149&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equifax (EFX) target raised by Needham &amp;amp; Co from $295 to $335 at Buy. Stock currently around $280&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nice (NICE) with two target raises. Stock currently around $312

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Citigroup from $328 to $364 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Royal Bank of Canada from $325 to $368 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NXP Semiconductors (NXPI) target raised by KeyCorp from $250 to $255 at Overweight. Stock currently around $218&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Finance Technologies (SOFI) target raised by Jefferies Financial from $4 to $26 at Buy. Stock currently around $23&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tapestry (TPR) with a host of target raises. Average price target $55 at Overweight. Stock currently around $45&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weibo (WB) target raised by Citigroup from $63 to $66 at Buy. Stock currently around $46&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“In my view, the biggest investment risk is not the volatility of prices, but whether you will suffer a permanent loss of capital. Not only is the mere drop in stock prices not risk, but it is an opportunity. Where else do you look for cheap stocks?” - Li Lu&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[感谢大家，我将在圣诞节给我妻子买一辆新的特斯拉。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsiab0/thanks_to_you_all_im_buying_my_wife_a_new_tesla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsiab0/thanks_to_you_all_im_buying_my_wife_a_new_tesla/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 01:39:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[富裕的年轻投资者认为他们父母所依赖的财富管理公司没有用处]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 富裕的千禧一代对财务顾问。谢谢你的高尔夫邀请，但你
> 不能投资我的钱

华尔街日报》最近写了一篇关于这个问题的文章。

你有没有想过要去找理财师？也许你试过--结果是什么？
经验？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qslgdm/wealthy_young_investors_dont_see_use_for_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qslgdm/wealthy_young_investors_dont_see_use_for_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 01:39:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rich Millennials to Financial Advisers: Thanks for the Golf Invite, but You Can’t Invest My Money&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WSJ recently wrote an article about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever thought of going to money managers? Maybe you tried - what was the expirince?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[工人辞职人数创新高，消费者情绪创10年新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[令人着迷的是，工人们正以迅猛的速度辞去工作，但同时消费者也没有信心。
同时，消费者也没有那么自信。在较高的工资和最近的通货膨胀之间可能存在一个滞后。
导致这些问题的原因可能是较高的工资和最近的房价上涨之间的滞后。

在第四季度看到收入高峰，然后再降低，这并不奇怪。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsn6yl/workers_quit_jobs_in_record_numbers_as_consumer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsn6yl/workers_quit_jobs_in_record_numbers_as_consumer/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 01:39:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Its fascinating to see how workers are quitting their jobs at a torrid pace but also that consumers are not being as confident. There could be a lag between the higher wages and the more recent porce increases causing these issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would not be surprised to see peak earnings in Q4 before lower confidence and higher prices really set into corporate earnings over the next year or so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/consumer-sentiment-hits-10-year-low-while-workers-quit-jobs-in-record-numbers.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/consumer-sentiment-hits-10-year-low-while-workers-quit-jobs-in-record-numbers.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[让我们再做一次]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsm8mh/lets_do_it_again/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsm8mh/lets_do_it_again/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 01:39:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我们能谈谈GameStop吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我对投资游戏有点陌生，所以如果我错过了关于这个问题的讨论，我很抱歉。
这方面的讨论。我在今年早些时候关注了GameStoo的传奇故事，最近开始
又开始关注支持它的两个大的subreddits。

根据我的理解，理论上说，短线实际上从未卖出...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsje5u/can_we_talk_about_gamestop/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsje5u/can_we_talk_about_gamestop/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:31:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m a bit new to the investing game so my apologies if I missed the discussions on this. I followed the GameStoo saga earlier this year and recently started looking again at the two big subreddits supporting it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To my understanding, the theory goes that the shorts never actually sold their positions (because they would have gone bankrupt), but instead used all sorts of trickery to delay and avoid. Some ppl, have caught on to this and are determined to hold the stock such that when the chickens come home to roost and the shorts are forced to close, will trigger, they’ll be able to skyrocket the price. I’ve seen claims that a single share could be worth millions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This of course sounds fantastical and far-fetched but would someone mind explaining how seemingly so many ppl have adopted this belief and are all-in on a once hated retail store? IE where are they wrong in their analysis? Is it just a case of the human factor not being realized; that once the price jumps a bit, ppl will start to sell, so the idea of holding into the 1000s plus is unrealistic?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我仍然微笑着]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsa3fj/im_still_smiling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsa3fj/im_still_smiling/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:31:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[刚刚在Discord上点击了一个骗局，我的MetaMask钱包被洗劫一空。进入周末的好方法。

我是NGMI]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459281438172491778</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459281438172491778</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 23:38:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta和微软宣布合作，整合Workplace和Teams]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/10/meta-and-microsoft-announce-partnership-to-integrate-workplace-and-teams.html

前身为Facebook的Meta公司宣布了一项伙伴关系，将
允许客户将工作场所与微软团队整合。

Meta公司和微软之间的合作关系...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsm2ow/meta_and_microsoft_announce_partnership_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsm2ow/meta_and_microsoft_announce_partnership_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 23:38:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/10/meta-and-microsoft-announce-partnership-to-integrate-workplace-and-teams.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/10/meta-and-microsoft-announce-partnership-to-integrate-workplace-and-teams.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meta, the company formerly known as Facebook, announced a partnership that will allow customers to integrate Workplace with Microsoft Teams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The partnership between Meta and Microsoft brings together two rivals that compete in the market of enterprise communication software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The partnership could prove most beneficial to Meta, whose Workplace service lags drastically behind its competitors in terms of users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is definitely a good partnership news that will benefit both companies. Microsoft teams is gaining more marketshare as it integrates into other softwares. The partnership could prove most beneficial to Meta as teams could help to boost its Workplace enterprise social network software users. Both stocks should be in the portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pssst，需要一些绿色的东西吗，先生？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsdeyo/pssst_need_some_greens_sir/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsdeyo/pssst_need_some_greens_sir/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 22:46:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为你的应急基金投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好! 前几天我在听《千禧年投资》播客的一集。
有一天。在这一集里，主持人采访了克里斯-卡瓦亚。克里斯提出的
争论说，最好是投资你的应急基金，而不是将其作为
现金。他建议将88%的资金投资于债券，另外12%的资金投资于银行账户。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsha3j/investing_your_emergency_fund/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsha3j/investing_your_emergency_fund/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 22:34:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello! I was listening to an episode of The Millenial Investing podcast the other day. In this episode, the host interviews Chris Kawaja. Chris makes the argument that it is better to invest your emergency fund rather than keep it as cash. He proposes investing 88% in bonds and the other 12% in a S&amp;amp;P 500 index fund. Historically, this combination has kept up or beaten inflation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you guys think? Anyone take this approach?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[关于迪士尼股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，我在两周前套现了，现在正坐在一大笔现金上等待合适的机会。
等待合适的机会。现在，随着迪斯尼在过去5天内大幅下跌15美元
过去5天里，你们认为将所有的2万块钱投资到DIS上怎么样？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsgldu/about_disney_stocks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsgldu/about_disney_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 22:14:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I cashed out about 2 weeks ago and a sitting on a large sum of cash waiting for the right opportunity. Right now with the huge 15$ drop of Disney in the past 5 days, what do you guys think about investing all 20k into DIS?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这个牛市与其他任何牛市一样......或者说是这样？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我从几年前就开始投资，所以我不知道2008年以前的投资感觉如何。
2008年以前的投资。我看到很多 "PE不再重要"，"这个周期是
不同 "之类的评论，我首先想到的是把它们当作 "不重要 "来抛弃。
我的第一个想法是把它们当作没有经验的想法，这些人和我一样，不知道什么是......。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsbs5s/this_bull_market_is_like_any_other_or_is_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsbs5s/this_bull_market_is_like_any_other_or_is_it/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 22:14:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been investing since a few years, so I have no idea of how it felt to invest pre 2008. I see a lot of &amp;#39;PE doesn&amp;#39;t matter anymore&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;this cycle is different&amp;#39; and that kind of comments, and my first thought is to discard them as inexperienced thoughts from people who, like me, don&amp;#39;t know what a serious bear market feels like. But I can&amp;#39;t pass on one thought: the information has changed. Before 2008, regular folks had access to a completely different kind of information than today. I don&amp;#39;t know how the landscape changed for institutions sinc ethen, maybe they already had access to the info we use nowadays to base our decisions, maybe they even had algo trading already, but the internet was so different that it must have made a tremendous impact for them as well. It seems a relevant discussion to be had, so I&amp;#39;m asking you: do you believe this time is different? If you don&amp;#39;t, what&amp;#39;s your counter argument?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[东芝将一分为三]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，企业集团正在解体，就像无人问津一样。首先是通用电气
现在是通用电气的直接竞争对手东芝，其根源可以追溯到1875年。此外
此外，我们还有强生公司的分拆。我们几乎应该期待
西门子也会采取同样的做法
途径。https://www.wsj.com/articles/toshiba...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsd3uu/toshiba_to_split_into_three/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsd3uu/toshiba_to_split_into_three/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 21:53:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conglomerates are breaking up like it&amp;#39;s nobody&amp;#39;s business this week. First GE and now a direct GE-competitor, Toshiba, whose roots date back to 1875. In addition we have the Johnson and Johnson s split. We should almost expect Siemens to follow the same path.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/toshiba-like-ge-plans-to-split-into-three-parts-11636700609?mod=hp_lead_pos3&quot;&gt;https://www.wsj.com/articles/toshiba-like-ge-plans-to-split-into-three-parts-11636700609?mod=hp_lead_pos3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这只是交易员基本技能的一部分]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsc3lg/its_just_a_part_of_basic_trader_skillset/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsc3lg/its_just_a_part_of_basic_trader_skillset/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 20:23:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[什么是最省税的Vanguard经纪基金？]]></title><description><![CDATA[就目前而言，我的现金有点太多了。目前我的IRA
和401k。什么是最有效的Vanguard非税收优惠基金？我在想
我在想一个简单的80/20的VTI/VXUS。债券现在不做任何事情，所以没有
入这些基金也没有用。

我有一个迫在眉睫的担忧，杰克...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs9id6/what_are_the_most_tax_efficient_vanguard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs9id6/what_are_the_most_tax_efficient_vanguard/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 18:00:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of right now, I have a little too much in cash.  Currently maxing out my IRA and 401k.  What are the most efficient Vanguard non-tax advantaged funds? I was thinking a simple 80/20 VTI/VXUS.  Bonds aren&amp;#39;t doing anything right now, so no use getting into those.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One looming concern I have, and Jack Bogle talks about this in his book, is &amp;quot;reversion of the mean&amp;quot;.  He even said in an interview that sometimes you do have to time the market.  But that&amp;#39;s just my personal choice, and I am going to choose to wait until the reversion of the mean to invest in a non-tax advantaged account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So thoughts on taxable ETFs? Reinvest dividends? Use dividends to pay taxes?  Are VTI and VXUS good choices?  Is skipping bonds completely a bad choice?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你是如何说服自己卖掉你最后的个人股票赢家，去完成3个基金的投资组合？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我几乎完全是一个拥有4个基金（VOO、VXUS、VGIT、TIP）的Bogelhead。但我
仍然坚持着过去的几个赢家。amzn, aapl, msft, zen, prgfx。
你是如何证明扣动扳机的？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsdb10/how_did_you_convince_yourself_to_sell_your_last/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsdb10/how_did_you_convince_yourself_to_sell_your_last/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 17:33:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am almost completely a Bogelhead with a 4-fund (VOO, VXUS, VGIT, TIP). But I still hang on to a couple winners from the past: AMZN, AAPL, MSFT, ZEN, PRGFX. How did you justify pulling the trigger?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[自闭症的赌注]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs96pb/autism_bets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs96pb/autism_bets/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 17:04:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[天价通胀不是因为 "供应链瓶颈"，而是因为印了太多的钱]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看到这些天有很多文章和帖子都在谈论供应链问题。
不管是关于购买一个集装箱有多贵，还是说
或航运港口没有足够的空间，或没有足够的
卡车司机，等等。

然而，这些都是微观层面的症状。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsdxg3/sky_high_inflation_isnt_due_to_supply_chain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsdxg3/sky_high_inflation_isnt_due_to_supply_chain/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 17:04:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I see a lot of articles and posts these days talking about supply chain issues: whether it&amp;#39;s about how expensive it is to buy a shipping container, or that there isn&amp;#39;t enough space at shipping ports, or that there aren&amp;#39;t enough truckers, etc. etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, these are all micro-level symptoms of a macro-level problem. Don&amp;#39;t miss the forest for the trees. Journalists need to write something new every day (or every hour it seems), even if there isn&amp;#39;t anything new to say. Which leads to a lot of noise that clouds your mind from making sense of what is really happening in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my view, the problem is clear: governments overdid it with stimulus. Unlike the 2008 Global Financial Crisis where policymakers did too little and acted too slow, this time around governments decided to err on the side of doing too much too quickly. If you look at consumer spending on FRED, it didn&amp;#39;t just fully recovery from the 2020 shock, it&amp;#39;s arguably on a stronger trajectory than it otherwise would be without the pandemic! At the same time, unemployment is still high and labor force participation is dreadfully low! The Fed created such a tremendous wealth effect, people are earning multiple years worth of stock market returns in the span of months. I&amp;#39;m not surprised many people are taking career breaks or retiring early. So why do we have red hot inflation? Because we&amp;#39;re printing more money and making less things, it&amp;#39;s that simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The inflation problem highlights how difficult it is to be a policymaker. On one hand, you don&amp;#39;t want to under spend and risk seeing long-term economic scarring, but if you stimulate too much, you risk fueling inflation as well as asset price bubbles. The other factor at play is the politicization of economic policy. You&amp;#39;re everyone&amp;#39;s favorite politician when you&amp;#39;re fueling spending, but it&amp;#39;s hard to get reelected when you advocate for cutbacks. Prudent policymaking requires spending when times are bad, and building reserves when times are good - politicians have forgot about the latter half of that equation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在目前的价格下，你会在V、MA和PYPL之间选择哪个？]]></title><description><![CDATA[支付宝的PE为48.6

万事达卡为43.6

Visa为37.4

虽然单纯从PE的角度来看，Paypal是最昂贵的，但我更倾向于他们，因为他们在过去的历史中一直是最受欢迎的。
我更倾向于他们，因为他们在历史上有更高的收入增长。
与其他两家相比，他们有更高的收入增长，而且他们是多元化的，或正试图多元化的
到诸如...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs4tiv/at_current_prices_which_would_you_choose_between/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs4tiv/at_current_prices_which_would_you_choose_between/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:59:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paypal at PE of 48.6&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mastercard at 43.6&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Visa at 37.4&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Paypal is the most expensive purely from PE point of view, I&amp;#39;m leaning more towards them because they&amp;#39;ve historically had higher revenue growth compared to the other two and they&amp;#39;re diversified or are trying to diversity into things like crypto, stock broker, etc. Also Paypal is around 33% off from its 52 week high, which is far lower than V or MA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you had to pick one out of these 3? Which would you buy at today&amp;#39;s prices?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>