<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 01:46:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[有没有在新西兰的Bogleheads？]]></title><description><![CDATA[与美国相比，新西兰的投资和税收情况略有不同。

如果有人感兴趣，我很想比较一下最好的方法。

对于资产配置，我目前是这样的。

 * 85%的AMP ACWI（60%美国/40%世界其他地区） - 69%对冲为新西兰元；以及

 * 15%的家庭偏见（简单...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2xg0t/any_bogleheads_in_new_zealand/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2xg0t/any_bogleheads_in_new_zealand/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 01:04:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a slightly different investing and tax landscape in NZ compared to the US. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d be keen to compare notes on the best approach if anyone is interested.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For asset allocation, I’m currently:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;85% AMP ACWI (60% US / 40% rest of the world) - 69% hedged to NZD; and &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% home bias (Simplicity NZ Share a fund)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we approach retirement I’m looking to move toward 60% shares / 40% fixed interest.   Weighing up the pros/cons of moving out of PIE funds and investing direct.  Although I don’t like the currency risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Covid：是时候为非洲服务了]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2v5f7/covid_its_time_for_africa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2v5f7/covid_its_time_for_africa/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 01:04:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么银行对新的Covid变体新闻大跌眼镜？]]></title><description><![CDATA[标题是不言自明的，但银行和新的covid变体的严重下降趋势背后的原因是什么？
银行和新的covid变体背后的原因是什么？在我看来，如果通货膨胀持续，银行将从最有可能的加息中受益。
如果通货膨胀持续下去，银行将从最可能的加息中受益。有谁能说明一下
谈谈这个问题？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2q5zd/why_banks_go_down_heavily_on_new_covid_variant/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2q5zd/why_banks_go_down_heavily_on_new_covid_variant/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 23:55:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Title is self-explanatory, but what&amp;#39;s the reasoning behind the heavy downtrend of banks and the new covid variant?
The way I see it banks will benefit from the most than likely interest hike if inflation persists. 
Anyone can shed some light on this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场上的F**Cockatoo回来了！!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2r088/market_fck_cockatoo_is_back/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2r088/market_fck_cockatoo_is_back/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 23:29:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天的股票市场就像]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2xdc2/the_stock_market_today_be_like/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2xdc2/the_stock_market_today_be_like/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 23:29:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国因担心安全问题要求滴滴出行从美国退市]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://archive.md/20211126053013/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-26/china-is-said-to-ask-didi-to-delist-from-u-s-on-security-fears

中国监管机构已要求滴滴全球公司的高管们制定一个计划，以从美国退市。
熟悉此事的人士称，滴滴全球公司的高管已经要求他们制定一个从美国证券市场退市的计划，...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2m6n2/china_asks_didi_to_delist_from_us_on_security/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2m6n2/china_asks_didi_to_delist_from_us_on_security/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 23:07:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.md/20211126053013/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-26/china-is-said-to-ask-didi-to-delist-from-u-s-on-security-fears&quot;&gt;https://archive.md/20211126053013/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-26/china-is-said-to-ask-didi-to-delist-from-u-s-on-security-fears&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chinese regulators have asked Didi Global Inc.’s top executives to devise a plan to delist from U.S. bourses, people familiar with the matter said, an unprecedented request that’s likely to revive fears about Beijing’s intentions for its giant tech industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The country’s tech watchdog wants management to take the company off the New York Stock Exchange because of concerns about leakage of sensitive data, the people said, asking not to be identified discussing a sensitive matter. The Cyberspace Administration of China, the agency responsible for data security in the country, has directed Didi to work out precise details, subject to government approval, they said.  Proposals under consideration include a straight-up privatization or a share float in Hong Kong followed by a delisting from the U.S., the people added. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the privatization proceeds, the proposal will likely be at least the $14 IPO price since a lower offer so soon after the June initial public offering could prompt lawsuits or shareholder resistance, the people said. If there is a secondary listing in Hong Kong, the IPO price would probably be a discount to the share price in the U.S., $8.11 as of Wednesday’s close. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shares in SoftBank Group Corp., Didi’s biggest minority shareholder, slid more than 5% in Tokyo. Deliberations continue and it’s possible regulators will backtrack on their request, the people said. Either option would deal a severe blow to a ride-hailing giant that pulled off the largest U.S. IPO by a Chinese firm since Alibaba Group Holding Ltd.’s in 2014. Representatives for Didi and the CAC didn’t respond to requests for comment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi sparked the ire of Beijing when it proceeded with its New York stock offering this summer, despite regulatory requests that it ensure the security of its data before the IPO. Chinese regulators quickly launched multiple investigations into the company and have considered a range of unprecedented penalties, Bloomberg News reported in July. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s possible that the delisting would be part of a package of punishments for Didi. Beijing’s municipal government has proposed an investment in the company that would give state-run firms effective control, Bloomberg News reported in September. Such an investment could help Didi finance the repurchase of its U.S.-traded shares. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi is currently controlled by the management team of co-founder Cheng Wei and President Jean Liu, which received aggregate voting power of 58% after the company’s U.S. initial public offering. SoftBank and Uber Technologies Inc. are Didi’s biggest minority shareholders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if Didi shifts its listing to Hong Kong, it will have to address the data security concerns that have drawn regulatory scrutiny. The company may have to give up control of its data to a third-party -- again undercutting its price tag.
Read more about Didi’s brushes with Beijing regulators&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regulators have weighed a delisting for Didi since the summer, after the world’s largest ride-hailing company infuriated officials by ploughing ahead with its U.S. IPO, Bloomberg News has reported. A withdrawal from U.S. bourses could stoke fears of an exodus of Chinese firms as Washington and Beijing quarrel about access to listed firms’ books. On Thursday, a senior Chinese regulatory official said such delistings would be a setback for relations with the U.S., while offering broad support for Hong Kong as an alternative venue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi -- once feted for defeating Uber in China -- has now become a test case for a broader Chinese government effort to curb the power of internet titans. Xi Jinping’s administration, keen to promote his vision of sharing the wealth or “common prosperity,” has targeted an internet sector that’s accumulated vast wealth by operating on the periphery of the law, minted an unprecedented number of billionaires and enriched local and foreign investors in the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A state-directed privatization would be unprecedented for a private firm of Didi’s stature, affirming that the Chinese government remains bent on curtailing the power of the country’s internet firms and unlocking the data and wealth hoarded during a decade of heady expansion. It would send a chilling signal to American investors, long accustomed to investing freely in China’s largest corporations from Alibaba to Baidu Inc. and JD.com Inc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beijing’s moves against Didi have been particularly harsh, even after a crackdown that has penalized giants like Alibaba and Tencent Holdings Ltd. The Cyberspace Administration of China saw Didi’s IPO decision as a challenge to the central government’s authority, which led to the CAC, the Ministry of Public Security, the Ministry of State Security and several other agencies initiating on-site inspections at Didi’s offices in July.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s since been ensnared by probes into data security and the way it treats its millions of drivers. Many of the options Beijing is weighing involve re-asserting state control over a company that’s traditionally operated in a legal gray zone, Bloomberg News has reported.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[醒来查看我的SPY看涨期权值多少钱]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2pbv0/waking_up_to_check_how_much_money_my_spy_calls/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2pbv0/waking_up_to_check_how_much_money_my_spy_calls/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 22:37:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[书籍推荐]]></title><description><![CDATA[除了《Boglehead投资指南》，你还会推荐哪些关于投资的书籍？
投资指南之外，还有哪些关于投资的书籍？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2q1y4/book_recommendations/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2q1y4/book_recommendations/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 21:43:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What books would you recommend on investing beyond the Boglehead guide to investing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天的交易策略在12秒内完成]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2ni8n/todays_trading_strategy_in_12_seconds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2ni8n/todays_trading_strategy_in_12_seconds/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 21:43:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天有谁在进行税收损失收割？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的新资金一直在进入债券和国际市场，所以我今天在美国ETF上没有任何损失。
今天在美国ETF上的损失。我在国际市场上已经超过了TLH的门槛。

今天有谁在收获税收损失吗？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2qzda/anyone_tax_loss_harvesting_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2qzda/anyone_tax_loss_harvesting_today/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 21:14:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My new money has been going into bonds and international, so I don’t have any losses on US ETFs today. I am over a TLH threshold for international. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anybody tax loss harvesting today?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[r/Stocks 每日讨论与基本面 2021年11月26日星期五]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是每日讨论，所以任何与股票有关的东西都可以，但今天的主题是基本面。
今天的主题是基本面，但如果基本面不是你的事，那么就
忽略这个主题和/或发表你反对基本面的论点......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2kb5u/rstocks_daily_discussion_fundamentals_friday_nov/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2kb5u/rstocks_daily_discussion_fundamentals_friday_nov/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 20:53:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the daily discussion, so anything stocks related is fine, but the theme for today is on fundamentals, but if fundamentals aren&amp;#39;t your thing then just ignore the theme and/or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+%22r%2Fstocks+semiannual+arguments+against+TA%22&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;post your arguments against fundamentals here&lt;/a&gt; and not in the current post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some helpful day to day links, including news:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finviz.com/quote.ashx?t=spy&quot;&gt;Finviz&lt;/a&gt; for charts, fundamentals, and aggregated news on individual stocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/markets&quot;&gt;Bloomberg market news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;StreetInsider news:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Market+Check&quot;&gt;Market Check&lt;/a&gt; - Possibly why the market is doing what it&amp;#39;s doing including sudden spikes/dips&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Reuters&quot;&gt;Reuters aggregated&lt;/a&gt; - Global news&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most fundamentals are updated every 3 months due to the fact that corporations release earnings reports every quarter, so traders are always speculating at what those earnings will say, and investors may change the size of their holdings based on those reports.  Expect a lot of volatility around earnings, but it usually doesn&amp;#39;t matter if you&amp;#39;re holding long term, but keep in mind the importance of earnings reports because a trend of declining earnings or a decline in some other fundamental will drive the stock down over the long term as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the following word cloud and click through for the wiki:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/wiki/fundamentals-themed-post&quot;&gt;Market Cap - Shares Outstanding - Volume - Dividend - EPS - P/E Ratio - EPS Q/Q - PEG - Sales Q/Q - Return on Assets (ROA) - Return on Equity (ROE) - BETA - SMA - quarterly earnings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a basic question, for example &amp;quot;what is EBITDA,&amp;quot; then google &amp;quot;investopedia EBITDA&amp;quot; and click the Investopedia article on it; do this for everything until you have a more in depth question or just want to share what you learned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Useful links:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/fundamental-analysis-4689757/&quot;&gt;Investopedia page&lt;/a&gt; on fundamental analysis including &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/university/dcf/&quot;&gt;Discounted Cash Flow&lt;/a&gt; analysis; see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/d/dcf.asp&quot;&gt;definition here&lt;/a&gt; and read &lt;a href=&quot;http://i.investopedia.com/inv/pdf/tutorials/fundamentalanalysis_intro.pdf&quot;&gt;their PDF on the topic.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finviz.com/quote.ashx?t=aapl&quot;&gt;FINVIZ&lt;/a&gt; for fundamental data, charts, and aggregated news&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.earningswhispers.com/stocks/aapl&quot;&gt;Earnings Whisper&lt;/a&gt; for earnings details&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See our past &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+%22r%2Fstocks+daily+discussion%22&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;daily discussions here.&lt;/a&gt;  Also links for:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Atechnicals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Technicals&lt;/a&gt; Tuesday, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Aoptions&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Options Trading&lt;/a&gt; Thursday, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Afundamentals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Fundamentals&lt;/a&gt; Friday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国禁止南非、博茨瓦纳、津巴布韦、纳米比亚、莱索托、埃斯瓦蒂尼、莫桑比克和马拉维的旅行。

听起来像种族主义者]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464309113484107784</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464309113484107784</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 20:41:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不得不把经典带回来]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2s89n/had_to_bring_back_the_classic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2s89n/had_to_bring_back_the_classic/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 20:25:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你是否同意，B.1.1.529 "可怕的 "杀手病毒株（50个尖峰蛋白突变）现在将成为任何做空备忘录股票的人的保证金调用催化剂？]]></title><description><![CDATA[该病毒突变还有其他10个基因突变。世卫组织召开紧急
会议。航空公司关闭旅行。市场跌宕起伏。截至本报告撰写时为止。
道琼斯指数期货下跌850点，罗素2000指数期货下跌4.5%。

我和我的朋友们进行了一些讨论，说单是这一点就可以...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2iejk/do_you_agree_that_the_b11529_horrific_killer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2iejk/do_you_agree_that_the_b11529_horrific_killer/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:59:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The virus mutation also has 10 other genetic mutations.  WHO convening emergency meeting.  Airlines shutting down travel.  Markets tumbling.  As of this writing, DOW futures are down 850 points, and russel 2000 index futures are down 4.5%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some talks with my friends going on about how this alone could serve as a GME, AMC &amp;#39;MOASS&amp;#39; catalyst, since collateral and margin maintenance requirements.  With markets crashing like this, the NSCC algos do indeed raise capital requirements.  What are your thoughts on the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GME, AMC, and other meme stocks have a negative beta and therefore serve as a hedge against falling markets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;These stocks remain heavily shorted, and therefore, funds that are stuck in egregious short positions have to buy to cover to get out, and potentially very quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.1.1.529 &amp;#39;horrific&amp;#39; killer virus strain could induce this market catalyst (as unfortunate as that is to say that it came to this in order to have free and fair markets).  Thoughts?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[南部非洲出现一个严重变异的Covid变体

扯淡]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464136788583329792</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464136788583329792</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:35:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资与交易。什么是最简单的财富积累方式？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我从今年2月开始投资，在股市中存入了26,000美元。
股票市场，目前我已经达到33,014美元，所以到目前为止我赚了25%的利润。我的
我的投资组合目前由九只股票组成。我一直在研究期权
交易，这涉及高风险，但可以带来高回报......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r24bqb/investing_vs_trading_what_is_the_easiest_way_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r24bqb/investing_vs_trading_what_is_the_easiest_way_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:34:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been investing since February of this year with $26,000 deposited in the stock market and I’m currently up to $33,014 so I made a 25% profit so far. My portfolio currently consists of nine stocks. I’ve been looking into options trading recently which involves high risk but can give high returns if I know what I’m doing. However, investing in established companies is obviously safer but takes longer to build wealth unless I have at least $200,000 in the market, and I can’t afford to deposit anywhere near that amount right now. Between investing in a diverse set of stocks, investing in two or three startup company stocks that may blow up one day, or doing options trading, which of these strategies do you think would be the easiest for building significant wealth within ten years?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[谢谢你的保险金]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2pexn/thanks_for_the_insurance_money/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2pexn/thanks_for_the_insurance_money/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:34:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有谁在DCA-ing进入迪士尼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[迪斯尼是官方的，远远低于我的平均成本154美元。
现在已经跌到了148美元。我一直在稳定地购买更多的股票
但不想落入落井下石的怪圈。

还有人买入更多的迪士尼吗？有什么我应该注意的吗，或者这只是
觊觎者...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2qwft/anyone_dcaing_into_disney/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2qwft/anyone_dcaing_into_disney/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 18:49:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disney is official well below my average cost of $154. It was at $200 at one point and now has crashed down to $148. I’ve been steadily buying more shares but don’t want to fall into the falling knife thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone else buying more of Disney? Anything I should be aware of or is this just a covid scare?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[来自越南弱智的黑色星期五快乐! 我应该卖出还是持有我的MRNA看涨期权？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2orio/happy_blackfriday_from_a_vietnamese_retard_should/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2orio/happy_blackfriday_from_a_vietnamese_retard_should/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 18:49:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我就发这个帖子，希望市场能转绿。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2oe7s/ima_just_post_this_in_hopes_of_the_market_turning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2oe7s/ima_just_post_this_in_hopes_of_the_market_turning/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 17:48:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔重返GPU市场对Nvidia的影响是否被低估了？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我注意到，这里的大多数人都非常看好Nvidia，即使在其目前的估值下也是如此。
但我没有看到很多关于英特尔重返GPU市场将如何影响Nvidia的估值和未来增长的讨论。
但我没有看到很多关于英特尔重返GPU市场将如何影响Nvidia的估值和未来增长的讨论。

英特尔拥有资金和人才，尤其是在拉贾-科杜里的领导下。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2l9n8/is_the_impact_of_intel_returning_to_the_gpu/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2l9n8/is_the_impact_of_intel_returning_to_the_gpu/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 17:48:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have noticed that most people on here are very bullish towards Nvidia even at its current valuation but I haven&amp;#39;t seen much talk about how Intel&amp;#39;s return to the GPU market will affect Nvidia&amp;#39;s valuation and future growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intel has the money and talent especially with Raja Koduri leading the Graphics department to become highly competitive with Nvidia if not a leader in the market. Intel will also have the advantage of using their new fabs in the future to produce their GPU&amp;#39;s whereas Nvidia will be reliant on TSMC/Samsung.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With AMD also becoming more competitive and both Intel and AMD not being as limited to just the GPU market unlike Nvidia, should people be worried that Nvidia may have to lower profit margins and suffer from lower growth that could make their current price look extremely high?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For disclosure I do own some INTC and would be interested in NVDA if the valuation was more reasonable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NVDA电话已经准备好了，今天要跟我干架了]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2iqrz/nvda_calls_are_ready_to_fck_me_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2iqrz/nvda_calls_are_ready_to_fck_me_today/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 17:34:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你现在对UIPath的看法是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[自今年上市以来，该公司的股票已经下跌了34%，市值已经下降了100亿美元。
跌了100亿美元。我最近一直在考虑买入一些股票，并在看到其
在看到他们最近的收益后，我明白他们没有盈利
因为他们一直在大幅增加他们的研发和...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r25k25/what_is_your_view_on_uipath_right_now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r25k25/what_is_your_view_on_uipath_right_now/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 17:05:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The stock has dropped 34% since it IPO&amp;#39;d this year and the market cap has dropped $10 billion. I have been considering picking up some shares recently and after seeing their recent earnings I understand that they are not profitable because they have been dramatically increasing their R&amp;amp;D plus Marketing Spend even though Revenues are increasing a good amount.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[关于DraftKings ($DKNG)的研究报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好，如果有人能看一下我的股票研究报告并提供一些反馈或讨论，我将不胜感激。
报告，并提供一些反馈或讨论。谢谢! -一位大学新生
对股票研究感兴趣

https://www.theancienteconomist.com/post/draftkings-dkng-equity-research-report

DraftKings被认为是一个...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r28h7w/research_report_on_draftkings_dkng/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r28h7w/research_report_on_draftkings_dkng/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 15:47:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey all, I’d appreciate it if someone could take a look at my equity research report and provide some feedback or discussion.
Thanks! -a college freshman interested in Equity research&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theancienteconomist.com/post/draftkings-dkng-equity-research-report&quot;&gt;https://www.theancienteconomist.com/post/draftkings-dkng-equity-research-report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DraftKings is regarded as one of the current leaders of the sports gambling indus- try. The company, since its founding in 2012, has obtained lucrative partnering agree- ments with the biggest players in sports and entertainment, establishing contracts with MLB, NFL, NASCAR, UFC, ESPN, 21st Century Fox Sports, and Bleacher Report. DraftK- ings offers live daily fantasy contests for over 13 sports. The online sports gambling in- dustry has huge growth potential, which has yielded a large number of competitors to spring up, such as Penn National Gaming (NASDAQ: $PENN), fuboTV (NYSE: $FUBO), and Flutter Entertainment (OTCMKTS: $PDYPY). Despite the lure of the sports gambling industry, the bearish case for DraftKings lies in waiting for a further correction before in- vesting due to competitive pressure, limited growth, and their profitability track record.
The quality of services is critical in determining the long-term growth and customer retainment for a firm, especially within the gaming sector. DraftKings’ narrow yet compact focus on live online sports betting limits their presence in the overall gam- bling industry, as opposed to other firms such as Penn National Gaming, which employs a generalist approach to available services. Penn, in addition to sports and casino style bet- ting, is a large operator of casino and resort locations. This versatility in gambling ser- vices could provide greater growth in a post-COVID world less reliant on virtual gaming, which DraftKings does not offer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在别人恐惧的时候要贪婪。当别人贪婪的时候，你要恐惧。]]></title><description><![CDATA[看起来所有的市场都会因为新的 "Covid "的消息而大吃一惊。
Covid的变体。关于这个消息的有趣之处在于，它只是新的菌株
是严重变异的，我们不知道这是否是坏事。我们应该把这看作是一个
机会，以折扣价买入更多股票。这发生了...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2lpz7/be_greedy_when_others_are_fearful_be_fearful_when/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2lpz7/be_greedy_when_others_are_fearful_be_fearful_when/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 15:27:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looks like all of the markets are going to take a shit on the news of the new Covid variant. Funny thing about the news on that, it is simply the new strain is heavily mutated and we don’t know if that’s bad. We should see this as an opportunity to buy more stocks at a discount. This happened earlier in the year and most stocks have recovered since then. Just like the Warren Buffett quote in the title. Sure everyone’s portfolio is red at the moment. Some people see the red and panic, I see a green opportunity on the horizon. Someone else once said, “scared money don’t make money”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[道指期货暴跌400点，担心在南非发现新的科威德变种]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2e6ss/dow_futures_plunge_400_points_amid_fears_of_new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2e6ss/dow_futures_plunge_400_points_amid_fears_of_new/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 13:31:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[必须把它们都打印出来 💵]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2jd98/gotta_print_them_all/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2jd98/gotta_print_them_all/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 13:31:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[开市时你要买什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[众所周知，由于担心出现新的变种，现在的期货是血红的。
当事情发生时，你真的应该做两件事，那就是什么都不做。
或买入。在这种情况下不要卖出，因为我保证你会后悔。

既然如此......如果你在买入组中，你有什么......？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2ivb9/what_are_you_buying_when_the_market_opens/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2ivb9/what_are_you_buying_when_the_market_opens/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 13:05:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As everyone knows, futures are bloody red right now on fears of a new variant. There are really two things you should do when things open and that is nothing, or buy. Do not sell in these conditions because I guarantee you will regret it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said…if you are in the buy group, what are you looking at when the markets open?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m looking at tech: APPLE, AMAZON and MSFT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[道指期货暴跌800点，担心在南非发现新的科威德变种]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/26/stock-futures-open-to-close-market-news.html

> 美国股票期货在周五早盘下跌，因为投资者
> 由于对南非发现的一种新的Covid病毒的担忧重新抬头，美国股票期货周五早盘下跌，因为投资者为缩短交易日做好了准备。
> 在南非发现的变体。
> 
> 道琼斯指数的期货...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2ko1v/dow_futures_plunge_800_points_amid_fears_of_new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2ko1v/dow_futures_plunge_800_points_amid_fears_of_new/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 12:39:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/26/stock-futures-open-to-close-market-news.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/26/stock-futures-open-to-close-market-news.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;U.S. stock futures dropped in early morning trading on Friday as investors geared up for a shortened trading day amid renewed Covid fears over a new variant found in South Africa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Futures for the Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 800 points, while those for the S&amp;amp;P 500 and Nasdaq 100 were also in in negative territory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The downward moves came after WHO officials on Thursday warned of a new Covid-19 variant that&amp;#39;s been detected in South Africa. The United Kingdom temporarily suspended flights from six African countries due to the variant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bond yields tumbled amid the flight to safety. The yield on the benchmark U.S. 10-year Treasury note fell to 1.5380%, a sharp reversal after surging above 1.65% earlier this week. Bond yields move inversely to prices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oil prices also tumbled, with U.S. crude futures down 6.2% to $73.57 per barrel, while the South African rand weakened 1.7% against the greenback to 16.231 per dollar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Asia markets were hit hard in Friday trade, with Japan&amp;#39;s Nikkei 225 and Hong Kong&amp;#39;s Hang Seng index both falling more than 2% each.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲市场下挫，投资者权衡最新的全球病毒担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲股市周五下挫，因为一些欧洲国家在冠状病毒感染激增后收紧了对旅行和商业的限制。
在冠状病毒感染率激增后，一些欧洲国家收紧了对旅行和商业的限制，而南非的
报告了一个新的变体。上海、东京、香港和悉尼都出现了下跌。美国
市场周四因感恩节假期休市....。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2g92r/asian_markets_sink_as_investors_weigh_latest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2g92r/asian_markets_sink_as_investors_weigh_latest/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 11:35:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asian stock markets sank Friday after some European countries tightened curbs on travel and business following a surge in coronavirus infections and South Africa reported a new variant. Shanghai, Tokyo, Hong Kong and Sydney declined. U.S. markets were closed Thursday for the Thanksgiving holiday. Austria imposed a nationwide 10-day lockdown after its daily virus deaths tripled, while Italy imposed curbs on activity by unvaccinated people. The U.S. government advised Americans to avoid travel to Germany and Denmark. Scientists in South Africa said a new variant was spreading among young people in its most populous province.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Investors are likely to shoot first and ask questions later until more is known,” Jeffrey Halley of Oanda said in a report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Shanghai Composite Index CN:SHCOMP lost 0.6% to 3,560.15 and the Nikkei 225 JP:NIK NIY00 in Tokyo plunged by an unusually wide 2.8% margin to 28,656.17. The Hang Seng HK:HSI in Hong Kong tumbled 2.3% to 24,161.55. The Kospi KR:180721 in Seoul lost 1.4% to 2,938.09 and Sydney’s S&amp;amp;P-ASX 200 AU:XJO fell 1.7% to 7,279. New Zealand and Southeast Asian markets also declined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wall Street’s benchmark S&amp;amp;P 500 SPX closed up 0.2% on Wednesday. U.S. markets are due to reopen Friday for a shortened post-Thanksgiving trading session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/asian-markets-sink-as-investors-weigh-latest-global-virus-concerns-01637900804?mod=mw_quote_news&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/asian-markets-sink-as-investors-weigh-latest-global-virus-concerns-01637900804?mod=mw_quote_news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[既然中国正在推动滴滴从美国退市，我有什么选择？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我拥有少量的滴滴股票。中国已要求滴滴从美国退市
因为担心安全问题。我有什么选择？

我使用BofA的ME来交易股票。他们不允许交易场外交易的证券。
场外交易的证券。

我应该采取观望的态度，还是立即卸货？

我读过...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2dmfx/what_are_my_options_since_china_is_pushing_didi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2dmfx/what_are_my_options_since_china_is_pushing_didi/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 10:11:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I own a small amount of Didi shares.  China has asked Didi to delist from the US over security fears.  What are my options?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use ME by BofA to trade stocks.  They don&amp;#39;t allow trading of securities that trade over-the-counter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should I take a wait and see approach or offload immediately?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve read that if privatization were to occur, it would be at the $14 IPO price.  The stock closed at $8.11 on Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If they were to delist, how would I go about trading the stock?  Or is it just considered a total loss?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[与Delta变体相比，Nu covid变体将如何影响市场？]]></title><description><![CDATA[与Nu变体的第一批问题 -

 * B.1.1.529，将被命名为Nu
 * 穗状蛋白的32个突变
 *最早的已知病例。南非，11月12日
 * 担心它可能更具传播性，逃避免疫力
 * 英国和以色列实施旅行禁令
 * 南非报告了2465个新病例，比上周增加了321%。

根据...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2e5iy/how_will_nu_covid_variant_affect_the_markets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2e5iy/how_will_nu_covid_variant_affect_the_markets/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 06:52:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;First issues with the Nu variant -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.1.1.529, to be named Nu&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;32 mutations in spike protein&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earliest known case: South Africa, Nov. 12&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fears it could be more transmissible, evade immunity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UK &amp;amp; Israel impose travel bans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SA reports 2,465 new cases, up 321% from last week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According here &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/drericding/status/1463998740340121601?s=21&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/drericding/status/1463998740340121601?s=21&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost double the mutations as delta&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Was vaccine resistant as people tested were double vaccinated with Pfizer (but did not have 3rd booster) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WHO already emergency meeting and UK and Israel have shut down flights coming from 6 nations. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biggest issue is that the new variant is VACCINE RESISTANT which seems awful long term unless people are really going to attempt to get us to take brand new vaccine shots in 3-4 months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[南非科学家在病例激增的情况下检测出新的冠状病毒变体。期货目前下跌严重...]]></title><description><![CDATA[你有什么想法？由于修改和规则，我无法链接任何文章，但
在网上快速搜索一下。

零售商会失去他们的冷血吗？我认为很多人在保证金上会吃亏
他们的袜子在接下来的日子里......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2eo5e/south_african_scientists_detect_new_coronavirus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2eo5e/south_african_scientists_detect_new_coronavirus/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 06:30:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What are your thoughts? I couldn’t link any articles due to mods and rules, but do a quick search online. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will retails lose their cold blood? I think a lot of people on margin will eat their socks in the next days…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我可以用以前投入普通经纪公司的钱来为罗斯个人退休帐户提供资金吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果这个问题已经得到解决，请让我知道。我在谷歌上搜索了一下
通过这个子，似乎找不到我的问题的答案。

我今年对我的Roth捐款不够，想达到6000美元的目标。
最高限额。问题是，我的收入进入了我的经纪公司，而我...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2ddl7/can_i_fund_a_roth_ira_with_money_that_i_had/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2ddl7/can_i_fund_a_roth_ira_with_money_that_i_had/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 05:22:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If this has been addressed, please let me know. I have googled and searched through this sub and can’t seem to find an answer to my question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t contribute enough to my Roth this year and want to reach the $6000 maximum. The problem is that my income went into my brokerage and I’m concerned about how it may look to the IRS if I withdraw money from my brokerage and deposit into my Roth. This money would not be in surplus to what I deposited into my brokerage. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The IRS website just says that the money used to fund it has to be earned wages, but doesn’t go into further depth. Is it still “earned” if I’m just withdrawing money that I had earned and churned through some day trades? Am I over thinking this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any answer is appreciated and thank you for your time&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国因担心安全问题要求滴滴出行从美国退市]]></title><description><![CDATA[(Bloomberg) -- 中国监管机构已经要求滴滴全球公司的高层管理人员制定从美国证券交易所退市的计划。
熟悉此事的人士表示，中国监管机构已要求滴滴全球公司的高管制定从美国证券交易所退市的计划。
熟悉此事的人士说，这一前所未有的要求可能会重新引起人们对中国政府对其巨型科技产业的意图的担忧。
熟悉此事的人士说，这一前所未有的要求可能会重新引起人们对中国政府对其巨大的科技产业的意图的担忧。

该国的科技产业...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2d32w/china_asks_didi_to_delist_from_us_on_security/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2d32w/china_asks_didi_to_delist_from_us_on_security/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 04:43:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Chinese regulators have asked Didi Global Inc.’s top executives to devise a plan to delist from U.S. bourses, people familiar with the matter said, an unprecedented request that’s likely to revive fears about Beijing’s intentions for its giant tech industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The country’s tech watchdog wants management to take the company off the New York Stock Exchange because of concerns about leakage of sensitive data, the people said, asking not to be identified discussing a sensitive matter. The Cyberspace Administration of China, the agency responsible for data security in the country, has directed Didi to work out precise details, subject to government approval, they said. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proposals under consideration include a straight-up privatization or a share float in Hong Kong followed by a delisting from the U.S., the people added. If the privatization proceeds, the proposal will likely be at least the $14 IPO price since a lower offer so soon after the June initial public offering could prompt lawsuits or shareholder resistance, the people said. If there is a secondary listing in Hong Kong, the IPO price would probably be a discount to the share price in the U.S., $8.11 as of Wednesday’s close. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shares in SoftBank Group Corp., Didi’s biggest minority shareholder, slid more than 5% in Tokyo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deliberations continue and it’s possible regulators will backtrack on their request, the people said. Either option would deal a severe blow to a ride-hailing giant that pulled off the largest U.S. IPO by a Chinese firm since Alibaba Group Holding Ltd.’s in 2014. Representatives for Didi and the CAC didn’t respond to requests for comment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi sparked the ire of Beijing when it proceeded with its New York stock offering this summer, despite regulatory requests that it ensure the security of its data before the IPO. Chinese regulators quickly launched multiple investigations into the company and have considered a range of unprecedented penalties, Bloomberg News reported in July. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s possible that the delisting would be part of a package of punishments for Didi. Beijing’s municipal government has proposed an investment in the company that would give state-run firms effective control, Bloomberg News reported in September. Such an investment could help Didi finance the repurchase of its U.S.-traded shares. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi is currently controlled by the management team of co-founder Cheng Wei and President Jean Liu, which received aggregate voting power of 58% after the company’s U.S. initial public offering. SoftBank and Uber Technologies Inc. are Didi’s biggest minority shareholders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if Didi shifts its listing to Hong Kong, it will have to address the data security concerns that have drawn regulatory scrutiny. The company may have to give up control of its data to a third-party -- again undercutting its price tag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regulators have weighed a delisting for Didi since the summer, after the world’s largest ride-hailing company infuriated officials by ploughing ahead with its U.S. IPO, Bloomberg News has reported. A withdrawal from U.S. bourses could stoke fears of an exodus of Chinese firms as Washington and Beijing quarrel about access to listed firms’ books. On Thursday, a senior Chinese regulatory official said such delistings would be a setback for relations with the U.S., while offering broad support for Hong Kong as an alternative venue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi -- once feted for defeating Uber in China -- has now become a test case for a broader Chinese government effort to curb the power of internet titans. Xi Jinping’s administration, keen to promote his vision of sharing the wealth or “common prosperity,” has targeted an internet sector that’s accumulated vast wealth by operating on the periphery of the law, minted an unprecedented number of billionaires and enriched local and foreign investors in the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A state-directed privatization would be unprecedented for a private firm of Didi’s stature, affirming that the Chinese government remains bent on curtailing the power of the country’s internet firms and unlocking the data and wealth hoarded during a decade of heady expansion. It would send a chilling signal to American investors, long accustomed to investing freely in China’s largest corporations from Alibaba to Baidu Inc. and JD.com Inc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beijing’s moves against Didi have been particularly harsh, even after a crackdown that has penalized giants like Alibaba and Tencent Holdings Ltd. The Cyberspace Administration of China saw Didi’s IPO decision as a challenge to the central government’s authority, which led to the CAC, the Ministry of Public Security, the Ministry of State Security and several other agencies initiating on-site inspections at Didi’s offices in July.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s since been ensnared by probes into data security and the way it treats its millions of drivers. Many of the options Beijing is weighing involve re-asserting state control over a company that’s traditionally operated in a legal gray zone, Bloomberg News has reported.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/china-asks-didi-to-delist-from-u-s-on-security-fears-1.1687281&quot;&gt;https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/china-asks-didi-to-delist-from-u-s-on-security-fears-1.1687281&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[好市多（COST）--为什么它就一直在跑？]]></title><description><![CDATA[COST今年取得了惊人的成绩，突破了300分，现在已经跃居500分。
现在已跃升至500点。我在4月开始投资时抓了10股
因为我知道这是一家有利可图的公司，经营良好，有一个坚实的
但我做梦也没想到......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2advu/costco_cost_why_does_it_just_keep_running/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2advu/costco_cost_why_does_it_just_keep_running/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 03:37:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;COST has gone on a ridiculous run this year, breaking out of the 300s and leaping now well into the 500s. I grabbed 10 shares when I started investing in April because I knew it was a profitable company that’s well-run with a solid loyal customer base, but never in my wildest dreams did I expect it to go on this kind of run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone find any reasons that COST is climbing like this? Seemingly not even the September correction could slow it down (unlike in March).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[明年就要满18岁了，需要一些建议......]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的目标是学习培养对金钱/投资/共同的良好认知。
社会系统（银行等取决于国家），并运用我的知识
以实现财务独立，也许还可以发展业务，或者仅仅是意识到
我的目标是培养对金钱/投资/普通社会制度（银行等，这些都取决于国家）的良好认知，并运用我的知识来实现财务独立，也许可以发展业务，或者只是在早期就意识到这些事情（任何建议的主题可能...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2367p/about_to_be_18_next_year_need_some_advices/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2367p/about_to_be_18_next_year_need_some_advices/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 02:38:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My goal is to learn to develop a good perception of money/investing/common social systems (banks, etc which are country dependent) and apply my knowledge to achieve financial independence and maybe develop businesses or  just be aware of these things at an early age (any suggested topics which might be useful to know at 18/19 are welcome)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m willing to read any novels/books regarding this… though I have 0 idea of commercial studies etc since I picked sciences as subjects at 16…so I don’t know basic stuff about accounting/economics (though I can read about it if required)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-with all these currency, stocks etc which I currently have no idea about, which one should I approach and what mentality should I keep before approaching these things? What books/sources do you recommend to gain knowledge about these things?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Please recommend any books which can help me develop my perception of money, maybe learn about investing/stocks, or which can help me develop my understanding of basic social systems like banks etc (if required) 
[ive only read basic books like rich dad, poor dad  etc but I don’t have formal knowledge regarding these in any way…]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-ANY general advice, maybe mistakes you made in early stage, any miscellaneous books or knowledge about the topics (like budgeting etc) you think are beneficial for me are welcome… go all out…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks in advance&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit- thank you all for the advices… I’ll take a ss and will review each advice and try my best to follow the suggestions the moment my entrance exams are done (assuming I go to a good uni, seems likely)
Thank you all again for the lists, I will save them 100%%%&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有没有人通过互联网泡沫的Boglehead？那将是超过7年的坚持不懈的过程。我不确定我是否能坚持下去。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2a7be/anyone_boglehead_through_the_dot_com_bubble_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2a7be/anyone_boglehead_through_the_dot_com_bubble_that/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 02:01:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为YOLO申请了一个信贷额度，有人建议吗？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r23rx6/took_a_line_of_credit_to_yolo_suggestions_anyone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r23rx6/took_a_line_of_credit_to_yolo_suggestions_anyone/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 00:58:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[大约是这样总结的]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r280jm/about_sums_it_up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r280jm/about_sums_it_up/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 23:54:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你最具投机性的股票是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[给我的是收入前的SPAC，无利可图的几分钱，以及在52周低点沉睡的
处于52周低点的巨头。我正在寻找那些100倍的机会和0%的可能性。
0倍的可能性。给我你最重的袋子，你仍然在增加，并且相信。
相信的。让我为没有投资于你的月球而感到羞愧...。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r260wh/what_is_your_most_speculative_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r260wh/what_is_your_most_speculative_stock/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 23:54:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Give me them pre-revenue SPACs, the unprofitable pennies, and the sleeping giants at their 52 week lows. I&amp;#39;m looking for those 100x opportunities with the 0x possibility. Shill me your heaviest bag that you are still adding too and believe in. Make me feel fomo for not investing in your moonshot tech stock. I&amp;#39;ll go first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$BLGO&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BioLargo OTC $.20&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These guys are basically pre-revenue, but they have spent the last few years making a water filtration system for PFAS&amp;#39;s. If the stars align just right with the EPA declaring PFAS a hazardous material and their tech works as advertised they are looking to lead a $180B industry. They also have a consumer product releasing soon called Pooph. It&amp;#39;s an anti smell cleaning product which could bring in a good amount of steady revenue in 2022. Management seems to have their head on straight and be focused on the right things. All in all definitely worth the ~2% of my portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲的博格赫德们]]></title><description><![CDATA[亲爱的Bogleheads朋友们，特别是欧洲的朋友们，你们好。

我真的很想加入3-way组合，但这本书看起来真的像
它是为美国人准备的。有几个问题。

- 你是否投资于sp500或SPY？或欧盟的类似基金/ETF？你认为欧盟
80%还是美国的80%的股票？

- 哪种...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r26hx5/bogleheads_in_europe/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r26hx5/bogleheads_in_europe/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 23:42:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello dear  Bogleheads friends, specially the European ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really want to get into the 3-way portfolio, but the book looks really like it´s for US  folks. A few questions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Do you invest in sp500 or SPY? or Similar funds/ETFs in EU? Do you consider EU 80% or US as 80% of stocks?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Which brokers you use in Europe for low commissions?  Any idea how taxes works? I´m in Portugal&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Overall indexes funds are better here or ETFs?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any literature or anything else would be much appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[嘿，至少我们很冷静]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r25vz2/hey_at_least_were_cool/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r25vz2/hey_at_least_were_cool/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 23:27:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[价格目标都是扯淡。比如$ETSY。]]></title><description><![CDATA[看看这段废话吧。

> 11月4日，Needham将etsy的目标价格从250美元调整为265美元，保持
> 买入评级。
> 
> 11月22日，Needham将etsy的目标价格从265美元上调至325美元，保持
> 买入评级。



18天以来，到底发生了什么根本性的变化？

保持你的原价...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r25dz0/price_targets_are_bullshit_like_etsy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r25dz0/price_targets_are_bullshit_like_etsy/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 23:05:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out this bullshit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On November 4, Needham adjusted price target on etsy to $265 from $250, keeps buy rating.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On November 22, Needham raises price target on etsy to $325 from $265, keeps buy rating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;what the fuck has fundamentally changed in 18 days???&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;keep your original price target, and stick to it. Stop raising the damn price target just because the stock price is being pumped up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is like a gamma squeeze. assholes are just pumping stocks for no reason, and people are gonna get burned when the whales pull the rug.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Billionaires are cashing out at these all time highs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I have no positions in etsy&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WSB DnD排列图]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r23ba1/wsb_dnd_alignment_chart/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r23ba1/wsb_dnd_alignment_chart/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 22:37:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[与朋友一起管理投资俱乐部的合法性]]></title><description><![CDATA[我和一群朋友已经投资了一段时间，我们每个人都有自己的
自己关注的 "领域"。一般来说，对于你自己在一个部门的部分资本
你会听从 "专家 "的意见，把它投资在哪里，而
他们会听从你的意见，因为你擅长的是什么。也有...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2043j/legality_of_managing_an_investment_club_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2043j/legality_of_managing_an_investment_club_with/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 22:19:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A group of friends and I have been investing for awhile and each of us has their own &amp;#39;area&amp;#39; they focus on. In general for you own portion of capital in a sector you will defer to the opinion of the &amp;#39;specialist&amp;#39; on where to invest it, and they to you for whatever you specialize in. There are also friends who follow along with us but do not have the time to research anything and so do not provide insights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This got us thinking, wouldn&amp;#39;t it be convenient to just pool our money in a club and let everyone handle their specialty independently but the effects would be felt collectively. John handles all the healthcare investments, Brian the banking, Steve the tech, etc. From what I have read on investment clubs its pretty clear that those who would actually manage investments can all form a club together and we wouldn&amp;#39;t need any sort of licensing. The question comes in with the silent members who do not research or invest themselves. If we had 4 people making the decisions and 6 whose money was in the partnership but they made no input, would this mean the 4 &amp;#39;managers&amp;#39; need licensing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, if we were to divide the partnership in a way that the active members received more through ownership means, would this break the rules for an investment club? Ex: Brain and Steve form an investment club and both contribute $50,000. Brain manages and makes all investment decisions so he gets a 60% interest in the LLC while Steve gets 40%. From my own understanding and research it seems this should be allowed under &amp;#39;sweat equity&amp;#39; rules but I know investing is subject to special stipulations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And yes, I am aware of the old &amp;#39;never invest your friends money&amp;#39; saying but we are all adults&amp;#39; with experience and this represents a tiny fraction of each of our net worth&amp;#39;s. Appreciate any input!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天市场关闭。感恩节快乐! 🦃🍽🍁 https://t.co/gd1nJWKToH]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1463871698948829193</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1463871698948829193</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 21:42:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[下一个有前途的科技股？]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，伙计们。

不幸的是，我错过了像$net $ttd $okta $crwd这样有前途的科技股，在它们的早期，现在的估值对我来说似乎有点高。
他们的早期，现在的估值对我来说似乎有点高，因为
风险/回报情况而言，现在的估值对我来说有点高。

所以我想问，你现在是否在关注任何有前途的科技股？
也许是一个仍然有点...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r21tcj/next_promising_tech_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r21tcj/next_promising_tech_stock/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 21:30:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey guys,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;unfortunately I missed the promising tech stocks like $net $ttd $okta $crwd in their early days and now the valuations seem a bit high for me regarding the risk/return profile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I would like to ask if you are watching any promising tech stock right now? Maybe one that is still a bit under the radar like the ones I mentioned where few years ago?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What tech/IT related sources you use to get information about these kind of stocks first?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wish在法国被屏蔽：95%的产品不符合欧盟法规。谷歌必须将其从搜索中删除]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r1yabs/wish_blocked_in_france_95_of_products_do_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r1yabs/wish_blocked_in_france_95_of_products_do_not/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 21:13:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[回顾R/Stock用户的预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年我发了一个帖子，告诉Reddit/股票用户预测2021年表现最好的
2021年表现最好的股票，答案非常有趣，可以说是
至少可以这么说。有很多特斯拉、阿里巴巴、Palantir、Cloudflare、Sea Limited。
等。

回顾过去，看看预测有多难，总是很有意思...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r21761/looking_back_at_rstock_users_predictions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r21761/looking_back_at_rstock_users_predictions/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 20:25:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year I made a post telling Reddit/stock users to predict the best performing stock of 2021, and the answers were very interesting to say the least. There was a lot of Tesla, Alibaba, Palantir, Cloudflare, Sea Limited, etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s always interesting to look back and see how hard it is to predict things in the stock market. Alot of mentioned stocks are still down for the year. Oh and btw the reward will be given out early next year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/kgtgh6/predict_the_best_performing_stock_of_2021_and/&quot;&gt;Predict the best performing stock of 2021 and receive a reward. : stocks (reddit.com)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>