<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 12:05:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[戊午]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3x0bn/ew/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3x0bn/ew/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 11:29:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果第一个10万美元是最难的，我是不是应该尝试将大多数投资合并到一个账户中？如果是这样，应该是什么类型的账户？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在了解退休账户之前，我开始在Robinhood（应税）投资。
账户和Bogleheads。学习指数基金和复利是令人兴奋的。
现在我想尽快把大量的钱塞进一个优化的地方。
尽可能快。

罗斯IRA让我眼前一亮，认为非常有价值，但...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3k44y/if_the_first_100000_is_the_hardest_shouldnt_i_try/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3k44y/if_the_first_100000_is_the_hardest_shouldnt_i_try/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 09:30:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I started investing in Robinhood (taxable) before learning about retirement accounts and Bogleheads. Learning about index funds and compound interest was exciting, and now I want to shovel a lot of money into an optimized place as fast as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roth IRA has stood out to me as very valuable, but the big 100k stands out to me too. Besides the Roth IRA, what account can I open to shovel 100k into over the years. Would it just be an IRA? Ideally I would be able to sell my investments in Robinhood, about $15k, to put towards the 100k&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我以这里列出的价格购买以下股票，是不是疯了？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我正在考虑在周一买入以下股票。我几乎肯定会
买入接近52周低点的股票（除非有什么理由我不买？
不该买？）。但在争论是否要买那些接近52周平均水平的股票。
有什么想法？我猜测我不应该买那些接近52周的股票......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3woxa/am_i_crazy_for_buying_the_following_stocks_at_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3woxa/am_i_crazy_for_buying_the_following_stocks_at_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 07:28:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m considering buying the following stocks on Monday. I&amp;#39;ll almost definitely buy the stocks that are near their 52-week low (unless there&amp;#39;s some reason I should not?). But debating whether to buy those near the 52-week average. Thoughts? And guessing I should buy none near their 52-week highs?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEAR 52-WEEK LOW:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CRSP @ &lt;strong&gt;$78&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;Low $77&lt;/strong&gt;; High $220, Avg $128)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DISNEY @ &lt;strong&gt;$147&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;Low $146&lt;/strong&gt;, High $201, Avg $177)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PAYPAL @ &lt;strong&gt;$187&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;Low $184&lt;/strong&gt;, High $310, Avg $257)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VISA @ &lt;strong&gt;$197&lt;/strong&gt; (Low &lt;strong&gt;$192&lt;/strong&gt;, High $252, Avg $222)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEAR 52-WEEK AVERAGE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SOFI @ &lt;strong&gt;$18&lt;/strong&gt; (Low $10, High $28, &lt;strong&gt;Avg $17&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;STARBUCKS &lt;strong&gt;@ $110&lt;/strong&gt; (Low $95, High $126, &lt;strong&gt;Avg $111&lt;/strong&gt;) (Even though it&amp;#39;s near it&amp;#39;s average I&amp;#39;m concerned it won&amp;#39;t drop below $110 this year so I might as well just buy now. Thoughts?)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEAR 52-WEEK HIGH:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AMD @ &lt;strong&gt;$154&lt;/strong&gt; (Low: $72, &lt;strong&gt;High $16&lt;/strong&gt;1, Avg $95)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple @ &lt;strong&gt;$156&lt;/strong&gt; (Low 116, &lt;strong&gt;High $165&lt;/strong&gt;, $136) (Even though it&amp;#39;s near it&amp;#39;s high I&amp;#39;m concerned it won&amp;#39;t drop below $156 this year so I might as well just buy now. Thoughts?)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Microsoft @ &lt;strong&gt;$328&lt;/strong&gt; (Low $209, &lt;strong&gt;High $349&lt;/strong&gt;, Avg $264)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nvidia @ &lt;strong&gt;$315&lt;/strong&gt; (Low $115, &lt;strong&gt;High $346&lt;/strong&gt;, Avg $178)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;QQQ &lt;strong&gt;@ $391&lt;/strong&gt; (Low $289, &lt;strong&gt;High $408&lt;/strong&gt;, Avg $353)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past I&amp;#39;ve just invested in total stock market mutual funds, but now I am looking at some company stocks. Any advice on the stocks I listed would be much appreciated. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一个ELI5的例子，I-Bonds进出HYSA，用于应急基金？]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bogleheads似乎很喜欢I Bonds，所以希望这个问题是恰当的。

情况是这样的。我和S/0上周（第一次）用来自我们HYSA的钱购买了2万的I-Bonds。
购了20K的I-Bonds（第一次），这些钱来自于我们的HYSA。我的想法是在一月初再购买2万（2022年）。
我的想法是在一月初再购买2万（2022年），资金也来自我们的HYSA。

我的目标是要有一个...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3so3o/an_eli5_example_of_ibonds_to_and_from_a_hysa_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3so3o/an_eli5_example_of_ibonds_to_and_from_a_hysa_for/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 07:09:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bogleheads seem to like I Bonds a lot so hope this question is apropos. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Context: S/0 and I purchased 20k of I-Bonds last week (for the first time) with money that came from our HYSA. My idea is to purchase 20k more (for 2022) at the start of January, also funded from our HYSA.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My goal is to have a 9-month EF of 35k made up of I-bonds instead of a 35k EF just sitting in a 0.5% HYSA. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If post-January 2023, f we urgently needed that 35k, or part of it,  do we just redeem the amount(s) we need, at will, into our linked HYSA? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is the best  strategy for doing this?  (We can fund the EF with other monies until we get a system in place and we&amp;#39;re post-12 month periods for the 2021 and 2022 I Bond purchases.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking for simple examples that show the steps  money goes from HYSA to I-Bond then back to HSYA in EF context. Steps to take, pitfalls to avoid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also curious, are  I-Bonds used like an escrow (word choice?) account to pay for short-term horizon goals like paying one&amp;#39;s annual property taxes?  (As opposed to having that money just sit in an HYSA.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗斯IRA与共同基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，伙计们，我终于无债一身轻，目前只需支付租金和杂货。
目前。我将有大约500美元可以放起来，我不需要
担心的问题。如果我做Roth或Vti这样的共同基金，是否更好？你能告诉我
我的优点和缺点？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3nxe7/roth_ira_vs_mutual_fund/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3nxe7/roth_ira_vs_mutual_fund/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 06:30:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey guys, I’m finally debt free and just paying rent and groceries at the moment. I will have about 500 dollars that I can put away that I don’t have to worry about. Is it better if I do a Roth or mutual fund like Vti? Could you tell me the pros and cons?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[让我以任何价格买入，而不是试图为市场计时的心理技巧]]></title><description><![CDATA[当我开始Bogleheads时，我一下子就把我所有的积蓄都倒进去了（大约1万美元）。价格
价格立即下跌，这引起了我相当不确定/紧张的反应。
在我身上。它把我变成了一个市场计时的人，我已经准备好跳槽了。I
我想，如果我当时多等一会儿就好了......

现在我不知道了...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3vqzz/the_mental_trick_that_got_me_to_buy_in_at_any/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3vqzz/the_mental_trick_that_got_me_to_buy_in_at_any/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 06:30:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I started Bogleheads, I dumped in all my savings at once (about $10k). The price immediately went down which invoked quite an uncertain/stressed reaction in me. It turned me into a market timing person and I was ready to bail. I thought, if only I had waited a bit longer...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well now I don&amp;#39;t try to time it, and I just buy whenever I have money to. It&amp;#39;s because of what I tell myself each time I buy. I mentally promise not to sell the newly acquired stock until 1 year has passed since its purchase. I back this up by thinking 1 year is what it takes for long-term capital gains tax to kick in. Although I don&amp;#39;t plan on selling anything for many years, that concept of waiting at least 1 year after each purchase makes me feel very indifferent to whatever happens shortly after I buy in and has allowed me to do it whenever I have money, not when I feel the price is low enough&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我发现这个子后的投资组合]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3w24v/my_portfolio_since_discovering_this_sub/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3w24v/my_portfolio_since_discovering_this_sub/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 05:47:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[散户投资者有哪些方式可以获得VC的投资？]]></title><description><![CDATA[风险投资（以及PE）是相当有趣的金融产品，因为
因为它们与其他类型的机构/产品有一些不同的运作方式。
机构/产品不同。然而，据我所知，风险投资也仍然更像是
一个 "大股票 "的投资工具，而且不那么容易接触到...。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3pllb/what_ways_do_retail_investors_have_to_get/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3pllb/what_ways_do_retail_investors_have_to_get/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 05:22:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Venture Capital (as well as PE) are quite the interesting financial product, due to them having somewhat of a different modus operandi to other types of institutions/products. However, as far as I know, VC also still remains more of a &amp;quot;big ticker&amp;quot; investment vehicle, and not so easily accessible to the average investor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought it&amp;#39;d be interesting to gather as responses to this thread all possible means retail investors can use to get invested (Both financially and &amp;quot;personally&amp;quot;) in VC, whether it&amp;#39;d be by buying shares of a publicly-traded VC (of which there are quite few, afaik) or other means.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please share what you know, could be really interesting!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[反向基金的意义何在？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在Trading 212看到有反向基金。他们的KIID报告显示，他们
几乎一直在亏钱。我只是不明白，亏损的股票有什么意义？
钱。他们似乎是为了应对市场的衰退，但他们的费用
真的很高。高到他们几乎与共同基金相提并论....]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3ji64/whats_the_point_of_inverse_funds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3ji64/whats_the_point_of_inverse_funds/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 04:47:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I saw there are inverse funds at Trading 212. Their KIID reports show that they lose money almost all time. I just don&amp;#39;t get what the point in equity that loses money. It seems that they are made to tackle market downturns, but their fees are really high. So high that they almost match mutual funds. And while they may work in short term, what&amp;#39;s the point in investing them, when something like bonds, REITs (to some extent as they are generally lagging behind stock market) or P2P loans (from my experience, if you analyze performance and invest manually, they seem to be stable and generate at least 9.3% returns even during current crisis. At worst they would be 7% profitable, but that would take something more serious than C19) seem to be profitable during those same times? They seem to be going against general wisdom of buying and holding and since you can&amp;#39;t predict bearish or bullish, even more time that precisely, I&amp;#39;m not really sure what&amp;#39;s the point of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[作为一个美国的投资者，你在国际市场上的股票投资比例是多少？]]></title><description><![CDATA[下面的投票只适用于位于美国境内的投资者。

关于你的投资组合中应该有多少资金分配给美国本土的投资和非美国本土的投资，已经有很多讨论。
分配给美国境内的投资与美国境外的投资。我很想知道
我很想看看这个分论坛中的投资组合如何比较。

在回答这个问题时...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3jdhi/as_a_us_based_investor_what_percentage_of_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3jdhi/as_a_us_based_investor_what_percentage_of_your/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 04:21:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The below poll only applies to investors located within the USA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There has been significant discussion about how much of your portfolio should be allocated to US based investments vs ex-US based investments. I&amp;#39;m  curious to see how the portfolios of those in this subreddit compare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When answering please consider individual stocks as well. Exclude bonds, cash, owned property, etc...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be clear, whatever the outcome of the poll, &lt;strong&gt;I would not consider this to be advice as to how any particular portfolio should be set up&lt;/strong&gt;. I&amp;#39;m just curious about what others have done. Only the future will show whether any particular portfolio was optimal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Edit: I created a similar post last week. However, in that I asked only whether  people invested &amp;quot;significantly&amp;quot; in international markets. I received a  few comments which made me curious about the percentage people invested  in international markets, hence this new poll.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here is that previous poll:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Bogleheads/comments/qz5ktd/as_a_us_based_investor_do_you_invest/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/Bogleheads/comments/qz5ktd/as_a_us_based_investor_do_you_invest/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/poll/r3jdhi&quot;&gt;View Poll&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[网络泡沫 -- 有什么纪录片推荐或轶事吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我试图更好地了解在20世纪90年代和早期，人们对蓬勃发展的科技行业有多少认识。
在20世纪90年代和21世纪初，人们对科技行业的蓬勃发展有多少认识。

它与今天的加密货币繁荣或任何其他（与技术无关的）领域有多大可比性？
领域有多大的可比性？



如果你喜欢编程，似乎很容易做一个 "创业公司"，并且
可以...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3sqf5/the_dotcom_bubble_any_documentary_recommendations/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3sqf5/the_dotcom_bubble_any_documentary_recommendations/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 04:21:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m trying to get a better picture of how much awareness there was of the booming tech industry in the 1990s and early 2000s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How comparable is it to the crypto boom today or any other (tech-unrelated) field?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seemed very easy to just make a &amp;quot;startup&amp;quot; if you were into programming and could actually build something of value. Sure the resources were not really there and the tools were limited. Making a simple website was for example much harder than it is nowadays. However many people could have tried their luck but they didnt. I&amp;#39;m trying to figure out why. Maybe only a few people knew about the upcoming new technology or they heard of it but remained sceptical?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["冠状病毒的新Omicron变体导致轻微的疾病，没有突出的症状。" 

-南非医学协会主席Angelique Coetzee。

星期天的斜坡]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464747781747261450</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464747781747261450</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 03:41:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[最近对美元成本平均法的痴迷是怎么回事？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看到很多新的投资者正在寻找投资他们的储蓄。
每次他们征求意见时，人们都告诉他们用美元成本平均法来分散风险。
分散他们的风险。

我理解对买入顶部的恐惧，但DCA'ing本质上是在赌
赌市场会走低，而平均而言，这...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3ken6/whats_up_with_the_recent_dollar_cost_averaging/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3ken6/whats_up_with_the_recent_dollar_cost_averaging/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 03:41:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I see a lot of new investors who are looking to invest their savings and everytime they ask for advice people tell them to dollar cost average to spread out their risk. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand the fear of buying on top, but DCA&amp;#39;ing is in essence betting against the market to trade lower, and on average that bet is not in your favor. The market has historically shown an uptrend and therefore &amp;quot;spreading out your risks&amp;quot; is hurting your investment. In more cases than not throwing all your money in the market at once would produce better results, without even considering trading fees being part of the equation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand the use of DCA when you have a monthly income and want to invest your savings but not when you have built up a lot of cash and want to spread it out. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would love to hear your take and insights on the subject!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么许多金融产品需要高额的最低投资？]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好。

据我所知，许多金融产品，如PE基金或对冲基金。
对投资者参与的初始投资有很高的要求。
即使是 "机器人顾问"，其最低投资额也经常达到6位数。
尽管他们的目标是较小的投资者。为什么这是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3omci/why_do_many_financial_products_require_high/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3omci/why_do_many_financial_products_require_high/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 02:40:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From what I&amp;#39;ve seen, many financial products, such as PE fonds or hedge funds, have very high requirements on initial investments for investors to participate. Even &amp;quot;roboadvisors&amp;quot; often have minimums that go into the 6-figure range, although they target smaller investors. Why is this the case? Those businesses are essentially pooling money together and then sharing profits of the pool with the investors that make up the pool depending on how much they invested, so wouldn&amp;#39;t every &amp;quot;little bit more&amp;quot; money in the fund help them operate? What are the high minimum requirements for? There has to be some underlying reason, but I&amp;#39;m not sure I really understand it at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你对TQQQ有什么看法？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的投资组合目前是100%的TQQQ，没有保证金。我的游戏计划很简单。
买入每一次下跌的机会。并简单地继续这样做。3%的下跌，再买5个。1%
跌了，再买5个，一直这样下去。你认为这是一个真正好的
的策略，最终会获得成功吗？我没有其他头寸，而且...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3mvha/whats_your_opinion_on_tqqq/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3mvha/whats_your_opinion_on_tqqq/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 01:15:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My portfolio current is 100% TQQQ with no margin. My game plan is quite simple. Buy every, single, dip. And simply continue doing that. 3% down buy 5 more. 1% down, buy another 5 more and on and on. Do you consider this a truly good strategy that will end up in success? I have no other positions and will NOT be needing the money in the longterm future. I expect I will hold this position for 5-10 years than revise my strategy when I&amp;#39;m 26-31 years old. Thank you very much for your time reading this and I appreciate all constructive feedbacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我应该在我的新账户中首先投资什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我16岁，我准备通过TD Ameritrade开一个托管账户。我将会
可以做股票、共同基金和ETF。我有大约2千美元可以投资。什么
我应该从哪些方面入手呢？对所有想法和建议持开放态度。
谢谢你! :)]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3k6pi/whats_the_first_thing_i_should_invest_in_my_new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3k6pi/whats_the_first_thing_i_should_invest_in_my_new/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 01:15:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m 16 and I’m about to open a custodial account through TD Ameritrade.  I’ll be able to do stocks, mutual funds and ETF’s.  I have about $2K I could invest.  What should I start with, any individual stocks?  Open to all ideas and suggestions, thank you! :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[做好派股缩水的准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pi将是下一个COVID变体。当派的变体出现时，全国的派的销量
将在全国范围内急剧下降，因为--不幸的是--公众是如此愚蠢。

下面这些人可能会有麻烦。

-馅饼

-面包店

-馅饼粉

-一些水果（南瓜、大黄、苹果、青柠）。

馅饼可能会成为一个...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3i8oq/be_prepared_for_a_drawdown_in_pie_stocks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3i8oq/be_prepared_for_a_drawdown_in_pie_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 23:59:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pi will be the next COVID variant.  When the pie variant comes out, sales of pies will plummet nationwide, because—unfortunately—the public is that stupid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following could be in trouble:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Pies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Bakeries&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Pie mixes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Some fruit (pumpkin, rhubarb, apples, key lime)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pies will likely become a political issue like masks, and congressmen and women will tweet about the oppression and atrocities of pies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, we can prepare to short pies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just be watching to see what the market has “baked in” to pie stocks (pun strongly intended).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Could be an opportunity to go long cake and doughnut stocks when pie eaters must switch to another delicacy to satisfy their sweet teeth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[专家说，奥米加的担忧应该刺激数百万未接种疫苗的美国人去接种科维德疫苗 --CNN

猜猜看，又是一脸懵逼]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464683327760252932</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464683327760252932</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 23:32:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[提前偿还抵押贷款的好处]]></title><description><![CDATA[我最近在12年内还清了30年的抵押贷款，我的利率是5.5%，我父亲的金融朋友告诉我，我的利率是5.5%。
我父亲在金融界的朋友告诉我，最好是把它付清而不是再融资。

有什么好处？有更多的钱可以投资？安心吗？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3nir2/benefits_of_paying_off_mortgage_early/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3nir2/benefits_of_paying_off_mortgage_early/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 23:32:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I recently paid off a 30 year mortgage in 12 years, I was at 5.5% and told by my Dads friend in finance it would be better to pay it off rather than refinance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are the benefits? More money to invest? Peace of Mind?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我在一家新公司工作已经有一段时间了。他们使用Fidelity。我应该把我现有的账户转到富达还是先锋？目前，我的401k是在一个既不是富达也不是先锋的集团。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3dxim/i_have_been_at_a_new_company_for_a_while_now_they/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3dxim/i_have_been_at_a_new_company_for_a_while_now_they/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 23:32:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么一些ETF和指数不包括英国？]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好，第一次发帖。

我注意到一些有趣的事情，当我看完一些ETF和指数
的时候注意到一些有趣的事情，并注意到有些说 "不包括英国"，而且往往有两个版本，一个是不包括英国，一个是包括英国。
一个不包括英国，一个包括英国。

我觉得这很有趣，为什么投资者会在这两个版本中选择呢？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3fbkh/why_some_etfs_and_indexes_exclude_the_uk/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3fbkh/why_some_etfs_and_indexes_exclude_the_uk/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 23:32:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey all first post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I noticed something interesting when looking through some of the ETF and Index options and noticed that some say &amp;quot;ex UK&amp;quot;, and often have 2 versions, one  that excludes and one that includes the UK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find this quite interesting, why would an investor chose between the two? Is there a measured reason why the UK specifically?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just a little curiosity I had. If anyone could kindly shed some light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the best!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为网络星期一做好准备]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3gidn/getting_ready_for_cyber_monday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3gidn/getting_ready_for_cyber_monday/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 20:27:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于你们这些弱智，我现在吸引了很多掘金者]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3l0w3/now_i_attract_gold_diggers_thanks_to_you_retards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3l0w3/now_i_attract_gold_diggers_thanks_to_you_retards/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 20:27:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约宣布因新的Covid变体而进入紧急状态]]></title><description><![CDATA[你认为市场在周一会有什么反应？
纽约宣布进入紧急状态，旨在增加医院的容量和解决医务人员的
纽约宣布进入紧急状态，旨在增加医院的能力并解决医务人员短缺的问题，因为全国都在准备应对冠状病毒的新欧米茄变体。

新协议将于12月3日生效，该命令将...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3jg1m/new_york_declares_state_of_emergency_due_to_new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3jg1m/new_york_declares_state_of_emergency_due_to_new/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 19:36:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;How do you think the market will react on Monday?New York declared a state of emergency aimed at increasing hospital capacity and addressing medical staffing shortages as the nation braces for the new omicron variant of the coronavirus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new protocols will take effect Dec. 3 and the order will remain in place at least until Jan. 15, when it will be reassessed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The emergency declaration will allow the state Department of Health to limit nonessential and nonurgent hospital procedures in situations where a hospital has less than 10% staffed bed capacity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.yahoo.com/news/york-declares-state-emergency-hike-074026369.html&quot;&gt;https://www.yahoo.com/news/york-declares-state-emergency-hike-074026369.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在家庭饭桌上谈论一个华尔街博彩公司的交易员]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3fh4o/talking_about_a_wallstreetbets_trader_at_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3fh4o/talking_about_a_wallstreetbets_trader_at_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 19:23:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你对市场调整的游戏计划是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[现在，这个子项目最不需要的就是对市场是否会崩溃/向下修正的更多无意义的猜测。
市场是否会崩溃/向下修正。我们没有人可以预测
我们都听说过，选择市场时机是徒劳的。让我们把这种
炒作到最低限度。

对于那些担心这个问题的人...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3fl3r/whats_your_game_plan_for_a_market_correction/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3fl3r/whats_your_game_plan_for_a_market_correction/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 18:52:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, the last thing this sub needs is more pointless speculation on whether or not the market&amp;#39;s going to crash/correct downward. None of us can predict the future and we&amp;#39;ve all heard that timing the market is futile. Let&amp;#39;s keep that speculation to a minimum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who are worried about this though, what positions are you taking? Do you have a small percentage of your portfolio in some type of hedge? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OTM SPY puts? VIX calls? A larger than usual cash position? What are you using and how much is it costing you? What&amp;#39;s the potential pay off?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to stay invested, but I also know that the market is historically overvalued, and I want peace of mind at night with some form of hedge. Any suggestions are welcomed. Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[原油价格昨天下跌13.1%，是有史以来第九大单日跌幅。$WTIC https://t.co/YKYxzbXBCM]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464612670590664706</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464612670590664706</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 18:38:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WSB之美]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r39952/the_beauty_of_wsb/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r39952/the_beauty_of_wsb/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 18:38:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你对晨星的看法如何？]]></title><description><![CDATA[问候。有没有人试过晨星保险费，你对它有什么看法？
你对它有什么看法？

如果你使用过或目前正在使用，你觉得他们的投资组合跟踪如何？
功能如何？诸如 *容易加载和更新头寸 *自定义视图
部门、市场、资产细分等属性的自定义视图

我看到...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3fy7k/whats_your_opinion_of_morningstar/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3fy7k/whats_your_opinion_of_morningstar/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 18:15:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greetings. Have anyone tried the Morningstar premium, and what’s your opinion on it? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you used it or currently use it, how do you like their portfolio tracking functions? Things like 
* ease of loading and updating positions 
* custom view on attributes like sector, market, assets breakdowns&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I saw some fundamentals attributes in the free service, does it provide more robust data on premium?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also what do you all use for portfolio tracking? (I also got personal capital, it’s great for my main portfolio…but hard to set up secondary and mock accounts)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks all!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么会有这么多新的电动汽车公司？]]></title><description><![CDATA[首先，自己造一辆车已经很困难了，而且还得有事情发生。
当你在路上遇到颠簸时就会散架。其次，制造汽车是一项
巨大的事业和资本支出。如果我想开一家新公司，电动汽车将是最后的选择。
电动汽车将是名单上的最后一件事，也许这就是原因？I...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3eer7/why_are_there_so_many_new_electric_vehicle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3eer7/why_are_there_so_many_new_electric_vehicle/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 18:15:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;First of all, it’s hard enough to build a car on it’s own without things falling apart when you hit a bump in the road. Second, to manufacture them is a humongous undertaking and capital expense. If I wanted to start a new company, EV’s would be the very last thing on the list, maybe that’s why? I don’t get it&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是一个完全陌生的人，正在考虑投资PayPal ?]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想过只买1股PayPal的股票，然后从那里开始。我觉得不好
我在23岁的时候才开始，而且可以投资的资金很少，我只有8千块钱
我的整个名字，这很糟糕。我可能会投资300美元，这是我所愿意失去的。
愿意失去的，再多就不负责任了。

任何...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3epsv/im_completely_new_and_thinking_about_investing_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3epsv/im_completely_new_and_thinking_about_investing_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 16:54:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thought about buying just 1 share of PayPal and starting from there. I feel bad that I’m starting late at 23 and with so little to even invest, I’ve only got 8k to my entire name which sucks lol. I’d invest maybe $300, that’s what I’m willing to lose, anything more would be irresponsible. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any advice? Is this a good start? Anything I should know as a complete newbie? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Words words words hopefully my post isn’t taken down for low effort this time&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GGPI (Polestar) vs LCID (Lucid) ???? 有什么想法吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直在考虑在我的月度投资清单中增加一个这样的项目。我是一个
长期投资者，我有一个每月投资的股票清单。

我的第一个问题..... GGPI股票是否只代表Polestar公司？

另外，我想知道你对这两家电动汽车制造商的看法。I...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r38awo/ggpi_polestar_vs_lcid_lucid_any_thoughts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r38awo/ggpi_polestar_vs_lcid_lucid_any_thoughts/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 15:51:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have been thinking of adding one of these to my monthly investing list. I am a long term investor and I have a list of stocks that I invest in every month. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first question..... Does GGPI stock represent Polestar only? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, I  want to know your views on these 2 Electric cars manufacturers. I am thinking of investing regularly in GGPI (Polestar) since they have successfully sold a significant number of cars. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not able to see any strong points favouring Lucid. Please fill me in if I am missing something important about them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know that scaling an electric car business is very difficult as stated by Elon Musk in multiple interviews. Keeping that in consideration I think Polestar has already solved its scaling issue since its parent company is Volve. I can&amp;#39;t say the same for Lucid though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$VIX周五飙升了54%，是历史上第四大单日涨幅（注：$VIX数据可追溯至1990年）。https://t.co/TmZcja9Otd]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464597978778382347</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464597978778382347</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 15:38:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你是如何为你的房子存钱的？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一个23岁的年轻人，有兴趣在我们20多岁到30多岁有孩子之前和我的另一半买房子。
我们在20多岁到30多岁时有了孩子（理想情况下）。有什么建议吗？
这个目标的建议？我听说你可以从你的Roth中拿出钱来支付首付。
这是真的吗？我现在有一笔微薄的储蓄，但正在把...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r37wyd/how_did_you_save_for_your_house/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r37wyd/how_did_you_save_for_your_house/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 15:38:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m a 23 year old interested in buying a house with my significant other before we have kids in our late 20s to early 30s (ideally). Any advice on how to save for this goal? I heard you can take money out of your Roth for a down payment is that true? I have a meager savings right now but am putting away what I can when I can. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在我看来，Vanguard应用程序的更新拿走了Vanguard应用程序最酷的一个功能。只是发泄一下。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我把这个贴在这里是因为Bogle经常与Vanguard交织在一起。
希望你能看到这一切是适用的。这似乎是一个 "为了改变而改变
变化 "的更新，他们被卖了。Vanguard应用程序本周更新。

上一个应用程序的最佳功能是你可以点击你的账户，...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r39ew4/the_vanguard_app_update_took_away_the_coolest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r39ew4/the_vanguard_app_update_took_away_the_coolest/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 14:42:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m posting this here because Bogle is often intertwined with Vanguard, hopefully you see it all as applicable. This seems like a “change for the sake of change” update they were sold on. The Vanguard app updated this week. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best feature of the last app was you could click your account, or performance, and hover/slide with your thumb over the months and see how much has changed in that one month. It was such a simple to use, nice features to see while looking at a chart. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new update? It’s gone. It’s almost as if they hired people who don’t use the app to update it. I’m sure that days is somewhere in the app, but not as cleanly and easily accessible as it was with the thumb/hold/slide feature of the last app. Bummer. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s all&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Omicron的恐慌。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3b8sc/omicron_panic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3b8sc/omicron_panic/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 13:53:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[周一80,000美元的SPY Puts，因为你们这些弱智在今天收盘时都买了看涨期权]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2u2a0/80000_spy_puts_for_monday_bc_all_you_retards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2u2a0/80000_spy_puts_for_monday_bc_all_you_retards/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 10:54:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[对在这次大流行中投资航空公司的想法？]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好，感谢大家的阅读。
世界已经发展成为一个许多事情都在网上完成的地方，而我已经
我决定加入进来，从投资股票开始。所以，对于主要的
问题。在100美元的起始预算下，我应该投资什么。当然，我并不是想通过投资赚取1000美元。
当然，我并不是想通过投资来赚取1000美元...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2wv59/thoughts_on_investing_in_airlines_during_this/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2wv59/thoughts_on_investing_in_airlines_during_this/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 10:54:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey all, and thanks for reading.&lt;br/&gt;
The world has grown to be a place   where so many things are done online, and I&amp;#39;ve decided to join in by  starting with investing in stocks. So, to the main question: What do I  invest in, with a starting budget of $100. I am, of  course, not looking  to make $1000 off of this $100 initial budget, but  seeing any profit  would motivate oneself to invest more in the future. I  was thinking of  investing in popular airlines I could get my hands on,  as with the new COVID variant, these businesses are likely to be worth  much less. So, thoughts on this? And, any other information anyone could  share on the  matter with how to start off?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[注意空头交易者]]></title><description><![CDATA[说到赚钱，我是最不走运的人，我所能做的就是在任何事情上输掉。
任何事情。我接触的所有东西在我购买的瞬间就自动变成了狗屎
100%准确。很明显，我有熊市的能力。

我也有能力瞬间让任何人生气，只是我的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r38uub/attention_short_position_traders/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r38uub/attention_short_position_traders/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 10:42:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am the unluckiest man when it comes to making money, all I can do is lose with anything. Everything I touch automatically turns to shit the instant I buy it with 100% accuracy. It is clear I have the power to bear markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also have the ability to instantly make anyone pissed off just by my mere presence alone. I am a true form of perfect negative energy in the universe, and thus I can be weaponized for hire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use my powers to short anything. Pay me up front, tell me what to buy one share of, and short your way to billions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[无论是否有COVID，哪些股票是强势股？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在这一点上，我只是预计每隔几个月就会有新的变种出现，所以
航空公司和一些行业，如邮轮留置权，对我来说风险太大，不能赌
的风险太大，我不想为了很少的回报而进行赌博。

另一方面，不管有没有COVID的消息，什么股票是好戏？
我个人喜欢Costco，它是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r36gk8/what_stocks_are_strong_plays_with_or_without_covid/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r36gk8/what_stocks_are_strong_plays_with_or_without_covid/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 09:57:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this point, I just anticipate new variants popping up every few months so airlines and some sectors like cruise liens are just too risky for me to gamble on for very little reward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, what stocks are good plays to get with or without COVID news? I personally like Costco which is defensive but also a trade that has sailed from earnings even post &amp;quot;delta&amp;quot;, Roblox which is another great stock in case of shutdowns but also had phenomenal earnings despite things reopening and kids going back to school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What else?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[零售业股票在黑色星期五的强劲销售中下挫。归咎于对Covid变体的恐惧]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五上午，零售股与大盘一起下跌，因为人们担心
新的Covid-19变体在可能强劲的黑色星期五销售中冲击着市场。
周五的销售。美元树(Dollar Tree)(DLTR)的股价，其大部分产品--包括玩具、家庭装饰品、厨房用品--都是在黑色星期五出售的。
该公司的大部分产品--包括玩具、家居装饰品、厨房用品和季节性产品--都是由Dollar Tree公司销售的。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2saq2/retail_stocks_sink_amid_strong_black_friday_sales/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2saq2/retail_stocks_sink_amid_strong_black_friday_sales/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 09:44:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Retail stocks, along with the broader market, were down Friday morning as fears of a new Covid-19 variant hammered the market amid potentially strong Black Friday sales. Shares of Dollar Tree (DLTR), which sells the majority of its products—including toys, home decor, kitchenware, and seasonal goods—was down nearly 4% to $140.81. Nordstrom (JWN) was down 7% at $21.04. Macy’s (M) was off 7.2%. Retailers that struggled to keep up with supply-chain crunches—as noted in their third-quarter earnings—including Kohls (KSS) and Gap (GPS) were down 2.1% to $54.09, and 3.4% to $17.25, respectively. Shares of Abercrombie &amp;amp; Fitch (ANF) were down 3.3% to $37.98.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the most part though, retail stocks have been gaining amid high demand this year. The SPDR S&amp;amp;P Retail exchange-traded fund (XRT) is up 50.05% this year as of Friday morning, still on pace for its best year since 2009, when it rose 74.8%. The ETF is down 2.8% in Friday trading. The Invesco S&amp;amp;P 500 Equal Weight Consumer Discretionary ETF (RCD) is up nearly 25% this year, a sign that despite the previous Delta variant, shoppers are ready to spend their cash and investors recognize the demand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Data from Friday morning showed U.S. consumers are expected to spend $12.9 billion in online sales and have already spent $6.9 billion online during Thanksgiving Day, up 1.1% from last year, according to data from Salesforce. The National Retail Federation estimates 58.1 million people will shop on Small Business Saturday, and 62.8 million will shop online on Cyber Monday. The trade organization projects consumers will spend an average of $997.73, with total spending up as much as 10.5% to $859 billion this season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;U.S. online sales for the first three weeks of November are up 10% year-over-year, $74 billion already spent, as consumers continue to fit in holiday shopping as early as possible over concerns regarding shipping delays and supply chain issues, according to Salesforce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Dow was on track for its worst Black Friday on record, with the S&amp;amp;P 500 and Nasdaq on pace for their worst Black Friday since 2009.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/articles/retail-stocks-sink-amid-strong-black-friday-sales-blame-covid-variant-fears-51637946074?mod=mw_latestnews&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/articles/retail-stocks-sink-amid-strong-black-friday-sales-blame-covid-variant-fears-51637946074?mod=mw_latestnews&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[白痴朋友们，你们是怎么做的？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2xi84/how_do_you_do_fellow_idiots/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2xi84/how_do_you_do_fellow_idiots/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 07:27:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[QQQ与SPY的对比？]]></title><description><![CDATA[考虑投资QQQ或SPY，但不能确定哪个是
适当的一个。或者我应该同时投资于这两种股票吗？

我的DD显示。

- QQQ跟踪纳斯达克100指数，而SPY跟踪标准普尔500指数 - QQQ是
少数行业中的100只股票，主要集中在科技领域。SPY是500
股票，分布在...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2snig/qqq_vs_spy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2snig/qqq_vs_spy/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 07:07:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Considering investing in either QQQ or SPY but can’t determine which is the right one.  Or should I invest in both? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My DD shows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;— QQQ tracks the NASDAQ 100 Index, while SPY tracks the S&amp;amp;P 500 Index
— QQQ is 100 stocks in a handful of sectors, largely concentrated in tech. SPY is 500 stocks spread across all sectors
— looks like QQQ is already inside SPY while SPY is over 1/4 tech.l
— expense fees for QQQ is higher (at 0.20%) meanwhile SPY is cheaper (at 0.09%)
— NASDAQ 100 has beaten the S&amp;amp;P 500 over the past 10 years, generating an average annual return of 20.27% vs 14.26%
— QQQ assets has $201.39B while SPY has $417.28B&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is everyone else’s thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT:  leaning towards VOO (due to low expense ratio) and QQQ.  Since SPY and VOO are so similar I think lower expense ratio is the deciding factor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[血腥的一天，但添加了BA,OKE, CVX,UPS,FDX, VZ]]></title><description><![CDATA[长期看，但利用今天的下跌机会买入一些高质量的
公司。

波音公司。$197.45. (已在238美元处建仓 😕)

奥诺克 61.00美元

雪佛龙112.50美元

联合包裹系统 204.85美元

联邦快递 $237.50

Verizon $51.60

不管是好是坏，我们都会看到结果。

如果你...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2u0pn/bloody_day_but_added_baoke_cvxupsfdx_vz/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2u0pn/bloody_day_but_added_baoke_cvxupsfdx_vz/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 06:29:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking long-term but use today’s selloff opportunities to buy some quality companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boeing.  $197.45. (Already has a position at $238 😕)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oneok         $61.00&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chevron  $112.50&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;United parcel system $204.85&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Federal Express.   $237.50&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verizon        $51.60&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For better or worse we will see what happens. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you purchased some shares today what did you buy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What did you want to buy that you did not buy?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[更多!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2qt2m/more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2qt2m/more/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 05:47:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克反对补贴，特斯拉决定不为德国电池厂提供国家援助]]></title><description><![CDATA[ * 特斯拉撤回对国家资金的申请
 * 马斯克在推特上说，所有的补贴都应该被取消
 * 汽车厂建设进展顺利--经济部
 * 区域资金申请仍在进行中

柏林，11月26日（路透社）--特斯拉（TSLA.O）周五表示，它已经撤回了其
撤回申请...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2xgg0/tesla_decides_against_state_aid_for_german/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2xgg0/tesla_decides_against_state_aid_for_german/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 03:52:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tesla withdraws application for state funding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All subsidies should be eliminated, Musk tweets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Car plant construction progressing well - economy ministry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regional funding application still underway&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BERLIN, Nov 26 (Reuters) - Tesla (TSLA.O) said on Friday it has withdrawn its application for state aid for its planned battery factory near Berlin as CEO Elon Musk declared the electric vehicle maker opposed all subsidies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The European Union in January approved a plan that included giving state aid to Tesla, BMW (BMWG.DE) and others to support production of electric vehicle batteries and help the bloc to reduce imports from industry leader China.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla was expected to receive 1.14 billion euros ($1.28 billion) in EU funding for its battery plant in Gruenheide, Brandenburg under the plan, with a final decision likely by the end of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Tesla has informed the Federal Ministry of Economics and the Brandenburg Ministry of Economics... it is withdrawing its IPCEI application for state funding for the battery factory in Grünheide,&amp;quot; a Tesla spokesperson said, referring to European subsidies allocated to so-called &amp;#39;Important Projects of Common European Interest&amp;#39;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Construction plans for the plant would not be affected by the decision, the spokesperson said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;It has always been Tesla’s view that all subsidies should be eliminated,&amp;quot; Musk posted on Twitter in response to a tweet by another user after Tesla said it had withdrawn its funding application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;But that must include the massive subsidies for oil &amp;amp; gas. For some reason, governments don’t want to do that...,&amp;quot; Musk added, deviating from the subject of the factory grant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla itself is investing 5 billion euros in the battery plant, according to German economy ministry estimates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, construction of a car production site alongside the battery plant, which Tesla has begun building under pre-approval permits while it awaits final approval from the regional government, has made good progress in the last few weeks, a spokesperson for the federal economy ministry said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The electric vehicle maker also applied in November 2020 for regional funding from Brandenburg, according to the regional government&amp;#39;s website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Brandenburg economy ministry spokesperson said this application had not been withdrawn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The amount Tesla applied for is undisclosed, but investments worth over 100 million euros are generally given 6.8% of their value, the website says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The latest round of online consultations for the public to express environmental and other concerns about the car factory and battery plant closed last week and Tesla CEO Elon Musk has said he hopes to formally begin production by the end of the year and then ramp up as quickly as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Musk has made his irritation for German laws and processes known, saying in a letter to authorities in April that the country&amp;#39;s complex planning requirements were at odds with the urgency needed to fight climate change. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-withdrew-state-funding-application-german-battery-plant-economy-ministry-2021-11-26/&quot;&gt;https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-withdrew-state-funding-application-german-battery-plant-economy-ministry-2021-11-26/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[https://t.co/WYYPr7IR71]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464429941706182667</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464429941706182667</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 03:40:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[凯西-伍德在最新的CNBC采访中把ARKK的目标价格更新为~440]]></title><description><![CDATA[以前的目标，~310，5年内每年15%。

新目标，~440，5年内达到4倍，或5年内每年达到33%。

或以表格形式显示

今天 2022 2023 2024 2025 2026 15% 155 178 205 236 271 312 33% 108 144 191 254
338 449]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2gt66/cathie_wood_updates_price_target_for_arkk_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2gt66/cathie_wood_updates_price_target_for_arkk_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 03:23:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous target, ~310, 15% per year for 5 years&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New Target, ~440, 4x in 5 years or 33% per year for 5 years&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or in table format&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Today&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2022&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2023&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2024&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2025&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2026&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;15%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;155&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;178&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;205&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;236&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;271&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;312&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;33%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;108&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;144&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;191&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;254&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;338&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;449&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bogleheads的方法只是针对富人的吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我对长期投资感兴趣，并最终来到这里，但我只是看到
人们投入40多万，最后得到100万。我没有那么多钱可以
我没有那么多钱投资，我有机会用小钱试试吗？比如说更少。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r30qt2/is_bogleheads_method_just_for_rich_people/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r30qt2/is_bogleheads_method_just_for_rich_people/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 02:56:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m interested in investing money for long term and end up here, but I just see people who put 400k+ and end with a million. I don&amp;#39;t have that much money to invest, do I have a chance to try with little money? Like more little.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$PSFE Paysafe最近下跌了50%。反弹交易的好机会？]]></title><description><![CDATA[跌幅如此之大，似乎是因为他们调整后的指引？这似乎是一个
跌幅极大，而且低于分析师目标价的下限。它正在
在日线图上也出现了看涨的rsi背离。

谁能告诉我股价在这里发生了什么？看起来像
a...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2r9dk/psfe_paysafe_down_50_recently_good_opportunity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2r9dk/psfe_paysafe_down_50_recently_good_opportunity/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 02:40:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Down so dramatically seemingly because of their adjusted guidance? Seems like an extreme drop and it&amp;#39;s below the lower band of analyst price targets. It&amp;#39;s putting in a bullish rsi divergence on the daily chart too. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can someone fill me in on what&amp;#39;s going on with the stock price here? Looks like a good buying opportunity to me but I haven&amp;#39;t done much research yet. Hoping one of you has been looking into this and can shed some light. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>