<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 15:25:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[葡萄牙规定，你的老板在工作时间之外与你联系是非法的 https://t.co/2RBNwvR264]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459341980719362049</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459341980719362049</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 14:42:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你对什么股票（不经常在这里讨论）最有信心？]]></title><description><![CDATA[就像它所要求的那样，请让我知道......本周末将做dd，所以我对检查一些我可能错过的股票感兴趣。
有兴趣看看我可能错过的一些股票。

除了你的股票之外，请随时提供任何原因。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsqnak/what_stock_not_discussed_here_often_do_you_have/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsqnak/what_stock_not_discussed_here_often_do_you_have/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 13:28:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just like it asks, please let me know...will be doing dd this weekend and so am interested in checking out some stocks I may have missed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please feel free to provide any reasons why in addition to your stock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[呃......。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsru0w/uhhh/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsru0w/uhhh/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 11:19:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我被骗了

https://t.co/89XBPLUCYT]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459327267184779277</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459327267184779277</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 09:38:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[用硼砂洗衣服--不是洗身体。https://t.co/vDmqO5E8CI]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459288322749210639</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459288322749210639</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 09:38:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这是你们中的哪一个猿人？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsu5ll/which_one_of_you_apes_is_this/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsu5ll/which_one_of_you_apes_is_this/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 09:22:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么媒体对恒大的违约行为撒谎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[以下是一些文章，声称恒大确实错过了他们的债券付款。

https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.nytimes.com/2021/11/10/business/evergrande-bond-deadline.amp.html

https://www.reuters.com/business/several-bondholders-china-evergrande-receive-overdue-bond-coupon-payments-media-2021...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsping/why_is_the_media_lying_about_evergrandes_default/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsping/why_is_the_media_lying_about_evergrandes_default/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 08:43:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are some articles claiming that evergrande has did miss their bond payment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.nytimes.com/2021/11/10/business/evergrande-bond-deadline.amp.html&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.nytimes.com/2021/11/10/business/evergrande-bond-deadline.amp.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/business/several-bondholders-china-evergrande-receive-overdue-bond-coupon-payments-media-2021-11-11/&quot;&gt;https://www.reuters.com/business/several-bondholders-china-evergrande-receive-overdue-bond-coupon-payments-media-2021-11-11/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.nytimes.com/2021/10/28/business/evergrande-bond-payment.amp.html&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.nytimes.com/2021/10/28/business/evergrande-bond-payment.amp.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the articles states this which I thought was interesting:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;{Evergrande’s challenges could spread outside of China as well, as they ripple through global financial markets. On Monday, the Federal Reserve said troubles in China’s property sector could threaten the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Given the size of China’s economy and financial system as well as its extensive trade linkages with the rest of the world, financial stresses in China could strain global financial markets through a deterioration of risk sentiment, pose risks to global economic growth, and affect the United States,” the Fed said in its twice-yearly update on the American financial system.} &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EVERGRANDE DID DEFAULT:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.yahoo.com/now/evergrande-officially-defaulted-dmsa-preparing-161200818.html&quot;&gt;https://www.yahoo.com/now/evergrande-officially-defaulted-dmsa-preparing-161200818.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am seriously concerned on the reasons why evergrande’s default is being silenced, and what this means for the market as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在短短一个多月内从400美元到51000美元]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qssi74/from_400_to_51k_in_just_over_a_month/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qssi74/from_400_to_51k_in_just_over_a_month/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 07:15:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[还有人讨厌股票分析文章的点击率标题吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我正在使用M1金融系统来寻找随机的股票代码，然后我注意到了一件事。
我注意到有件事让我很不爽，那就是他们在说股票上涨或下跌时使用的整个戏剧性语言。
他们用整个戏剧性的语言来说明一只股票的涨跌。

如果一只股票上涨了一美元或5%左右，他们就会说一些愚蠢的废话，如："这只股票今天大涨。
这只股票今天大涨。"或者...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsofa3/anyone_else_hate_the_click_bait_titles_for_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsofa3/anyone_else_hate_the_click_bait_titles_for_stock/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 06:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was using M1 finance to just look around for random stocks tickers and something I noticed that really bugged me, is the whole dramatic language they use to say a stock went up or down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If a stock goes up by a dollar or around 5%, they say dumb crap like, &amp;quot;this stock has surged today.&amp;quot; or ascended, or spiked, or is sky rocketing. But like, the stock I was looking at had an ipo price of $12 and now it&amp;#39;s $4 and its apparently &amp;quot;skyrocketing.&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;like no, no it&amp;#39;s not. if I&amp;#39;m an investor from day one, and I read the phrase skyrocket, I&amp;#39;m thinking this thing is like $100 a share or something. Like the people who write these articles, I don&amp;#39;t know how they get paid for this. These analysts are paid to type nonsense every single day, but they aren&amp;#39;t paid to be accurate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was wondering if there was some enforced rules to these fancy adjectives. Because i see it with every company. They say plummet, or downward spiral, or falling when a company goes down even 1%, but jettisoned, surged, or sky rocket when it&amp;#39;s doing mildly good. I think it&amp;#39;s meant to keep people nervous and excited so people keep buying and selling and eventually make no money in the end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[戳穿通货膨胀阴谋论的漏洞，作者：Larry Swedroe]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsrov3/poking_holes_in_the_inflation_conspiracy_theory/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsrov3/poking_holes_in_the_inflation_conspiracy_theory/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 06:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[巨大的F***k Robinhood能量!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的$aapl 150看涨期权今天到期，在没有通知的情况下，他们关闭了我的
他们在下午3:02关闭了我的仓位，当时股价为149.76美元。当然，它在下午3:30之前反弹到
到下午3:30的时候，钱已经涨到了150.40美元。

我立即打电话给支持部门，在绕了一圈后，他们在收盘后给我回电说
市场关闭后，他们给我回电话说...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsllfi/big_fk_robinhood_energy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsllfi/big_fk_robinhood_energy/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 04:51:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I had $aapl 150 calls expiring today and WITHOUT notice they closed my position at 3:02pm when the stock was $149.76. And of course it rallied into the money by as much as $150.40 by 3:30pm!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I immediately called support and after a run around they called me back after the market closed saying that the risk assessment team made the decision to close. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why wouldn’t they send a notification ahead of time stating that by a certain time they would close the position? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nothing… They sold right before the stock rallied into close. The CSR offered zero condolences or any modicum of help. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this is another PSA: Fuck Robinhood!! I hope their stock burns to the ground, I’m withdrawing all my funds and moving to a better platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: Lesson learned, yes I’m retarded and don’t know how to read. More or less just venting to my fellow apes. For those who are unaware of this, we’ll now you know! Thank you for the lashing, but still fuck RH!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是今天（2021年11月12日，星期五）的市场回顾]]></title><description><![CDATA[心理市场回顾 - 2021年11月12日，星期五

周五股市稳步上扬，市场参与者继续平衡
在通胀上升的情况下，企业盈利好于预期。标准普尔500指数（SPY）
收盘上涨0.75%，科技股重仓的纳斯达克指数（QQQ）上涨1.05%，道琼斯...
琼斯...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsmfuq/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_friday_november/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsmfuq/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_friday_november/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 03:24:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Friday, November 12, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks advanced firmly on Friday, with market participants continuing to balance better-than-expected corporate earnings amid rising inflation. The S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) closed the day 0.75% higher, the tech-heavy Nasdaq (QQQ) rose 1.05%, and the Dow Jones (DIA) broke a three day losing streak to finish 0.51% higher. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of Friday’s close, the SPY closed the week 0.4% lower following volatility after the release of the October Consumer Price Index. However, after five consecutive weeks of gains, the market remains marginally below previous all-time highs. The QQQ closed the week 0.91% lower, while the DIA closed the week 0.97% lower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the Labor Department released the monthly Consumer Price Index, which showed prices soared 6.2% in a year-on-year period, accelerating from September’s 5.4% YoY rate, and higher than the 5.9% expected. This represents that fastest pace of inflationary expansion since 1990, though one has to take into account easy comparisons to last year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The staying power and magnitude of inflationary pressures has, perhaps, become the central question for market participants, with companies across the board reporting rising input costs and price hikes passed on to the consumers to preserve margins. While Q3 earning results have robustly demonstrated that companies in the SPY were largely able to navigate these cost pressures, the possibility remains that if inflation runs hotter than expected for longer than expected, it could begin to hamper consumer demand. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While a rise in inflation was expected, the pace of the increase surprised to the upside. If the pace of increase is not moderated soon, it carries meaningful implications for corporations, consumers, and the Federal Reserve. As input costs rise, companies will pass the increase in cost to consumers to preserve their bottom line, who will be forced to pay the higher prices. The Fed would then be forced to step in and rise interest rates, which will makes the cost to borrow money more expensive, which means people and companies will likely spend less, leading to a fall in demand for goods and services. A rise in interest rates would particularly hurt high P/E tech stocks that have been flying in the last two years, as these companies rely on borrowing to fund their aggressive expansion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still, the Federal Reserve and many economists have reaffirmed that the inflationary pressures are transitory, caused by pandemic-era disruptions in global trade and will eventually ease, albeit while likely settling at a higher level than had been present before the pandemic. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gabriela Santos, Global Market Strategist at JP Morgan, said “Inflation should moderate. We’re talking about settling at 2%, 2.5% over the course of the next 12 months. So we&amp;#39;re still talking about real wage gains, and that&amp;#39;s extremely supportive, certainly of people&amp;#39;s livelihoods, but also of consumption and hence the economy overall. We do expect a big re-acceleration in growth starting this quarter and throughout next year, [and] 5% average growth just over the next three quarters. So we would characterize this not as stagflation, but as reflation. And that difference is, reflation is actually quite good for earnings growth and quite good for the stock market, especially cyclical sectors.&amp;quot; So far, expectations are that the Fed will step in sometime mid-2022 to raise interest rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Rivian (RIVN), which is backed by Ford and Amazon,  continue to be on absolute fire. The company, which is expected to lose $1.28 billion on no more than $1 million in revenue this quarter, now has a market cap of more than $100 billion. For perspective, they are now the fourth largest automaker in the world by market cap. I’m not a stickler for valuation, but this is absolute insanity and unsustainable. The company has not started production and is already priced to perfection, which they are bound to hit a snag with. I don’t think this price is sustainable. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The University of Michigan’s closely monitored Consumer Sentiment survey showed the consumer sentiment index decreased to 66.8 from 71.7 in October, missing estimates of 72.5. Waning confidence reflects “ an escalating inflation rate and the growing belief among consumers that no effective policies have yet been developed to reduce the damage from surging inflation,” Richard Curtin, director of the survey, said in a statement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Snap (SNAP) investor sued the social media company alleging it downplayed how Apple’s (AAPL) change in privacy would affect revenue. Remember, the stock plummeted 25% after an earnings miss, citing Apple’s changes as hampering ad revenue. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After more than a decade of explosive growth, China&amp;#39;s Singles&amp;#39; Day, the world&amp;#39;s biggest online shopping fest, is losing its gloss and bracing for more modest growth in coming years, hurt by a slower economy and tighter regulatory scrutiny. Alibaba (BABA) said on Friday its sales - or gross merchandise value (GMV) - during the 11 day event grew 8.5%, the slowest rate ever and the first time it came under double-digits growth. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Friday said it rejected an exchange-traded fund from VanEck that would have tracked Bitc… spot prices directly. This would have stood in contrast to the ProShares ETF (BITO), which was approved and which only tracks futures rather than prices directly.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current stock price was written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Affirm (AFRM) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $140 to $185 at Overweight. Stock currently around $149&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equifax (EFX) target raised by Needham &amp;amp; Co from $295 to $335 at Buy. Stock currently around $280&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nice (NICE) with two target raises. Stock currently around $312

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Citigroup from $328 to $364 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Royal Bank of Canada from $325 to $368 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NXP Semiconductors (NXPI) target raised by KeyCorp from $250 to $255 at Overweight. Stock currently around $218&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Finance Technologies (SOFI) target raised by Jefferies Financial from $4 to $26 at Buy. Stock currently around $23&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tapestry (TPR) with a host of target raises. Average price target $55 at Overweight. Stock currently around $45&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weibo (WB) target raised by Citigroup from $63 to $66 at Buy. Stock currently around $46&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“In my view, the biggest investment risk is not the volatility of prices, but whether you will suffer a permanent loss of capital. Not only is the mere drop in stock prices not risk, but it is an opportunity. Where else do you look for cheap stocks?” - Li Lu&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[感谢大家，我将在圣诞节给我妻子买一辆新的特斯拉。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsiab0/thanks_to_you_all_im_buying_my_wife_a_new_tesla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsiab0/thanks_to_you_all_im_buying_my_wife_a_new_tesla/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 01:39:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[富裕的年轻投资者认为他们父母所依赖的财富管理公司没有用处]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 富裕的千禧一代对财务顾问。谢谢你的高尔夫邀请，但你
> 不能投资我的钱

华尔街日报》最近写了一篇关于这个问题的文章。

你有没有想过要去找理财师？也许你试过--结果是什么？
经验？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qslgdm/wealthy_young_investors_dont_see_use_for_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qslgdm/wealthy_young_investors_dont_see_use_for_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 01:39:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rich Millennials to Financial Advisers: Thanks for the Golf Invite, but You Can’t Invest My Money&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WSJ recently wrote an article about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever thought of going to money managers? Maybe you tried - what was the expirince?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[工人辞职人数创新高，消费者情绪创10年新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[令人着迷的是，工人们正以迅猛的速度辞去工作，但同时消费者也没有信心。
同时，消费者也没有那么自信。在较高的工资和最近的通货膨胀之间可能存在一个滞后。
导致这些问题的原因可能是较高的工资和最近的房价上涨之间的滞后。

在第四季度看到收入高峰，然后再降低，这并不奇怪。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsn6yl/workers_quit_jobs_in_record_numbers_as_consumer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsn6yl/workers_quit_jobs_in_record_numbers_as_consumer/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 01:39:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Its fascinating to see how workers are quitting their jobs at a torrid pace but also that consumers are not being as confident. There could be a lag between the higher wages and the more recent porce increases causing these issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would not be surprised to see peak earnings in Q4 before lower confidence and higher prices really set into corporate earnings over the next year or so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/consumer-sentiment-hits-10-year-low-while-workers-quit-jobs-in-record-numbers.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/consumer-sentiment-hits-10-year-low-while-workers-quit-jobs-in-record-numbers.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[让我们再做一次]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsm8mh/lets_do_it_again/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsm8mh/lets_do_it_again/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 01:39:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我们能谈谈GameStop吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我对投资游戏有点陌生，所以如果我错过了关于这个问题的讨论，我很抱歉。
这方面的讨论。我在今年早些时候关注了GameStoo的传奇故事，最近开始
又开始关注支持它的两个大的subreddits。

根据我的理解，理论上说，短线实际上从未卖出...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsje5u/can_we_talk_about_gamestop/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsje5u/can_we_talk_about_gamestop/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:31:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m a bit new to the investing game so my apologies if I missed the discussions on this. I followed the GameStoo saga earlier this year and recently started looking again at the two big subreddits supporting it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To my understanding, the theory goes that the shorts never actually sold their positions (because they would have gone bankrupt), but instead used all sorts of trickery to delay and avoid. Some ppl, have caught on to this and are determined to hold the stock such that when the chickens come home to roost and the shorts are forced to close, will trigger, they’ll be able to skyrocket the price. I’ve seen claims that a single share could be worth millions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This of course sounds fantastical and far-fetched but would someone mind explaining how seemingly so many ppl have adopted this belief and are all-in on a once hated retail store? IE where are they wrong in their analysis? Is it just a case of the human factor not being realized; that once the price jumps a bit, ppl will start to sell, so the idea of holding into the 1000s plus is unrealistic?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我仍然微笑着]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsa3fj/im_still_smiling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsa3fj/im_still_smiling/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:31:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[刚刚在Discord上点击了一个骗局，我的MetaMask钱包被洗劫一空。进入周末的好方法。

我是NGMI]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459281438172491778</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459281438172491778</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 23:38:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta和微软宣布合作，整合Workplace和Teams]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/10/meta-and-microsoft-announce-partnership-to-integrate-workplace-and-teams.html

前身为Facebook的Meta公司宣布了一项伙伴关系，将
允许客户将工作场所与微软团队整合。

Meta公司和微软之间的合作关系...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsm2ow/meta_and_microsoft_announce_partnership_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsm2ow/meta_and_microsoft_announce_partnership_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 23:38:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/10/meta-and-microsoft-announce-partnership-to-integrate-workplace-and-teams.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2021/11/10/meta-and-microsoft-announce-partnership-to-integrate-workplace-and-teams.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meta, the company formerly known as Facebook, announced a partnership that will allow customers to integrate Workplace with Microsoft Teams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The partnership between Meta and Microsoft brings together two rivals that compete in the market of enterprise communication software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The partnership could prove most beneficial to Meta, whose Workplace service lags drastically behind its competitors in terms of users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is definitely a good partnership news that will benefit both companies. Microsoft teams is gaining more marketshare as it integrates into other softwares. The partnership could prove most beneficial to Meta as teams could help to boost its Workplace enterprise social network software users. Both stocks should be in the portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pssst，需要一些绿色的东西吗，先生？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsdeyo/pssst_need_some_greens_sir/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsdeyo/pssst_need_some_greens_sir/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 22:46:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为你的应急基金投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好! 前几天我在听《千禧年投资》播客的一集。
有一天。在这一集里，主持人采访了克里斯-卡瓦亚。克里斯提出的
争论说，最好是投资你的应急基金，而不是将其作为
现金。他建议将88%的资金投资于债券，另外12%的资金投资于银行账户。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsha3j/investing_your_emergency_fund/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsha3j/investing_your_emergency_fund/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 22:34:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello! I was listening to an episode of The Millenial Investing podcast the other day. In this episode, the host interviews Chris Kawaja. Chris makes the argument that it is better to invest your emergency fund rather than keep it as cash. He proposes investing 88% in bonds and the other 12% in a S&amp;amp;P 500 index fund. Historically, this combination has kept up or beaten inflation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you guys think? Anyone take this approach?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[关于迪士尼股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，我在两周前套现了，现在正坐在一大笔现金上等待合适的机会。
等待合适的机会。现在，随着迪斯尼在过去5天内大幅下跌15美元
过去5天里，你们认为将所有的2万块钱投资到DIS上怎么样？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsgldu/about_disney_stocks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsgldu/about_disney_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 22:14:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I cashed out about 2 weeks ago and a sitting on a large sum of cash waiting for the right opportunity. Right now with the huge 15$ drop of Disney in the past 5 days, what do you guys think about investing all 20k into DIS?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这个牛市与其他任何牛市一样......或者说是这样？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我从几年前就开始投资，所以我不知道2008年以前的投资感觉如何。
2008年以前的投资。我看到很多 "PE不再重要"，"这个周期是
不同 "之类的评论，我首先想到的是把它们当作 "不重要 "来抛弃。
我的第一个想法是把它们当作没有经验的想法，这些人和我一样，不知道什么是......。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsbs5s/this_bull_market_is_like_any_other_or_is_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsbs5s/this_bull_market_is_like_any_other_or_is_it/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 22:14:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been investing since a few years, so I have no idea of how it felt to invest pre 2008. I see a lot of &amp;#39;PE doesn&amp;#39;t matter anymore&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;this cycle is different&amp;#39; and that kind of comments, and my first thought is to discard them as inexperienced thoughts from people who, like me, don&amp;#39;t know what a serious bear market feels like. But I can&amp;#39;t pass on one thought: the information has changed. Before 2008, regular folks had access to a completely different kind of information than today. I don&amp;#39;t know how the landscape changed for institutions sinc ethen, maybe they already had access to the info we use nowadays to base our decisions, maybe they even had algo trading already, but the internet was so different that it must have made a tremendous impact for them as well. It seems a relevant discussion to be had, so I&amp;#39;m asking you: do you believe this time is different? If you don&amp;#39;t, what&amp;#39;s your counter argument?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[东芝将一分为三]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，企业集团正在解体，就像无人问津一样。首先是通用电气
现在是通用电气的直接竞争对手东芝，其根源可以追溯到1875年。此外
此外，我们还有强生公司的分拆。我们几乎应该期待
西门子也会采取同样的做法
途径。https://www.wsj.com/articles/toshiba...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsd3uu/toshiba_to_split_into_three/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsd3uu/toshiba_to_split_into_three/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 21:53:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conglomerates are breaking up like it&amp;#39;s nobody&amp;#39;s business this week. First GE and now a direct GE-competitor, Toshiba, whose roots date back to 1875. In addition we have the Johnson and Johnson s split. We should almost expect Siemens to follow the same path.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/toshiba-like-ge-plans-to-split-into-three-parts-11636700609?mod=hp_lead_pos3&quot;&gt;https://www.wsj.com/articles/toshiba-like-ge-plans-to-split-into-three-parts-11636700609?mod=hp_lead_pos3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这只是交易员基本技能的一部分]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsc3lg/its_just_a_part_of_basic_trader_skillset/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsc3lg/its_just_a_part_of_basic_trader_skillset/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 20:23:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[什么是最省税的Vanguard经纪基金？]]></title><description><![CDATA[就目前而言，我的现金有点太多了。目前我的IRA
和401k。什么是最有效的Vanguard非税收优惠基金？我在想
我在想一个简单的80/20的VTI/VXUS。债券现在不做任何事情，所以没有
入这些基金也没有用。

我有一个迫在眉睫的担忧，杰克...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs9id6/what_are_the_most_tax_efficient_vanguard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs9id6/what_are_the_most_tax_efficient_vanguard/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 18:00:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of right now, I have a little too much in cash.  Currently maxing out my IRA and 401k.  What are the most efficient Vanguard non-tax advantaged funds? I was thinking a simple 80/20 VTI/VXUS.  Bonds aren&amp;#39;t doing anything right now, so no use getting into those.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One looming concern I have, and Jack Bogle talks about this in his book, is &amp;quot;reversion of the mean&amp;quot;.  He even said in an interview that sometimes you do have to time the market.  But that&amp;#39;s just my personal choice, and I am going to choose to wait until the reversion of the mean to invest in a non-tax advantaged account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So thoughts on taxable ETFs? Reinvest dividends? Use dividends to pay taxes?  Are VTI and VXUS good choices?  Is skipping bonds completely a bad choice?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你是如何说服自己卖掉你最后的个人股票赢家，去完成3个基金的投资组合？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我几乎完全是一个拥有4个基金（VOO、VXUS、VGIT、TIP）的Bogelhead。但我
仍然坚持着过去的几个赢家。amzn, aapl, msft, zen, prgfx。
你是如何证明扣动扳机的？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsdb10/how_did_you_convince_yourself_to_sell_your_last/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsdb10/how_did_you_convince_yourself_to_sell_your_last/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 17:33:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am almost completely a Bogelhead with a 4-fund (VOO, VXUS, VGIT, TIP). But I still hang on to a couple winners from the past: AMZN, AAPL, MSFT, ZEN, PRGFX. How did you justify pulling the trigger?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[自闭症的赌注]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs96pb/autism_bets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs96pb/autism_bets/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 17:04:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[天价通胀不是因为 "供应链瓶颈"，而是因为印了太多的钱]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看到这些天有很多文章和帖子都在谈论供应链问题。
不管是关于购买一个集装箱有多贵，还是说
或航运港口没有足够的空间，或没有足够的
卡车司机，等等。

然而，这些都是微观层面的症状。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsdxg3/sky_high_inflation_isnt_due_to_supply_chain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsdxg3/sky_high_inflation_isnt_due_to_supply_chain/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 17:04:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I see a lot of articles and posts these days talking about supply chain issues: whether it&amp;#39;s about how expensive it is to buy a shipping container, or that there isn&amp;#39;t enough space at shipping ports, or that there aren&amp;#39;t enough truckers, etc. etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, these are all micro-level symptoms of a macro-level problem. Don&amp;#39;t miss the forest for the trees. Journalists need to write something new every day (or every hour it seems), even if there isn&amp;#39;t anything new to say. Which leads to a lot of noise that clouds your mind from making sense of what is really happening in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my view, the problem is clear: governments overdid it with stimulus. Unlike the 2008 Global Financial Crisis where policymakers did too little and acted too slow, this time around governments decided to err on the side of doing too much too quickly. If you look at consumer spending on FRED, it didn&amp;#39;t just fully recovery from the 2020 shock, it&amp;#39;s arguably on a stronger trajectory than it otherwise would be without the pandemic! At the same time, unemployment is still high and labor force participation is dreadfully low! The Fed created such a tremendous wealth effect, people are earning multiple years worth of stock market returns in the span of months. I&amp;#39;m not surprised many people are taking career breaks or retiring early. So why do we have red hot inflation? Because we&amp;#39;re printing more money and making less things, it&amp;#39;s that simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The inflation problem highlights how difficult it is to be a policymaker. On one hand, you don&amp;#39;t want to under spend and risk seeing long-term economic scarring, but if you stimulate too much, you risk fueling inflation as well as asset price bubbles. The other factor at play is the politicization of economic policy. You&amp;#39;re everyone&amp;#39;s favorite politician when you&amp;#39;re fueling spending, but it&amp;#39;s hard to get reelected when you advocate for cutbacks. Prudent policymaking requires spending when times are bad, and building reserves when times are good - politicians have forgot about the latter half of that equation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在目前的价格下，你会在V、MA和PYPL之间选择哪个？]]></title><description><![CDATA[支付宝的PE为48.6

万事达卡为43.6

Visa为37.4

虽然单纯从PE的角度来看，Paypal是最昂贵的，但我更倾向于他们，因为他们在过去的历史中一直是最受欢迎的。
我更倾向于他们，因为他们在历史上有更高的收入增长。
与其他两家相比，他们有更高的收入增长，而且他们是多元化的，或正试图多元化的
到诸如...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs4tiv/at_current_prices_which_would_you_choose_between/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs4tiv/at_current_prices_which_would_you_choose_between/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:59:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paypal at PE of 48.6&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mastercard at 43.6&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Visa at 37.4&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Paypal is the most expensive purely from PE point of view, I&amp;#39;m leaning more towards them because they&amp;#39;ve historically had higher revenue growth compared to the other two and they&amp;#39;re diversified or are trying to diversity into things like crypto, stock broker, etc. Also Paypal is around 33% off from its 52 week high, which is far lower than V or MA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you had to pick one out of these 3? Which would you buy at today&amp;#39;s prices?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[收入（TTM）...
里维安：0美元
通用汽车：1310亿美元
福特：1350亿美元

净收入（TTM）...
里维安：-16亿美元
通用汽车：111亿美元
福特：29亿美元

市值...
里维安：1050亿美元
通用汽车：900亿美元
福特：780亿美元

$RIVN $GM $F

数据来自@ycharts https://t.co/xlR1mX989K]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459153703320043523</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459153703320043523</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:47:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[卖出Vanguard ETFs(VTI)并转移到Vanguard共同基金(VTSAX)]]></title><description><![CDATA[我开了一个非税收优惠的Vanguard账户，与我的退休账户分开。
账户。我的Vanguard账户只是用于个人投资。

我不想为我的3个基金投资组合分配足够的资金以满足3千美元的最低限额，以购买海军司令部的股份。
3个基金组合。

随着时间的推移或更多的钱变得可用，我是否应该被...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs99dt/sell_vanguard_etfs_vti_and_move_to_vanguard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs99dt/sell_vanguard_etfs_vti_and_move_to_vanguard/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:47:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I opened a non tax advantaged Vanguard account separate from my retirement accounts. My Vanguard account is just for personal investing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t want to allot enough to meet the $3k minimums for admiral shares for my 3 fund portfolio. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As time goes on or more money becomes available should I being selling the ETFs and use the proceeds to move my 3 fund portfolio to Vanguard mutual funds instead of ETFs?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有道理。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsbj9q/makes_sense/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsbj9q/makes_sense/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你的妻子，你妻子的男友，你的股票爆炸后的你]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs599y/your_wife_your_wifes_bf_you_after_your_stocks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs599y/your_wife_your_wifes_bf_you_after_your_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你希望在你开始投资之前有人告诉你什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一个初级投资者，目前正在学习所有的基础知识，并尽力教育自己。
我想知道：你们认为有哪些重要的概念/方法/工具导致了你的成功？
导致你们成功的一些重要概念/方法/工具？最重要的是。
什么导致了你最大的失败，你是如何恢复的？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsavil/what_do_you_wish_someone_told_you_before_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsavil/what_do_you_wish_someone_told_you_before_you/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 14:47:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m a beginner investor learning all the basics currently and educating myself as best as I can to be successful and was wondering: what do you guys think are some vital concepts/methods/tools that led to your successes? Most importantly, what led to your biggest failures and how did you recover? Failure is truly a teacher and I want to hear about yours! I figure that I could go into the market and fail again myself (down 46% already lmao), or I could utilize the failures from the three million investors on here!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[强生公司计划分拆为两家公司，分离消费者健康业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[强生公司的股价在盘前交易中跳涨，此前该公司的医疗保健巨头宣布
在医疗保健巨头宣布将自己拆分为两家上市公司后，强生公司的股价在盘前交易中跳升。

新公司将包括一个专注于消费产品的公司，如
Band-Aid绷带和婴儿爽身粉，另一家则专注于...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs9ko5/johnson_johnson_plans_to_split_into_two_companies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs9ko5/johnson_johnson_plans_to_split_into_two_companies/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 14:35:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares of Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson jumped in premarket trading after the healthcare giant announced that it is splitting itself into two publicly traded companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new companies will consist of one focused on consumer products, such as Band-Aid bandages and baby powder, and another focused on prescription drugs and medical devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson was already undergoing a major transition, as CEO Alex Gorsky has previously announced that he will step down in January. Joaquin Duato, who was tapped as Gorsky’s successor, will lead the new J&amp;amp;J following the spinoff, the company said Friday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the company said it planned to keep its total dividend “at least at the same level” following the change. J&amp;amp;J currently sports a divided yield of about 2.6%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson plans to split into two companies, separating consumer health business &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/jj-shares-jump-after-ceo-says-health-giant-plans-to-break-up-in-wsj-report.html?__source=iosappshare%7Ccom.apple.UIKit.activity.CopyToPasteboard&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/jj-shares-jump-after-ceo-says-health-giant-plans-to-break-up-in-wsj-report.html?__source=iosappshare%7Ccom.apple.UIKit.activity.CopyToPasteboard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[仍然不明白期权/期货以及它们是如何运作的，或者它们的意义何在？]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以我看了关于期权和期货的视频，我知道它们都是
不同，但保持着类似的原则，就像你得到了在未来买入/卖出某物的权利。
但从根本上讲，这对我来说没有任何意义。
我不明白。

比如你为什么不直接购买或持有某样东西？什么...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs3vvg/still_dont_get_optionsfutures_and_how_they_work/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs3vvg/still_dont_get_optionsfutures_and_how_they_work/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 14:35:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;#39;ve watched the videos on options and futures and I get that they&amp;#39;re both different but maintain a similar principle that like you get the right to buy/sell something in the future but fundamentally it doesn&amp;#39;t make any sense to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like why wouldn&amp;#39;t you just buy or hold something? What advantage do options or futures give you over just traditional investing? I get things like margin or leverage as in riskily buying more than you can afford but I just don&amp;#39;t get what the point or how options or futures work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, options sounds like ok I&amp;#39;ll buy the right to buy a stock at this price, if it goes down I just won&amp;#39;t fulfill the obligation because I don&amp;#39;t have to and if it goes up then sure I&amp;#39;ll fulfill the contract. Again, that&amp;#39;s definitely not right because that would just be an infinite money glitch because you would always never take the option if it&amp;#39;s going down and always take it if it goes up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Futures makes a little more sense because you have to oblige the contract. But then why wouldn&amp;#39;t you just buy something normally? What&amp;#39;s the benefit of buying at a set time?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL:DR, genuinely have no idea how options/futures work and what their point is, and I probably sound really dumb but if someone can explain in a way that makes sense I would really appreciate that, thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Paysafe - 是买入还是转出？]]></title><description><![CDATA[Paysafe（PSFE）的股票今天下跌了40%，因为第三季度的收益报告令人沮丧。
该公司收入比2020年第三季度下降了1%。

到目前为止，分析师对Paysafe的评价相当高，特别是随着在线赌博市场的增长，以及该公司收购了几个较小规模的公司。
特别是随着在线赌博市场的增长，以及它收购了几个较小的
欧洲金融科技...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qru6rq/paysafe_buy_the_dip_or_gtfo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qru6rq/paysafe_buy_the_dip_or_gtfo/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 14:20:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paysafe (PSFE) stock dropped 40% today following a soberiing Q3 earnings report where company revenue dropped 1% from Q3 2020. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Up until now, analysts had been quite high on Paysafe, particularly as the market for online gambling has grown, and as it acquired several smaller European fintech companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have about 2% of my portfolio in Paysafe, and until today was already at a -12% ROI, but that&amp;#39;s in part bexause I was already buying it&amp;#39;s not 10 month dip. The plan was to hold for no fewer than five years. Is it time to double down and take advantage of the freefall, or cut losses and bail?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[强生公司计划分拆为两个独立的公司!]]></title><description><![CDATA[将把它的消费者部门与它的制药和医疗设备部门分开。
器械部门。大家对这个新方向有什么看法？强生公司
强生公司是世界上销售额最大的健康产品公司，但认为
这两个部门的方向和增长正在迅速分化....。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs9jsv/johnson_and_johnson_planning_on_splitting_into/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs9jsv/johnson_and_johnson_planning_on_splitting_into/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 13:56:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will be separating it&amp;#39;s consumer division from it&amp;#39;s pharmaceutical and medical device division. What&amp;#39;s everyone&amp;#39;s take on this new direction?   Johnson and Johnson is the world&amp;#39;s largest health products companies by sales but believes that the two divisions directions and growth are diverging rapidly. 
     Is this the right direction for them to take?   No decision yet one what they will do when it comes to holding a stock offering.&lt;br/&gt;
     I&amp;#39;ve always felt J n J was a safe long term hold how does this change that now?  More growth potential with the pharmaceutical division but comes with more risk too.  As the WSJ article states the consumer division comes with its own  issues,  as it&amp;#39;s  &amp;quot;Sales are growing more slowly than at the other businesses, and have lower margins too. &amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这有意义吗？EV讨论 ($RIVN) ($LCID) ($TSLA) ($F)]]></title><description><![CDATA[电动汽车初创公司Rivian（RIVN）已经在公开市场上大放异彩，公开募股，市值达1160亿美元。
杀手级的公开募股，市值达到1160亿美元。这比
通用汽车（GM）的价值，比福特（F）多出47%。里维安在今年之前从未出售过
辆，直到今年。通用汽车销售了约700万辆汽车...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrz8ji/does_this_make_sense_ev_discussion_rivn_lcid_tsla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrz8ji/does_this_make_sense_ev_discussion_rivn_lcid_tsla/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 13:31:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Electric-vehicle startup Rivian (RIVN) has roared into public markets with a killer public offering and a market value of $116 billion. That’s 32% more than General Motors (GM) is worth, and 47% more than Ford (F). Rivian has never sold a vehicle until this year. GM sells around 7 million vehicles per year; Ford, 4 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you add up the market value of Tesla (TSLA), Rivian, and 5 other startups including Lucid (LCID), Nikola (NKLA), Fisker (FSR), Lordstown Motors (RIDE) and Workhorse (WKHS), their combined capitalization is nearly $1.3 trillion. Nine of the world’s biggest automakers—GM, Ford, Stellantis, Toyota, Nissan, Honda, Volkswagen, BMW and Daimler-Benz—are only worth $845 billion. So those 9 giant automakers are worth 34% less than 7 fledgling EV manufacturers. As for sales, the established manufacturers outsell the EV upstarts 100 to 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The market now seems to view &lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rivian-ceo-sees-annual-production-144553789.html&quot;&gt;Rivian&lt;/a&gt; as a Tesla-in-the-making, especially since it already has backing from Amazon and Ford. By focusing on sport pickups and delivery vans, Rivian has one foot in consumer vehicles and the other in commercial applications, a shrewd mix that lets the company spread its bets on a trend that is already a revolution in ground transportation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Growth.&lt;/strong&gt; In market terms, investors consider &lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-is-not-enough-engine-no-1-bets-on-gm-white-paper-details-electric-vehicle-landscape-124811083.html&quot;&gt;EV newcomers&lt;/a&gt; such as Tesla and Rivian to be growth and technology companies with tons of upside potential. Traditional automakers are industrial concerns capable of incremental growth, at best. While virtually every big automaker is developing EV technology, the old ones won’t attain nearly the same rapid growth as the new ones will. That’s because they have massive investments in internal-combustion engines, or ICE—a.k.a. gas-and diesel-powered cars—that will decline as the new EV technology ramps up. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GM, for instance, sold 202,000 EVs in 2020, which was third most of any automaker, behind Tesla and Volkswagen. But for GM the technology of the future represented just 3% of all sales. The other 97% were legacy ICE vehicles likely to decline as a share of the overall market for years to come. At Tesla, 100% of sales were EVs, with no legacy business to manage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new technology is where the growth is. Tesla’s revenue growth rate during the last two years has been 39%, according to S&amp;amp;P Capital IQ. GM’s has been a negative 5%. Pandemic disruptions have been a factor in both company’s performance, but the trend was the same before the pandemic. GM still makes a lot of money selling high-margin pickups and SUVs, but investors view that as a business that could someday dwindle to no profit at all. Electrics, by contrast, will only get more profitable as costs drop, technology advances and more people buy them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capital.&lt;/strong&gt; Traditional carmakers such as GM and Ford argue that the profitability of existing lineups gives them an advantage because they have in-house funding for new EV technology. But startups haven’t needed in-house funding because capital markets have been a ready source of money. “Capital for EV [manufacturers] is widely available and cheap in current market conditions, so we believe momentum/support for many of the stocks will persist,” analyst John Murphy of Bank of America wrote in a recent research note. “As has proven the case for Tesla over the past decade, the higher the upward spiral of stock, the cheaper capital becomes to fund growth.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/its-bizarro-world-in-the-auto-industry-again-203740250.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/its-bizarro-world-in-the-auto-industry-again-203740250.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[杠杆投资 [Ben Felix谈杠杆ETF]]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrs6wk/investing_with_leverage_ben_felix_on_leveraged/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrs6wk/investing_with_leverage_ben_felix_on_leveraged/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 12:38:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[无论怎样，我都会达到目的的！"。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs6dd0/one_way_or_another_im_getting_there/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs6dd0/one_way_or_another_im_getting_there/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 12:38:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特股票和里维安股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，我完全糊涂了，需要帮助理解。我不可能
我不可能理解，福特汽车公司已经存在了这么久，并且有一个既定的商业模式。
既定的商业模式，在未来几年将逐步改变为电动汽车。
在接下来的几年里，福特汽车公司将逐步向电动汽车转变。自从Rivian进入市场以来，所有...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs3uds/ford_stock_and_rivian_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs3uds/ford_stock_and_rivian_stock/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 11:34:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok, I’m completely confused and need help understanding. I can’t possibly understand how Ford motor company has been around for so long and has an established business model that is progressively going to change here in the next couple of years to electric vehicles. Since Rivian hit the market all kinds of questions have come to mind especially the market cap of these companies and how they’re surpassing other companies that have been around for decades. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can someone explain to me how Ford stock is $19.00 a share at $100B market value and the most sold truck in America…Yet, Rivian sold 156 trucks to date and the stock is $124.00 ish and $120B market. This makes so sense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师们似乎只是在股票上涨时编造目标价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-nvda-stock-price-target-boosts-earnings-51636640350?siteid=yhoof2

"Nvidia股票在盈利前获得了49%的目标价格提升。为什么分析师们会
看涨。
以奥本海默公司的Rick Schafer为首的分析师重申了他们对Nvidia股票的 "跑赢大盘 "评级，并将其目标价提高了49%。
的评级，并提高了对Nvidia股票...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs5xcq/analysts_seem_to_just_make_up_price_targets_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs5xcq/analysts_seem_to_just_make_up_price_targets_as/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 11:22:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-nvda-stock-price-target-boosts-earnings-51636640350?siteid=yhoof2&quot;&gt;https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-nvda-stock-price-target-boosts-earnings-51636640350?siteid=yhoof2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Nvidia Stock Gets a 49% Price Target Boost Before Earnings. Why Analysts Are Bullish.&lt;br/&gt;
 Analysts led by Rick Schafer at Oppenheimer reiterated their Outperform rating on Nvidia stock and raised their target price on the shares by 49% to $350 from $235.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Meanwhile, Christopher Rolland at Susquehanna reiterated his Positive rating on Nvidia stock and hiked his target price to $360 from $250. &amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it just me or do these guys just raise their prise targets as the stock soars so their performance on websites like tipranks doesn&amp;#39;t suffer? Nothing about nvidia&amp;#39;s performance has changed this quarter that would suddenly warrant an increase of nvidia&amp;#39;s market cap by 300 billion dollars. I think price targets are an important tool, especially for retail investors, but lately these guys seem to just make it up as they go. At $350b nvidia is a 900b company on 10b of forward net earnings. That&amp;#39;s just bonkers and these guys seem to base their price targets on how far they think the current bull market can inflate the ever increasing sentiment instead of what the stock is fundamentally worth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1月1日要做的事情]]></title><description><![CDATA[我所在的州对捐给529账户的钱有税收减免，所以我打算
在1月1日（之后的第一个交易日）将其全部投资。有什么事情是我
应该在今年年初做什么？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrxckw/things_to_do_on_january_1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrxckw/things_to_do_on_january_1/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 07:56:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My state has tax deductions on money contributed to a 529 account so I plan to invest it all on (the first trading day after) January 1. Are there any things I should be doing at the start of the year?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔不支付股息的实际逻辑原因是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，"巴菲特比你更擅长投资 "的老借口根本没有
有意义（了）。

 1. 巴菲特把他的现金囤积在储蓄里，甚至没有投资它
 2. 公司已经达到了规模经济，很难再有增长，所以
    实事求是地说，即使你没有更好的发展...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs1a74/what_is_an_actual_logical_reason_that_berkshire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs1a74/what_is_an_actual_logical_reason_that_berkshire/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 07:43:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So the old excuse &amp;quot;Buffett is better at investing it than you&amp;quot; simply doesn&amp;#39;t make sense (anymore)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Buffett is stockpiling his cash in savings and not even investing it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The company has reached economies of scale and has a hard time growing so realistically, even if you aren&amp;#39;t better off investing it, it makes more sense for the cash to be distributed to shareholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It really makes no sense. Can someone explain it to me?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[需要一个好的经纪账户，尽快]]></title><description><![CDATA[今天想通过Vanguard设立我的Roth IRA账户，但由于某些原因
网站不允许我进行设置--不管怎样。决定打电话给
Vanguard，在等待了30分钟后，我终于和一位同事通了电话。
同事。结果发现他们的网站已经有两个问题了。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs2q71/need_a_good_brokerage_account_asap/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs2q71/need_a_good_brokerage_account_asap/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 07:30:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tried to set up my Roth IRA account today through Vanguard but for some reason the site wasn&amp;#39;t letting me go through with the setup- whatever. Decided to call Vanguard, and after 30 minutes of waiting I was finally on the phone with an associate. Turns out they&amp;#39;ve been having site issues for 2 months now- how convenient. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The associate created an account for me which I greatly appreciated, and he gave me some paperwork to fill out about taxes, place of work, etc. I was pretty frustrated after my call, so I decided that I&amp;#39;d work on this paperwork later, so I logged out of the site. Tried to log back on just now and it turns out that I can&amp;#39;t even log back, and now I have to recall about getting back in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After the nightmare that was setting up an account in the first place&lt;/strong&gt;, I really don&amp;#39;t want to go through this process again. Is it worth it just to set up an account with Fidelity instead? Even Robinhood seems better than this. What should I do?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿斯瓦特-达莫多兰的特斯拉估值]]></title><description><![CDATA[无论你对特斯拉有什么看法，都要尊重我认识的一位最好的金融学老师，他在计算股票风险方面的工作。
他在计算股票风险溢价方面的工作。相当
有趣的阅读。我对特斯拉没有硬性的意见，除了我喜欢他们的
他们的汽车，但这是一个更有智慧的诚实和...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs0jf3/aswath_damodorans_tesla_valuation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs0jf3/aswath_damodorans_tesla_valuation/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 06:32:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever your thoughts on Tesla, gotta respect one of the best teacher&amp;#39;s of finance who I know for his work in calculating the equity risk premium. Pretty interesting read.  I have no hard opinions on Tesla beyond the fact that I like their cars,  but this is one of the more intellectually honest and humble attempts at intrinsically valuing the company. &lt;a href=&quot;https://aswathdamodaran.blogspot.com/2021/11/teslas-trillion-dollar-moment-valuation.html&quot;&gt;https://aswathdamodaran.blogspot.com/2021/11/teslas-trillion-dollar-moment-valuation.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[JPow发现通货膨胀的镜头。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrpp8b/footage_of_jpow_finding_out_about_inflation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrpp8b/footage_of_jpow_finding_out_about_inflation/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 06:32:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>