<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 21:56:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Covid公司的FUD并没有欺骗任何人]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4wcpo/covid_fud_aint_fooling_nobody/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4wcpo/covid_fud_aint_fooling_nobody/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:57:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[缩放电话得到了回报。我可以正式说我赚了6位数。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4x1ec/zoom_calls_paid_off_i_can_officially_say_i_make_6/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4x1ec/zoom_calls_paid_off_i_can_officially_say_i_make_6/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:57:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我正在考虑卖掉我的富达账户中的所有东西，用先锋基金代替。]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好，我是一个来自英国的新手投资者，24岁，我一直在投资。
我从2020年金融危机前就开始投资。

我一开始在vanguard（买入生命策略100%+sp500基金）。
然而，我觉得我的选择有限，于是开了一个富达的账户。

我每个月都会存钱...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r52oqd/thinking_about_selling_everything_in_my_fidelity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r52oqd/thinking_about_selling_everything_in_my_fidelity/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:45:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi there, I&amp;#39;m a newbie investor from the UK here, 24 years old, I&amp;#39;ve been investing since just before covid 2020 crash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started off with vanguard (buying into life strategy 100% + sp500 fund), however I felt limited with my options and opened up a fidelity account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been depositing monthly into my fidelity account and into various different funds, Which I regret because I clearly have no idea what I&amp;#39;m doing... &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The funds have an average fee of 0.5% and I think this is quiet high (correct me if I am wrong). + the account fee + platform fee... this, over time, will eat into the value of my assets. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am writing today to get a second opinion and a bit of guidance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/jrhxnaieyk281.png?width=1920&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=f6ae3a1beda911396086e49e1aa8dd1dce48ca59&quot;&gt;30 fund portfolio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/0yy6ivbczk281.png?width=1482&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=1ffe3ea17a82b79b0cbdb88dbc3e1d2983a0e931&quot;&gt;vanguard portfolio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please help me... I am not too sure on what to do now... &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know this is a mess, all suggestions are welcome! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NSFW, my portfolio might give you anxiety. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在大流行病交易中赚取26亿美元的对冲基金投资者表示，大流行病可能会对股市产生利好作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[对冲基金大亨比尔-阿克曼（Bill Ackman）周末表示，新的欧米茄变体的
导致COVID-19的冠状病毒的新变种，如果它被证明会导致感染者出现轻度到中度的症状，那么可能会对股票产生利好。
感染者会出现轻度至中度症状。该病毒的发现
该变种的发现导致了最糟糕的黑色星期五之一...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r517w5/hedgefund_investor_who_made_26_billion_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r517w5/hedgefund_investor_who_made_26_billion_on/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:32:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hedge-fund luminary Bill Ackman over the weekend said the new omicron variant of the coronavirus that causes COVID-19 could be bullish for stocks if it proves to result in mild to moderate symptoms for those who contract it. The discovery of the variant resulted in one of the worst Black Friday trading sessions in recent memory, with the Dow Jones Industrial Average DJIA, 0.98%, the S&amp;amp;P 500 index SPX, 1.62% and the Nasdaq Composite Index COMP, 2.08% all tumbling by at least 2%, but Ackman’s comments suggest that investors’ knee-jerk response may have been an overreaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bond yields on Friday also fell as prices for government debt saw a rush to the perceived safety of Treasurys on the back of fresh concerns about new restrictions that could result from a strain of COVID that the World Health Organization on Friday designated a variant of concern. However, stocks were bouncing back on Monday and the 10-year Treasury note yield TMUBMUSD10Y, 1.528% was up 8 basis points at 1.56%. Prices for Treasurys fall as yields rise. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ackman, who runs Pershing Square Capital, is known for his lucrative COVID wager. The Financial Times reported back in 2020 that the investor cashed out on bet that netted him a $2.6 billion profit on a $27 million at risk, on the premise that insurance premiums would soar during the height of the 2020 COVID pandemic as economies locked down. He also later in 2020 said that he placed bearish bets on corporate credit on the day that Pfizer PFE, -0.64%  and BioNTech BNTX, 3.65% released positive trial data on their COVID-19 vaccine, which triggered a whipsaw rally in stocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ackman was wagering that the vaccines would lead to mask-wearing complacency. However, that bet presumably turned out wrong as markets continued to surge in the aftermath of those vaccines. The danger posed by the omicron variant isn’t yet fully understood, even though governments in Europe, Asia, the Middle East and the Americas immediately restricted travel from southern Africa. Vaccine manufacturers have said that they are examining the variant closely and note that the current batch of remedies might still prove effective against the strain and new vaccines could be readied in early 2022 if needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/hedge-fund-investor-who-made-2-6-billion-on-pandemic-trades-says-omicron-could-be-bullish-for-stock-market-11638198173?mod=home-page&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/hedge-fund-investor-who-made-2-6-billion-on-pandemic-trades-says-omicron-could-be-bullish-for-stock-market-11638198173?mod=home-page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[年轻时承担更大风险的谬误]]></title><description><![CDATA[我经常听到这样的话。当你年轻的时候要承担更大的风险。当你在
你20多岁的时候，重仓高风险/高回报的股票是可以的。但这是
有缺陷的推理。

事实上，在你年轻的时候冒大风险是更有风险的，因为
机会成本。人们总是提到...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r533z7/the_fallacy_of_taking_bigger_risks_when_you_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r533z7/the_fallacy_of_taking_bigger_risks_when_you_are/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:32:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I hear this all the time. Take bigger risks when you are young. When you are in your 20’s its fine to go heavy in high risk/high reward stocks. But this is flawed reasoning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The truth is taking big risks when you are young is more risky because of opportunity costs. People always mention compounding interest over decades. But fail to apply this to investing in risky stocks when you are young. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lets say you are 20 years old and you have $10k to invest. Its common to hear people say you can be more risky since you are so young. And even if you do YOLO and lose it all you can easily recover. But think opportunity cost. What did you really lose doing a YOLO?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$10,000&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invest in an index fund that returns 8.5% annualized return &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Withdraw at 65 years old&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That $10k becomes $400k. So you basically lost $400k because you YOLOed on a risky stock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you hold till 70 you lost $600k. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At age 90 you can give your children and grandchildren $3.2 million. Or you could have fun and lose it all on a risky stock. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bottom line is a young persons greatest asset is TIME. Throwing investment time away by taking unnecessary risk is a massive mistake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not saying don’t buy stocks that are risky hyper growth companies. But also don’t gamble needlessly. Because you are gambling much more than that couple hundred or thousand you see next to the stock ticker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[游戏店。Finviz报告112%的SI - 第二回合？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r503cb/gamestop_finviz_reporting_112_si_round_2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r503cb/gamestop_finviz_reporting_112_si_round_2/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 19:14:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊准备在2022年初超过UPS和联邦快递，成为美国最大的快递公司，执行官说]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/amazon-on-track-to-be-largest-us-delivery-service-by-2022-exec-says.html

亚马逊全球消费者首席执行官戴夫-克拉克（Dave Clark）周一告诉CNBC，该公司有望成为美国最大的快递公司。
该公司有望在2021年底或2022年初成为美国最大的快递服务。
2021年底或2022年初成为美国最大的快递公司。

分析师们已经...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4zkvm/amazon_poised_to_pass_ups_and_fedex_to_become/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4zkvm/amazon_poised_to_pass_ups_and_fedex_to_become/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 18:16:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/amazon-on-track-to-be-largest-us-delivery-service-by-2022-exec-says.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/amazon-on-track-to-be-largest-us-delivery-service-by-2022-exec-says.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dave Clark, Amazon’s CEO of worldwide consumer, told CNBC on Monday that the company is on track to become the nation’s largest delivery service by the end of 2021 or early 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Analysts have long predicted Amazon would overtake carriers like UPS, FedEx and the U.S. Postal Service, thanks to its increasingly in-house network of planes, trucks, vans and ships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a positive development as Amazon dependence on other carriers will be lessen. The logistic and warehouse networks are in a optimal mode now as Amazon has been invested heavily to fight off the competition. This proves that the investment cycle has finally paid off as patience investors will be holding the amazon stocks and waiting for the next stock appreciation cycle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我刚刚在经纪公司存入7千美元，28岁，你会在这些股票中买入哪些股票做长线？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在上班前发这个帖子，所以请原谅我不是很详细，将尽力而为。
尽量使其与大家息息相关，而不仅仅是我对这3只股票的看法。
股票，我想知道对长期的意见。

特斯拉

苹果

索菲

我拥有特斯拉是因为.... 这就是特斯拉。在我看来，人们希望...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4wghb/i_just_deposited_7k_into_brokerage_age_28_which/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4wghb/i_just_deposited_7k_into_brokerage_age_28_which/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 18:16:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Posting this right before work so forgive me for not being super detailed, will try my best to make this relevant for everyone and not just me about these 3 stocks I want to know opinions on for long term: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sofi &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I own Tesla because.... It is Tesla. People in my honest opinion want to believe they will only be making vehicles in the future. Not the case if Elon Musk gets his way (check out the Tesla bot for example, not to mention space travel, etc). Before today held 2 shares of Tesla, plan on buying 2 more. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple is a good long term buy and hold because it is Apple of course. I do not believe the Apple car that should be releasing in the next 3 years has been priced in to the stock at all yet. I could see Apple being worth over $500/share say 3 years from now. Before today held 14 shares of Apple, plan on buying 10 more. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sofi is an underdog stock. I could see this stock going much further down, possibly to/below $10 a share again. Sofi is by definition loosing money, and it is the outlier compared to say a Tesla or an Apple stock... However I see it as being revolutionary when it comes to financial products for the everyday person. As a millennial most of my friends from around the United States seem to know more about Sofi than Goldman Sachs, Wells Fargo, etc. I would be shocked if Sofi is not worth $40 a share this time next year. Before today held 48 shares, will be buying 25 more today, and will wait for a potential dip below $12 - if that happens will buy as many shares as I can. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tell me if I am missing anything with these stocks, and for us readers in similar situations, maybe a few stocks to consider purchasing in lieu of any of the above 3?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[10月耐用品订单下滑0.5%。]]></title><description><![CDATA[10月耐用品新订单按季节性调整后减少了1美元。
经调整的12亿美元或0.5%，至2601亿美元，美国人口普查局公布。
宣布。 

这一下降是连续两个月的下降，此前9月份经季节性调整后为0.4%。
9月下降。不包括运输业，新订单...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r4z1e9/orders_for_durable_goods_slid_05_in_october/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r4z1e9/orders_for_durable_goods_slid_05_in_october/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:53:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;New orders for manufactured durable goods in October decreased A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $1.2  billion or 0.5% to $260.1 billion, the U.S. Census Bureau announced. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This decrease, down two consecutive months, followed a SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 0.4% September  decrease. Excluding transportation, new orders increased  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 0.5%.  Excluding defense, new orders increased  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 0.8%. Transportation equipment,  down three of the last four months, drove the SEASONALLY ADJUSTED decrease, 2.0 billion or  2.6% to $75.3 billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shipments of manufactured durable goods in October, up five of the  last six months, increased  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $4.0 billion or 1.5% to $261.5 billion. This  followed  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 0.6% September increase. Transportation equipment, up  following two consecutive monthly decreases, led the increase,  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $2.3  billion or 3.2% to $75.3 billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfilled orders for manufactured durable goods in October, up nine  consecutive months, increased  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $3.1 billion or 0.2% to $1,249.7 billion.  This followed  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 0.7% September increase. Machinery, up nineteen  consecutive months, led the increase, up  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED$1.4 billion or 1.2% to $113.7  billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inventories of manufactured durable goods in October, up nine  consecutive months, increased  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $2.8 billion or 0.6% to $466.0 billion.  This followed  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 1.0% September increase. Fabricated metal products, up  thirteen consecutive months, led the increase, up  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $0.9 billion or 1.4% to  $61.0 billion.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.floordaily.net/flooring-news/orders-for-durable-goods-slid-05-in-october&quot;&gt;https://www.floordaily.net/flooring-news/orders-for-durable-goods-slid-05-in-october&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一支你拥有相当比例的股票在瞬间上涨了数百万美元

但这只是因为你要卸任CEO了 https://t.co/GnA0DQORMb]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465330319331139596</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465330319331139596</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:40:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于通货膨胀，COVID-19现在是COVID-20.178。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465372508228624401</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465372508228624401</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:40:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[科维德的死亡率没有上升。由于Omicron突变是 "超级温和 "的变种，世卫组织和将限制和大规模歇斯底里换成了谨慎的乐观态度。]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，伙计们，如果你们对市场的突然下滑感到担忧，这里有一个好消息
一些好消息

世界卫生组织和世界各地的冠状病毒专家今天上午呼吁
各国放弃旅行限制，结束大规模的歇斯底里，转而采取
谨慎乐观的态度，因为最初的报告显示...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4z16b/covid_death_rate_not_rising_swap_restrictions_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4z16b/covid_death_rate_not_rising_swap_restrictions_and/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:15:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey guys, if you&amp;#39;re worried about the sudden downturn in the markets, here&amp;#39;s some great news &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The WHO and Coronavirus experts around the world are calling this morning for countries to drop travel restrictions and end the mass hysteria and instead be cautiously optimistic as initial reports out of South Africa suggest the new Omicron variant is not more lethal than the previous Delta variant. In fact, there have been no reports of hospitalisations or deaths as a result of anyone being diagnosed with Omicron. Most patients merely experience a severe headache, nausea, dizziness and a high pulse rate, according to hospitals and medics across Southern Africa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the news of the new variant, first reported in South Africa, led to mass hysteria around the world: markets thumbed and dozens of countries imposed travel restrictions and additional checks, including the UK, US, EU, Israel, Australia and Japan after the new mutation popped up in the UK, Germany, Italy, Czech Republic and Israel among other countries. Dr Angelique Coetzee, chair of the South African Medical Association, said this reaction was “medically seen, not justified.” A GP for over three decades, and chair of the South African Medical Association, she was the first African doctor to suggest to local authorities Covid had mutated into a new strain. Coetzee called the response from many European countries, including the UK, “just a hype.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Africa’s health minister Joe Phaahla also said the majority of cases of Omicron seen by doctors in his country have been “mild”. He added he has heard from GPs that the “majority of the people they’ve been seeing are mild.” “Our clinicians have not witnessed severe illness. Part of it may be because the majority of those who are positive are young people,” Dr Paahla added.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full story here &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cityam.com/covid-death-rate-not-rising-swap-travel-restrictions-and-mass-hysteria-for-cautious-optimism-as-omicron-mutation-is-super-mild-variant-who-and-coronavirus-experts-say/&quot;&gt;https://www.cityam.com/covid-death-rate-not-rising-swap-travel-restrictions-and-mass-hysteria-for-cautious-optimism-as-omicron-mutation-is-super-mild-variant-who-and-coronavirus-experts-say/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[多尔西从推特卸任]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.huffpost.com/entry/jack-dorsey-stepping-down-twitter-ceo_n_61a4e36fe4b025be1aec6591

Twitter的投资者似乎很喜欢这个，但有趣的是，SQ是平的。你会
你认为这对SQ来说是好事，因为他现在可以只关注该公司，而不是分散注意力。
而不是分散他的注意力。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4y3ma/dorsey_stepping_down_from_twitter/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4y3ma/dorsey_stepping_down_from_twitter/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:15:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.huffpost.com/entry/jack-dorsey-stepping-down-twitter-ceo_n_61a4e36fe4b025be1aec6591&quot;&gt;https://www.huffpost.com/entry/jack-dorsey-stepping-down-twitter-ceo_n_61a4e36fe4b025be1aec6591&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Twitter investors seem to like this, but interesting that SQ is flat. You&amp;#39;d think this would be good for SQ since he can now focus on just that company and not divide his attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我见过的最有趣的狗屎。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4xaoj/funniest_shit_ive_ever_seen/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4xaoj/funniest_shit_ive_ever_seen/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:15:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场在Tilray上犯了一个错误；至少有30%的上升空间]]></title><description><![CDATA[一直在关注大麻行业的人知道，Tilray最近的交易表现令人失望。
交易表现一直不尽如人意。在我看来，该公司交易业绩的最大障碍是由于加拿大的成人娱乐活动。
该公司的交易表现的最大障碍是由于加拿大成人娱乐业的
行业的广泛挑战，以及与大麻相关的零售...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4urxr/market_made_a_mistake_on_tilray_at_least_30_upside/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4urxr/market_made_a_mistake_on_tilray_at_least_30_upside/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:15:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those who&amp;#39;ve been following the cannabis industry, knows that Tilray&amp;#39;s recent trading performance has been underwhelming. In my opinion, the biggest hurdle to the company&amp;#39;s trading performance is due to the Canadian adult recreational industry wide challenge along with covid-related retail headwinds. There&amp;#39;s been struggles for the Canadian cannabis LPs to generate growth organically within the adult recreational segment. For example, while Tilray, market leader in Canadian adult recreational, generated 26% topline growth from $405 million in 2020 to $513 million in 2021, much of that topline growth is derived from acquisitions. In other words, Tilray&amp;#39;s recent revenue growth were &amp;quot;bought&amp;quot; instead of generated organically as the market expands. Low growth within the segment along with some structural challenges and covid-related shut-downs further negatively impacted the industry&amp;#39;s outlook and profitability, resulting in depressing trading performances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As cannabis companies remain illegal in the United States at a federal level and debt capital raising are off the table as a result, Canadian cannabis LPs relies on equity issuance to fund acquisition opportunities to &amp;quot;grow&amp;quot; their toplines. Result of both stagnant growth and share dilution, Tilray traded down from $40 in February 2021 to $10 last close. Tilray&amp;#39;s TTM EV/Sales declined from 40x to 10x. For a growth company within a quickly expanding market that&amp;#39;s only 3 years old, 10x TTM sales EV is a good price in my opinion. What makes it even more attractive is that there&amp;#39;s a catalyst that the market has dismissed and forgotten that will completely derail the stagnant market growth narrative for Tilray.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Germany&amp;#39;s new coalition government has recently reached a deal that&amp;#39;s set to legalize recreational cannabis use. As a result, German pot stocks popped last week on Frankfurt exchange. For example, German cannabis company Synbiotic rose by 33% to $29 Euro, which implies a $100mm market cap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What the market has forgotten however is that Canadian cannabis LP Tilray is actually the market leader in the Germany&amp;#39;s cannabis market. But the stock didn&amp;#39;t move last week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do I know the market made a mistake instead of &amp;quot;everything has been priced in&amp;quot; narrative?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Easy. First, almost every German pot companies moved up last week. The fact that Tilray didn&amp;#39;t change at all suggests that whoever was making market genuinely forgot that Tilray is a market leader in the German cannabis market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, if we assume status quo on Tilray&amp;#39;s 10x EV/Sales multiple, which is a very conservative assumption because we&amp;#39;re completely dismissing the potential of a new, 3-days old, 83 million population addressable market. And if we proxy $90 million of additional revenue, which is another very conservative assumption as Tilray generated $90 million in revenue after Canada legalized their adult recreational cannabis market in 2018; Conservative because German population doubles of Canadian. With the conservative multiple assumption while holding other variables constant, just by adding the additional $90 million in revenue, we should expect Tilray trade up by at least 30%. The fact that it didn&amp;#39;t trade up at the slightest suggests whoever was making market was sleeping in his office after he had his turkey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Third, Tilray is production and distribution ready. Tilray operates two state-of-art facilities in Portugal and Germany with over 3 million square feet of production capacity. Tilray also owns and operates one of the largest market cap pharmaceutical company, CC Pharma, in Germany. Because of the company&amp;#39;s production and distribution capacity, institutional support, larger balance sheet, domestic moms &amp;amp; pops cannabis producers in Germany aren&amp;#39;t like to able to compete against Tilray in the immediate 24 months of legalization, allowing Tilray to secure market leadership. Again, this echoes with why assume only $90 million of revenue and 10x EV/Sales is a very conservative estimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Forth, there has been consistencies showing that the cannabis MTM is very inefficient. Most of you are aware that there were a squeeze with the Canadian cannabis LPs that took place in February. It was driven by Democrats winning the election, investors bet in favour that recreational cannabis use will be legalized in the U.S. It was similar to what&amp;#39;s happening today; similar but different. What&amp;#39;s similar is that both are political driven catalyst and market has gotten it completely wrong. Different was that last time Tilray were traded up for the wrong reason, Tilray has minimal operations in the United States, while they&amp;#39;re already a market leader in the German cannabis market with operations and infrastructures that are unmatched by their competitors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading, let me know if I got it wrong. Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Position: 500 shares long TLRY at C$13.32&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我想我做什么 - 我做什么]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4ugcq/what_i_think_i_do_what_i_do/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4ugcq/what_i_think_i_do_what_i_do/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 16:50:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[S&P500和恢复时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好! 在看到另一个子网站上关于S&P500和破净的评论后，它让我想到了
让我想到了。如果我在最高价时投资于标准普尔500指数，然后价格下跌并不再投入资金，那么最长的时间是多久？
跌，并且不再投入资金，那么历史上最长的时间是多久？
历史上需要多长时间才能达到收支平衡？

希望这有意义？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4ibbc/sp500_and_recovery_time/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4ibbc/sp500_and_recovery_time/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 16:07:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello! After seeing a comment on the s&amp;amp;p500 and breaking Even on another sub, it got me thinking.  If I invest into the s&amp;amp;p500 at the peak Price and the price falls and never put anymore money in, what’s the longest amount of time historically has it taken to breakeven? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully that makes sense? 😅 I’ll try to explain better if it’s not clear what I’m asking &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[对购买共同基金股票感到困惑]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好，我一直想投资一些钱在FXAIX指数基金，但
我对这些股票是如何定价和交易的感到困惑。

从我读到的内容来看，共同基金的股票价格是在每天收市后更新的，这也是股票交易的时间。
这也是股票交易的时间。这是否意味着我将不知道价格
的价格。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r4lz4c/confused_about_buying_mutual_fund_shares/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r4lz4c/confused_about_buying_mutual_fund_shares/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 15:30:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi there, I’ve been looking to invest some money in the FXAIX index fund, but I’m confused about how these shares are priced and traded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From what I read, mutual fund share prices are updated after market close each day, which is also when shares are traded. Does that mean I won’t know the price of the shares I’m buying until they are calculated after close, or am I buying them at the price they’re listed at during the day?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[彼得-林奇的《华尔街》一书摘要]]></title><description><![CDATA[领先于华尔街

 *股票最有可能被接受为审慎的时刻，他们不是
 * 只投资你能承受的损失而不影响你的日常生活。
   只投资你能承受的损失，而不影响你的日常生活
 * 不要高估专业人士的技能和智慧
 * 利用你的优势...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4oizg/peter_lynch_one_up_on_wall_street_book_summary/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4oizg/peter_lynch_one_up_on_wall_street_book_summary/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 15:04:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;h1&gt;One Up on Wall Street&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stocks are most likely to be accepted as prudent at the moment they are not&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only invest what you could afford to lose without that loss having any effect on your daily life&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;#39;t overestimate the skill and wisdom of professionals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take advantage of what you already know&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look for opportunities that haven&amp;#39;t been discovered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Invest in a home first&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Invest in companies, not the stock market&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ignore short term movements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Predicting the economy is futile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Predicting the short term movement of the stock market is futile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Long term stocks have outperformed bonds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The average person is exposed to local companies years before wall street&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the stock market, one in the hand is worth 10 in the bush&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;Any idiot can run this business&amp;quot; is one characteristic of the perfect company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Invest in companies that make products people need to keep buying&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the company insiders are buying, you should too. Management normally sells 2.3 shares for every 1 share they buy. In 1987 after the crash, it was 4 buys for 1 sell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid the hottest stock in the hottest industry, any stock being touted as the next X&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A share of stock is NOT a lotto ticket. It is a part ownership of a business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;P/E ratio can be thought of as the number of years to earn back your original investment. IE = P/E of 10 would be 10 years assuming earnings stay constant. Ratios tend to be lower for slow growers and highest for the fast growers with cyclicals in between depending on the current cycle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look at average P/E ratios on the company you are researching and peers going back several years to determine if it is a good buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid stocks with HIGH P/E ratios. They must have incredible earnings growth to justify the price&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;P/E ratio that is half the growth rate (annual earnings) is very positive and one that is twice the growth rate is very negative. IE = P/E of 10 should be growing at 10%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formula = Growth rate plus dividend yield divided by P/E. IE = 12% growth + 3% yield/10 P/E = 1.5. Less than 1 is bad. 1.5 is ok and 2+ is great.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The stock market as a whole has its own collective P/E ratio, which is a good indicator of weather the market at large is over or under valued. If some stocks are selling at inflated prices relative to earnings, then it could be likely most stocks are selling at inflated prices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest rates have a large effect on p/e ratios as investors pay higher p/e when interest rates are lower and bonds less attractive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dividend paying stocks keep the stock price from falling as far as if there was no dividend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You CAN&amp;#39;T predict future earnings. Wall Street has battalions of analysts trying to do this and they are wrong a lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cash Flow – amount of money a company takes in as a result of doing business. You want to buy companies that don&amp;#39;t need to spend a lot of money to make money IE = company spends 20 million to make 100 million is better than one that needs to spend 90 million to make 100 million. Formula = $20 stock with $2 per share annual cash flow has a 10-1 ratio which is standard (10%). $20 stock with $4 CF = 20% return on cash. Focus on free cash flow – what is left over after normal capital spending is taken out&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debt to equity ratio - normal is 25% debt to 75% equity but higher equity % is better&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[闪电般的下降楔形，是时候做空纳斯达克了!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4ramn/descending_wedge_on_lightning_time_to_short_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4ramn/descending_wedge_on_lightning_time_to_short_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 13:32:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有什么好办法能在短短几句话中说服别人相信指数基金和复利的力量？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4nh1z/whats_a_good_way_to_convince_someone_on_the_power/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4nh1z/whats_a_good_way_to_convince_someone_on_the_power/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 13:32:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一个全面的回顾。看看好市多的股息和股票价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[好市多是世界第三大零售商，是SP500指数中第12大公司。
市值为1,990亿美元。在21财年，好市多的销售额为1920亿美元。
他们在全球有815个仓库。此外，6170万个家庭拥有
此外，6170万户家庭拥有活跃的好市多会员资格，为好市多带来了39亿美元的收入。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4nt8g/a_comprehensive_review_a_look_at_costcos_dividend/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4nt8g/a_comprehensive_review_a_look_at_costcos_dividend/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 11:57:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Costco is the world&amp;#39;s 3rd largest retailer, 12th largest company in the SP500, and has a market cap of $199~ Billion. In FY21&amp;#39; Costco did $192 Billion in sales from their 815 warehouses globally. Additionally, 61.7 million households have active Costco memberships, bringing Costco another $3.9 billion in membership fees alone, all with a 91.3% renewal rate. Let&amp;#39;s take a closer look at Costco from an investment standpoint.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Costco P/E Ratio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
    Costco&amp;#39;s historical P/E hovers around 32x - 35x. Costco&amp;#39;s current P/E ratio sits around 48x which is decently high considering its&amp;#39; historical averages. The increase in Costco&amp;#39;s TTM and current P/E ratio is due to Costco&amp;#39;s stock price appreciating by 44%~ in the last six months alone. I expect Costco&amp;#39;s stock price to stabilize or fall slightly in 2022 as the P/E ratio returns to normal values as long as Costco&amp;#39;s earnings continue to grow. The recent Covid variant could affect Costco&amp;#39;s performance moving into 2022 if the areas where they operate return to lockdown, primarily US and Candian storefronts.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Costco Free Cash Flow&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
    Costco continues to increase their FCF with TTM values sitting around $6 billion. This is ~45% increase in FCF when compared to their 3Y FCF value around $4.2 billion. Costco&amp;#39;s ability to keep increasing free cash flow will ensure they can pay creditors and contributes to the safety of their dividend. Although not guaranteed, Costco has paid special dividend three out the last six years. This is a nice bonus to shareholders considering Costco&amp;#39;s yield is sub one percent.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Costco Profit Margin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
    Costco has historically kept their profit margins right around 2%. The TTM value sits just below 2.5% which is strong indicator for Costco that customers are returning to stores post Covid. 2.5% may not seem like a high number but remember Costco generated around $192 billion in sales last year, meaning they produced a profit on that around $4.8 billion. Couple that with their membership fees as they have healthy sustainable margins.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Costco Dividend Yield &amp;amp; Dividend Yield on Cost&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
    Costco&amp;#39;s dividend yield, as of 26 November 2021, sits at .58% which is the lowest it&amp;#39;s been when compared to historical averages. Again, this is attributed to Costco&amp;#39;s stock price appreciation of ~44% over the last six months. This is another indicator that Costco shares may be overvalued and you should wait to invest. Costco currently pays $3.16 in dividends per share per year. Absent a dividend increase Costco&amp;#39;s price would need to drop to around $430 per share to realign its dividend with the 3Y average. It&amp;#39;s unlikely that Costco is going depreciate by 22% from its current $550 per share value. Costco&amp;#39;s Yield on Cost is where you as an investor can get your return on investment when it comes to building passive income. Costco has a high compound annual growth rate (CAGR) around 13% meaning if you had bought Costco 15 years ago your YOC would be above 6%! Considering Costco has routinely increased their dividend at a rate higher than average you can see your dividends increase quickly without having to invest more capital. This is one of the reasons I decided to invest in Costco. Costco has been increasing their dividends for the past 17 years and I expect that trend to continue as they move closer to joining the dividend aristocrat list.  Costco spends approximately $1.4B per year to maintain their dividend. This and the growth associated appears safe considering Costco&amp;#39;s ability to maintain and increase free cash flow and profit margins.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dividend Payout Ratio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
    Lastly, Costco&amp;#39;s dividend payout ratio sits around 27% with an average around 29-31%. This is significantly lower that most dividend companies including some long-standing dividend aristocrats. Costco is only paying around 30% of its earnings out as dividends meaning they have money available to continue funding further expansion in the future. Costco has strong track record of consistently increasing earnings YoY which contributes to their ability to maintain a stable dividend payout ratio. This will also ensure they are able to continue growing their dividend in the future.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
    Costco is a great growth stock that also pays a dividends. Currently, however, Costco is overvalued. Looking at the current FIBs I wouldn&amp;#39;t expect the price to fall below the .786 FIB at $502. If you are looking to add to your position or start a new position I would wait for a pullback in December or early 2022. Costco is overvalued when you compare both Dividend Yield and P/E ratios with their historical values. I also expect Costco to raise their dividend in 2022 so getting in prior to the increase will help boost your yield on cost so you could always invest now if that&amp;#39;s what you&amp;#39;re look for. I&amp;#39;ll be watching Costco&amp;#39;s price action over the next month or so to find a good entry point to expand my current position.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investingupgraded.com/post/a-comprehensive-review-a-look-at-costco-s-dividend-and-stock-price&quot;&gt;Link to the Full Article with Pictures&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope this helps everyone! Happy Investing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have open positions in Costco.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[接种疫苗的人口百分比，1个以上剂量的Covid-19疫苗。
葡萄牙：89%
韩国：83%。
西班牙：82%。
阿根廷：81%
法国：80%
加拿大: 80%
日本: 79%
澳大利亚: 78%
意大利: 78%
爱尔兰: 78%
巴西: 77%
英国: 76%
以色列: 73%
德国: 71%
美国：70%
土耳其: 68%
墨西哥: 60%
印度: 57%
俄罗斯: 45%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465002199193473027</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465002199193473027</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 11:35:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧米茄可能导致大规模的牛市运行]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果这种变体真的被证明具有高度传染性但不致死
那么这可能是Covid的末日的开始。

假设携带Omicron抗体的人对Delta菌株有免疫力，那么一个新的非致命菌株占领世界并取代Delta菌株，将成为Covid的末日。
新的非致命性菌株占领世界并取代三角洲菌株将是
理想的方式是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r4rvqm/omicron_could_cause_a_massive_bull_run/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r4rvqm/omicron_could_cause_a_massive_bull_run/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 10:57:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If somehow this variant does turn out to be highly contagious but non-lethal then this could be the beginning of the end of Covid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assuming someone carrying Omicron antibodies is immune to the Delta strain, a new non lethal strain taking over the world and replacing Delta would be the ideal way to end this pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Encouraging Omicron to spread is going to spread delta-immunity across the 3rd world much faster than vaccines ever could.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course we won’t really know for a couple of weeks just how deadly this strain is, but if early reports are true and it does turn out to be non-lethal this could be massive for the world and of course markets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[本杰明-格雷厄姆《聪明的投资者》一书摘要]]></title><description><![CDATA[聪明的投资者

 * 一项投资业务是在彻底分析后能保证本金安全和适当回报的业务。
   本金的安全和足够的回报。其他都是投机。
 * 投机者对股票市场波动的态度在于试图
   预测并从市场波动中获利。
 *...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4ojsl/benjamin_graham_the_intelligent_investor_book/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4ojsl/benjamin_graham_the_intelligent_investor_book/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 10:45:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Intelligent Investor&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An investment operation is one which upon thorough analysis promises safety of principal and an adequate return. Anything else is speculation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speculators attitude toward stock market movements lies in trying to anticipate and profit from market fluctuations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Investor&amp;#39;s primary interest lies in acquiring and holding suitable securities at suitable prices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unintelligent speculation is speculation when you think you are investing, any trades done on margin, doing it seriously instead of a pastime, risking more than you can afford to lose.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you are going to speculate, put a small amount aside and don&amp;#39;t add money because you are up. Understand that you in fact are speculating and be prepared to lose.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An investor cannot hope for better than average results by buying IPOs or &amp;quot;Hot&amp;quot; stocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Defensive Investor – Interested in safety and freedom from bother. Purchase investment funds vs creating a stock portfolio, use investment counsel firm, or dollar-cost average.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aggressive Investor – To enjoy a reasonable chance of success, the investor must follow policies which are sound and promising and are NOT popular on Wall Street.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must be either a defensive/conservative investor or an aggressive/enterprising investor. You can&amp;#39;t be 50/50.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speculative stock movements are carried too far in both directions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Savings Accounts can also be a good choice in lieu of bonds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do NOT buy on margin. You are speculating.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the investors funds are placed into high grade short maturity bonds (&amp;amp;lt;7 years), he will not be affected by market prices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Longer term bonds and equities will vary during his lifetime and he must be prepared for this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Investment of most intelligent when it is most businesslike.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Defensive Investor&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferred Stocks are not usually a good investment. It carries no share in the company&amp;#39;s profits beyond a fixed dividend. Thus the preferred holder lacks both the legal claim of a bondholder (Creditor) and the profit possibilities of a common stockholder (Partner). You are dependent on the ability and desire of the company to pay dividends on its common stock. They are under no obligation to pay you unless they pay the common shareholder. This investment vehicle is better for corporations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The choice of a corporate bond vs tax free municipal bond is made by the tax rate payed by the individual. Example – If a municipal pays 30% less than a corporate bond. The investor was at a tax bracket above 30% he would have a net saving by choosing the municipal bond. The opposite is true if the tax was below 30%. Usually tax-free bonds are better for individuals in high tax brackets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only invest in high quality bonds – AAA, AA, A. Do NOT invest in lower quality (2nd grade) issues to get a higher return. Stay away from high yield &amp;quot;Junk Bonds&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rules for Defensive Common Stock Component – A. Adequate diversification but not excessive B. Company should be large, prominent, and conservatively financed C. Long record of dividend payments D. Have a limit on the price willing to pay. Say 25x average earnings over the last 7 years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Defensive investors should usually stay away from Growth Stocks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of the most persuasive test of high quality is uninterrupted record of dividend payments for the last 20 years or more. The defensive investor might be justified in limiting his purchases to those.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock Selection – Adequate size, strong financial condition (Current ratio 2/1), positive earnings for the past 10 years, uninterrupted dividends for the past 20 years, EPS growth of at least 33% in the past 10 years, P/E of less than 15 for the last 3 years earnings, current price not more than 1.5x book value&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short vs Long Maturity Bonds – if the investor wants to assure himself against a decline in the principal of his bond but at the cost of a lower annual yield and loss of possibility of a gain in principal, pick short maturity bonds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It might be best for the conservative investor to concentrate on issues selling at a close approx. to their tangible asset value (book value). Say not more than 1/3 above that figure. Consider this a premium an extra fee paid for the advantage of a stock exchange listing and ability to quickly sell/buy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But just because a stock is selling for its book value doesn&amp;#39;t make it a good investment. The investor should demand a satisfactory P/E ratio, strong financial position, and the prospect that its earnings will at least be maintained over the year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The risk of paying too high a price for good quality issues is not the chief hazard confronting the average invest. Observation is that the chief losses to investors come from the purchase of low quality issues at times of favorable business conditions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aggressive Investor&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Growth Stock – one which has increased their per share earnings in the past at well above the rate for common stocks and is generally expected to continue to do so.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Growth stocks have 2 problems – Growth stocks with good records and apparently good prospects sell at correspondingly high prices. The investor maybe right in his judgement of the prospects and still not do well. Merely because he overpaid for the expected prosperity. The 2nd is his judgment as the future may prove wrong. Rapid growth can&amp;#39;t last forever.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay away from IPO&amp;#39;s/Common stock offerings. They tend to be offered in &amp;quot;favorable&amp;quot; market conditions for the sellers, not the buyers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The habit of the market is to overvalue common stocks which have been showing excellent growth, but it will also undervalue companies that are out of favor because unsatisfactory developments of a temporary nature.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If looking at growth companies, concentrate on the larger companies that are going through a period of unpopularity. Smaller companies don&amp;#39;t have the resources to withstand the storm and the market is slower to react to improvement vs larger companies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 major sources of undervaluation. A. currently disappointing results and B. unpopularity. But make sure these are temporary and not permanent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The investor should require an indication of at least reasonable stability of earnings over the past decade. No years of earnings deficit plus size and strength to meet possible setbacks. The ideal combination here is that of a large and prominent company selling both well below its past average price and its past average P/E ratio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Secondary Company – one that is not a leader in a fairly important industry. They tend to be undervalued at all times. Buy them only when they are at &amp;quot;Bargain&amp;quot; prices. Bargain being a stock that has an indicated value 50% above the share price.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ways to profit from secondary buys. A. The dividends are relatively high. B. The reinvested earnings are high relative to price paid and will affect the price. C. A bull market is most generous to lower priced issues. D. Smaller companies may be acquired by larger.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The broadest category of investments for the enterprising investor are undervalued stocks of secondary issues. Invest in these only when they can be bought at 2/3 or less of indicated value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Market Fluctuations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 ways to profit from pendulum swings in the market A. Timing – anticipate the direction of the market and buy/sell accordingly (Very Difficult to do). B. Pricing – buying or selling when the stock are quoted above or below fair value. You may do dollar cost averaging when the market is fair value or undervalued to replicate this strategy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A less ambitious form of pricing is the simple effort that you do not pay too much for your stocks. This may work for the defensive investor who is planning on holding long term. You can dollar cost average during fair or low value markets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bull Market Signs – Historically high price levels, high P/E ratios, low dividend yields against bond yields, speculation on margin, lots of public offerings of low quality stocks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The more successful a company, the more likely its price will fluctuate widely. Secondary issues will also fluctuate more widely than major ones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Never buy a stock because it has gone up or sell because it has gone down.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The speculators primary interest lie in anticipating and profiting from market fluctuations. The investor&amp;#39;s primary interest lies in acquiring and holding suitable securities at good prices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Buy-Low Sell High – very difficult to do, so instead increase the proportion of bonds in your portfolio during bull markets and reduce the common stock element. Say 75B/25S during bull markets and 25B/75S during bear and 50/50 during fair value. This allows the investor to feel as if they are doing something and to prevent you from following the crowd.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[周一开幕的好运符]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4obfa/good_luck_charm_for_monday_opening/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4obfa/good_luck_charm_for_monday_opening/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 09:29:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[期货市场现在上涨，可能在周一走向反弹？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看到期货市场上涨了1%左右，这是否预示着周一可能会出现
周一的反弹？我知道，如果期货上涨，并不总是意味着市场会上涨。
市场将上涨，但我对这种情况感到好奇。对不起，我是个新手
问题，我只是想了解一切]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4m67c/futures_market_up_right_now_possibly_heading_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4m67c/futures_market_up_right_now_possibly_heading_for/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 08:33:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I saw the futures market up by around 1 percent, does this signal a possibly rebound for Monday? I know that if futures are up, it doesn’t always mean the markets will be up, but I’m curious in this case. Sorry this is a really newbie question I’m just trying to learn everything&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我们捐赠的大猩猩今晚上了60分钟的节目]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4hryh/the_gorillas_we_donated_to_are_on_60_minutes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4hryh/the_gorillas_we_donated_to_are_on_60_minutes/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 08:33:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[🌈🐻当SPY下跌2%时]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4hd3s/when_spy_drops_2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4hd3s/when_spy_drops_2/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 07:21:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["风险容忍度是指投资者在市场大跌时忍受投资损失的情绪和心理能力，而不会卖出或过度担心，如失眠。要知道一个投资组合是否适合你的风险承受能力，你需要对自己残酷地诚实。" [BH Wiki]]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4kin0/risk_tolerance_is_an_investors_emotional_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4kin0/risk_tolerance_is_an_investors_emotional_and/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 06:42:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我不觉得超重--梅布-法布尔关于全球多元化的文章]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4gqjh/i_dont_feel_overweight_article_on_global/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4gqjh/i_dont_feel_overweight_article_on_global/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 06:42:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪斯尼的 "安康 "赢得票房]]></title><description><![CDATA[迪斯尼在延长的假期中继续其在美国票房中的统治地位。
周末，随着动画片《安康》的上映，该片在周三的票房达到4030万美元。
该片在周三至周日期间在3980家影院上映，获得4030万美元的票房。
戏院上映。

尽管在周末的前10名中名列前茅...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4fnqv/disneys_encanto_wins_the_box_office/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4fnqv/disneys_encanto_wins_the_box_office/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 06:16:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disney continued its dominance of the U.S. box office over the extended holiday weekend with the release of the animated feature “Encanto,” which grossed $40.3 million across the Wednesday-through-Sunday span from a release in 3,980 theaters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite landing in the top berth of the weekend’s top 10 and scoring the best opening weekend numbers for an animated feature in the pandemic era, the five-day gross for “Encanto” was considerably lower than the box office takes for earlier Disney animated films that opened over the Thanksgiving period, including “Frozen II” in 2019 ($123.7 million), “Ralph Breaks the Internet” in 2018 ($84.6 million) and “Coco” in 2017 ($71 million).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, “Encanto” had strong competition from last week’s box office champ, Ghostbusters: Afterlife,” which finished in a close second place behind the Disney film with $35.2 million from 4,315 theaters during the five-day haul. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.benzinga.com/news/21/11/24321697/disneys-encanto-elbows-aside-ghostbusters-afterlife-at-us-holiday-weekend-box-office&quot;&gt;Walt Disney Company (The) (NYSE:DIS), Amazon.com, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMZN) - Disney&amp;#39;s &amp;#39;Encanto&amp;#39; Elbows Aside &amp;#39;Ghostbusters: Afterlife&amp;#39; At US Holiday-Weekend Box Office | Benzinga&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔并不担心。你担心吗？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4anhu/powell_aint_worried_are_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4anhu/powell_aint_worried_are_you/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 06:16:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[销售和税收--你有什么想法？]]></title><description><![CDATA[你对销售和税收有什么看法？

我来来回回--我父亲总是说'现在你得为短期收益缴税了
我的继父总是说："是的，但利润的税收仍然是利润"。

我知道税收很糟糕，但我也明白，我为我工作的工资交税。
而且实际上我有...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r48czc/selling_and_taxes_what_are_your_thoughts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r48czc/selling_and_taxes_what_are_your_thoughts/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 06:16:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What are your thoughts on selling and taxes?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I go back and forth - my dad always says ‘now you gotta pay taxes on short term gains’ and my stepdad always says ‘yes but taxes on profit are still profit’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I get taxes suck; but I also understand that I pay taxes on wages I work for; and actually have to do work for that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have an IRA, 401k, and brokerage so I take advantage of tax shelters and am mostly long term with some trades when profit is high; but am interested to learn people’s thoughts on this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团。"我们会买入任何跌停板"]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 花旗集团(Citigroup)的分析师也表示，"我们会买入任何跌幅"，并指出
> 其看跌清单并没有显示出重大的红旗。"估值看起来
> 但其他因素（信贷利差、资金流动）还没有特别扩大。
>特别扩展，"花旗写道，18个红旗中的7.5个...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4hd64/citigroup_we_would_buy_into_any_dip/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4hd64/citigroup_we_would_buy_into_any_dip/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 05:52:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Analysts at Citigroup also said that &amp;quot;we would buy into any dip,&amp;quot; noting that its bearish checklist doesn&amp;#39;t indicate significant red flags. &amp;quot;Valuations look stretched, but other factors (credit spreads, fund flows) are not yet especially extended,&amp;quot; Citi writes, with 7.5 out of 18 red flags triggered in its measures of global markets while the U.S. is seeing 9.5 of 18.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you guys expecting the strong rebound and green end of the year?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[买入跌停板或等待市场复苏]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着旅行限制和紧急状态的到来，随着它的出现
期货显示出有希望的市场复苏，你认为明天会如何？市场是否
市场将完全恢复，并从黑色星期五的病毒恐慌中反弹出来。
变种恐慌，还是人们将开始意识到疫苗...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4jnvr/buying_the_dip_or_waiting_for_a_market_recover/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4jnvr/buying_the_dip_or_waiting_for_a_market_recover/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 05:40:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As travel restrictions and state of emergencies are settling in, along with it futures showing promising market recovery, how do you think tomorrow will do? Is the market going to recover fully and bounce back from Black Friday’s covid variant scare, or will people start to realize that the vaccine and up to date boosters are still effective in containing the virus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are your moved for tomorrow?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Not to be biased whatsoever, but I personally believe that after delta’s variant scare, I believe that pharmaceuticals and government officials are better prepared to research the virus and assign its concern accordingly; whether it be creating a whole new vaccine (very, very unlikely) or safety measures (vaccine/booster mandates, social distancing, hospital beds, etc). In addition, I believe that it has been proven that the tech sector in particular has shown great resistance to virus. From learning from past events, investors, like myself, are going to be less weary of the dips and expand holdings into strong companies like AMD, Microsoft, Apple, etc. Idk how reliable futures are but they’ve shown to be very bullish for tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在接近网络泡沫和2008年崩溃的高峰期时，情况是怎样的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一个相当新的投资者（Covid崩溃后，大约在六月底开始投资）。
我想知道我在哪里可以找到一些关于2000年和2008年崩盘前交易员/投资者的心理学的阅读材料
我想知道在哪里可以找到一些关于2000年和2008年崩盘前的交易员/投资者的心理学读物。我今年16岁，所以我
我没有真正经历过金融危机，我相信...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4mdnd/what_was_it_like_near_the_peak_of_the_dot_com/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4mdnd/what_was_it_like_near_the_peak_of_the_dot_com/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 05:27:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m a fairly new investor (post Covid crash—started investing around late June) and I was wondering where I could find some reading material on the psychology of traders/investors before the crashes in 2000 and 2008. I’m 16 years old so I haven’t really lived through a financial crisis, I believe it’s crucial to study the history of the markets to have better judgment about the future of the stock market. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Im super curious as to what people were thinking about the state of market prior to the market crashing. If people could provide some articles, forum pages, papers etc concerning this topic that would be very helpful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你们中的哪一个失败者需要工作？你妻子的男朋友的哥哥是那里的副经理，可以给你介绍。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4d59u/which_of_you_losers_needs_a_job_your_wifes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4d59u/which_of_you_losers_needs_a_job_your_wifes/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 03:54:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你是一个懒惰的长期投资者，正在寻找一些经典投资书籍的Cliffs Notes版本吗？ u/captmorgan50已经为你提供了帮助。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4jgo2/are_you_a_lazy_longterm_investor_looking_for_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4jgo2/are_you_a_lazy_longterm_investor_looking_for_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 03:23:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME中200%的净值（100%净值+100%保证金）。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4cf4z/200_net_worth_in_gme_100_net_worth_100_margin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4cf4z/200_net_worth_in_gme_100_net_worth_100_margin/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 01:08:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爸爸总是提供]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4bp4u/papa_always_delivers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4bp4u/papa_always_delivers/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 01:08:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[反VAXXERS!
 https://t.co/icI7ZhsOOK]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465076453536583696</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465076453536583696</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 23:43:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[弗兰克-帕亚诺教授的投资入门]]></title><description><![CDATA[弗兰克-帕亚诺教授的投资介绍

 * 必须知道你的投资时间跨度
   * 短期投资 - 1年或以下
   * 中线投资 - 2-5年
   * 长期投资 - 5年以上
 * 投资是流动性的（股票）还是非流动性的（房地产）？
 *...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4bzsy/intro_to_investments_by_professor_frank_paiano/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4bzsy/intro_to_investments_by_professor_frank_paiano/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 23:43:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intro into Investments by Professor Frank Paiano&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must know your time horizon for investments

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short Term Investments – 1 year or less&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intermediate Term Investments – 2-5 years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Long Term Investments – 5 plus years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is the investment Liquid(stocks) or Illiquid (Real Estate)?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;#39;t buy preferred shares or convertible shares of stock. They have tax advantages that individual investors can&amp;#39;t get&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Derivative assets(futures) - derive their value from an underlying security or something else (very speculative)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stocks – you are the owner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonds – you are the bank&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short term securities – cash = principal is safe. Inflation risk still exists.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mutual Funds – managed on your behalf&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stocks have historically done better than bonds but move up and down more (Do you want to eat well or do you want to sleep well?)

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stocks have a greater distribution range than bonds. IE – they up 30% one year and down 10% the next&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Investment returns over time tend to mirror a normal distribution or &amp;quot;bell curve&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The greater the standard deviation, the wider the distribution of returns and the risker the investment. Stocks have wider distribution and more risk than bonds. But long term they provide a higher average return&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;#39;t chase the next big thing. You will lose&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;#39;t speculate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do NOT invest in an annuity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short Term Investments - Cash

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 year or less&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Usually Guaranteed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very liquid&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Low Risk-Low Return&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good place for emergency fund&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can lose purchasing power if they don&amp;#39;t keep up with inflation. Which they sometimes don&amp;#39;t&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Common types&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Savings accounts – stated rate of interest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Series EE savings bonds - Discount method – buy for $50 and redeem for $100 later.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Series I savings bonds – indexed to inflation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Treasury Bills – 1, 3 or 6-month maturity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Certificate of Deposit (CD) – have to be on deposit for a certain amount of time. From days to years. They usually rollover if you don&amp;#39;t stop them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Money Market Mutual Fund – mutual fund that invests only in short term securities. Unlike savings, they are not federally guaranteed but are considered risk free because other companies will bail them out in a problem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mutual Funds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose a family, not a fund&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional money management and diversification&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DCA – Dollar cost average is a great way to invest in mutual funds. You don&amp;#39;t worry what the market is doing or where it is going.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;#39;t try to time the market. DCA!!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep a long-term horizon and DCA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Most mutual fund investors BUY HIGH and SELL LOW. Don&amp;#39;t do this. Do not bail out of stocks when the market is down and buy on the way up. Most mutual fund investors do worse than the funds they invest in.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose a fund family and stick with them. Re-evaluate your investments once a year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PITA (Pain in the A**) factor is low&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management fee - Between 0.05% and 2% based on asset value&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12b-1 – &amp;quot;Advertisement fee&amp;quot; usually under 1%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trading Cost – not disclosed in the prospectus. Look at the fund turnover. Higher turnover = higher trading costs. Lower turnover = lower trading costs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Load – charge a commission when the fund is bought. Paid to the financial representative. Usually 3-5%

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A – front end load – paid upfront&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B – back end load – paid when shares are sold&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deferred sales charge – ladder down then go to zero. 5,4,3,2,1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No Load – no commission when the fund is bought

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No sales representative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12b-1 Fee can&amp;#39;t be over 0.25%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I, F = don&amp;#39;t have a &amp;quot;load&amp;quot; but charge a &amp;quot;management fee&amp;quot; of usually 1-2%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Index funds are usually true no load funds – be careful because some 401K&amp;#39;s have index funds with very high fee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;REIT – Real Estate Investment Trust&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pass through investments that must distribute 95% of earnings to shareholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own various forms of real estate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good long-term investment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No PITA factor unlike being a landlord&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very liquid&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They are a hedge against inflation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No management concerns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Offer diversification&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stocks&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow general public ownership in a business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Historically the best return is in stocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very liquid&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Primary Market – IPO&amp;#39;s – don&amp;#39;t get involved in this&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Secondary Market – where most investors trade&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay away from OTC (Over the Counter) markets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bid (Sell) - Ask (Buy) – what they will buy or sell a security for. The market makers make the spread between the bid/ask and provide liquidity to the market&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;#39;t buy on margin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;#39;t sell short&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dow Jones – price weighted index of 30 companies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S+P 500 – market cap weighted index of 500 companies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MSCI and EAFE – index of foreign companies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock spin off – conversion of a company&amp;#39;s subsidiaries into a standalone company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock split – increase in number of shares outstanding. IE 2 for 1. You had 100 shares at $10 but now you have 200 shares at $5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share buyback – company buys back their own shares and this increases the EPS because you have less shares&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stocks can have different classes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A – original shares&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B, C, D, E, etc – companies can have different share classes that have different rights or benefits. IE – higher dividend, more votes, etc. look at what you are buying&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You want cash dividends, not stock dividends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Valuation techniques&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fundamental analysis of finance holds that the value of a stock is based on the present value of its future cash flows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The worth of a company is primarily based on the earnings the company will produce in the future (difficult to predict)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The most fundamental influence on stock prices is the level and duration of the future growth earnings and dividends. However, future earnings are dividends are NOT easily estimated even by professionals – Burton Malkiel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is no single financial ratio(P/E) that can summarize the general state of affairs of the company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;P/E ratio – current price of a company divided by the earnings per share. Industries tend to have certain P/E ratios. Some tend to have higher or lower P/E&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Historically P/E was supposed to match its growth rate. IE – 20% growth rate = 20 P/E. But P/E have been 100+ at times&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Growth stocks tend to have high P/E – must have very high earnings to justify&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Value stocks tend to have low P/E – doesn&amp;#39;t necessarily mean it is a good buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The P/E ratio tells you how long to earn back your investment back. IE – P/E 10 takes 10 years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Price/Sales ratio (P/S) – same as P/E but you used sales instead of earnings. Usually used for fast growing companies who don&amp;#39;t have any earnings. Wall St. justified high prices on internet stocks during the late 90&amp;#39;s by using a P/S ratio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Price/Book Ratio (P/B) – Book value is assets minus liabilities. P/B ratio is current price divided by book value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Price Ratio Analysis - Expected stock price =

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5-year average P/E or P/S or P/Cash Flow x Current EPS X (1 + EPS Growth Estimate)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Price Ratio Analysis has not been very reliable analysis tool&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dividend Discount Model (DDM)

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of a stock are valued on the basis of the present value of the future dividend streams the stock is projected to produce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This strategy worked very well during the 2001 downturn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Value of a stock = present value of all future dividend payments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present value – the value today of a lump sum to be received at some future date&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Different types of DDM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zero Growth – assumes dividends will continue at a fixed rate indefinitely. Works well for stable income producing stocks

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take annual dividends and divide by required rate of return (you generate this number)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IE – Dividend of $3 a share and 6% required rate of return = $50 share value&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zero growth is another way to think about dividend yield&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IE – Dividend divided by market price = rate of return&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Example – Utility stock pays a $2.86 dividend. Current price is $75. If we want an 8% return take 2.86/0.08 = $35.75 – stock is overvalued based on our expected 8% return&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can also flip the formula to get what the market thinks the return is going to be. Take the dividend/price. 2.86/75 = 3.81%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Constant perpetual growth model – assumes dividends will grow at a specified rate perpetuity into the future. Good for companies with consistent dividend growth

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Example – dividend of $10 per share and a 5% dividend growth rate. Required rate of return = 15%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(10 x 1.05) / (15% - 5%) = 10.5 / 10% (0.1) = $105&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3M example - $230.37 per share. $5.44 dividend. Dividend growth 8%. Required rate of return 13%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(5.44 x 1.08) / (13 – 8) = 5.87 / 5% = $117.50 – overvalued based on example. But this formula is very susceptible to changes in required rate of return&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The constant perpetual growth model is very sensitive to dividend growth and required return rates plugged into the formula&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can&amp;#39;t use DDM for a company that isn&amp;#39;t paying dividends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dividend growth rates are very difficult to estimate. Unless you are looking at large cap, well established companies. But for smaller, faster growing companies in new industries, it is almost impossible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DDM – The value of a stock is based on the present value of its future cash flows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This strategy is good for prudent, long term investors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The value line investment survey is a good place to get your information. You can get this information at some library&amp;#39;s.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doing all this math only tilts the odds in our favor. It doesn&amp;#39;t guarantee that it will work like we wanted. Ask yourself a simple question. Would I want to own this company if I had X dollars? That is the real question.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is no one financial ratio that tells you to buy or sell a stock&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Balance Sheet

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Financial summary of firm&amp;#39;s assets, liabilities, and shareholders&amp;#39; equity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assets – liabilities = shareholder equity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Current – Less than 1 year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Long Term – More than 1 year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Income Statement

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Financial summary of the operating results for a specified period&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue – expenses = income&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cash Flow Statement

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Financial summary of the cash flow of the company and other events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reports

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10K – annual&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10Q – quarterly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Financial Ratios – remember there is no one ratio to consider

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;P/E – Price/Earnings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Most popular stock market ratio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Price/EPS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tells you how long in years it will take the company to earn back its price. P/E of 5 = 5 years to earn back your investment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look at competitor&amp;#39;s P/E ratio. Don&amp;#39;t just look at one number&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The P/E ratio should approximately match the growth rate. PEG ratio of 1. Higher than 1 = P/E is higher than growth rate. Less than 1 = P/E is lower than growth rate. More than 1 is common now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dividend per share&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dividend/Number of shares outstanding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dividend Yield&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dividend per share/market price&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dividend payout ratio – how much of the earnings are being paid out in dividends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dividend per share/EPS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Book Value&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shareholders equity/Number of shares outstanding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It tells you the &amp;quot;liquid&amp;quot; value of the company if you sold off all the assets and paid off all the debts and paid off the shareholders. Many companies trade above book value because they are worth more intact than split up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Price to book value per share – tells an investor how far above the market value is above the book value&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;market price/book value&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-4+ is not uncommon. IE – Book value of $5 and market value of $20&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Less than 1 is bad because the company is in danger because raiders might try to take the company and sell off the assets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Price to cash flow and price to sales – don&amp;#39;t use these&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A way to &amp;quot;value&amp;quot; companies without earnings. Many companies were valued with this during the internet boom of the late 90&amp;#39;s&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profitability ratio

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Net Profit Margin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rate of profit earned after expenses and taxes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Varies based on industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Net Income/Total Revenue&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gross Profit Margin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rate of profit earned from gross profit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gross Profit/Total Revenue&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Operating Margin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rate of profit being earned from net income adjusting for non-cash items&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Operating Income/Total Revenue&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The higher the better with the profitability ratios. But check your competitors and see what is the normal for your industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Return on assets (ROA)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Measures profitability relative to its total assets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Net Income/Total Assets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Return on equity (ROE)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Measure of the overall profitability of a company in relation to shareholders equity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Net Income/Total Stockholder equity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Return on equity is sensitive to the amount of debt a company carries. If a company carries more debt, it will have a higher ROE.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ROA and ROE can be drastically different, especially if a company carries lots of debt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Liquidly Ratios

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Current Ratio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Current Assets/Current Liabilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Current ratio of 1.0 or higher is good. It means you have enough money to fund your short-term obligations. Higher number is better&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage Ratios

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debt to equity ratio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Long-term debt/Total stockholder equity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A higher ratio means that the company is financing its growth with debt. The lower the number the better&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sir Issac Newton – I can calculate the movement of the stars but not the madness of men&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maynard Keynes – The market can stay irrational longer than you can stay solvent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From 1963-1998 the S+P 500 Index funds beat the active funds in 22 of the 36 years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Many mutual funds have high expenses and high turnover rates. They also have a short time horizon. This makes it hard for them to beat the market.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you hear – BE CAREFUL!!!

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&amp;#39;s a new era&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&amp;#39;s different this time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The old ways of valuing stocks are gone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ben Graham – the investing public is incorrigible. It will buy anything, at any price, if there seems to be some action in progress.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mania&amp;#39;s will end with a crash every time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ben Graham – Be greedy when others are fearful and be fearful when others are greedy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;John Templeton – Bear markets are born of pessimism, grow on skepticism, mature on optimism, and die on euphoria. The time of maximum pessimism is the best time to buy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diversification – spreading your investments across asset classes to eliminate some, but not all risk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diversification – guarantees that some investments will not do well any given year. You have to look at the whole portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cash has not been the top performer vs stocks or bonds in the last 25 years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[萨蒂亚-纳德拉出售他在MSFT的一半股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[萨提亚-纳德拉，在11月22日至11月23日期间卖出了~838.6K。股票被
价值范围为334.37美元和349.22美元。这使他的绝对报价
的绝对报价达到831K。微软CEO萨提亚-纳德拉披露出售839K
股票。

这些销售与行使期权或...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4de7y/satya_nadella_sells_half_of_his_shares_of_msft/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4de7y/satya_nadella_sells_half_of_his_shares_of_msft/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 23:30:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Satya Nadella, sold  ~838.6K between November 22 and November 23. Shares were sold in a value  scope of $334.37 and $349.22. This brings his absolute offer to build  up to 831K offers. Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella discloses the sale of  839K shares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These sales were not related to an options exercise or an established 10b5-1 plan and were his largest sales ever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link to the SEC filing: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/789019/000106299321011647/xslF345X03/form4.xml&quot;&gt;https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/789019/000106299321011647/xslF345X03/form4.xml&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BABA的持包人你还有希望吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的BABA股票的平均成本约为177美元。它占投资组合的13%左右
而目前的价格为133美元，下跌了约25%。

我相信BABA最终会回到300美元以上，但我不认为它将会
回归的速度足以证明我锁定资本的年限是合理的。
会...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4eqvn/baba_bagholders_do_you_still_have_hope/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4eqvn/baba_bagholders_do_you_still_have_hope/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 22:51:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My average cost of BABA shares is around $177. Its around 13% of the portfolio and currently at a price of 133 down around 25%. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe in BABA eventually coming back to 300+ BUT i don&amp;#39;t think its going to come back fast enough to justify being capital locked for the number of years i would potentially have to wait to make the investment worthwhile. If i sold now i would have to take around 15k loss- it hurts but i hate looking at the position... especially on something i don&amp;#39;t believe in anymore. Anyone else in a similar situation?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[破解TQQQ的神话]]></title><description><![CDATA[似乎很多发帖人都在传播很多关于TQQQ（以及一般的杠杆ETF）的错误信息。
杠杆ETF），所以我确信很多读者已经内化了许多错误的神话。
许多错误的神话，我想破除这些神话。

TQQQ与3倍QQQ相比，总会随着时间的推移而衰减。

错

基本上TQQQ每天收盘后都会重新平衡。基本上，TQQQ每天收盘后都会进行调整。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4d4wt/mythbusting_tqqq/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4d4wt/mythbusting_tqqq/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 22:51:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seems many posters are circulating a lot of misinformation about TQQQ (and leveraged ETFs in general) so I&amp;#39;m certain a lot of readers have internalized many false myths that I want to bust:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TQQQ will always decay over time vs 3x QQQ&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FALSE&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically TQQQ rebalances daily after the close.  The purpose of the rebalancing is to ensure TQQQ will perform at 3x the next day so it will reduce or increase it&amp;#39;s exposure appropriately.  This rebalancing means TQQQ will have a variance to 3x QQQ over time.  If bullish, TQQQ will be &amp;gt;3x, bearish &amp;lt;3x which are both positive developments for investors.  The problem is choppy markets will cause TQQQ to decline in value vs. QQQ which is what a lot of myths focus on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bloggers have coined this &amp;quot;volatility decay&amp;quot; and this is a bad misnomer.  Decay implies the rebalancing is always bad as in negative to the returns on TQQQ.  For example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On February 19, 2020 the pre-pandemic closing high for QQQ is $236.98, for TQQQ is $118.06 (pre-2021 split).  On March 23, 2020, QQQ closed at $170.46, a drop of 28.1%.  A 3x drop would be 84.2% and many bloggers would have you believe the drop would be even worse with volatility decay --  WRONG.  On March 23, 2020, TQQQ closed at $35.62, a drop of 69.8% which while significant is still way less than 3x and a &lt;em&gt;positive&lt;/em&gt; variance of 14.4%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, let&amp;#39;s take it from there to the close on September 1, 2020.  QQQ is at $299.92, a 75.9% gain.  3x would be 227.8% but TQQQ closed at $169.74 a 376.5% increase and a huge &lt;em&gt;positive&lt;/em&gt; variance of 148.7% to 3x QQQ.  Thus, the rebalancing or &amp;quot;volatility decay&amp;quot; can be positive or negative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TQQQ will go to zero one day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FALSE&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only way to have TQQQ drop to zero is if the NASDAQ 100 drops 33.4%+ in &lt;em&gt;one&lt;/em&gt; trading session.  Remember, it has to be &lt;em&gt;one&lt;/em&gt; trading session.  Just think about that, what would it take for the index to drop that much in a single day?  Probably something that makes money worthless like a nuclear war or huge asteroid strike.  And then we have circuit breakers on the exchanges.  Not going into detail but a drop of 20% should shut down trading for the day and TQQQ will rebalance.  Even if this kept on and on the bottom line is TQQQ will continue to exist.  Want more evidence?  SQQQ is still alive and kicking despite the massive bull market and many reverse stock splits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also bloggers have cited many leveraged ECN&amp;#39;s and commodity ETFs closing and citing contango as a built in negative factor.  There are so many problems with this.  TQQQ is based off stock index and while contango is a real thing it is inapplicable to TQQQ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My Opinion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me TQQQ has been great for swing trading and writing options on.  But I watch it daily, use technical analysis, and have been lucky to sniff out major drops before the bottom and sell, and then get back in.  Yes, I got murdered on the way down but I recovered it all and then some.  Buy and hold (and the implied &lt;em&gt;forget&lt;/em&gt;) is IMHO too dangerous no matter what backtesting tells you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is the big question; will you have the discipline to sell out when the next big correction hits?  And also will you buy back in before it completely bounces back?  If you don&amp;#39;t think you can do both then I would stay away from TQQQ.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[杰克-博格尔说，国际股票投资（VXUS，VT）是不必要的。为什么你仍然投资于它们？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我很欣赏最近围绕国际股票投资的讨论
从u/Chiron494 [/u/Chiron494]的帖子中，我很欣赏最近关于国际股票投资的讨论，比如这一篇
[https://www.reddit.com/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3jdhi/as_a_us_based_investor_what_percentage_of_your/?utm_medium=android_app&utm_source=share]

然而，作为一个新手...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4e07c/jack_bogle_said_international_equity_investments/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4e07c/jack_bogle_said_international_equity_investments/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 22:38:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve appreciated the recent discussion around international equity investments from posts by &lt;a href=&quot;/u/Chiron494&quot;&gt;u/Chiron494&lt;/a&gt; like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3jdhi/as_a_us_based_investor_what_percentage_of_your/?utm_medium=android_app&amp;amp;utm_source=share&quot;&gt;this one&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, as a newbie I&amp;#39;m a bit shocked at the amount of people who invest 20%+ in international, some investing even up to 40% because it matches the allocations of VT. Is it simply a case of diversification?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jack Bogle, in Common Sense on Mutual Funds, writes: “Overseas investments—holdings in the corporations of other nations—are not essential, nor even necessary, to a well-diversified portfolio. For investors who disagree—and there are some valid reasons for global investing—we recommend limiting international investments to a maximum of 20 percent of a global equity portfolio.” 
- Excerpt from Chapter 8 of BH Guide to Investing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are your thoughts on this stance, and if you do, why do you personally invest more than this recommended amount in international equities?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: I understand that Vanguard recommends international equities much more than Jack Bogle, the individual, did during his lifetime. Thank you to everyone who has commented&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[目前，外面的泡沫是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们上一次的大泡沫是95年到00年的网络泡沫，由互联网和软件公司主导。
是由互联网和软件公司主导的。纳斯达克指数从1000
到5400点，在此期间。然后在接下来的两年里崩溃了。52%的
网络公司破产了。

我对寻找和把握时机感兴趣...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r40k6m/what_are_the_bubbles_to_out_there_at_the_moment/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r40k6m/what_are_the_bubbles_to_out_there_at_the_moment/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 21:32:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The last big bubble we had was the dot-com bubble that lasted from ‘95 to ‘00 and was fuled by the Internet and software companies. The Nasdaq went from 1000 to 5400 in this period. And crashed down the following two years. 52% of the dot-com companies went bust.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m interested finding and timing other bubbles out there, if you see more bubbles around please drop a coment. So far the most obvious one is the EV bubble. The question is also when it will burst.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s look at peak valuation ( not current )&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla - $1243.49 - $1.25 Trillion, just shy of 40% of the global market cap for vehicle production, and they produce 0.65% of the cars in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rivian - $179.47 - $150 Billion, a round 5% of the global mareket cap for vehicle production, and they produce 0% of the cars in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NIO - $66.99 - $110 Billion, a round 3.5% of the global market cap for vehicle production, and they produce 0.03% of the cars in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lucid - $64.86 - $105 Billion, around 3.5% of the global market cap for vehicle production, and they produce 0.00003% of the cars in the world this year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;XPEV - $68.42 - $54 Billion, 1.8% of the global cap, and 0.1% of global production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then you have ARVL, FSKR, NKLA, GOEV. All worth billions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我应该保留哪些记录？]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，今年是我的投资首次达到的纳税年度。
复杂程度，我想知道我真正应该保持跟踪的是什么？
以及我应该以何种 "格式 "保存它们。主要是我想避免出现
20年后，我希望自己能保留一些数据的情况。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3zq8t/what_records_should_i_keep/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r3zq8t/what_records_should_i_keep/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 21:32:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So this is the first tax year that my investments have reached the level of complexity that I am wondering what I should really be keeping track of long-term and in what &amp;quot;format&amp;quot; I should keep them.   Mainly I want to avoid a situation where 20 years from now I wish I would have kept some data that I no longer have access to, probably for tax purposes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m hoping that some of you who have discovered the hard way what you should keep on paper (or in an electronic document) would enlighten me about what is and isn&amp;#39;t useful to keep around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这是个好的买入价格吗？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4ad1q/is_this_a_good_price_to_buy_in_at/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4ad1q/is_this_a_good_price_to_buy_in_at/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 20:54:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>