<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 02:53:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[以下是今天（星期三）的市场回顾，2021年11月10日]]></title><description><![CDATA[心理市场回顾 - 2021年11月10日，星期三

股市令人眼花缭乱的涨势在下列情况下戛然而止
发布了一份关键的通货膨胀报告，该报告显示，尽管新申请的失业救济金人数达到了大流行的水平，但消费者价格的跳升幅度超过了预期。
尽管新申请的失业救济金人数达到了大流行时期的低点，但股市令人目眩的涨势还是戛然而止。证券时报
标准普尔500指数...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr6lxi/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_wednseday_nov_10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr6lxi/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_wednseday_nov_10/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 02:18:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Wednesday, November 10, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dizzying rally in the stock market came to a screeching halt following the release of a key inflation report that showed a greater than expected jump in consumer prices despite new jobless claims coming in at a pandemic-era low. The S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) closed 0.8% lower, the tech-heavy Nasdaq (QQQ) closed 1.47% in its third consecutive red day while the Dow Jones (DIA) closed 0.61% lower. The Russell 2000 (IWM), which tracks the performance of small-caps, closed 1.58% lower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning, the Labor Department released the monthly Consumer Price Index, which showed prices soared 6.2% in a year-on-year period, accelerating from September’s 5.4% YoY rate, and higher than the 5.9% expected. This represents that fastest pace of inflationary expansion since 1990, though one has to take into account easy comparisons to last year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The staying power and magnitude of inflationary pressures has, perhaps, become the central question for market participants, with companies across the board reporting rising input costs and price hikes passed on to the consumers to preserve margins. While Q3 earning results have robustly demonstrated that companies in the SPY were largely able to navigate these cost pressures, the possibility remains that if inflation runs hotter than expected for longer than expected, it could begin to hamper consumer demand. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though the Fed has commenced a tapering in the pace of quantitative easing, members of the Fed have so far maintained that supply-chain disruptions and labor market imbalances caused by the pandemic have prevented producers from keeping up with demand, particularly as we head into the busiest time of the year, the holiday season. I broadly agree with this narrative, even the Fed has conceded that inflation could last longer “than they currently assume”. The latest Fed meeting minutes said, “Most participants saw inflation risks as weighted to the upside because of concerns that supply disruptions and labor shortages might last longer and might have larger or more persistent effects on prices and wages than they currently assumed.” We’ll have to see what happens in the coming months, if inflation doesn’t begin moderating in the next 5-6 months, the Fed will likely be forced to step in and raise interest rates in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With roughly 89% of companies in the S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) having already reported earnings, 81% of those have so far posted better than expected earnings per share and 75% of those reported better than expected revenue. FactSet projects that the year-on-year earnings growth rate for the index stands at 40%, though this number has continued creeping higher as earnings season unfolds. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_110521.pdf&quot;&gt;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_110521.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No highlights today sorry, will be back tomorrow&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt; -Eleanor Roosevelt&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场时机日记：像你这样的普通人如何预测了过去1次崩盘中的9次]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们定期在这里收到对市场有疑问的人的帖子。
今天，在恒大、加密货币和天知道其他什么之间，有很多的
不确定性的原因。确切地说，我没有投资日记，但我有一个
但我对自己的投资者情绪有很好的记录，因为我开始......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qr7hcg/market_timing_diary_how_a_regular_guy_like_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qr7hcg/market_timing_diary_how_a_regular_guy_like_you/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 01:45:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Periodically, we get posts on here of people with doubts about the market. Today, between Evergrande, crypto, and lord knows what else, there are plenty of reasons for uncertainty. I don&amp;#39;t have an investing diary, exactly, but I have a pretty good account of my own investor sentiment since I started investing in 2013. My approach was Bogle-inspired, although as I note, I shifted a bit (often for bad reasons). I thought I might share them, as a good representation of timing the market, as well as illustrating other cognitive biases one might have (e.g. the way we can become overcommitted to a strategy once we have emotionally invested in it). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;January 2015: I started to get worried when the Shiller forward P/E went above 25, the level it was before the 2008 financial crisis. I have generally fretted about this, and the Buffet indicator (market cap: GDP) since then. I did shift my portfolio from being 100% domestic to include international index funds at this point (not that it did any good).  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;November 2016: I thought Trump winning the 2016 election would tank the markets (actually it did briefly upset overnight futures markets). It didn&amp;#39;t, of course. Rather, the market boomed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;October 2017: I still remember the cover of The Economist. &amp;quot;The bull market in everything&amp;quot;. I was sure that there was something afoot. There would be a few subsequent moments that felt like &amp;quot;now it&amp;#39;s about to start&amp;quot;. In February 2018 the VIX surged as the trade war accelerated and the Fed raised rates above 1%. There &lt;em&gt;was&lt;/em&gt; (and this points to the difficulty of timing) a sharp correction in December 2018, but the market almost immediately recovered.    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;August 2019: the yield curve inverted, and once again I began to thought that the end was nigh. There was going to be a recession and that was it. The rise of the S&amp;amp;P 500 into early 2020 felt suspicious to me. Arguably, this is the one time my gut might have been right. &lt;em&gt;But&lt;/em&gt; I was right for the wrong reasons. The crash of 2020 was caused by the pandemic, which I obviously hadn&amp;#39;t considered in August 2019 (nor even in January 2020). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;March 9, 2020: now, those were crazy times my friend. Some days were up double-digits and some were down by the same. It was circuit breaker city, man. Critically though, the signs of a financial crisis were there - repo markets were drying up and even treasuries were dropping.On March 9th I came damn close to shifting large amounts of my portfolio into bonds. I still have the trade confirmation, though I stopped it at the last second. The S&amp;amp;P 500 had fallen to something like 2800.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;April 9, 2020: I held through the bottom, when a strange thing started happening. The market recovered very rapidly. In a few days the S&amp;amp;P 500 was up from a low of something in the 2200s to almost 2800. I thought there was no way it could keep going like this. I remember looking at graphs (which people were posting widely at the time) showing the market through the Great Depression. One of the striking takeaways was that it hadn&amp;#39;t just been down down down followed by recovery. There were so many bear traps. Could this be one of them? It was at this point that I broke from Bogle advice. As the market recovered, I shifted modest amounts into bonds reasoning that when the real bottom appeared I would buy everything cheap. A completely irrational factor in my move: relatives bragging that they saw the crash coming and pulled everything out just in time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;June 6, 2020: as my fear of bear traps receded, I reverted back to my long-term optimal portfolio. One day later, the market saw the biggest crash since the heady days of March. A-ha! I thought. It turns out I was right all along. And &lt;em&gt;of course&lt;/em&gt; I was - unemployment had just hit the highest levels since the Great Depression, some states were prematurely reopening from the pandemic, etc. I didn&amp;#39;t sell everything, but I maintained an overly bond-heavy portfolio for my age (mid-30s). As the market rose further in July and August, I continued to shift assets to bonds (I also shifted my bond holdings to TIPS which did work out... so far). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;September 2020: through August I had read the story about Softbank&amp;#39;s sometimes insane bets on tech, and was again sure that a crash was nigh. I felt bearish - one day I went running in the woods and literally saw a family of black bears crossing the road. And indeed, the S&amp;amp;P 500 started to correct (the Nasdaq somewhat more). And yet... pretty soon after, it was back to normal. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;January 22, 2021: this story involves my active trading account, which represents a very small proportion of my investments. When GME started to surge to $65 (vs. $4 in August 2020) following the beginnings of the campaign on Wall Street Bets, I was sure that the stock would fall. I bought OTM puts. When it rose more, I bought more OTM puts - and I even was able to time the peak correctly the second time. Obviously, the first set of puts became worthless, but interestingly, so did the second because I had bought them when volatility was so high that the stock would have to hit ridiculously low levels for my puts to print.      &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m sure that there are other folks out there who are better investors than I. Maybe they have the time to do research and find diamonds in the rough. Maybe they have the discipline to avoid going double or nothing (and to resist confirmation bias) when their theses prove false. And hey, maybe they are smarter and possessed of some abilities that I lack. But I would have to say that the smartest thing I&amp;#39;ve ever done is to ignore my instincts, saved, diversified, and waited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian Gain Porn. 16分钟和18,456美元 🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr0gsr/rivian_gain_porn_16_min_and_18456/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr0gsr/rivian_gain_porn_16_min_and_18456/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 01:45:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[好了......重新设置计数器]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr5jeo/welpresetting_the_counter/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr5jeo/welpresetting_the_counter/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 01:45:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么贝宝的价格这么低？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在230美元的时候购买了一些PayPal的股票，因为有人告诉我这是一个很好的买点，而且我也经常使用PayPal，而且它的业绩也不是很好。
因为我也经常使用PayPal，而且它已经有一段时间没有这么低了。
但是它就这样一直跌到了204美元？有没有人知道，如果
这是否有什么原因？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr4603/why_is_paypal_so_low/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr4603/why_is_paypal_so_low/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 01:45:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I purchased some PayPal shares at 230$ because I was told it was a good buy, and because I frequently use PayPal as well and it had not been that low in a while. But it has just continued to drop all the way down to 204$?? Does anyone know if there is a reason for this&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克应该在推特上发表关于通货膨胀率的文章，以便使其暴跌]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458590725872963595</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458590725872963595</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:43:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[https://t.co/rQX0CVaPQg]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458424227732901895</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458424227732901895</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:43:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[恒大满足付息期限，避免违约]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.nytimes.com/2021/11/10/business/evergrande-bond-deadline.html

陷入困境的房地产巨头中国恒大，至少在两个项目上支付了利息。
一位公司债券持有人表示，周三至少有两笔债券的利息支付，这表明它再次成功地避免了违约。
这表明它又一次成功地避免了违约。

恒大欠投资者的是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr68n0/evergrande_meets_interest_payment_deadline_avoids/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr68n0/evergrande_meets_interest_payment_deadline_avoids/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:43:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2021/11/10/business/evergrande-bond-deadline.html&quot;&gt;https://www.nytimes.com/2021/11/10/business/evergrande-bond-deadline.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;China Evergrande, the troubled property giant, made interest payments on at least two of its bonds on Wednesday, a company bondholder said, a sign that it yet again managed to head off default.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evergrande owed investors interest payments totaling nearly $150 million on three bonds, with the grace periods for those payments set to expire on Wednesday. Missing them would have triggered a default that could ripple through the Chinese economy: With some $300 billion in debt outstanding, the company’s inability to pay its debt would potentially hurt banks, property developers, and even home buyers in the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, the company has managed to leap from one deadline to the next, meeting its obligations at the last minute — but often without explaining how or even publicly disclosing that it had done so. The company has tried to sell off parts of its empire to raise enough cash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In October, when Evergrande said it had scrapped its effort to sell a $2.6 billion stake in its property services company to another developer, the company warned in a Hong Kong securities filing that there was “no guarantee” it would be able to meet its financial obligations or negotiate an extension with its creditors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday, the company met its interest payment deadline for bonds that mature in 2022 and 2023, the company bondholder said, speaking on condition of anonymity to discuss the matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The person did not specify if a payment on the third bond had also been made, but Bloomberg News reported that obligations for all three bonds were met, citing a spokesman for a clearing house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company didn’t respond to a request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although Evergrande has managed to avoid default so far, its troubles have already begun to weigh on other Chinese developers, with the government tightening controls on borrowing and investors retreating from the sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least six Chinese property developers have defaulted on foreign bonds in recent weeks, rattling domestic financial markets and raising the cost of borrowing for all Chinese companies. Property prices are slowing and fewer people are buying apartments, worsening the outlook for real estate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evergrande’s challenges could spread outside of China as well, as they ripple through global financial markets. On Monday, the Federal Reserve said troubles in China’s property sector could threaten the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Given the size of China’s economy and financial system as well as its extensive trade linkages with the rest of the world, financial stresses in China could strain global financial markets through a deterioration of risk sentiment, pose risks to global economic growth, and affect the United States,” the Fed said in its twice-yearly update on the American financial system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪斯尼的收益好坏参半]]></title><description><![CDATA[迪士尼在收盘后公布了收益。以下是结果。

每股收益。37美分，预期51美分。

收入：185.3亿美元，预期187.9亿美元

该公司可能显示其迪斯尼+流媒体服务的增长放缓。在
高盛Communacopia会议期间，该公司可能显示其迪斯尼+流媒体服务的增长放缓。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr4d2i/disney_has_mixed_earnings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr4d2i/disney_has_mixed_earnings/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 23:52:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disney reported earnings after the bell. Here are the results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earnings per share: 37 cents adj. vs 51 cents expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revenue: $18.53 billion vs $18.79 billion expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company may show slowing growth of its Disney+ streaming service. During the Goldman Sachs Communacopia Conference in September, CEO Bob Chapek said the segment&amp;#39;s growth has &amp;quot;hit some headwinds&amp;quot; and that Disney expects to add &amp;quot;low single-digit millions&amp;quot; of streaming subscribers in the fourth quarter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/disney-dis-fiscal-q4-2021-earnings.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/disney-dis-fiscal-q4-2021-earnings.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reddit准备在明年某个时候进行IPO]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据这篇文章
[https://www.reuters.com/technology/exclusive-reddit-seeks-hire-advisers-us-ipo-sources-2021-09-02/]。
Reddit的目标似乎是成为某种备忘录股票，其价值约为15美元。
150亿美元。他们仍在为明年某个时候发布的IPO做准备。
但它主要是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qr2h5r/reddit_poised_to_offer_ipo_sometime_next_year/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qr2h5r/reddit_poised_to_offer_ipo_sometime_next_year/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 23:24:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Per this &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/technology/exclusive-reddit-seeks-hire-advisers-us-ipo-sources-2021-09-02/&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;, Reddit seems to be aiming to become some sort of meme stock valued at approx. $15 Billion. They are still preparing for their IPO to be released sometime next year but it mostly depends on market conditions but for now their preparations for an IPO are confidential (My bet is Spring 2022).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now, they don&amp;#39;t have a release date for their IPO but I think they are aiming to become a meme stock. What do you guys think?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[请说服我，等待下一次崩溃是愚蠢的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我真的非常想成为一个Boglehead，但只有一件事：我相信
很快就会有一次股市崩溃。我的意思是，只要看看正在发生的事情
廉价的钱让僵尸企业活着，市盈率没有任何意义
毫无意义，中国的房地产陷入困境，伯里越来越......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qr2ojs/please_convince_me_that_waiting_for_the_next/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qr2ojs/please_convince_me_that_waiting_for_the_next/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 22:34:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I really really want to be a Boglehead but there&amp;#39;s just one thing: I&amp;#39;m convinced that there will be a stock market crash soon. I mean, just look at what&amp;#39;s happening: cheap money keeping zombie corporations alive, P/E ratios that don&amp;#39;t make ANY sense, China&amp;#39;s real estate in trouble, Burry getting into hardcore Cassandra mode, Buffett not buying much... I mean come on, a crash has to happen at any minute now, right? The thing is I&amp;#39;m thinking this for over a year now. Already so many &amp;quot;lost&amp;quot; earnings and so much time &amp;quot;lost&amp;quot; not being in the market. Please help me to convince myself to finally start investing / Bogleing instead of stupidly trying to time my market entry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街赌局传奇]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqvirr/wallstreetbets_legends/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqvirr/wallstreetbets_legends/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 22:34:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[从以前的帖子中修正了它。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr1jo7/fixed_it_from_a_previous_post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr1jo7/fixed_it_from_a_previous_post/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 20:39:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我现在开始接受被动投资了。我应该如何处理我目前混乱的投资组合呢？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在加入并阅读/观看视频后，我开始投资于被动的
ETFs。我现在的问题是，我应该如何处理我目前的投资组合中的几只
我仍然拥有的几只股票。例如，我有大约10,000美元的红利股票在一个
免税储蓄账户中约有1万美元的红利股票。我是否应该卖掉这些股票，并把它们放入...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qqxtjq/im_now_on_board_with_passive_what_do_i_do_with_my/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qqxtjq/im_now_on_board_with_passive_what_do_i_do_with_my/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 20:24:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;After joining and reading/watching the videos I&amp;#39;ve started investing in passive ETFs.  My question now is what do I do with my current portfolio with the few stocks I still own.  For example I have about $10,000 in dividend stocks in a taxfree savings account.  Should I sell those and put them into passive ETFs?  I also own a couple thousand $ in Nintendo and in Tencent which have dropped about $1000.00 in value from when I purchased (I know my fault should never have invested in Chinese stocks but I&amp;#39;m learning and that&amp;#39;s why I&amp;#39;m here.)  Should I also sell these at a loss and put them into passive investing?  I know all future deposits will go into passive investing but wondering about what to do with my older less wise purchases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also are there Canadians in here?  I&amp;#39;ve been putting into VFV which seems to be the Canadian VOO but what else do you recommend for passive as a Canadian?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nvidia试图通过新的人工智能工具引领进入元气的淘金热潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.marketwatch.com/story/nvidia-seeks-to-lead-gold-rush-into-the-metaverse-with-new-ai-tools-11636445322

Nvidia表示，它正在推出Omniverse Avatar，它可以根据该公司提供的数据生成交互式AI
该公司基于该公司在语音、计算机视觉、自然语言理解等方面的技术，生成互动的人工智能头像。
语言理解等方面的技术。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqvgpu/nvidia_seeks_to_lead_gold_rush_into_the_metaverse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqvgpu/nvidia_seeks_to_lead_gold_rush_into_the_metaverse/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 20:24:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/nvidia-seeks-to-lead-gold-rush-into-the-metaverse-with-new-ai-tools-11636445322&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/nvidia-seeks-to-lead-gold-rush-into-the-metaverse-with-new-ai-tools-11636445322&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nvidia said it is launching Omniverse Avatar, which generates interactive AI avatars based on the company’s technologies in speech, computer vision, natural language understanding, recommendation engines, and simulation. Also, the company is launching Omniverse Replicator, an engine that generates the vast amounts of data needed to train the deep neural networks that constitute AI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using Omniverse Replicator, Nvidia announced DRIVE Sim, which closes the gaps and increases the fidelity between virtual and actual worlds to help autonomous cars better perceive and navigate their environment and respond to rapid changes. DRIVE Sim can also be paired with Omniverse Avatar that would allow not only for an AI chauffeur but also a concierge in one’s car, the company said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is another positive announcement by Nvidia to leading the AI field. It is clearly that Metaverse is what Nvidia want to concentrate going forward and invest heavily to develop more powerful AI chips. There are a lot of potentials for Nvidia to develop and the stock will become part of MAMAA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我们为什么关心迈克尔-伯利。]]></title><description><![CDATA[[受此主题启发。迈克尔-伯里叫板埃隆-马斯克，将今天的市场比作
市场与郁金香狂热的比较
[https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/qq85ed/the_big_short_investor_michael_burry_says_elon/]

有人问："半严肃的问题，但为什么我们曾经关心过迈克尔-伯利的想法？
Michael Burry的想法？"...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqtvp3/why_we_care_about_michael_burry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqtvp3/why_we_care_about_michael_burry/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 20:24:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;[&lt;em&gt;Inspired by this thread:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/qq85ed/the_big_short_investor_michael_burry_says_elon/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Michael Burry calling out Elon Musk, comparing today&amp;#39;s market to tulip mania&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Someone asked &amp;quot;semi-serious question, but why have we ever cared about what Michael Burry thinks?&amp;quot;  This was my answer, and I think it&amp;#39;s important enough to warrant its own discussion.]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People care because the 2008 Global Financial Crisis was such a devastating and world-shattering event. It&amp;#39;s basically unprecedented in our times. The only thing that comes close to it is the Great Depression, but you could argue that 2008 was even more shocking given the fact that an advanced, modern, technology-based financial system came to the brink of complete and utter failure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That in and of itself leads to a compelling story. But what truly makes the whole thing amazing is the fact that people went on about their business like everything was fine, everything was great, and that we had entered into a new era of prosperity where nothing would or could go wrong. People like Burry were scorned, marginalized and laughed at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s truly amazing that the mob had no idea they were on the verge of one of the greatest societal disasters of our lifetimes. They were walking towards a precipice, blissfully unaware, and when the whole thing came crashing down, there was suddenly real fear that nothing was ever going to be the same again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think most people around here don&amp;#39;t understand just how scary the 2008 crisis was, and just how close we came to total financial meltdown. In retrospect it&amp;#39;s hard to appreciate how blissfully unaware just about anyone who&amp;#39;s anyone was about the possibility of this occurring. Those who were around and paying attention at the time seem to have forgotten, but that&amp;#39;s in part because of the emergency measures taken by central banks around the world which helped pump asset prices but still haven&amp;#39;t restored the real economy to normality. 13 years later and monetary policy still hasn&amp;#39;t been normalized. The scars are still being felt around the world. Inequality is on the rise in the US, directly resulting in the populism we saw from 2016-2020, and Spain, the country where I live, has become a shadow of what it what it was pre-housing boom. This is a big deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, you wouldn&amp;#39;t think it was a big deal if you&amp;#39;re just a middle or upper class stock market investor. You&amp;#39;re doing OK. The crowd marches onward, blissfully ignorant of the fact that the economy and markets are complex adaptive systems that have the potential for failure at any moment. Unprecedented liquidity and monetary policy do not help this situation, and even Bernanke spoke about weighing the &amp;quot;costs and risks&amp;quot; of these policies when they were first implemented 13 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honestly, I don&amp;#39;t know what&amp;#39;s going to happen, but the mystique around Burry is that he was seemingly the only one who was sensible at a time when the rest of the world was marching blindly off a cliff. I think for a lot of people he&amp;#39;s seen as the voice of reason against human greed, ignorance, and stupidity. Burry was always an outcast, and it took an outcast to say &amp;quot;hey, what the mob is doing isn&amp;#39;t right&amp;quot;. It took courage, and it took vision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s going to happen going forward, I don&amp;#39;t know. But to those of us who feel the world is a little more complicated than most people want to let on, and that markets (and life) aren&amp;#39;t always smooth sailing, Michael Burry represents an alternative voice.  It&amp;#39;s a voice that&amp;#39;s willing to call things as they are, even if it&amp;#39;s not always comfortable to look at them that way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As far as I&amp;#39;m concerned, it&amp;#39;s not about raining on a parade, or preaching gloom and doom.  It&amp;#39;s about seeking prosperity in a way that is sustainable and just, and moving forward in a way which takes into account the risks and does an adequate job of preparing for them.  True prosperity cannot be founded on lies and wishful thinking, and 2008 was the perfect illustration of that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[考虑多样化，并对即将到来的动荡进行对冲。]]></title><description><![CDATA[不，我不是在预测崩溃。我不是在告诉你到底该买什么公司
购买。我的目的是，如果你对目前的市场情况不相信，我可以给你一些思考的余地。
目前的市场状况。

我在5年前开始投资，以年均复合增长率击败了市场，并且有很好的
从那时起，我就以年均复合增长率击败了市场（与SP500相比，我有20%的回报率......）。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqxa47/consider_diversifying_and_hedging_against/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqxa47/consider_diversifying_and_hedging_against/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 19:33:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;No I am not predicting a crash. No I am not telling you exactly what company to buy. I am aiming to give you food for thought if you are in disbelief about the current market situation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started investing 5 years ago and have beaten the market by CAGR with a good margin ever since (20% vs SP500 14% something). Most of it I attribute to value investing. A school of investing that has consistently outperformed growth investing besides the past half decade. The basic idea is to invest in sound undervalued stocks with a margin of security to minimize risk and maximize upside in all market environments. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will not go intro details but if you want to read into it go for Benjamin Graham, Buffett, Lynch. A good start could be Modern Value Investing by Sven Carlin, a PhD Prof. in Amsterdam. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;#39;s market situation is incredible to say the least. We have rising CPI, money printing, Infrastructure Bills, Defaults in China, Tapering, Fake money velocity being created with the intent of kicking the can down the road in hopes of not hitting it off a cliff soon because it will happen. On top of that a high and rising CAPE (Shiller) of almost 40! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A high CAPE is correlated to low future stock market returns. A Shiller this high signals 0 to NEGATIVE avg SP500 returns. This could also go on for years so that we could see stagnation is the market for 5 - 10 - 15 years even. The point is not if this will happen, we have empirical data on this, but that is only a matter of time until it does. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TSLA is maybe the mascot of this circus alongside Altcoins and the Crypto boom. If you made money until now, great for you. If you are thinking of jumping in now, understand that overpaying for equity is at least as bad as buying bad equity. Again, there is empirical data on the correlation of high valuation and low future equity returns. If you buy most equities right now without thorough anaysis and valuation you will guarantee yourself low returns in the future. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could go on and on about what dangers lie ahead and why now is the worse time to jump into trendy stocks. But let&amp;#39;s talk now about how to hedge yourself from downturn in the coming years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hedging at its core deals with minimizing risk of total loss through different strategies. These strategies start from derivative plays to metals and global diversification. So let me present you some ways to limit your downside down the road. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currency Hedging ( Gold Miners, Miner ETFs, Fixed rate Debt) 
Use this if you think the USD will lose power. Buffett&amp;#39;s words &amp;quot;gold is going long fear&amp;quot;. Fear is spreding and capital will slowly flow into this asset class. Gold goes up and you are protected. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Derivatives (buying SP500 Puts) 
A very simple straight to the point thing to do is buying puts on the US economy via LEAPS. The risk lies in the fact that you need to be right 2 times. Once on the direction of the market and once on the time frame. Longer LEAPS cost a lot so it depends on your liquidity if you can/want/should do this. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diversify globally ( China, Europe, Russia) 
Get your hand on good, undervalued global stocks. Most other regions have lower CAPE than the US. Germany is looking good for this alongside China with the recent BABA drop. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep some cash 
Cash can only be lost to theft and inflation. Keeping 15 - 20% in cash might not be that bad since a market crash would present amazing buying opportunities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A popular saying is &amp;quot;value investing is dead&amp;quot;. I would argue for the fact that growth investing is dead for the moment. We are at the end of a huge debt cycle. This, just like valuation needs to return to the mean sooner or later. The next period will be favorable for value investing as the house of cards begins to crash down. You will be down a bit if you follow this strategy but you will secure your profits in the long run. This will help your compounding overall. When the crash comes, be prepared to find bargains and go all in. You will thank yourself later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[恒大正式违约--大商所正准备对恒大集团启动破产程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国恒大集团今天再次拖欠了对国际投资者的利息支付。
国际投资者。DMSA本身也投资于这些债券，并且没有
在今天的宽限期结束之前，没有收到任何利息付款。现在DMSA
正准备对恒大提起破产诉讼，并呼吁所有...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr0lp8/evergrande_officially_defaulted_dmsa_is_preparing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr0lp8/evergrande_officially_defaulted_dmsa_is_preparing/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 19:20:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;China Evergrande Group today again defaulted on interest payments to international investors. DMSA itself is invested in these bonds and has not received any interest payments until today&amp;#39;s end of the grace period. Now DMSA is preparing bankruptcy proceedings against Evergrande and calls on all bond investors to join it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;China Evergrande Group, the second largest real estate developer in China, defaulted on interest payments on two bonds back in September, with the 30-day grace period still ending in October. However, shortly before the end of the grace period, the public was misled by rumors about alleged interest payments. The international media also took the rumors for granted. Only the DMSA - Deutsche Marktscreening Agentur (German Market Screening Agency) already recognized the default at that time and proved in a study that the bankruptcy of Evergrande, the world&amp;#39;s most indebted corporation, could ultimately lead to a &amp;quot;Great Reset&amp;quot;, i.e. the final meltdown of the global financial system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Note to journalists: See DMSA press releases dated Oct. 25 and Oct. 29, 2021, and the DMSA study &amp;quot;The Great Reset - Evergrande and the Final Meltdown of the Global Financial System&amp;quot;; all available via the DMSA homepage &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dmsa-agentur.de/&quot;&gt;www.dmsa-agentur.de&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;But while the international financial market has so far met the financial turmoil surrounding the teetering giant Evergrande with a remarkable basic confidence - one can also say: with remarkable naivety - the U.S. central bank Fed confirmed our view yesterday,&amp;quot; says DMSA senior analyst Dr. Marco Metzler. &amp;quot;In its latest stability report, it explicitly pointed out the dangers that a collapse of Evergrande could have for the global financial system.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to be able to file for bankruptcy against the company as a creditor, DMSA itself invested in Evergrande bonds, whose grace period expired today (Nov. 10, 2021). In total, Evergrande would have had to pay $148.13 million in interest on three bonds no later than today. &amp;quot;But so far we have not received any interest on our bonds,&amp;quot; explains Metzler. He adds, &amp;quot;With banks in Hong Kong closing today, it&amp;#39;s certain that these bonds have defaulted.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Note to editors: Exact details of the bonds that have defaulted so far can be found in the appendix to this press release.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Particularly problematic for Evergrande: all 23 outstanding bonds have a cross-default clause. &amp;quot;This means that if a single one of these bonds defaults, all 23 outstanding bonds automatically have &amp;#39;default&amp;#39; status&amp;quot; DMSA senior analyst Metzler knows. However, this does not automatically result in a bankruptcy for Evergrande Group. To determine bankruptcy, a insolvency petition must be filed with the court. This can be done either by the company itself or by one or more of the company&amp;#39;s creditors. And this is precisely what is now planned. Metzler: &amp;quot;DMSA is preparing bankruptcy proceedings against Evergrande. We are already holding talks with other investors in this regard. We would be pleased if other investors were to join our action group.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the DMSA expert, it is clear: &amp;quot;As soon as a court opens insolvency proceedings, Evergrande will also be officially bankrupt - and that is only a matter of days.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full story here- &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/evergrande-officially-defaulted---dmsa-is-preparing-bankruptcy-proceedings-against-evergrande-group-301421327.html&quot;&gt;https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/evergrande-officially-defaulted---dmsa-is-preparing-bankruptcy-proceedings-against-evergrande-group-301421327.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国发生了08年的事件，我觉得我们完蛋了]]></title><description><![CDATA[让我们来谈谈严肃的事情吧，伙计们。我知道这个页面充满了一些合法的
我知道这个页面充满了一些合法的发件人，而且我们喜欢把它全部扔到黑色的地方。

但我们认为中国的情况如何？他们上个月拖欠了3050亿
月。我相信其中5亿或更多是美国债权人的。在我们的
亿元在我们的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqw2pw/china_pulled_an_08_and_i_feel_we_are_fucked/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqw2pw/china_pulled_an_08_and_i_feel_we_are_fucked/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 19:01:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s talk about something serious guys. I know this page is full of some legit senders and we like to throw it all on black. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what do we thinks going down with China? They defaulted 305 BILLION last month. And I believe 500 million or more of it was on American creditors. With a billion in our real estate here in the americas and another 3 billion around Europe? I think numbers could be a bit off but the default is a solid number that was calculated. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This reeks of 08. And of course people claim that they will be bailed out. Except someone’s going to hold the bag like JP and Lehman did in 08.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, we know China and the US aren’t the friendliest buddies. Or even Europe for that matter. What’s to stop them from pushing it to us? Who’s following this and what’s your plan or position? It’s easy to pull capital and “wait” but who knows how long that will be till the bottom drops and to what extent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在FOMO和偏离boglehead哲学后寻求建议]]></title><description><![CDATA[直到今年年初，我一直遵循boglehead哲学，以
然后我在1月发现了某支备忘录股票，并从最初的投资中赚取了许多倍的利润。
我的初始投资。我应该意识到，我很幸运，很早就进入了这个行业
但我很固执，过于自信。我开始做...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qqtjy9/seeking_advice_after_fomo_and_straying_from/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qqtjy9/seeking_advice_after_fomo_and_straying_from/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 19:01:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up until the beginning of the year, I had followed the boglehead philosophy to the T. Then I discovered a certain meme stock in Jan and made many multiples off my initial investment. I should have realized that I got lucky getting in early but I was stubborn and overconfident. I started doing research on other sectors and individual stocks, and decided to allocate 25% of my net worth in an actively managed strategy. That strategy did not work very well. I either didn’t have conviction and sold or had too much conviction to sell when there were “bad signs” that indicated trouble. As a result, my actively managed portfolio has underperformed VT by 10%. I am still up 57% for the year (thanks to the initial meme stock and some crypto). I suppose I should feel grateful that I am still positive for the year but I can’t help but feel like I have failed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point I want to sell everything and either go cash/DCA or go lump sum back into a broad market index fund. I have realized that it isn’t great for my mental health to obsess over my portfolio like this.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see posts from people who have gotten insanely rich off this bull run and it makes me feel FOMO. But I have also seen people who blow up their portfolio and end up with nothing. It makes me wonder about the distribution of gains/losses by during this bull run. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you have any advice for me? How do you deal with the FOMO?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[什么是购买新股的最佳时机？- 我在过去20年里分析了1000多宗IPO! 下面是结果!]]></title><description><![CDATA[鉴于围绕650亿美元的Rivian IPO的炒作越来越多
[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/05/rivian-raises-ipo-price-range-and-could-now-be-worth-up-to-65-billion.html]
[1]，我觉得这是一个完美的时间来跟进我的第一个分析，对...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqseif/what_is_the_best_time_to_buy_an_ipo_i_analyzed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqseif/what_is_the_best_time_to_buy_an_ipo_i_analyzed/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 19:01:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given the growing hype surrounding the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/05/rivian-raises-ipo-price-range-and-could-now-be-worth-up-to-65-billion.html&quot;&gt;$65 Billion Rivian IPO&lt;/a&gt; [1], I felt this is the perfect time to follow up on my &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ny6wpp/i_analyzed_3600_ipos_over_the_past_two_decades_to/&quot;&gt;first analysis on IPOs&lt;/a&gt;. In the previous analysis, we realized that the majority of gains were made from the listing itself and those who invested on listing day gained a measly 1.3%. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/f4e0nywl7ry71.png?width=950&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=5c9bb06a416c3cdedcd34b3e91c6f43af1e97f8b&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In most cases, &lt;a href=&quot;https://money.usnews.com/investing/investing-101/articles/how-to-buy-ipo-stock-at-its-offer-price&quot;&gt;less than 10% of the total IPO&lt;/a&gt; is allocated to retail investors. Adding to this, a multitude of other factors such as your brokerage account, account balance, the historical trading pattern will all contribute to whether you get the IPO shares or not in the end [2].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given that the chances of you making it into the IPO allotment are bleak, what I wanted to analyze is, if we miss the IPO bus,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the best time to buy into a recently IPO’d stock?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should it be on the listing day itself or should you wait a day, week, or even a month for all the hype surrounding the IPO to die down and the stock to come back to its “real” valuation [3]?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/n5wmym9n7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=a3106183b0670cb5c790d5034bf7ee76a4ca194b&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have leveraged the same data source (iposcoop.com) that I used last time. They have documented almost all the IPOs from 2000. But for this analysis, I also needed stock price-related information for periods long after the stock had been listed in the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stock price information was obtained using Yahoo Finance. After all the quality checks, we are left with 1,063 IPOs from 2000-2020. All the data used in the analysis has been shared through a Google sheet at the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/9skwwgan7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=9789e067c476b12b7b962d587c002320623c388b&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Analysis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the idea is to find the best time to invest in an IPO, we have to compare the returns for multiple time periods. I calculated the one month and one year returns in case you had invested on the day of the IPO as well as if you had invested in the stock after&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One month&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The returns are then compared against each other to find the optimal time to invest in the stock after it has IPO’d. The returns were finally benchmarked against SPY to see if it makes sense to put in all these efforts - only to maybe underperform the market!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/w2qnh2an7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=6e659778bbe8aaf8893f5d6f2ea21288ef4b7a71&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/w2qnh2an7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=6e659778bbe8aaf8893f5d6f2ea21288ef4b7a71&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/vknekrzo7ry71.png?width=730&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=7fe4c5b99687e881d342df706a16fcd0ac0f255f&quot;&gt; All calculations are done using the adjusted closing price  &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Surprisingly, the gains you would have made from the IPOs are inversely proportional to the amount of time you waited for your investment. On average &lt;strong&gt;the most amount of return is obtained by someone who invested on the day of the IPO itself&lt;/strong&gt;. The more amount of time you wait for your investment, the lesser your return is!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what if you are not interested in the short-term returns? What if you are a buy-and-hold type of investor?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/uazvvt0q7ry71.png?width=730&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=38ff88f577596544308b493f072d66240507cc7d&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a long-term investor, &lt;strong&gt;you would be better off buying the IPO after waiting for a week&lt;/strong&gt;, as it generated the most amount of return. But what is interesting is that waiting a week for the hype to die down would only increase your return by 9%. Waiting any further would only &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;decrease your overall return.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you are planning on buying into an IPO but did not get an allocation at the listing price, you can wait a week so as to see how it performs in the market, avoid any large swings that the first week might cause, and still come out on top over the long run!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, let’s compare the performance of IPO stocks against SPY. After all, even though you are getting a good return on your investment, if it does not beat the market, you would have been better off just investing it in SPY rather than doing all this research on IPOs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ehviuevq7ry71.png?width=900&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=880c9f18392da5832a239819b38cd6dc04893875&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IPOs’ returns on average &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;beat the market&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; over the last two decades. The trends are similar to the ones observed earlier with the delta over the market return depending on how much time you waited before investing into the IPO and generating the highest amount of delta by waiting one week from the day of the IPO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now it would be amiss not to discuss the inherent risks associated with investing in an IPO. Out of the 1,063 IPO’s in our analysis, only 62% of them gained in value and only a measly 29% of the IPOs beat the market over the long run. The outperformance over the market is coming due to a few outliers (Tesla - 25,000%+, Shopify - 5800%+, etc.) If you miss out on the top 1% of successful IPOs, your returns would be much lesser than the market. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/5np1iman7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=ed89afca9e90fdc3288899fcab548a8155beecdc&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Limitations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above analysis comes with some limitations that you should be aware of before trying to replicate the strategy&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The number of IPOs in the analysis is approximately 1/3rd of the total IPOs which occurred during 2000-2020 [4]. I don’t think this is a major concern since our sample of 1000+ stocks would be much more than enough to give statistical significance to our analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Another limitation is that the delta that you are observing here might just be due to the additional risk that you are taking by buying into lesser-known/small-cap companies. The risk-adjusted return might give a different result.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuing from the above point, we are currently in a massive bull run with ATH being broken every week. So the additional risk you are taking will be well rewarded but the outcome might look different if we do the same analysis in the middle of a bear market.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/qk5hm49s7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=77fe292757c841d6ecd666b499a9315e48595f25&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buying into an IPO is an exciting prospect. Our analysis proves that even if you miss out on getting the IPO allocation, it’s still possible to beat the market by investing after the stock is listed on the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ny6wpp/i_analyzed_3600_ipos_over_the_past_two_decades_to/&quot;&gt;explained in my last post on IP&lt;/a&gt;O, investment banks are incentivized to slightly underprice while listing (unless it’s a really popular company) so that the IPO issue is 100% subscribed (their fees are dependent on a successful IPO) [5].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever the case may be, if you are planning on holding on to the IPO only for a short period of time, you can maximize your returns by investing in the IPO as soon as it’s listed whereas if you are a long term investor who is planning to hold on to the stock for a very long time, its better to wait a week or so for the stock price to settle before making your move!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Analysis Sheet containing all the data: &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1QqRNZEsTfgG6f8GfI-n6qBAai9wrUA47hFMYg6tz098/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until next week…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/inx7eq9s7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=bd82af6c741804d784b964b632a1af10ae31eb0c&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Footnotes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[1] The company has &lt;a href=&quot;https://insideevs.com/news/542908/rivian-production-numbers-first-month/&quot;&gt;only built and delivered 56&lt;/a&gt; vehicles as of Oct21. If Rivian IPO’d at $65 Billion, it means that each vehicle it delivered added more than $1 Billion in value to its shareholders. A similarly valued Ford delivered 4.1 Million vehicles in 2020. Truly wild times we are living in!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[2] Brokerages tend to allocate IPO shares to their premium clients - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tdameritrade.com/investment-products/IPOs.html&quot;&gt;In the case of TD Ameritrade&lt;/a&gt;, your account must have a value of at least $250,000 or have completed 30 trades in the last 3 months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[3] Take the examples of Robinhood and Coinbase IPO. Robinhood tanked on listing day losing 8% only to rally almost 100% in the next one week before coming back down to near its IPO pricing. Coinbase also had a wild ride on listing day with the share price going as high as $429 before crashing back down to ~$310.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[4] The major limitation was the absence of financial data in Yahoo Finance for certain stocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[5] There are a lot of contradictory opinions regarding this with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0275531918309280&quot;&gt;some research&lt;/a&gt; showcasing that IPO’s are usually undervalued while &lt;a href=&quot;https://academic.oup.com/rfs/article-abstract/17/3/811/1612977?redirectedFrom=PDF&quot;&gt;others argue&lt;/a&gt; that IPOs are overvalued. I guess you can twist data however you want to tell your story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ohspvw9s7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=b152439751b7c5cba562695a713a9c1d89b2a8f6&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/ohspvw9s7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=b152439751b7c5cba562695a713a9c1d89b2a8f6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: I am not a financial advisor. Please do your own research before investing.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[第三季度营收不及分析师预期，Coinbase股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[盘后下跌13%。

https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/09/coinbase-coin-earnings-q3-2021.html

美国最大的加密货币交易所Coinbase在周二收盘后公布了第三季度财报。
周二收盘后公布了第三季度财报，收入方面未达到分析师的预期。
收入。该股在延长后下挫超过13%。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqjz2e/coinbase_shares_plummet_after_thirdquarter/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqjz2e/coinbase_shares_plummet_after_thirdquarter/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 18:49:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Down 13% after hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/09/coinbase-coin-earnings-q3-2021.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/09/coinbase-coin-earnings-q3-2021.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coinbase, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in the U.S., reported third-quarter earnings after the bell on Tuesday and missed analysts’ estimates on revenue. The stock sank more than 13% in extended trading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earnings: $1.62 a share&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue: $1.31 billion vs. $1.57 billion consensus estimate, according to Refinitiv&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Monday, bitcoin hit a new all-time high of $68,000, and ethereum set a new record, topping $4,800.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[给我的投资组合评分]]></title><description><![CDATA[VT: 100%

有何感想？我认为我有太多的股票。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qr06wl/rate_my_portfolio/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qr06wl/rate_my_portfolio/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 18:49:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;VT: 100%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts? I think I have too many stocks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师在下调股票评级时称Palantir开始出现 "裂缝]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大皇家银行强调政府收入的急剧下降，并表示未来几年30%以上的整体增长目标是 "不可能的"。
未来几年的整体增长目标 "难以保证"。

Palantir Technologies的股价周三似乎有望继续下滑
在加拿大皇家银行资本市场的分析师Rishi Jaluria下调了该股的评级，并警告...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qquzog/palantir_is_starting_to_show_cracks_analyst_says/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qquzog/palantir_is_starting_to_show_cracks_analyst_says/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 18:08:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;RBC highlights a sharp deceleration in government revenue and says 30%-plus overall growth target for next few years is ‘hard to underwrite’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shares of Palantir Technologies look on track to extend their slide Wednesday after RBC Capital Markets analyst Rishi Jaluria downgraded the stock, warning of “cracks emerging in the story.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jaluria is concerned about a deceleration in Palantir’s government business as shown in the company’s Tuesday morning earnings commentary. While Jaluria had anticipated a slowdown, he noted that the growth rate for this part of the business was almost cut in half relative to the second quarter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Palantir executives called out 34% growth in government revenue during the third quarter, while this segment was up 66% in the second quarter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We believe Palantir got direct benefits from COVID-related spending and those benefits have already faded,” Jaluria wrote in his note to clients, while lowering his rating on Palantir’s stock to underperform from sector perform and cutting his price target to $19 from $25.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shares of Palantir are off more than 2% in premarket trading Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jaluria also said that while Palantir’s commercial business continues to accelerate, he believes some of the growth there is due to a program through which the company makes strategic investments in earlier-stage businesses that then use its technology. “We do not believe revenue from S**C investments is sustainable, especially given the relatively small size of the companies Palantir is investing in,” he wrote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Palantir’s management team continues to expect revenue growth of at least 30% for this year and the following four years, but Jaluria views this target as “hard to underwrite” given the deceleration in the government business and his estimation of the impact that S**C investments are having on commercial growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We still believe Palantir has good technology and strong customer government relationships, but given the valuation, would like to see additional proof points of clean, sustainable 30%+ growth before getting more constructive,” he wrote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Palantir shares have added 5.8% over the past three months as the S&amp;amp;P 500 SPX, -0.35% has gained 5.6%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;m arketwatch.com/story/palantir-is-starting-to-show-cracks-analyst-says-in-downgrade-11636552230?mod=mw_latestnews&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[凯西为什么要把Palantir买进ARKG？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我当然不知道ARKG内的全部公司，但我
我收到了所有ARK ETF的每日买入/卖出的电子邮件。在ARKG（Genomic
Revolution）今天买入了约29万股Palantir的股票。我喜欢Palantir。
但这与整个篮子有什么关系？



我投资于...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqikv2/why_is_cathie_buying_palantir_into_arkg/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqikv2/why_is_cathie_buying_palantir_into_arkg/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 18:08:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I certainly don&amp;#39;t know the entire basket of companies within ARKG, but I received the daily email of buy/sells into all the ARK ETFs.  In ARKG (Genomic Revolution) about 290,000 shares of Palantir were bought today.  I love Palantir, but how does this fit in with the overall basket?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m invested in almost all of the ARK funds.  But I don&amp;#39;t like that some companies that don&amp;#39;t belong, are traded in the funds anyway.  I noticed Netflix was one of the first companies purchased into ARKX when it debuted this year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anybody know why Palantir would be bought into the Genomic fund?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[恒大正式违约]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqvo6g/evergrande_officially_defaulted/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqvo6g/evergrande_officially_defaulted/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:50:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[珍妮特-耶伦谈通货膨胀...
二月：没什么可担心的。
三月：小而可控。
五月：只是暂时的。
6月：可能达到3%，但只是过渡性的。
10月初：未来几个月会更高。
10月下旬：增加数万亿的支出将降低价格。https://t.co/BGScAa7QEa https://t.co/3UqmnVqQUS]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458434830874595337</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458434830874595337</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:38:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[突破。有报道称，恒大在30天的宽限期内没有支付债券，使他们正式陷入违约。德国公司DMSA已经对他们提出正式的破产程序。]]></title><description><![CDATA[现在关于这个问题的新闻正在不断涌现（在推特上越来越多），看起来像是
主流消息来源还没有报道，或正在淡化。在这里你可以
找到DMSA的新闻稿，http://www.dmsa-agentur.de/pressemitteilungen

据我所知，1.48亿美元的离岸债券付款 "今天 "到期...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqy68o/breaking_reports_are_coming_in_that_evergrande/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqy68o/breaking_reports_are_coming_in_that_evergrande/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:22:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;News is trickling in on this right now (gaining steam on Twitter), looks like mainstream sources haven&amp;#39;t picked it up yet or are downplaying. Here You can find DMSA&amp;#39;s press release, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dmsa-agentur.de/pressemitteilungen&quot;&gt;http://www.dmsa-agentur.de/pressemitteilungen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From what I gather, a $148 million offshore bond payment due &amp;quot;today&amp;quot; still hasn&amp;#39;t been paid, triggering formal bankruptcy proceedings against the company.  I believe that the deadline was midnight in China timezone, and the press release was filed right around there. We cannot know for sure if a last-hour payment was made. But if this is all true , it could have some pretty strong short term shocks for the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now treat this with a grain of salt until more verification and information. Either way, buckle up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**EDIT: English Press Release ** &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/evergrande-officially-defaulted---dmsa-is-preparing-bankruptcy-proceedings-against-evergrande-group-301421327.html&quot;&gt;https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/evergrande-officially-defaulted---dmsa-is-preparing-bankruptcy-proceedings-against-evergrande-group-301421327.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[通货膨胀率飙升至1990年以来最高]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.npr.org/2021/11/10/1054019175/inflation-surges-to-its-highest-since-1990

> 美国劳工部周三报告说，10月份消费者价格比去年同期高出6.2%。
> 10月份比一年前高6.2%。这是自1990年11月以来的最大幅度增长。
> 1990.
> 
> 价格上涨是广泛的，其中...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqxz18/inflation_surges_to_its_highest_since_1990/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqxz18/inflation_surges_to_its_highest_since_1990/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:22:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npr.org/2021/11/10/1054019175/inflation-surges-to-its-highest-since-1990&quot;&gt;https://www.npr.org/2021/11/10/1054019175/inflation-surges-to-its-highest-since-1990&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Labor Department reported Wednesday that consumer prices were 6.2% higher in October than a year ago. That&amp;#39;s the sharpest increase since November of 1990.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Price increases were widespread, with energy, shelter, food and vehicles all costing more. Excluding volatile food and energy costs, prices were up 4.6%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Much of the upward pressure on prices is the result of a mismatch between booming demand and limited supply, as businesses struggle to find both parts and workers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many employers have increased pay in order to attract more workers. But growing paychecks have quickly been eroded by the rising cost of gas and groceries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;For families, they&amp;#39;re feeling it right now,&amp;quot; says Mary Daly, president of the Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco. &amp;quot;If you got to a grocery store, you buy food that you usually buy, you then fill your gas tank on the way home so you can go to work or take your kids to school, you&amp;#39;re feeling this.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;When you then look at the winter coming and you realize your fuel bill for heating your home is going to rise as the winter comes, you&amp;#39;re nervous,&amp;quot; she added.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2021/11/10/business/economy/consumer-price-inflation-october.html&quot;&gt;https://www.nytimes.com/2021/11/10/business/economy/consumer-price-inflation-october.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[国税局在WSB上滚动播放钻石手的收益色情片]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqk0i1/the_irs_scrolling_through_diamond_hand_gain_porn/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqk0i1/the_irs_scrolling_through_diamond_hand_gain_porn/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[从年初开始的通胀变化...
美国：上升5.0% (1.2% --&gt; 6.2%)
欧元区：上升4.4% (-0.3% --&gt; 4.1%)
加拿大。高出3.4% (1.0% --&gt; 4.4%)
英国：上升2.8% (0.3% --&gt; 3.1%)

中央银行利率从年初开始的变化...
美联储 0%
欧洲央行: 0%
英国央行：0
英国央行：0

曲线背后]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458435864082714629</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458435864082714629</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 16:37:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[10月通胀率创30年新高，为6.2%。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqutgr/inflation_hit_30_year_high_in_october_of_62/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqutgr/inflation_hit_30_year_high_in_october_of_62/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 16:37:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[统一公司的季度收入超过预期，并收购了Weta公司。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Unity正在收购Weta，一家领先的数字视觉效果公司。他们的工具
将成为Unity创造者套件的一部分。非常令人兴奋的事情。 

他们为《指环王》和最大的Marvel电影创造了视觉效果。
仅举几例。https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ygAsQxDtXic

第三季度收益

...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqsdzh/unity_exceeds_quarterly_earning_expectations_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqsdzh/unity_exceeds_quarterly_earning_expectations_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 16:37:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unity is acquiring Weta, a leading digital visual effects company. Their tools will be a part of the Unity creator suite. Very exciting stuff. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They created visual effects for Lord of the Rings and the biggest Marvel movies, to name a few. 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ygAsQxDtXic&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ygAsQxDtXic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q3 earnings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solid quarter. Stocks dropped in the premarket, which is reasonable, the price was at an all time high. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Q3 revenue up 43% year-over-year, exceeding expectations; company raises guidance. Still operating at a 6c loss per share. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;They continue to heavily invest into the future and creating a lock-in effect with their customer base. Lots of acquisitions and more R&amp;amp;D expenditure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bottom line:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They&amp;#39;re building a substantial ecosystem and are well positioned as a top player for some of the biggest buzzwords of the next decade, the metaverse, gaming, augmented- and virtual reality. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Current price is high considering fundamentals. But in my opinion, it&amp;#39;s still being slept on. I have a gut feeling this will become a hype stock within 2-3 years, so I&amp;#39;ll continue to buy.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;d personally be very happy with buying below $120. But I think ~$135 is probably a more reasonable entry point in the next 12 months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币在过去一年中上涨了340%。

但如果你考虑到6%的通货膨胀率，实际回报率只有334%。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458441469040250882</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458441469040250882</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:47:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[去年的商品价格上涨...
WTI原油: +109%
取暖用油。+106%
汽油: +105%
布伦特原油: +101
咖啡。+88%
天然气: +74%
棉花: +71%
铜: +39%
铝: +37%
玉米。+36%
糖: +34%
小麦: +30%
木材: +15%
大豆: +9%
白银: +3%
黄金：-1%。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458441345824067590</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458441345824067590</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:47:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国通货膨胀率6.2

30年抵押贷款利率3.1

是否有一个更好的时间成为借款人？https://t.co/JUV5Got4f4]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458434239784005634</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458434239784005634</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:47:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian IPO定价为78美元/股，市值达760亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[就在几个月前，Rivian公司交付了它的第一批车辆，主要是给它自己的员工。
自己的员工。到年底，该公司在伊利诺伊州Normal的工厂将只生产大约1200辆。
它在伊利诺伊州Normal的工厂到年底只能生产约1200辆。

从这个角度来看，NIO在最近的12个月里销售了142,036辆电动汽车。
个月。

里维安的估值很高，而且...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqtrgm/rivian_ipo_priced_at_78_a_share_giving_it_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqtrgm/rivian_ipo_priced_at_78_a_share_giving_it_a/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:47:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just a couple of months ago, Rivian delivered its first vehicles, mostly to its own employees. It will only produce about 1,200 units by year-end at its plant in Normal, Illinois. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To put it in perspective, NIO sold 142,036 electric cars on the most recent 12 months. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rivian’s valuation is huge, and its $78B market cap outpaces Chinese EV maker NIO ‘s (NIO) $63 billion market value, and it is more than those of EV start-up Lucid (LCID) and XPeng (XPEV) combined. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ford has a market cap of $78.4 billion, GM&amp;#39;s is $84.4 billion and Stellantis NV, the former Fiat Chrysler, is valued at $64 billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quoting An article from a few days ago when Rivian’s was valued at $52 billion … The $52B valuation implies that Rivian will sell 2 million vehicles in 2030, or nearly 2.5 times the number of Tesla (TSLA) vehicles produced over the past 12 months and 66% more vehicles than Honda sold in the U.S. in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These manufacturing milestones are highly improbable given Rivian’s lack of manufacturing infrastructure and experience as well as the intense competition it faces in the EV market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1. 股票：历史新高
2. 房价：历史高点
3. 比特币：历史高点
4. 工资：历史高点
5. 职位空缺：历史新高
6. 通货膨胀：30多年来的最高水平
7. 美联储/政府：我们需要将利率压低到0%，并且多借/多花几万亿。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458430231715500032</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458430231715500032</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 14:35:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球通货膨胀率... https://t.co/6mNnpyO6tp]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458435460544540677</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458435460544540677</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 14:35:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[与去年相比，价格上涨（CPI报告）...
汽油。+49.6%
燃气公用事业: +28.1%
二手汽车: +26.4%
肉类/鱼类/蛋类: +11.9%
新汽车: +9.8%
电力: +6.5%
整体CPI: +6.2%
家里的食物。+5.4%
外出食品：+5.4%。+5.3%
交通运输: +4.5%
服装: +4.3%
庇护所: +3.5%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458428272384040960</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458428272384040960</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 14:35:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[去年美国消费者价格增长6.2%，是我们30多年来看到的最高通胀率。

图表来自@ycharts https://t.co/YdBRyaZGhT]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458429773760368643</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458429773760368643</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 14:35:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[10月份消费者价格指数飙升6.2%，大大超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[消费者每天购买的广泛产品的通货膨胀甚至比预期的还要糟糕。
10月份的情况比预期的还要糟糕，达到了30多年来的最高点。
劳工部周三报告说。

消费者价格指数是由一篮子产品组成的，包括汽油、保健品和其他产品。
和医疗保健到...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqukg1/consumer_price_index_surges_62_in_october/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqukg1/consumer_price_index_surges_62_in_october/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 14:21:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inflation across a broad swath of products that consumers buy every day was even worse than expected in October, hitting its highest point in more than 30 years, the Labor Department reported Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The consumer price index, which is a basket of products ranging from gasoline and health care to groceries and rents, rose 6.2% from a year ago. That compared to the 5.9% Dow Jones estimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consumer price index surges 6.2% in October, considerably more than expected &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/consumer-price-index-october.html?__source=iosappshare%7Ccom.apple.UIKit.activity.CopyToPasteboard&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/consumer-price-index-october.html?__source=iosappshare%7Ccom.apple.UIKit.activity.CopyToPasteboard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这就是为什么拥有股票是一个很好的对冲通货膨胀的工具。

投入成本上升 --gt；公司提价 --gt；消费者抱怨，但还是要支付更高的价格 --gt；公司的利润率保持不变。

@SamRo说的好 

https://t.co/ZKrUy9AkV0 https://t.co/nQLfjibYFM]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458104251796922380</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458104251796922380</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 13:44:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[真正的华尔街之狼]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qq9vgf/the_real_wolf_of_wall_street/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qq9vgf/the_real_wolf_of_wall_street/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 13:31:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[铜的目前状况令人担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在几个月前投资了一些铜的股票，看到它最近的波动情况
最近，我觉得我应该对我在上面投资的钱感到担心。
价格忽高忽低，而且随着可审查能源的需求。
一切都会变得更加混乱。已经有问题的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqs5bp/coppers_current_situation_is_concerning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqs5bp/coppers_current_situation_is_concerning/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 12:36:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I invested in some copper stocks a few months back, and seeing how volatile it is recently, I feel like I should be worried with the money I invested on it. The prices are going up and down and with the demand for reviewable energy, everything’s going to be messier. There have been issues with the supply recently as well, especially with bigger producers due to issues with miners or because of the restrictions brought about by the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now I have some I also have some &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fortitudegold.com/&quot;&gt;Fortitude Gold&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/FTCO/&quot;&gt;FTCO&lt;/a&gt;). They are a pretty small producer but has no debts and recently increased the monthly dividend they are paying 16.7% to $0.035 per common share, or $0.42 annually. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.solarisresources.com/&quot;&gt;Solaris Resources&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/SLSSF/&quot;&gt;SLSSF&lt;/a&gt;) which I got despite it being risky since it is an exploration. They have positive results with their drilling, and they recently started their maiden drilling at the Warintza South target, targeting the 4th major copper discovery. They also have a massive cash cushion and their cash burn is way under, plus they have about $60 million on the balance sheet right now. I also placed some on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.comstockmining.com/&quot;&gt;Comstock Mining Inc&lt;/a&gt;.(&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/LODE/&quot;&gt;LODE&lt;/a&gt;), and their primary focus of the company’s exploration efforts are their projects in the Dayton Resource/Spring Valley as well as the Lucerne resource area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not planning to invest on any anytime soon, since I feel a little anxious with all the investments I made seeing how volatile the situation is right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[嗯，这是官方的：这都是我们的错。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqkbbc/well_its_official_this_is_all_our_fault/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqkbbc/well_its_official_this_is_all_our_fault/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 12:36:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你建议一个年轻的投资人要有多大的多元化。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我24岁，我已经建立了一个价值约13万的投资组合。

我在大约20只不同的股票和ETF中拥有股份。我最大的赢家是
Nvidia和亚马逊。

我大概有60%的科技股，30%的ETF，10%的其他。

考虑到我的日常工作都是关于技术的，我最了解的公司是
科技。我首先...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qql530/how_diversified_would_you_suggest_a_young/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qql530/how_diversified_would_you_suggest_a_young/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 11:44:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m 24 YO and I&amp;#39;ve built up a portfolio worth about 130k. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have share in about 20 different stocks and ETFs. My biggest winners being Nvidia and Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m like 60% tech stocks 30% ETFs 10% other. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Considering my day job is all about technology the companies I know best are tech. I first purchased 5 shares of Nvidia in 2016 because they simply made superior graphic cards. Then crypto and Tesla autonomy and ARM really put the boosters on! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like the idea of being diversified but I feel like I&amp;#39;d be better off trying to pick 5 winners and just take the hits on the bad days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有些人只是被诅咒了]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqb82o/some_are_just_cursed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqb82o/some_are_just_cursed/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 11:19:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[COINBASE（COIN股票）21年第三季度的想法。COIN在盘后交易中下跌13%。]]></title><description><![CDATA[刚刚听完15分钟的电话会议，并仔细阅读了他们第三季度的
投资者信。

我认为Coinbase的风险在于对费用的依赖，因为行业会找到越来越多的
越来越多的方法来提供更便宜的交易，或免收佣金。

这里有一个好消息。

在2020年第三季度，有低...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqlmbs/coinbase_coin_stock_q3_21_thoughts_coin_down_13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqlmbs/coinbase_coin_stock_q3_21_thoughts_coin_down_13/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 10:56:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just got done listening to 15m of the conference call, and poured over their Q3 investor letter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the risk to Coinbase is reliance on fees, as the industry will find more and more ways to offer trading more cheaply, or commission free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s the good news. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During Q3 2020, there was low Crypto volitily. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That means commissions income was down 44%. Q-on-Q.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Q3 21, Y-on-Y, commissions income is up 290% from Q3 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although subscriptions/fees are only, currently, like 10%, of Coinbases revenue stream -- they&amp;#39;ve grown that revenue stream by 41% from last quarter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take away:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The price of COIN is highly correlated to the price of crypto assets rising and failing..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;.. it&amp;#39;s recent rise in price has been due to the the current rise in vaule in crypto assets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This gap will fill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be it one month or one quarter, or 2 years, barring a market crash, I think it will fill. This sell off is dumb, short sided, and backwards, not forward looking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s a dip worth holding and buying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;COIN success included recently adding more coins to compete with competitors, 24/7 phone support coming next quarter, Coin Prime &amp;amp; Coin Cloud, services recently added, to my understanding, to sell crypto to institutions (think NBA and FB deal,) and also to allow websites to accept direct payment IN crypto (Coin Cloud.) That move will continue to help Crypto become more and more mainstream, which stands to benefit Coin more than the average competitor due to their Mainstream UI/branding and first mover market share domance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I own some COIN stock.
This is my opinion.
It&amp;#39;s not investment advice. Don&amp;#39;t buy or sell things because of what people on the internet say.
I hope to provoke conversation. To have my assumptions challenged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉的市值仍然是大众集团的7倍，而大众集团的利润是5倍，销售的汽车是11倍，而且可比的电动车销售增长更快。]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至昨晚，大众汽车市值为1430亿美元，特斯拉为1.01万亿美元。

到2021年第三季度，大众汽车的利润为168亿美元，而特斯拉为32亿美元。

到2021年第三季度，大众汽车售出695.1万辆汽车，而特斯拉售出62.7万辆。

到2021年第三季度，大众汽车电动车销量为539K（到2020年期间+135%），而特斯拉为627K
(+97%).

I...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqolej/teslas_mkt_cap_is_still_7_x_vw_group_which_makes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqolej/teslas_mkt_cap_is_still_7_x_vw_group_which_makes/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 10:26:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;VW mkt cap was $143 billion as of last night vs Tesla at $1.01 trillion.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To 3Q 2021 YTD VW profits were $16.8 billion vs Tesla $3.2 billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To 3Q 2021 YTD VW sold 6.951 million cars vs Tesla 0.627 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To 3Q 2021 YTD VW EV sales were 539K (+135% to 2020 period) vs Tesla&amp;#39;s 627K (+97%).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I won&amp;#39;t torment Tesla shareholders with obvious comments - the stats speak for themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>