<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 07:23:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[6万美元的GME YOLO，不能停止不会停止]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r56bii/60k_gme_yolo_cant_stop_wont_stop/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r56bii/60k_gme_yolo_cant_stop_wont_stop/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 06:40:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[与顾问开始时的麻烦]]></title><description><![CDATA[可能是顾问们最讨厌的事情：我不知道自己在做什么，但已经关注Boglehead几个月了。
已经关注Bogleheads几个月了。在过去，我一直是一个
在财务问题上完全是个白痴。最近我父亲去世了，给我们留下了一笔
相当多的钱。我的妻子非常坚定地认为她想要一个顾问和...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r5bqrk/trouble_starting_off_with_an_advisor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r5bqrk/trouble_starting_off_with_an_advisor/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 05:20:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably what advisors hate the most: I have no idea what I&amp;#39;m doing but have been following Bogleheads for a few months now. In the past I have been a complete idiot with financial matters. Recently my dad passed away and left us a considerable sum. My wife is pretty adamant she wants an advisor and looking at my past financial mistakes I agree with her. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I went out and researched like crazy. We met with a friend&amp;#39;s trusted 1% Aum guy, a Vanguard PAS guy and an advice-only guy. I liked the AUM guy and his advice but I think Bogleheads has turned me sour on AUM. Plus the AUM guy wanted everything at his brokerage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We initially liked the advice-only guy because he was cheaper and I thought he help me get my feet underneath me for DIY down the road. We could set everything up wherever we want. I also liked him because he set us up on their version of Mint to track all our spending. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But he constantly hmmed and hawed on allocation. We had our 2nd meeting today and for an hour and a half he talked about getting a new credit card and retirement goals and tasks and ... I finally jumped in and said if you had to invest my dad&amp;#39;s money what funds in the market tomorrow and what allocation would he recommend? He pulls up his website and hits an 70/30 Risk button - hits another button and boom pops out an 11 fund portfolio. I ask him what&amp;#39;s the software they&amp;#39;re using and he talks about low cost ratios. I asked him if they&amp;#39;re licensing a robo-advisor of some kind and he kind of yada yada&amp;#39;d that one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/0tddsua71n281.png?width=920&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=b10ab2c9e458779ecc41a882376843dc097f360a&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/0tddsua71n281.png?width=920&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=b10ab2c9e458779ecc41a882376843dc097f360a&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got kind of mad that it took him this long to throw out how he delivers allocation advice. I&amp;#39;ve been looking at 3 and 4 fund Vanguard and Fidelity portfolios and told him that&amp;#39;s what I wanted. Then my wife got mad. &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m so tired of hearing about Boogle Heads,&amp;quot; she says. She&amp;#39;s like &amp;quot;what&amp;#39;s wrong with this?&amp;quot; - and I just shut up. I really don&amp;#39;t know what I&amp;#39;m doing I&amp;#39;m just a guy that reads a forum who&amp;#39;s messed up pretty bad in the past. Bogleheads is tough when you don&amp;#39;t have a clue what you&amp;#39;re doing but yet know you want something super simple but can&amp;#39;t explain why that&amp;#39;s better. I can&amp;#39;t explain why VTI/VXUS/BND is better than this. Maybe it&amp;#39;s not all that better? Maybe this is a perfectly fine portfolio?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He also said he wants to DCA this and not lump sum. So my question is - say I go along with this in a Fidelity account. How hard would it be to convert this into a VTI/VXUS/BND down the road?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[索尼的《蜘蛛侠：无路可退》让电影票网站崩溃]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 当时间停留在11月29日的午夜时分，《蜘蛛侠：无路可走》的门票开始销售。
>回家 "开始销售。几分钟之内，国内电影票网站开始崩溃
>因为电影观众急于为今年最令人期待的电影之一抢占座位。
> 今年最令人期待的电影之一。
> 
> 这是在票房上未曾有过的事情。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r5ba4y/sonys_spidermanno_way_home_crashes_movie_ticket/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r5ba4y/sonys_spidermanno_way_home_crashes_movie_ticket/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 05:03:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the clock stuck midnight on Nov. 29, tickets for “Spider-Man: No Way Home” went on sale. Within minutes domestic movie ticket sites began to crash as moviegoers rushed to snag seats for one of the most anticipated films of the year.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is something that the box office has not experienced since the pandemic began and a sign that with the right releases, the movie theater industry has a “bright future,” experts say.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pandemic battered cinemas, crushing demand and nearly bankrupting some of the industry’s largest exhibitors. The box office has been slow to rebound, but sustained momentum over the last six months has provided confidence in an eventual recovery.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overnight, the latest installment of the Marvel Cinematic Universe, a co-production between &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/DIS&quot;&gt;Disney&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/6758.T-JP&quot;&gt;Sony&lt;/a&gt;, has sparked even more optimism. Ticketing sites like Atom Tickets, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/CMCSA&quot;&gt;Fandango&lt;/a&gt; and MovieTickets.com alongside movie theater sites like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AMC&quot;&gt;AMC&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/CNK&quot;&gt;Cinemark&lt;/a&gt; and Regal saw a surge of demand for tickets leading many to crash or place visitors in hour-long online queues.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“There are different tiers of intense fan demand when it comes to box office pre-sales, and this film is clearly showing it belongs near the top with a select few others,” said Shawn Robbins, chief analyst at BoxOffice.com. “For anyone who doubted the communal draw of the theatrical experience over the past two years, look to this enthusiasm for ‘Spider-Man’ as a major inflection point during the box office recovery period and the sign of a bright future ahead.”  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This kind of fervor has not been seen at the box office since 2019 when advanced tickets for titles like “Avengers: Endgame” and “Star Wars: The Rise of Skywalker” went on sale.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/spider-man-no-way-home-ticket-demand-crashed-box-office-sites.html&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;Spider-Man: No Way Home&amp;#39; ticket demand crashed box office sites (cnbc.com)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME YOLO! 终于去做了! 我卖了几个月的csp，收集了很多溢价，周五我被分配到了，不能再兴奋了。Lfg!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r526kl/gme_yolo_finally_went_for_it_been_selling_csps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r526kl/gme_yolo_finally_went_for_it_been_selling_csps/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 04:37:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[是什么催化剂将半导体股票推得如此之高？]]></title><description><![CDATA[尤其是今天--AMD创下了新高，大多数人都像没有明天一样火箭般地上升了。
涨势，就像没有明天一样。当你看到他们过去一个月的表现时，这很疯狂，但我
但我知道他们的收益和所有这些好东西都是在那段时间出来的。
芯片短缺=高需求=永不倒闭似乎不是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r59rt3/what_catalysts_are_pushing_up_the_semiconductor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r59rt3/what_catalysts_are_pushing_up_the_semiconductor/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 04:37:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Especially today - AMD hit a new high and most rocketed like there’s no tomorrow. When you look at their past month performance, it’s crazy, but I understand their earnings and all those good stuff were out during that period. Chip shortage = high demand = never out of business doesn’t seem to be the main push anymore. What else is behind this crazy push?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你是怎么找到这个分论坛的？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我个人是从我看的一个优酷网友那里了解到指数基金的，这让我找到了这个社区。
找到这个社区。你呢？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r5bcjb/how_did_you_find_this_subreddit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r5bcjb/how_did_you_find_this_subreddit/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 04:13:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Personally I learned about index funds from a youtuber I watch and it led me to find this community. How about you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[420.69 GameStop (GME) 股票 🚀🚀🚀🚀]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r56xmz/42069_gamestop_gme_shares/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r56xmz/42069_gamestop_gme_shares/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 03:27:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我错过了什么吗？试图了解红利的价值...]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，假设我有一支价值50美元的股票。它的季度股息为每股1美元
股。这意味着在除息日，该股票的价值为49美元/股。
所以我所有的股票价值将下降1美元，但我在支付日得到1美元的回报。
但我在支付日得到了这1美元的回报。有人怎么能从...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r52i1y/am_i_missing_something_trying_to_understand_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r52i1y/am_i_missing_something_trying_to_understand_the/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 03:27:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok, say I have a stock worth $50 a share. It gives a quarterly dividend of $1 a share. This means that on the ex dividend date, the stock will be worth $49 a share, so all my stock value will drop by $1 a share, but I get paid that $1 a share back on the pay date. How does anyone make any money from dividends if the stock price drops?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[60岁退休--什么能让你在65岁时享受到医疗保险？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想我有足够的钱在60岁时退休，但不确定我是否想支付一大笔健康保险费用。
不知道我是否想为健康保险支付一大笔钱。我在考虑做非全职工作或一份轻松的工作，直到65岁，只是为了福利。
勤的工作，直到65岁，只是为了福利。

有什么想法？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r59bmz/retire_at_age_60_what_gets_you_through_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r59bmz/retire_at_age_60_what_gets_you_through_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 03:27:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think I will have enough to retire at 60, but not sure if I want to pay a bunch of money for health insurance. I was thinking of working par-time or a light job until 65 just for the benefits. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这是什么意思？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r59os6/what_does_it_mean/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r59os6/what_does_it_mean/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 02:39:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是2021年11月29日星期一的市场回顾。请欣赏!]]></title><description><![CDATA[心理市场回顾 - 2021年11月29日，星期一

在经历了极度动荡、假期缩短的一周后，股市在周一出现反弹。
周一，在科技股大幅反弹的推动下，股票出现反弹，因为市场参与者
市场参与者正在努力应对新发现的 "Omicron "冠状病毒的潜在影响。
冠状病毒变体的潜在影响。该...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r55t5m/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_nov_29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r55t5m/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_nov_29/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:58:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Monday, November 29, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following an extremely volatile, holiday-shortened week, stocks rebounded on Monday, driven higher by a huge bounce in technology, as market participants grapple with the potential implications of the newly discovered “Omicron” coronavirus variant. The Dow Jones (DIA) closed higher after its worst day since October 2020, as the price of oil, which suffered its worst day all year, somewhat rebounded. While it is way too early to make any conclusions, I am personally looking at this dip as a potential buying opportunity in equities that were overstretched before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wedbush analyst Dan Ives wrote in a note to clients, “Ultimately this is not the first or last variant scare and our tech playbook over the last 18 months has been to use these macro/risk-off events as buying opportunities to own the tech sector specifically cloud, cyber-security, and 5G winners. While we are seeing a return to normalcy, a semi-remote workforce environment we believe is here to stay which underscores our tech cloud thesis into 2022 that the digital transformation build-out will be accelerated and is not a one time COVID pull forward event&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The US and EU have banned a host of destinations to ban flights from several African countries after the new variant was discovered. But cases of the variant, which the World Health Organization (WHO) has so far designated as a &amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.who.int/news/item/26-11-2021-classification-of-omicron-(b.1.1.529&quot;&gt;variant of concern&lt;/a&gt;-sars-cov-2-variant-of-concern),&amp;quot; have also detected in regions including the U.K., Hong Kong, Australia, Germany and Italy, among others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While there is still much that needs to be studies regarding the Omicron variant, Pfizer (PFE) and Moderna (MRNA), the two largest producers the current COVID vaccine, asid they are already working to adapt current inoculations for the new variant and that, if a tailor made vaccine is necessary, would be completed relatively quickly. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/28/moderna-says-an-omicron-variant-vaccine-could-be-ready-in-early-2022.html&quot;&gt;Moderna’s Chief Medical Officer Paul Burton said a new vaccine to address the Omnicron variant &lt;/a&gt;would be widely available in early 2022 and &lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/omicron-covid-19-variant-pfizer-184458407.html&quot;&gt;Pfizer said it could take about 100 days to have a tailor made vaccine ready to be widely available.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;President Biden said of the new variant, “his variant is a cause for concern, not a cause for panic. We have the best vaccines in the world, the best medicine, the best scientists, and we’re learning more every single day. We have more tools today to fight the variant than we ever have before.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite concerns present in the market, consumer spending, which accounts for roughly 70% of US GDP, continues accelerating. While supply-chain disruptions could lead shoppers toward in-stock items at physical stores this year, I think overall spending will see a healthy increase. The National Retail Federation (NRF) is forecasting an 8.5%-10.5% increase in holiday sales this year, compared with 2020. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The latest reading shows the personal savings rate is 7.5% (savings as a % of disposable income), the third-highest rate coming into Thanksgiving in the last quarter century. While this is down dramatically from the spike during the pandemic lockdowns (when consumers were unable to consume), the savings rate remains notably above the long-term average of 6.5% (6.1% excluding 2020). We think elevated savings will be drawn down, representing additional dry powder that will power consumer-spending growth for an extended period. At 4.2%, wage growth is now the highest it&amp;#39;s been since Thanksgiving of 2007, providing additional fuel for consumers. Looking back over the last 25 years, when wage growth was above 4% and accelerating, GDP growth averaged 3.2%, compared with an average of 2.5% over the entire period, according to a report by Edward Jones. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chief Executive Satya Nadella sold about half of his shares in the company last week, according to a federal securities filing. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/0001513142/000106299321011647/xslF345X03/form4.xml?campaign_id=4&amp;amp;emc=edit_dk_20211129&amp;amp;instance_id=46511&amp;amp;nl=dealbook&amp;amp;regi_id=90401093&amp;amp;segment_id=75585&amp;amp;te=1&amp;amp;user_id=b1b6731f732a5b8d7bb632a925fe64b9&quot;&gt;In the filing last week&lt;/a&gt; with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, the Redmond, Wash.-based software company reported Mr. Nadella sold 838,584 shares over two days, down from close to 1.7 million shares.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jack Dorsey announced he will be stepping down as CEO of social media Twitter (TWTR), giving the lead role to Chief Technology Officer Parag Agrawal. In my opinion, this is good news for Twitter, given they will now have more focused leadership. Dorsey, who is also the CEO of Square (SQ) has a lot on his plate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nissan Motors announced it was planning to spend $18 billion over five years to accelerate growth of their EVs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Alibaba (BABA) stock fell to its lowest level in four years amid the continued regulatory push by the Chinese Communist Party (CCP).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tencent (TCEHY) will further open their super-app WeChat, with over 1.2 billion users in China, and allow links to external shopping sites like Alibaba. This was a new regulation instituted by the CCP in order to encourage competition among the big tech firms. Previously, apps in China did not allow competitor links in their platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Russia will continue slowing down the speed of Twitter on mobile devices until all content deemed illegal is deleted, state communications regulator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note price target upgrades were written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;John Deere (DE) with three target raises. Stock currently around $350

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evercore ISI from $354 to $415 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deutsche Bank from $375 to $398 at Hold&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stifel Nicolaus from $430 to $445 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Marvell Technology (MRVL) with two target raises. Stock currently around $75

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JP Morgan from $74 to $85 at Overweight&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B. Riley from $83 to $90&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pfizer (PFE) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $50 to $60 at Equal Weight. Stock currently around $53&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snowflake (SNOW) target raised by BTIG Research from $353 to $421 at Buy. Stock currently around $366&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zscaler (ZS) target raised by Needham from $345 to $390 at Strong-Buy. Stock currently around $354.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“All our dreams can come true, if we have the courage to pursue them.” - Walt Disney&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列现在报告说，欧米茄的社区传播是由一位服用3个剂量的心脏病专家传播给另一位服用3个剂量的心脏病专家的。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465473422817959947</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465473422817959947</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:13:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这真的很简单，伙计们。

为了阻止这个新的变种，我们必须做那些已经对旧变种失败的事情。

但这次我们必须更努力地去做，以便在它再次失败时有更多人受害。

如果这对你来说毫无意义，你就是个坏人。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465482430802968580</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465482430802968580</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:13:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国现在建议每3个月进行一次covid强化治疗
https://t.co/UKOndcb7la]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465454012250132487</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465454012250132487</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:13:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AAPL现在是一个好的买点吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，伙计们，我刚刚开始更多的分析股票，我想我将尝试
并在这里发表。这是我对AAPL的第二次分析，最后一次是
5月份的。如果你对我有任何反馈意见，那将是非常好的。
感谢。如果你有问题，请随时提出，我将尽力解决。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r576vm/is_aapl_a_good_buy_right_now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r576vm/is_aapl_a_good_buy_right_now/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:13:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey there guys, I just started analyzing stocks more and I thought I´ll try to do that and post it here. That´s my second analysis for AAPL, the last one was from May. If you have any feedback for me that would be great and highly appreciated. If you have questions feel free to ask, I´ll try to answer everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we will look through the basics of Apple´s business and then see if we can come up with a fair value for Apple´s stock using discounted free cashflow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not financial advice and I personally own shares in Apple. Nevertheless I will try to stay as unbiased and objective as I can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First let´s review their different revenue streams. Their biggest stream, around &lt;strong&gt;50%&lt;/strong&gt; of their sales comes from the &lt;strong&gt;iPhone&lt;/strong&gt;. The &lt;strong&gt;Mac&lt;/strong&gt; makes up around &lt;strong&gt;11%&lt;/strong&gt;, the &lt;strong&gt;iPad&lt;/strong&gt; around &lt;strong&gt;9%&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Services&lt;/strong&gt; around &lt;strong&gt;19%&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Wearables, Home and Accessories&lt;/strong&gt; around &lt;strong&gt;11%&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the valuation:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We take &lt;strong&gt;analyst estimates&lt;/strong&gt;, we discount that by our &lt;strong&gt;required return of 8%&lt;/strong&gt;. Then we use the &lt;strong&gt;perpetual growth rate of 2,5%&lt;/strong&gt; and that gave us a fair value for Apple´s stock of &lt;strong&gt;$99 per share&lt;/strong&gt;. But because we have to account for &lt;strong&gt;Apple´s debt&lt;/strong&gt; as well, our &lt;strong&gt;fair value of equity&lt;/strong&gt; would be &lt;strong&gt;$94 per share&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now feel free to include a margin of safety to that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Apple´s price being at &lt;strong&gt;$160&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;per share&lt;/strong&gt; right now, it´s a little too high. That´s why I don´t think buying heavily is a good idea. Although you can always dollar-cost-average. That´s where you invest every month the same amount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where I see Apple´s stock price in 5 years.&lt;/strong&gt; We can calculate where the price might be in 5 years with the &lt;strong&gt;Earnings Per Share (EPS TTM)&lt;/strong&gt;, the &lt;strong&gt;Estimated Growth Rate&lt;/strong&gt; and the &lt;strong&gt;Future P/E Value&lt;/strong&gt;. With this method I get a stock price of &lt;strong&gt;$293 per share&lt;/strong&gt; which is higher than what it is now. Almost double. That´s why you have to be careful with this analysis. Always do your own due diligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What I´ll do.&lt;/strong&gt; I believe in Apple. I think they will stay for a long time and innovate even more. That´s why, although the price is not where I would want it to be, I will continue to &lt;strong&gt;dollar-cost-average&lt;/strong&gt;. That way I don´t mind the volatile market and hold for the longterm. Even if they don´t double in 5 years, I´m rather bullish on this company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading and I hope I´ll see you again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[杰克-多尔西辞职，专注于他的胡须]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r51mb7/jack_dorsey_resigns_to_focus_on_his_beard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r51mb7/jack_dorsey_resigns_to_focus_on_his_beard/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:13:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[自从《华尔街日报》和《巴伦周刊》写了关于现在是投资小盘股的最佳时机的文章后，罗素指数已经下跌200点。]]></title><description><![CDATA[11月12日
https://www.wsj.com/articles/inflation-bets-give-a-boost-to-small-cap-stocks-11636885800

"通胀押注给小盘股带来推动力 较小的公司可以管理通胀
投资者说，较小的公司比较大的公司能更快地管理通货膨胀的压力。
他们说，小型公司比大型公司能更快地管理通货膨胀的压力，他们正在寻求价格的庇护...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r585l8/since_wsj_and_barrons_wrote_articles_on_now_being/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r585l8/since_wsj_and_barrons_wrote_articles_on_now_being/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:13:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;November 12th: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/inflation-bets-give-a-boost-to-small-cap-stocks-11636885800&quot;&gt;https://www.wsj.com/articles/inflation-bets-give-a-boost-to-small-cap-stocks-11636885800&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Inflation Bets Give a Boost to Small-Cap Stocks
Smaller companies can manage inflationary pressures more quickly than larger ones, say investors who are seeking refuge from price increases&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;November 12th: Barrons 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/cheap-small-company-stocks-51636763053&quot;&gt;https://www.barrons.com/articles/cheap-small-company-stocks-51636763053&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Small-Cap Stocks Are in Line to Be Big Winners in 2022&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look at the 1 month chart and it&amp;#39;s been a steady drop since these 2 articles happened. Very frustrating as I went all in on small caps and they are easily my biggest losers especially on a day like today with the market super up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the 12th, there has been only ONE day the Index went up (by a measly 5 points), every other day has gone down. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/search?client=safari&amp;amp;rls=en&amp;amp;q=Russell+index&amp;amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;amp;oe=UTF-8&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/search?client=safari&amp;amp;rls=en&amp;amp;q=Russell+index&amp;amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;amp;oe=UTF-8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$HIMX是一个不费吹灰之力的产品，在这个价格上是一个便宜货，是你正在寻找的DD。]]></title><description><![CDATA[奇景科技有限公司是一家领先的供应商和无晶圆厂半导体制造商，总部位于台湾台南市。
总部位于台湾台南市，成立于2001年6月12日。

该公司IMHO在这个价格上被低估了，有很大的上升空间。
HIMX在过去4个季度有强劲的收入和盈利增长，但...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r522vr/himx_is_a_fukin_no_brainer_and_a_bargain_at_this/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r522vr/himx_is_a_fukin_no_brainer_and_a_bargain_at_this/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 23:46:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Himax Technologies, Inc. is a leading supplier and fabless semiconductor manufacturer headquartered in Tainan City, Taiwan founded on 12 June 2001.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company IMHO is so undervalued at this price and has much room to go up, HIMX had strong revenue and earnings growth in the last 4 quarters, but the stock price did not act accordingly, and I believe this growth will continue due to chip shortage, and the transformation in the global economy to electric cars, in 2030 most of the big cars brands are expected to stop producing diesel cars and produce only electric cars, this is regardless the already existed electric cars brands like Xpeng, Nio, Tesla etc. this will cause constant demand on chips and more production and revenue for HIMX and other semiconductor stocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/u5g0jy7vvk281.png?width=485&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=12c95a4227644109ca4be596b4ce38d3a91b3ff1&quot;&gt;HIMX Revenue and Earnings over the last 4 quarters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below a comparison between AMD and HIMX performance for the last 4 quarters:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;.HIMX Revenue growth ................  AMD Revenue growth&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q4 2020 $276M &lt;strong&gt;QoQ +15%&lt;/strong&gt; ----- Q4 2020 $3.24B &lt;strong&gt;QoQ +15%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q1 2021 $309M &lt;strong&gt;QoQ +12%&lt;/strong&gt; ------ Q1 2021 $3.45B &lt;strong&gt;QoQ +7%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q2 2021 $365M &lt;strong&gt;QoQ +18%&lt;/strong&gt; ------- Q2 2021 $3.85B &lt;strong&gt;QoQ +12%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q3 2021 $421M &lt;strong&gt;QoQ +15% -------&lt;/strong&gt; Q3 2021 $4.31B &lt;strong&gt;QoQ +12%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;....................HIMX...........AMD
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Price to Earnings ............ 5.35 .................... 49.23&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Price to Sales  ..................1.29  ....................12.76&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Book value per share .....$4.17!! 🤯  ...........$5.89!! 🤯&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Current ratio  ...................2.01 ...................... 2.24&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AMD is definitely bigger name than HIMX but I used this comparison just to show how HIMX is growing on the same pace as AMD, how it has healthy statistics, and how cheap its valuation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IMO HIMX is a solid play and a bargain at this price, the only thing that is holding back the stock price is the possible conflict between China and Taiwan, but if that happens, all the market will tank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My conservative prediction is that One year from now assuming normal market conditions HIMX price will be at least $20.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also 15% short interest add some spice to the stock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And my last word is, see you on the moon 🚀 🚀 🚀 🌙 🌙 🌙&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: this is not a financial advice, do your own DD before investing.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我必须要读这个。现在你也知道了。https://t.co/7wwXuzu0uF]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465434225667153923</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465434225667153923</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 23:35:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列国内情报机构已经获得临时许可，可以访问该国已确认的Omicron变体病例的人的电话数据，用于追踪联系人。https://t.co/78ndtWqKvN]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465449663570583558</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465449663570583558</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 23:35:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这个男人、神话和传奇人物将在美国东部时间今天下午6点加入我们的Twitter Spaces，谈论他的最新专辑，他对比特币的看法，以及更多的内容 ⚡️ https://t.co/6AypLg2HjR]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465441807374897152</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465441807374897152</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 23:35:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[网络星期一即将来临]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4oryc/cyber_monday_is_coming/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4oryc/cyber_monday_is_coming/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 21:35:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Covid公司的FUD并没有欺骗任何人]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4wcpo/covid_fud_aint_fooling_nobody/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4wcpo/covid_fud_aint_fooling_nobody/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:57:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[缩放电话得到了回报。我可以正式说我赚了6位数。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4x1ec/zoom_calls_paid_off_i_can_officially_say_i_make_6/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4x1ec/zoom_calls_paid_off_i_can_officially_say_i_make_6/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:57:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我正在考虑卖掉我的富达账户中的所有东西，用先锋基金代替。]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好，我是一个来自英国的新手投资者，24岁，我一直在投资。
我从2020年金融危机前就开始投资。

我一开始在vanguard（买入生命策略100%+sp500基金）。
然而，我觉得我的选择有限，于是开了一个富达的账户。

我每个月都会存钱...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r52oqd/thinking_about_selling_everything_in_my_fidelity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r52oqd/thinking_about_selling_everything_in_my_fidelity/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:45:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi there, I&amp;#39;m a newbie investor from the UK here, 24 years old, I&amp;#39;ve been investing since just before covid 2020 crash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started off with vanguard (buying into life strategy 100% + sp500 fund), however I felt limited with my options and opened up a fidelity account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been depositing monthly into my fidelity account and into various different funds, Which I regret because I clearly have no idea what I&amp;#39;m doing... &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The funds have an average fee of 0.5% and I think this is quiet high (correct me if I am wrong). + the account fee + platform fee... this, over time, will eat into the value of my assets. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am writing today to get a second opinion and a bit of guidance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/jrhxnaieyk281.png?width=1920&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=f6ae3a1beda911396086e49e1aa8dd1dce48ca59&quot;&gt;30 fund portfolio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/0yy6ivbczk281.png?width=1482&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=1ffe3ea17a82b79b0cbdb88dbc3e1d2983a0e931&quot;&gt;vanguard portfolio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please help me... I am not too sure on what to do now... &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know this is a mess, all suggestions are welcome! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NSFW, my portfolio might give you anxiety. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在大流行病交易中赚取26亿美元的对冲基金投资者表示，大流行病可能会对股市产生利好作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[对冲基金大亨比尔-阿克曼（Bill Ackman）周末表示，新的欧米茄变体的
导致COVID-19的冠状病毒的新变种，如果它被证明会导致感染者出现轻度到中度的症状，那么可能会对股票产生利好。
感染者会出现轻度至中度症状。该病毒的发现
该变种的发现导致了最糟糕的黑色星期五之一...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r517w5/hedgefund_investor_who_made_26_billion_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r517w5/hedgefund_investor_who_made_26_billion_on/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:32:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hedge-fund luminary Bill Ackman over the weekend said the new omicron variant of the coronavirus that causes COVID-19 could be bullish for stocks if it proves to result in mild to moderate symptoms for those who contract it. The discovery of the variant resulted in one of the worst Black Friday trading sessions in recent memory, with the Dow Jones Industrial Average DJIA, 0.98%, the S&amp;amp;P 500 index SPX, 1.62% and the Nasdaq Composite Index COMP, 2.08% all tumbling by at least 2%, but Ackman’s comments suggest that investors’ knee-jerk response may have been an overreaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bond yields on Friday also fell as prices for government debt saw a rush to the perceived safety of Treasurys on the back of fresh concerns about new restrictions that could result from a strain of COVID that the World Health Organization on Friday designated a variant of concern. However, stocks were bouncing back on Monday and the 10-year Treasury note yield TMUBMUSD10Y, 1.528% was up 8 basis points at 1.56%. Prices for Treasurys fall as yields rise. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ackman, who runs Pershing Square Capital, is known for his lucrative COVID wager. The Financial Times reported back in 2020 that the investor cashed out on bet that netted him a $2.6 billion profit on a $27 million at risk, on the premise that insurance premiums would soar during the height of the 2020 COVID pandemic as economies locked down. He also later in 2020 said that he placed bearish bets on corporate credit on the day that Pfizer PFE, -0.64%  and BioNTech BNTX, 3.65% released positive trial data on their COVID-19 vaccine, which triggered a whipsaw rally in stocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ackman was wagering that the vaccines would lead to mask-wearing complacency. However, that bet presumably turned out wrong as markets continued to surge in the aftermath of those vaccines. The danger posed by the omicron variant isn’t yet fully understood, even though governments in Europe, Asia, the Middle East and the Americas immediately restricted travel from southern Africa. Vaccine manufacturers have said that they are examining the variant closely and note that the current batch of remedies might still prove effective against the strain and new vaccines could be readied in early 2022 if needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/hedge-fund-investor-who-made-2-6-billion-on-pandemic-trades-says-omicron-could-be-bullish-for-stock-market-11638198173?mod=home-page&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/hedge-fund-investor-who-made-2-6-billion-on-pandemic-trades-says-omicron-could-be-bullish-for-stock-market-11638198173?mod=home-page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[年轻时承担更大风险的谬误]]></title><description><![CDATA[我经常听到这样的话。当你年轻的时候要承担更大的风险。当你在
你20多岁的时候，重仓高风险/高回报的股票是可以的。但这是
有缺陷的推理。

事实上，在你年轻的时候冒大风险是更有风险的，因为
机会成本。人们总是提到...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r533z7/the_fallacy_of_taking_bigger_risks_when_you_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r533z7/the_fallacy_of_taking_bigger_risks_when_you_are/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:32:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I hear this all the time. Take bigger risks when you are young. When you are in your 20’s its fine to go heavy in high risk/high reward stocks. But this is flawed reasoning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The truth is taking big risks when you are young is more risky because of opportunity costs. People always mention compounding interest over decades. But fail to apply this to investing in risky stocks when you are young. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lets say you are 20 years old and you have $10k to invest. Its common to hear people say you can be more risky since you are so young. And even if you do YOLO and lose it all you can easily recover. But think opportunity cost. What did you really lose doing a YOLO?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$10,000&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invest in an index fund that returns 8.5% annualized return &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Withdraw at 65 years old&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That $10k becomes $400k. So you basically lost $400k because you YOLOed on a risky stock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you hold till 70 you lost $600k. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At age 90 you can give your children and grandchildren $3.2 million. Or you could have fun and lose it all on a risky stock. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bottom line is a young persons greatest asset is TIME. Throwing investment time away by taking unnecessary risk is a massive mistake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not saying don’t buy stocks that are risky hyper growth companies. But also don’t gamble needlessly. Because you are gambling much more than that couple hundred or thousand you see next to the stock ticker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[游戏店。Finviz报告112%的SI - 第二回合？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r503cb/gamestop_finviz_reporting_112_si_round_2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r503cb/gamestop_finviz_reporting_112_si_round_2/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 19:14:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊准备在2022年初超过UPS和联邦快递，成为美国最大的快递公司，执行官说]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/amazon-on-track-to-be-largest-us-delivery-service-by-2022-exec-says.html

亚马逊全球消费者首席执行官戴夫-克拉克（Dave Clark）周一告诉CNBC，该公司有望成为美国最大的快递公司。
该公司有望在2021年底或2022年初成为美国最大的快递服务。
2021年底或2022年初成为美国最大的快递公司。

分析师们已经...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4zkvm/amazon_poised_to_pass_ups_and_fedex_to_become/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4zkvm/amazon_poised_to_pass_ups_and_fedex_to_become/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 18:16:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/amazon-on-track-to-be-largest-us-delivery-service-by-2022-exec-says.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/amazon-on-track-to-be-largest-us-delivery-service-by-2022-exec-says.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dave Clark, Amazon’s CEO of worldwide consumer, told CNBC on Monday that the company is on track to become the nation’s largest delivery service by the end of 2021 or early 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Analysts have long predicted Amazon would overtake carriers like UPS, FedEx and the U.S. Postal Service, thanks to its increasingly in-house network of planes, trucks, vans and ships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a positive development as Amazon dependence on other carriers will be lessen. The logistic and warehouse networks are in a optimal mode now as Amazon has been invested heavily to fight off the competition. This proves that the investment cycle has finally paid off as patience investors will be holding the amazon stocks and waiting for the next stock appreciation cycle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我刚刚在经纪公司存入7千美元，28岁，你会在这些股票中买入哪些股票做长线？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在上班前发这个帖子，所以请原谅我不是很详细，将尽力而为。
尽量使其与大家息息相关，而不仅仅是我对这3只股票的看法。
股票，我想知道对长期的意见。

特斯拉

苹果

索菲

我拥有特斯拉是因为.... 这就是特斯拉。在我看来，人们希望...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4wghb/i_just_deposited_7k_into_brokerage_age_28_which/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4wghb/i_just_deposited_7k_into_brokerage_age_28_which/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 18:16:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Posting this right before work so forgive me for not being super detailed, will try my best to make this relevant for everyone and not just me about these 3 stocks I want to know opinions on for long term: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sofi &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I own Tesla because.... It is Tesla. People in my honest opinion want to believe they will only be making vehicles in the future. Not the case if Elon Musk gets his way (check out the Tesla bot for example, not to mention space travel, etc). Before today held 2 shares of Tesla, plan on buying 2 more. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple is a good long term buy and hold because it is Apple of course. I do not believe the Apple car that should be releasing in the next 3 years has been priced in to the stock at all yet. I could see Apple being worth over $500/share say 3 years from now. Before today held 14 shares of Apple, plan on buying 10 more. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sofi is an underdog stock. I could see this stock going much further down, possibly to/below $10 a share again. Sofi is by definition loosing money, and it is the outlier compared to say a Tesla or an Apple stock... However I see it as being revolutionary when it comes to financial products for the everyday person. As a millennial most of my friends from around the United States seem to know more about Sofi than Goldman Sachs, Wells Fargo, etc. I would be shocked if Sofi is not worth $40 a share this time next year. Before today held 48 shares, will be buying 25 more today, and will wait for a potential dip below $12 - if that happens will buy as many shares as I can. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tell me if I am missing anything with these stocks, and for us readers in similar situations, maybe a few stocks to consider purchasing in lieu of any of the above 3?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[10月耐用品订单下滑0.5%。]]></title><description><![CDATA[10月耐用品新订单按季节性调整后减少了1美元。
经调整的12亿美元或0.5%，至2601亿美元，美国人口普查局公布。
宣布。 

这一下降是连续两个月的下降，此前9月份经季节性调整后为0.4%。
9月下降。不包括运输业，新订单...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r4z1e9/orders_for_durable_goods_slid_05_in_october/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r4z1e9/orders_for_durable_goods_slid_05_in_october/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:53:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;New orders for manufactured durable goods in October decreased A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $1.2  billion or 0.5% to $260.1 billion, the U.S. Census Bureau announced. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This decrease, down two consecutive months, followed a SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 0.4% September  decrease. Excluding transportation, new orders increased  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 0.5%.  Excluding defense, new orders increased  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 0.8%. Transportation equipment,  down three of the last four months, drove the SEASONALLY ADJUSTED decrease, 2.0 billion or  2.6% to $75.3 billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shipments of manufactured durable goods in October, up five of the  last six months, increased  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $4.0 billion or 1.5% to $261.5 billion. This  followed  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 0.6% September increase. Transportation equipment, up  following two consecutive monthly decreases, led the increase,  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $2.3  billion or 3.2% to $75.3 billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfilled orders for manufactured durable goods in October, up nine  consecutive months, increased  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $3.1 billion or 0.2% to $1,249.7 billion.  This followed  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 0.7% September increase. Machinery, up nineteen  consecutive months, led the increase, up  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED$1.4 billion or 1.2% to $113.7  billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inventories of manufactured durable goods in October, up nine  consecutive months, increased  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $2.8 billion or 0.6% to $466.0 billion.  This followed  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 1.0% September increase. Fabricated metal products, up  thirteen consecutive months, led the increase, up  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $0.9 billion or 1.4% to  $61.0 billion.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.floordaily.net/flooring-news/orders-for-durable-goods-slid-05-in-october&quot;&gt;https://www.floordaily.net/flooring-news/orders-for-durable-goods-slid-05-in-october&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一支你拥有相当比例的股票在瞬间上涨了数百万美元

但这只是因为你要卸任CEO了 https://t.co/GnA0DQORMb]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465330319331139596</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465330319331139596</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:40:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于通货膨胀，COVID-19现在是COVID-20.178。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465372508228624401</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465372508228624401</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:40:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[科维德的死亡率没有上升。由于Omicron突变是 "超级温和 "的变种，世卫组织和将限制和大规模歇斯底里换成了谨慎的乐观态度。]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，伙计们，如果你们对市场的突然下滑感到担忧，这里有一个好消息
一些好消息

世界卫生组织和世界各地的冠状病毒专家今天上午呼吁
各国放弃旅行限制，结束大规模的歇斯底里，转而采取
谨慎乐观的态度，因为最初的报告显示...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4z16b/covid_death_rate_not_rising_swap_restrictions_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4z16b/covid_death_rate_not_rising_swap_restrictions_and/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:15:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey guys, if you&amp;#39;re worried about the sudden downturn in the markets, here&amp;#39;s some great news &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The WHO and Coronavirus experts around the world are calling this morning for countries to drop travel restrictions and end the mass hysteria and instead be cautiously optimistic as initial reports out of South Africa suggest the new Omicron variant is not more lethal than the previous Delta variant. In fact, there have been no reports of hospitalisations or deaths as a result of anyone being diagnosed with Omicron. Most patients merely experience a severe headache, nausea, dizziness and a high pulse rate, according to hospitals and medics across Southern Africa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the news of the new variant, first reported in South Africa, led to mass hysteria around the world: markets thumbed and dozens of countries imposed travel restrictions and additional checks, including the UK, US, EU, Israel, Australia and Japan after the new mutation popped up in the UK, Germany, Italy, Czech Republic and Israel among other countries. Dr Angelique Coetzee, chair of the South African Medical Association, said this reaction was “medically seen, not justified.” A GP for over three decades, and chair of the South African Medical Association, she was the first African doctor to suggest to local authorities Covid had mutated into a new strain. Coetzee called the response from many European countries, including the UK, “just a hype.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Africa’s health minister Joe Phaahla also said the majority of cases of Omicron seen by doctors in his country have been “mild”. He added he has heard from GPs that the “majority of the people they’ve been seeing are mild.” “Our clinicians have not witnessed severe illness. Part of it may be because the majority of those who are positive are young people,” Dr Paahla added.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full story here &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cityam.com/covid-death-rate-not-rising-swap-travel-restrictions-and-mass-hysteria-for-cautious-optimism-as-omicron-mutation-is-super-mild-variant-who-and-coronavirus-experts-say/&quot;&gt;https://www.cityam.com/covid-death-rate-not-rising-swap-travel-restrictions-and-mass-hysteria-for-cautious-optimism-as-omicron-mutation-is-super-mild-variant-who-and-coronavirus-experts-say/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[多尔西从推特卸任]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.huffpost.com/entry/jack-dorsey-stepping-down-twitter-ceo_n_61a4e36fe4b025be1aec6591

Twitter的投资者似乎很喜欢这个，但有趣的是，SQ是平的。你会
你认为这对SQ来说是好事，因为他现在可以只关注该公司，而不是分散注意力。
而不是分散他的注意力。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4y3ma/dorsey_stepping_down_from_twitter/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4y3ma/dorsey_stepping_down_from_twitter/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:15:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.huffpost.com/entry/jack-dorsey-stepping-down-twitter-ceo_n_61a4e36fe4b025be1aec6591&quot;&gt;https://www.huffpost.com/entry/jack-dorsey-stepping-down-twitter-ceo_n_61a4e36fe4b025be1aec6591&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Twitter investors seem to like this, but interesting that SQ is flat. You&amp;#39;d think this would be good for SQ since he can now focus on just that company and not divide his attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我见过的最有趣的狗屎。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4xaoj/funniest_shit_ive_ever_seen/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4xaoj/funniest_shit_ive_ever_seen/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:15:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场在Tilray上犯了一个错误；至少有30%的上升空间]]></title><description><![CDATA[一直在关注大麻行业的人知道，Tilray最近的交易表现令人失望。
交易表现一直不尽如人意。在我看来，该公司交易业绩的最大障碍是由于加拿大的成人娱乐活动。
该公司的交易表现的最大障碍是由于加拿大成人娱乐业的
行业的广泛挑战，以及与大麻相关的零售...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4urxr/market_made_a_mistake_on_tilray_at_least_30_upside/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4urxr/market_made_a_mistake_on_tilray_at_least_30_upside/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:15:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those who&amp;#39;ve been following the cannabis industry, knows that Tilray&amp;#39;s recent trading performance has been underwhelming. In my opinion, the biggest hurdle to the company&amp;#39;s trading performance is due to the Canadian adult recreational industry wide challenge along with covid-related retail headwinds. There&amp;#39;s been struggles for the Canadian cannabis LPs to generate growth organically within the adult recreational segment. For example, while Tilray, market leader in Canadian adult recreational, generated 26% topline growth from $405 million in 2020 to $513 million in 2021, much of that topline growth is derived from acquisitions. In other words, Tilray&amp;#39;s recent revenue growth were &amp;quot;bought&amp;quot; instead of generated organically as the market expands. Low growth within the segment along with some structural challenges and covid-related shut-downs further negatively impacted the industry&amp;#39;s outlook and profitability, resulting in depressing trading performances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As cannabis companies remain illegal in the United States at a federal level and debt capital raising are off the table as a result, Canadian cannabis LPs relies on equity issuance to fund acquisition opportunities to &amp;quot;grow&amp;quot; their toplines. Result of both stagnant growth and share dilution, Tilray traded down from $40 in February 2021 to $10 last close. Tilray&amp;#39;s TTM EV/Sales declined from 40x to 10x. For a growth company within a quickly expanding market that&amp;#39;s only 3 years old, 10x TTM sales EV is a good price in my opinion. What makes it even more attractive is that there&amp;#39;s a catalyst that the market has dismissed and forgotten that will completely derail the stagnant market growth narrative for Tilray.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Germany&amp;#39;s new coalition government has recently reached a deal that&amp;#39;s set to legalize recreational cannabis use. As a result, German pot stocks popped last week on Frankfurt exchange. For example, German cannabis company Synbiotic rose by 33% to $29 Euro, which implies a $100mm market cap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What the market has forgotten however is that Canadian cannabis LP Tilray is actually the market leader in the Germany&amp;#39;s cannabis market. But the stock didn&amp;#39;t move last week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do I know the market made a mistake instead of &amp;quot;everything has been priced in&amp;quot; narrative?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Easy. First, almost every German pot companies moved up last week. The fact that Tilray didn&amp;#39;t change at all suggests that whoever was making market genuinely forgot that Tilray is a market leader in the German cannabis market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, if we assume status quo on Tilray&amp;#39;s 10x EV/Sales multiple, which is a very conservative assumption because we&amp;#39;re completely dismissing the potential of a new, 3-days old, 83 million population addressable market. And if we proxy $90 million of additional revenue, which is another very conservative assumption as Tilray generated $90 million in revenue after Canada legalized their adult recreational cannabis market in 2018; Conservative because German population doubles of Canadian. With the conservative multiple assumption while holding other variables constant, just by adding the additional $90 million in revenue, we should expect Tilray trade up by at least 30%. The fact that it didn&amp;#39;t trade up at the slightest suggests whoever was making market was sleeping in his office after he had his turkey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Third, Tilray is production and distribution ready. Tilray operates two state-of-art facilities in Portugal and Germany with over 3 million square feet of production capacity. Tilray also owns and operates one of the largest market cap pharmaceutical company, CC Pharma, in Germany. Because of the company&amp;#39;s production and distribution capacity, institutional support, larger balance sheet, domestic moms &amp;amp; pops cannabis producers in Germany aren&amp;#39;t like to able to compete against Tilray in the immediate 24 months of legalization, allowing Tilray to secure market leadership. Again, this echoes with why assume only $90 million of revenue and 10x EV/Sales is a very conservative estimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Forth, there has been consistencies showing that the cannabis MTM is very inefficient. Most of you are aware that there were a squeeze with the Canadian cannabis LPs that took place in February. It was driven by Democrats winning the election, investors bet in favour that recreational cannabis use will be legalized in the U.S. It was similar to what&amp;#39;s happening today; similar but different. What&amp;#39;s similar is that both are political driven catalyst and market has gotten it completely wrong. Different was that last time Tilray were traded up for the wrong reason, Tilray has minimal operations in the United States, while they&amp;#39;re already a market leader in the German cannabis market with operations and infrastructures that are unmatched by their competitors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading, let me know if I got it wrong. Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Position: 500 shares long TLRY at C$13.32&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我想我做什么 - 我做什么]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4ugcq/what_i_think_i_do_what_i_do/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4ugcq/what_i_think_i_do_what_i_do/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 16:50:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[S&P500和恢复时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好! 在看到另一个子网站上关于S&P500和破净的评论后，它让我想到了
让我想到了。如果我在最高价时投资于标准普尔500指数，然后价格下跌并不再投入资金，那么最长的时间是多久？
跌，并且不再投入资金，那么历史上最长的时间是多久？
历史上需要多长时间才能达到收支平衡？

希望这有意义？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4ibbc/sp500_and_recovery_time/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4ibbc/sp500_and_recovery_time/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 16:07:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello! After seeing a comment on the s&amp;amp;p500 and breaking Even on another sub, it got me thinking.  If I invest into the s&amp;amp;p500 at the peak Price and the price falls and never put anymore money in, what’s the longest amount of time historically has it taken to breakeven? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully that makes sense? 😅 I’ll try to explain better if it’s not clear what I’m asking &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[对购买共同基金股票感到困惑]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好，我一直想投资一些钱在FXAIX指数基金，但
我对这些股票是如何定价和交易的感到困惑。

从我读到的内容来看，共同基金的股票价格是在每天收市后更新的，这也是股票交易的时间。
这也是股票交易的时间。这是否意味着我将不知道价格
的价格。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r4lz4c/confused_about_buying_mutual_fund_shares/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r4lz4c/confused_about_buying_mutual_fund_shares/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 15:30:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi there, I’ve been looking to invest some money in the FXAIX index fund, but I’m confused about how these shares are priced and traded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From what I read, mutual fund share prices are updated after market close each day, which is also when shares are traded. Does that mean I won’t know the price of the shares I’m buying until they are calculated after close, or am I buying them at the price they’re listed at during the day?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[彼得-林奇的《华尔街》一书摘要]]></title><description><![CDATA[领先于华尔街

 *股票最有可能被接受为审慎的时刻，他们不是
 * 只投资你能承受的损失而不影响你的日常生活。
   只投资你能承受的损失，而不影响你的日常生活
 * 不要高估专业人士的技能和智慧
 * 利用你的优势...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4oizg/peter_lynch_one_up_on_wall_street_book_summary/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4oizg/peter_lynch_one_up_on_wall_street_book_summary/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 15:04:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;h1&gt;One Up on Wall Street&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stocks are most likely to be accepted as prudent at the moment they are not&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only invest what you could afford to lose without that loss having any effect on your daily life&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;#39;t overestimate the skill and wisdom of professionals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take advantage of what you already know&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look for opportunities that haven&amp;#39;t been discovered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Invest in a home first&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Invest in companies, not the stock market&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ignore short term movements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Predicting the economy is futile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Predicting the short term movement of the stock market is futile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Long term stocks have outperformed bonds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The average person is exposed to local companies years before wall street&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the stock market, one in the hand is worth 10 in the bush&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;Any idiot can run this business&amp;quot; is one characteristic of the perfect company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Invest in companies that make products people need to keep buying&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the company insiders are buying, you should too. Management normally sells 2.3 shares for every 1 share they buy. In 1987 after the crash, it was 4 buys for 1 sell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid the hottest stock in the hottest industry, any stock being touted as the next X&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A share of stock is NOT a lotto ticket. It is a part ownership of a business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;P/E ratio can be thought of as the number of years to earn back your original investment. IE = P/E of 10 would be 10 years assuming earnings stay constant. Ratios tend to be lower for slow growers and highest for the fast growers with cyclicals in between depending on the current cycle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look at average P/E ratios on the company you are researching and peers going back several years to determine if it is a good buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid stocks with HIGH P/E ratios. They must have incredible earnings growth to justify the price&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;P/E ratio that is half the growth rate (annual earnings) is very positive and one that is twice the growth rate is very negative. IE = P/E of 10 should be growing at 10%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formula = Growth rate plus dividend yield divided by P/E. IE = 12% growth + 3% yield/10 P/E = 1.5. Less than 1 is bad. 1.5 is ok and 2+ is great.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The stock market as a whole has its own collective P/E ratio, which is a good indicator of weather the market at large is over or under valued. If some stocks are selling at inflated prices relative to earnings, then it could be likely most stocks are selling at inflated prices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest rates have a large effect on p/e ratios as investors pay higher p/e when interest rates are lower and bonds less attractive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dividend paying stocks keep the stock price from falling as far as if there was no dividend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You CAN&amp;#39;T predict future earnings. Wall Street has battalions of analysts trying to do this and they are wrong a lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cash Flow – amount of money a company takes in as a result of doing business. You want to buy companies that don&amp;#39;t need to spend a lot of money to make money IE = company spends 20 million to make 100 million is better than one that needs to spend 90 million to make 100 million. Formula = $20 stock with $2 per share annual cash flow has a 10-1 ratio which is standard (10%). $20 stock with $4 CF = 20% return on cash. Focus on free cash flow – what is left over after normal capital spending is taken out&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debt to equity ratio - normal is 25% debt to 75% equity but higher equity % is better&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[闪电般的下降楔形，是时候做空纳斯达克了!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4ramn/descending_wedge_on_lightning_time_to_short_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4ramn/descending_wedge_on_lightning_time_to_short_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 13:32:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有什么好办法能在短短几句话中说服别人相信指数基金和复利的力量？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4nh1z/whats_a_good_way_to_convince_someone_on_the_power/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4nh1z/whats_a_good_way_to_convince_someone_on_the_power/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 13:32:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一个全面的回顾。看看好市多的股息和股票价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[好市多是世界第三大零售商，是SP500指数中第12大公司。
市值为1,990亿美元。在21财年，好市多的销售额为1920亿美元。
他们在全球有815个仓库。此外，6170万个家庭拥有
此外，6170万户家庭拥有活跃的好市多会员资格，为好市多带来了39亿美元的收入。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4nt8g/a_comprehensive_review_a_look_at_costcos_dividend/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4nt8g/a_comprehensive_review_a_look_at_costcos_dividend/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 11:57:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Costco is the world&amp;#39;s 3rd largest retailer, 12th largest company in the SP500, and has a market cap of $199~ Billion. In FY21&amp;#39; Costco did $192 Billion in sales from their 815 warehouses globally. Additionally, 61.7 million households have active Costco memberships, bringing Costco another $3.9 billion in membership fees alone, all with a 91.3% renewal rate. Let&amp;#39;s take a closer look at Costco from an investment standpoint.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Costco P/E Ratio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
    Costco&amp;#39;s historical P/E hovers around 32x - 35x. Costco&amp;#39;s current P/E ratio sits around 48x which is decently high considering its&amp;#39; historical averages. The increase in Costco&amp;#39;s TTM and current P/E ratio is due to Costco&amp;#39;s stock price appreciating by 44%~ in the last six months alone. I expect Costco&amp;#39;s stock price to stabilize or fall slightly in 2022 as the P/E ratio returns to normal values as long as Costco&amp;#39;s earnings continue to grow. The recent Covid variant could affect Costco&amp;#39;s performance moving into 2022 if the areas where they operate return to lockdown, primarily US and Candian storefronts.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Costco Free Cash Flow&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
    Costco continues to increase their FCF with TTM values sitting around $6 billion. This is ~45% increase in FCF when compared to their 3Y FCF value around $4.2 billion. Costco&amp;#39;s ability to keep increasing free cash flow will ensure they can pay creditors and contributes to the safety of their dividend. Although not guaranteed, Costco has paid special dividend three out the last six years. This is a nice bonus to shareholders considering Costco&amp;#39;s yield is sub one percent.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Costco Profit Margin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
    Costco has historically kept their profit margins right around 2%. The TTM value sits just below 2.5% which is strong indicator for Costco that customers are returning to stores post Covid. 2.5% may not seem like a high number but remember Costco generated around $192 billion in sales last year, meaning they produced a profit on that around $4.8 billion. Couple that with their membership fees as they have healthy sustainable margins.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Costco Dividend Yield &amp;amp; Dividend Yield on Cost&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
    Costco&amp;#39;s dividend yield, as of 26 November 2021, sits at .58% which is the lowest it&amp;#39;s been when compared to historical averages. Again, this is attributed to Costco&amp;#39;s stock price appreciation of ~44% over the last six months. This is another indicator that Costco shares may be overvalued and you should wait to invest. Costco currently pays $3.16 in dividends per share per year. Absent a dividend increase Costco&amp;#39;s price would need to drop to around $430 per share to realign its dividend with the 3Y average. It&amp;#39;s unlikely that Costco is going depreciate by 22% from its current $550 per share value. Costco&amp;#39;s Yield on Cost is where you as an investor can get your return on investment when it comes to building passive income. Costco has a high compound annual growth rate (CAGR) around 13% meaning if you had bought Costco 15 years ago your YOC would be above 6%! Considering Costco has routinely increased their dividend at a rate higher than average you can see your dividends increase quickly without having to invest more capital. This is one of the reasons I decided to invest in Costco. Costco has been increasing their dividends for the past 17 years and I expect that trend to continue as they move closer to joining the dividend aristocrat list.  Costco spends approximately $1.4B per year to maintain their dividend. This and the growth associated appears safe considering Costco&amp;#39;s ability to maintain and increase free cash flow and profit margins.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dividend Payout Ratio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
    Lastly, Costco&amp;#39;s dividend payout ratio sits around 27% with an average around 29-31%. This is significantly lower that most dividend companies including some long-standing dividend aristocrats. Costco is only paying around 30% of its earnings out as dividends meaning they have money available to continue funding further expansion in the future. Costco has strong track record of consistently increasing earnings YoY which contributes to their ability to maintain a stable dividend payout ratio. This will also ensure they are able to continue growing their dividend in the future.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
    Costco is a great growth stock that also pays a dividends. Currently, however, Costco is overvalued. Looking at the current FIBs I wouldn&amp;#39;t expect the price to fall below the .786 FIB at $502. If you are looking to add to your position or start a new position I would wait for a pullback in December or early 2022. Costco is overvalued when you compare both Dividend Yield and P/E ratios with their historical values. I also expect Costco to raise their dividend in 2022 so getting in prior to the increase will help boost your yield on cost so you could always invest now if that&amp;#39;s what you&amp;#39;re look for. I&amp;#39;ll be watching Costco&amp;#39;s price action over the next month or so to find a good entry point to expand my current position.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investingupgraded.com/post/a-comprehensive-review-a-look-at-costco-s-dividend-and-stock-price&quot;&gt;Link to the Full Article with Pictures&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope this helps everyone! Happy Investing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have open positions in Costco.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[接种疫苗的人口百分比，1个以上剂量的Covid-19疫苗。
葡萄牙：89%
韩国：83%。
西班牙：82%。
阿根廷：81%
法国：80%
加拿大: 80%
日本: 79%
澳大利亚: 78%
意大利: 78%
爱尔兰: 78%
巴西: 77%
英国: 76%
以色列: 73%
德国: 71%
美国：70%
土耳其: 68%
墨西哥: 60%
印度: 57%
俄罗斯: 45%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465002199193473027</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465002199193473027</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 11:35:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧米茄可能导致大规模的牛市运行]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果这种变体真的被证明具有高度传染性但不致死
那么这可能是Covid的末日的开始。

假设携带Omicron抗体的人对Delta菌株有免疫力，那么一个新的非致命菌株占领世界并取代Delta菌株，将成为Covid的末日。
新的非致命性菌株占领世界并取代三角洲菌株将是
理想的方式是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r4rvqm/omicron_could_cause_a_massive_bull_run/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r4rvqm/omicron_could_cause_a_massive_bull_run/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 10:57:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If somehow this variant does turn out to be highly contagious but non-lethal then this could be the beginning of the end of Covid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assuming someone carrying Omicron antibodies is immune to the Delta strain, a new non lethal strain taking over the world and replacing Delta would be the ideal way to end this pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Encouraging Omicron to spread is going to spread delta-immunity across the 3rd world much faster than vaccines ever could.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course we won’t really know for a couple of weeks just how deadly this strain is, but if early reports are true and it does turn out to be non-lethal this could be massive for the world and of course markets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[本杰明-格雷厄姆《聪明的投资者》一书摘要]]></title><description><![CDATA[聪明的投资者

 * 一项投资业务是在彻底分析后能保证本金安全和适当回报的业务。
   本金的安全和足够的回报。其他都是投机。
 * 投机者对股票市场波动的态度在于试图
   预测并从市场波动中获利。
 *...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4ojsl/benjamin_graham_the_intelligent_investor_book/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4ojsl/benjamin_graham_the_intelligent_investor_book/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 10:45:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Intelligent Investor&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An investment operation is one which upon thorough analysis promises safety of principal and an adequate return. Anything else is speculation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speculators attitude toward stock market movements lies in trying to anticipate and profit from market fluctuations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Investor&amp;#39;s primary interest lies in acquiring and holding suitable securities at suitable prices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unintelligent speculation is speculation when you think you are investing, any trades done on margin, doing it seriously instead of a pastime, risking more than you can afford to lose.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you are going to speculate, put a small amount aside and don&amp;#39;t add money because you are up. Understand that you in fact are speculating and be prepared to lose.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An investor cannot hope for better than average results by buying IPOs or &amp;quot;Hot&amp;quot; stocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Defensive Investor – Interested in safety and freedom from bother. Purchase investment funds vs creating a stock portfolio, use investment counsel firm, or dollar-cost average.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aggressive Investor – To enjoy a reasonable chance of success, the investor must follow policies which are sound and promising and are NOT popular on Wall Street.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must be either a defensive/conservative investor or an aggressive/enterprising investor. You can&amp;#39;t be 50/50.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speculative stock movements are carried too far in both directions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Savings Accounts can also be a good choice in lieu of bonds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do NOT buy on margin. You are speculating.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the investors funds are placed into high grade short maturity bonds (&amp;amp;lt;7 years), he will not be affected by market prices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Longer term bonds and equities will vary during his lifetime and he must be prepared for this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Investment of most intelligent when it is most businesslike.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Defensive Investor&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferred Stocks are not usually a good investment. It carries no share in the company&amp;#39;s profits beyond a fixed dividend. Thus the preferred holder lacks both the legal claim of a bondholder (Creditor) and the profit possibilities of a common stockholder (Partner). You are dependent on the ability and desire of the company to pay dividends on its common stock. They are under no obligation to pay you unless they pay the common shareholder. This investment vehicle is better for corporations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The choice of a corporate bond vs tax free municipal bond is made by the tax rate payed by the individual. Example – If a municipal pays 30% less than a corporate bond. The investor was at a tax bracket above 30% he would have a net saving by choosing the municipal bond. The opposite is true if the tax was below 30%. Usually tax-free bonds are better for individuals in high tax brackets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only invest in high quality bonds – AAA, AA, A. Do NOT invest in lower quality (2nd grade) issues to get a higher return. Stay away from high yield &amp;quot;Junk Bonds&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rules for Defensive Common Stock Component – A. Adequate diversification but not excessive B. Company should be large, prominent, and conservatively financed C. Long record of dividend payments D. Have a limit on the price willing to pay. Say 25x average earnings over the last 7 years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Defensive investors should usually stay away from Growth Stocks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of the most persuasive test of high quality is uninterrupted record of dividend payments for the last 20 years or more. The defensive investor might be justified in limiting his purchases to those.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock Selection – Adequate size, strong financial condition (Current ratio 2/1), positive earnings for the past 10 years, uninterrupted dividends for the past 20 years, EPS growth of at least 33% in the past 10 years, P/E of less than 15 for the last 3 years earnings, current price not more than 1.5x book value&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Short vs Long Maturity Bonds – if the investor wants to assure himself against a decline in the principal of his bond but at the cost of a lower annual yield and loss of possibility of a gain in principal, pick short maturity bonds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It might be best for the conservative investor to concentrate on issues selling at a close approx. to their tangible asset value (book value). Say not more than 1/3 above that figure. Consider this a premium an extra fee paid for the advantage of a stock exchange listing and ability to quickly sell/buy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But just because a stock is selling for its book value doesn&amp;#39;t make it a good investment. The investor should demand a satisfactory P/E ratio, strong financial position, and the prospect that its earnings will at least be maintained over the year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The risk of paying too high a price for good quality issues is not the chief hazard confronting the average invest. Observation is that the chief losses to investors come from the purchase of low quality issues at times of favorable business conditions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aggressive Investor&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Growth Stock – one which has increased their per share earnings in the past at well above the rate for common stocks and is generally expected to continue to do so.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Growth stocks have 2 problems – Growth stocks with good records and apparently good prospects sell at correspondingly high prices. The investor maybe right in his judgement of the prospects and still not do well. Merely because he overpaid for the expected prosperity. The 2nd is his judgment as the future may prove wrong. Rapid growth can&amp;#39;t last forever.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay away from IPO&amp;#39;s/Common stock offerings. They tend to be offered in &amp;quot;favorable&amp;quot; market conditions for the sellers, not the buyers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The habit of the market is to overvalue common stocks which have been showing excellent growth, but it will also undervalue companies that are out of favor because unsatisfactory developments of a temporary nature.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If looking at growth companies, concentrate on the larger companies that are going through a period of unpopularity. Smaller companies don&amp;#39;t have the resources to withstand the storm and the market is slower to react to improvement vs larger companies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 major sources of undervaluation. A. currently disappointing results and B. unpopularity. But make sure these are temporary and not permanent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The investor should require an indication of at least reasonable stability of earnings over the past decade. No years of earnings deficit plus size and strength to meet possible setbacks. The ideal combination here is that of a large and prominent company selling both well below its past average price and its past average P/E ratio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Secondary Company – one that is not a leader in a fairly important industry. They tend to be undervalued at all times. Buy them only when they are at &amp;quot;Bargain&amp;quot; prices. Bargain being a stock that has an indicated value 50% above the share price.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ways to profit from secondary buys. A. The dividends are relatively high. B. The reinvested earnings are high relative to price paid and will affect the price. C. A bull market is most generous to lower priced issues. D. Smaller companies may be acquired by larger.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The broadest category of investments for the enterprising investor are undervalued stocks of secondary issues. Invest in these only when they can be bought at 2/3 or less of indicated value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Market Fluctuations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 ways to profit from pendulum swings in the market A. Timing – anticipate the direction of the market and buy/sell accordingly (Very Difficult to do). B. Pricing – buying or selling when the stock are quoted above or below fair value. You may do dollar cost averaging when the market is fair value or undervalued to replicate this strategy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A less ambitious form of pricing is the simple effort that you do not pay too much for your stocks. This may work for the defensive investor who is planning on holding long term. You can dollar cost average during fair or low value markets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bull Market Signs – Historically high price levels, high P/E ratios, low dividend yields against bond yields, speculation on margin, lots of public offerings of low quality stocks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The more successful a company, the more likely its price will fluctuate widely. Secondary issues will also fluctuate more widely than major ones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Never buy a stock because it has gone up or sell because it has gone down.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The speculators primary interest lie in anticipating and profiting from market fluctuations. The investor&amp;#39;s primary interest lies in acquiring and holding suitable securities at good prices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Buy-Low Sell High – very difficult to do, so instead increase the proportion of bonds in your portfolio during bull markets and reduce the common stock element. Say 75B/25S during bull markets and 25B/75S during bear and 50/50 during fair value. This allows the investor to feel as if they are doing something and to prevent you from following the crowd.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[周一开幕的好运符]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4obfa/good_luck_charm_for_monday_opening/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4obfa/good_luck_charm_for_monday_opening/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 09:29:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[期货市场现在上涨，可能在周一走向反弹？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看到期货市场上涨了1%左右，这是否预示着周一可能会出现
周一的反弹？我知道，如果期货上涨，并不总是意味着市场会上涨。
市场将上涨，但我对这种情况感到好奇。对不起，我是个新手
问题，我只是想了解一切]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4m67c/futures_market_up_right_now_possibly_heading_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4m67c/futures_market_up_right_now_possibly_heading_for/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 08:33:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I saw the futures market up by around 1 percent, does this signal a possibly rebound for Monday? I know that if futures are up, it doesn’t always mean the markets will be up, but I’m curious in this case. Sorry this is a really newbie question I’m just trying to learn everything&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我们捐赠的大猩猩今晚上了60分钟的节目]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4hryh/the_gorillas_we_donated_to_are_on_60_minutes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4hryh/the_gorillas_we_donated_to_are_on_60_minutes/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 08:33:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>