<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 20:26:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[考虑多样化，并对即将到来的动荡进行对冲。]]></title><description><![CDATA[不，我不是在预测崩溃。我不是在告诉你到底该买什么公司
购买。我的目的是，如果你对目前的市场情况不相信，我可以给你一些思考的余地。
目前的市场状况。

我在5年前开始投资，以年均复合增长率击败了市场，并且有很好的
从那时起，我就以年均复合增长率击败了市场（与SP500相比，我有20%的回报率......）。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqxa47/consider_diversifying_and_hedging_against/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqxa47/consider_diversifying_and_hedging_against/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 19:33:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;No I am not predicting a crash. No I am not telling you exactly what company to buy. I am aiming to give you food for thought if you are in disbelief about the current market situation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started investing 5 years ago and have beaten the market by CAGR with a good margin ever since (20% vs SP500 14% something). Most of it I attribute to value investing. A school of investing that has consistently outperformed growth investing besides the past half decade. The basic idea is to invest in sound undervalued stocks with a margin of security to minimize risk and maximize upside in all market environments. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will not go intro details but if you want to read into it go for Benjamin Graham, Buffett, Lynch. A good start could be Modern Value Investing by Sven Carlin, a PhD Prof. in Amsterdam. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;#39;s market situation is incredible to say the least. We have rising CPI, money printing, Infrastructure Bills, Defaults in China, Tapering, Fake money velocity being created with the intent of kicking the can down the road in hopes of not hitting it off a cliff soon because it will happen. On top of that a high and rising CAPE (Shiller) of almost 40! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A high CAPE is correlated to low future stock market returns. A Shiller this high signals 0 to NEGATIVE avg SP500 returns. This could also go on for years so that we could see stagnation is the market for 5 - 10 - 15 years even. The point is not if this will happen, we have empirical data on this, but that is only a matter of time until it does. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TSLA is maybe the mascot of this circus alongside Altcoins and the Crypto boom. If you made money until now, great for you. If you are thinking of jumping in now, understand that overpaying for equity is at least as bad as buying bad equity. Again, there is empirical data on the correlation of high valuation and low future equity returns. If you buy most equities right now without thorough anaysis and valuation you will guarantee yourself low returns in the future. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could go on and on about what dangers lie ahead and why now is the worse time to jump into trendy stocks. But let&amp;#39;s talk now about how to hedge yourself from downturn in the coming years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hedging at its core deals with minimizing risk of total loss through different strategies. These strategies start from derivative plays to metals and global diversification. So let me present you some ways to limit your downside down the road. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currency Hedging ( Gold Miners, Miner ETFs, Fixed rate Debt) 
Use this if you think the USD will lose power. Buffett&amp;#39;s words &amp;quot;gold is going long fear&amp;quot;. Fear is spreding and capital will slowly flow into this asset class. Gold goes up and you are protected. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Derivatives (buying SP500 Puts) 
A very simple straight to the point thing to do is buying puts on the US economy via LEAPS. The risk lies in the fact that you need to be right 2 times. Once on the direction of the market and once on the time frame. Longer LEAPS cost a lot so it depends on your liquidity if you can/want/should do this. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diversify globally ( China, Europe, Russia) 
Get your hand on good, undervalued global stocks. Most other regions have lower CAPE than the US. Germany is looking good for this alongside China with the recent BABA drop. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep some cash 
Cash can only be lost to theft and inflation. Keeping 15 - 20% in cash might not be that bad since a market crash would present amazing buying opportunities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A popular saying is &amp;quot;value investing is dead&amp;quot;. I would argue for the fact that growth investing is dead for the moment. We are at the end of a huge debt cycle. This, just like valuation needs to return to the mean sooner or later. The next period will be favorable for value investing as the house of cards begins to crash down. You will be down a bit if you follow this strategy but you will secure your profits in the long run. This will help your compounding overall. When the crash comes, be prepared to find bargains and go all in. You will thank yourself later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[恒大正式违约--大商所正准备对恒大集团启动破产程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国恒大集团今天再次拖欠了对国际投资者的利息支付。
国际投资者。DMSA本身也投资于这些债券，并且没有
在今天的宽限期结束之前，没有收到任何利息付款。现在DMSA
正准备对恒大提起破产诉讼，并呼吁所有...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr0lp8/evergrande_officially_defaulted_dmsa_is_preparing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr0lp8/evergrande_officially_defaulted_dmsa_is_preparing/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 19:20:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;China Evergrande Group today again defaulted on interest payments to international investors. DMSA itself is invested in these bonds and has not received any interest payments until today&amp;#39;s end of the grace period. Now DMSA is preparing bankruptcy proceedings against Evergrande and calls on all bond investors to join it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;China Evergrande Group, the second largest real estate developer in China, defaulted on interest payments on two bonds back in September, with the 30-day grace period still ending in October. However, shortly before the end of the grace period, the public was misled by rumors about alleged interest payments. The international media also took the rumors for granted. Only the DMSA - Deutsche Marktscreening Agentur (German Market Screening Agency) already recognized the default at that time and proved in a study that the bankruptcy of Evergrande, the world&amp;#39;s most indebted corporation, could ultimately lead to a &amp;quot;Great Reset&amp;quot;, i.e. the final meltdown of the global financial system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Note to journalists: See DMSA press releases dated Oct. 25 and Oct. 29, 2021, and the DMSA study &amp;quot;The Great Reset - Evergrande and the Final Meltdown of the Global Financial System&amp;quot;; all available via the DMSA homepage &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dmsa-agentur.de/&quot;&gt;www.dmsa-agentur.de&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;But while the international financial market has so far met the financial turmoil surrounding the teetering giant Evergrande with a remarkable basic confidence - one can also say: with remarkable naivety - the U.S. central bank Fed confirmed our view yesterday,&amp;quot; says DMSA senior analyst Dr. Marco Metzler. &amp;quot;In its latest stability report, it explicitly pointed out the dangers that a collapse of Evergrande could have for the global financial system.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to be able to file for bankruptcy against the company as a creditor, DMSA itself invested in Evergrande bonds, whose grace period expired today (Nov. 10, 2021). In total, Evergrande would have had to pay $148.13 million in interest on three bonds no later than today. &amp;quot;But so far we have not received any interest on our bonds,&amp;quot; explains Metzler. He adds, &amp;quot;With banks in Hong Kong closing today, it&amp;#39;s certain that these bonds have defaulted.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Note to editors: Exact details of the bonds that have defaulted so far can be found in the appendix to this press release.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Particularly problematic for Evergrande: all 23 outstanding bonds have a cross-default clause. &amp;quot;This means that if a single one of these bonds defaults, all 23 outstanding bonds automatically have &amp;#39;default&amp;#39; status&amp;quot; DMSA senior analyst Metzler knows. However, this does not automatically result in a bankruptcy for Evergrande Group. To determine bankruptcy, a insolvency petition must be filed with the court. This can be done either by the company itself or by one or more of the company&amp;#39;s creditors. And this is precisely what is now planned. Metzler: &amp;quot;DMSA is preparing bankruptcy proceedings against Evergrande. We are already holding talks with other investors in this regard. We would be pleased if other investors were to join our action group.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the DMSA expert, it is clear: &amp;quot;As soon as a court opens insolvency proceedings, Evergrande will also be officially bankrupt - and that is only a matter of days.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full story here- &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/evergrande-officially-defaulted---dmsa-is-preparing-bankruptcy-proceedings-against-evergrande-group-301421327.html&quot;&gt;https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/evergrande-officially-defaulted---dmsa-is-preparing-bankruptcy-proceedings-against-evergrande-group-301421327.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国发生了08年的事件，我觉得我们完蛋了]]></title><description><![CDATA[让我们来谈谈严肃的事情吧，伙计们。我知道这个页面充满了一些合法的
我知道这个页面充满了一些合法的发件人，而且我们喜欢把它全部扔到黑色的地方。

但我们认为中国的情况如何？他们上个月拖欠了3050亿
月。我相信其中5亿或更多是美国债权人的。在我们的
亿元在我们的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqw2pw/china_pulled_an_08_and_i_feel_we_are_fucked/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqw2pw/china_pulled_an_08_and_i_feel_we_are_fucked/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 19:01:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s talk about something serious guys. I know this page is full of some legit senders and we like to throw it all on black. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what do we thinks going down with China? They defaulted 305 BILLION last month. And I believe 500 million or more of it was on American creditors. With a billion in our real estate here in the americas and another 3 billion around Europe? I think numbers could be a bit off but the default is a solid number that was calculated. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This reeks of 08. And of course people claim that they will be bailed out. Except someone’s going to hold the bag like JP and Lehman did in 08.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, we know China and the US aren’t the friendliest buddies. Or even Europe for that matter. What’s to stop them from pushing it to us? Who’s following this and what’s your plan or position? It’s easy to pull capital and “wait” but who knows how long that will be till the bottom drops and to what extent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在FOMO和偏离boglehead哲学后寻求建议]]></title><description><![CDATA[直到今年年初，我一直遵循boglehead哲学，以
然后我在1月发现了某支备忘录股票，并从最初的投资中赚取了许多倍的利润。
我的初始投资。我应该意识到，我很幸运，很早就进入了这个行业
但我很固执，过于自信。我开始做...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qqtjy9/seeking_advice_after_fomo_and_straying_from/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qqtjy9/seeking_advice_after_fomo_and_straying_from/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 19:01:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up until the beginning of the year, I had followed the boglehead philosophy to the T. Then I discovered a certain meme stock in Jan and made many multiples off my initial investment. I should have realized that I got lucky getting in early but I was stubborn and overconfident. I started doing research on other sectors and individual stocks, and decided to allocate 25% of my net worth in an actively managed strategy. That strategy did not work very well. I either didn’t have conviction and sold or had too much conviction to sell when there were “bad signs” that indicated trouble. As a result, my actively managed portfolio has underperformed VT by 10%. I am still up 57% for the year (thanks to the initial meme stock and some crypto). I suppose I should feel grateful that I am still positive for the year but I can’t help but feel like I have failed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point I want to sell everything and either go cash/DCA or go lump sum back into a broad market index fund. I have realized that it isn’t great for my mental health to obsess over my portfolio like this.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see posts from people who have gotten insanely rich off this bull run and it makes me feel FOMO. But I have also seen people who blow up their portfolio and end up with nothing. It makes me wonder about the distribution of gains/losses by during this bull run. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you have any advice for me? How do you deal with the FOMO?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[什么是购买新股的最佳时机？- 我在过去20年里分析了1000多宗IPO! 下面是结果!]]></title><description><![CDATA[鉴于围绕650亿美元的Rivian IPO的炒作越来越多
[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/05/rivian-raises-ipo-price-range-and-could-now-be-worth-up-to-65-billion.html]
[1]，我觉得这是一个完美的时间来跟进我的第一个分析，对...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqseif/what_is_the_best_time_to_buy_an_ipo_i_analyzed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqseif/what_is_the_best_time_to_buy_an_ipo_i_analyzed/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 19:01:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given the growing hype surrounding the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/05/rivian-raises-ipo-price-range-and-could-now-be-worth-up-to-65-billion.html&quot;&gt;$65 Billion Rivian IPO&lt;/a&gt; [1], I felt this is the perfect time to follow up on my &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ny6wpp/i_analyzed_3600_ipos_over_the_past_two_decades_to/&quot;&gt;first analysis on IPOs&lt;/a&gt;. In the previous analysis, we realized that the majority of gains were made from the listing itself and those who invested on listing day gained a measly 1.3%. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/f4e0nywl7ry71.png?width=950&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=5c9bb06a416c3cdedcd34b3e91c6f43af1e97f8b&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In most cases, &lt;a href=&quot;https://money.usnews.com/investing/investing-101/articles/how-to-buy-ipo-stock-at-its-offer-price&quot;&gt;less than 10% of the total IPO&lt;/a&gt; is allocated to retail investors. Adding to this, a multitude of other factors such as your brokerage account, account balance, the historical trading pattern will all contribute to whether you get the IPO shares or not in the end [2].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given that the chances of you making it into the IPO allotment are bleak, what I wanted to analyze is, if we miss the IPO bus,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the best time to buy into a recently IPO’d stock?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should it be on the listing day itself or should you wait a day, week, or even a month for all the hype surrounding the IPO to die down and the stock to come back to its “real” valuation [3]?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/n5wmym9n7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=a3106183b0670cb5c790d5034bf7ee76a4ca194b&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have leveraged the same data source (iposcoop.com) that I used last time. They have documented almost all the IPOs from 2000. But for this analysis, I also needed stock price-related information for periods long after the stock had been listed in the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stock price information was obtained using Yahoo Finance. After all the quality checks, we are left with 1,063 IPOs from 2000-2020. All the data used in the analysis has been shared through a Google sheet at the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/9skwwgan7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=9789e067c476b12b7b962d587c002320623c388b&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Analysis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the idea is to find the best time to invest in an IPO, we have to compare the returns for multiple time periods. I calculated the one month and one year returns in case you had invested on the day of the IPO as well as if you had invested in the stock after&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One month&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The returns are then compared against each other to find the optimal time to invest in the stock after it has IPO’d. The returns were finally benchmarked against SPY to see if it makes sense to put in all these efforts - only to maybe underperform the market!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/w2qnh2an7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=6e659778bbe8aaf8893f5d6f2ea21288ef4b7a71&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/w2qnh2an7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=6e659778bbe8aaf8893f5d6f2ea21288ef4b7a71&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/vknekrzo7ry71.png?width=730&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=7fe4c5b99687e881d342df706a16fcd0ac0f255f&quot;&gt; All calculations are done using the adjusted closing price  &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Surprisingly, the gains you would have made from the IPOs are inversely proportional to the amount of time you waited for your investment. On average &lt;strong&gt;the most amount of return is obtained by someone who invested on the day of the IPO itself&lt;/strong&gt;. The more amount of time you wait for your investment, the lesser your return is!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what if you are not interested in the short-term returns? What if you are a buy-and-hold type of investor?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/uazvvt0q7ry71.png?width=730&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=38ff88f577596544308b493f072d66240507cc7d&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a long-term investor, &lt;strong&gt;you would be better off buying the IPO after waiting for a week&lt;/strong&gt;, as it generated the most amount of return. But what is interesting is that waiting a week for the hype to die down would only increase your return by 9%. Waiting any further would only &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;decrease your overall return.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you are planning on buying into an IPO but did not get an allocation at the listing price, you can wait a week so as to see how it performs in the market, avoid any large swings that the first week might cause, and still come out on top over the long run!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, let’s compare the performance of IPO stocks against SPY. After all, even though you are getting a good return on your investment, if it does not beat the market, you would have been better off just investing it in SPY rather than doing all this research on IPOs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ehviuevq7ry71.png?width=900&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=880c9f18392da5832a239819b38cd6dc04893875&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IPOs’ returns on average &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;beat the market&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; over the last two decades. The trends are similar to the ones observed earlier with the delta over the market return depending on how much time you waited before investing into the IPO and generating the highest amount of delta by waiting one week from the day of the IPO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now it would be amiss not to discuss the inherent risks associated with investing in an IPO. Out of the 1,063 IPO’s in our analysis, only 62% of them gained in value and only a measly 29% of the IPOs beat the market over the long run. The outperformance over the market is coming due to a few outliers (Tesla - 25,000%+, Shopify - 5800%+, etc.) If you miss out on the top 1% of successful IPOs, your returns would be much lesser than the market. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/5np1iman7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=ed89afca9e90fdc3288899fcab548a8155beecdc&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Limitations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above analysis comes with some limitations that you should be aware of before trying to replicate the strategy&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The number of IPOs in the analysis is approximately 1/3rd of the total IPOs which occurred during 2000-2020 [4]. I don’t think this is a major concern since our sample of 1000+ stocks would be much more than enough to give statistical significance to our analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Another limitation is that the delta that you are observing here might just be due to the additional risk that you are taking by buying into lesser-known/small-cap companies. The risk-adjusted return might give a different result.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuing from the above point, we are currently in a massive bull run with ATH being broken every week. So the additional risk you are taking will be well rewarded but the outcome might look different if we do the same analysis in the middle of a bear market.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/qk5hm49s7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=77fe292757c841d6ecd666b499a9315e48595f25&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buying into an IPO is an exciting prospect. Our analysis proves that even if you miss out on getting the IPO allocation, it’s still possible to beat the market by investing after the stock is listed on the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ny6wpp/i_analyzed_3600_ipos_over_the_past_two_decades_to/&quot;&gt;explained in my last post on IP&lt;/a&gt;O, investment banks are incentivized to slightly underprice while listing (unless it’s a really popular company) so that the IPO issue is 100% subscribed (their fees are dependent on a successful IPO) [5].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever the case may be, if you are planning on holding on to the IPO only for a short period of time, you can maximize your returns by investing in the IPO as soon as it’s listed whereas if you are a long term investor who is planning to hold on to the stock for a very long time, its better to wait a week or so for the stock price to settle before making your move!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Analysis Sheet containing all the data: &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1QqRNZEsTfgG6f8GfI-n6qBAai9wrUA47hFMYg6tz098/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until next week…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/inx7eq9s7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=bd82af6c741804d784b964b632a1af10ae31eb0c&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Footnotes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[1] The company has &lt;a href=&quot;https://insideevs.com/news/542908/rivian-production-numbers-first-month/&quot;&gt;only built and delivered 56&lt;/a&gt; vehicles as of Oct21. If Rivian IPO’d at $65 Billion, it means that each vehicle it delivered added more than $1 Billion in value to its shareholders. A similarly valued Ford delivered 4.1 Million vehicles in 2020. Truly wild times we are living in!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[2] Brokerages tend to allocate IPO shares to their premium clients - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tdameritrade.com/investment-products/IPOs.html&quot;&gt;In the case of TD Ameritrade&lt;/a&gt;, your account must have a value of at least $250,000 or have completed 30 trades in the last 3 months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[3] Take the examples of Robinhood and Coinbase IPO. Robinhood tanked on listing day losing 8% only to rally almost 100% in the next one week before coming back down to near its IPO pricing. Coinbase also had a wild ride on listing day with the share price going as high as $429 before crashing back down to ~$310.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[4] The major limitation was the absence of financial data in Yahoo Finance for certain stocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[5] There are a lot of contradictory opinions regarding this with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0275531918309280&quot;&gt;some research&lt;/a&gt; showcasing that IPO’s are usually undervalued while &lt;a href=&quot;https://academic.oup.com/rfs/article-abstract/17/3/811/1612977?redirectedFrom=PDF&quot;&gt;others argue&lt;/a&gt; that IPOs are overvalued. I guess you can twist data however you want to tell your story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ohspvw9s7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=b152439751b7c5cba562695a713a9c1d89b2a8f6&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/ohspvw9s7ry71.png?width=1728&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=b152439751b7c5cba562695a713a9c1d89b2a8f6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: I am not a financial advisor. Please do your own research before investing.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[第三季度营收不及分析师预期，Coinbase股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[盘后下跌13%。

https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/09/coinbase-coin-earnings-q3-2021.html

美国最大的加密货币交易所Coinbase在周二收盘后公布了第三季度财报。
周二收盘后公布了第三季度财报，收入方面未达到分析师的预期。
收入。该股在延长后下挫超过13%。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqjz2e/coinbase_shares_plummet_after_thirdquarter/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqjz2e/coinbase_shares_plummet_after_thirdquarter/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 18:49:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Down 13% after hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/09/coinbase-coin-earnings-q3-2021.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/09/coinbase-coin-earnings-q3-2021.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coinbase, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in the U.S., reported third-quarter earnings after the bell on Tuesday and missed analysts’ estimates on revenue. The stock sank more than 13% in extended trading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earnings: $1.62 a share&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue: $1.31 billion vs. $1.57 billion consensus estimate, according to Refinitiv&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Monday, bitcoin hit a new all-time high of $68,000, and ethereum set a new record, topping $4,800.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[给我的投资组合评分]]></title><description><![CDATA[VT: 100%

有何感想？我认为我有太多的股票。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qr06wl/rate_my_portfolio/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qr06wl/rate_my_portfolio/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 18:49:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;VT: 100%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts? I think I have too many stocks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师在下调股票评级时称Palantir开始出现 "裂缝]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大皇家银行强调政府收入的急剧下降，并表示未来几年30%以上的整体增长目标是 "不可能的"。
未来几年的整体增长目标 "难以保证"。

Palantir Technologies的股价周三似乎有望继续下滑
在加拿大皇家银行资本市场的分析师Rishi Jaluria下调了该股的评级，并警告...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qquzog/palantir_is_starting_to_show_cracks_analyst_says/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qquzog/palantir_is_starting_to_show_cracks_analyst_says/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 18:08:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;RBC highlights a sharp deceleration in government revenue and says 30%-plus overall growth target for next few years is ‘hard to underwrite’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shares of Palantir Technologies look on track to extend their slide Wednesday after RBC Capital Markets analyst Rishi Jaluria downgraded the stock, warning of “cracks emerging in the story.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jaluria is concerned about a deceleration in Palantir’s government business as shown in the company’s Tuesday morning earnings commentary. While Jaluria had anticipated a slowdown, he noted that the growth rate for this part of the business was almost cut in half relative to the second quarter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Palantir executives called out 34% growth in government revenue during the third quarter, while this segment was up 66% in the second quarter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We believe Palantir got direct benefits from COVID-related spending and those benefits have already faded,” Jaluria wrote in his note to clients, while lowering his rating on Palantir’s stock to underperform from sector perform and cutting his price target to $19 from $25.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shares of Palantir are off more than 2% in premarket trading Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jaluria also said that while Palantir’s commercial business continues to accelerate, he believes some of the growth there is due to a program through which the company makes strategic investments in earlier-stage businesses that then use its technology. “We do not believe revenue from S**C investments is sustainable, especially given the relatively small size of the companies Palantir is investing in,” he wrote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Palantir’s management team continues to expect revenue growth of at least 30% for this year and the following four years, but Jaluria views this target as “hard to underwrite” given the deceleration in the government business and his estimation of the impact that S**C investments are having on commercial growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We still believe Palantir has good technology and strong customer government relationships, but given the valuation, would like to see additional proof points of clean, sustainable 30%+ growth before getting more constructive,” he wrote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Palantir shares have added 5.8% over the past three months as the S&amp;amp;P 500 SPX, -0.35% has gained 5.6%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;m arketwatch.com/story/palantir-is-starting-to-show-cracks-analyst-says-in-downgrade-11636552230?mod=mw_latestnews&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[凯西为什么要把Palantir买进ARKG？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我当然不知道ARKG内的全部公司，但我
我收到了所有ARK ETF的每日买入/卖出的电子邮件。在ARKG（Genomic
Revolution）今天买入了约29万股Palantir的股票。我喜欢Palantir。
但这与整个篮子有什么关系？



我投资于...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqikv2/why_is_cathie_buying_palantir_into_arkg/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqikv2/why_is_cathie_buying_palantir_into_arkg/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 18:08:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I certainly don&amp;#39;t know the entire basket of companies within ARKG, but I received the daily email of buy/sells into all the ARK ETFs.  In ARKG (Genomic Revolution) about 290,000 shares of Palantir were bought today.  I love Palantir, but how does this fit in with the overall basket?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m invested in almost all of the ARK funds.  But I don&amp;#39;t like that some companies that don&amp;#39;t belong, are traded in the funds anyway.  I noticed Netflix was one of the first companies purchased into ARKX when it debuted this year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anybody know why Palantir would be bought into the Genomic fund?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[恒大正式违约]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqvo6g/evergrande_officially_defaulted/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqvo6g/evergrande_officially_defaulted/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:50:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[珍妮特-耶伦谈通货膨胀...
二月：没什么可担心的。
三月：小而可控。
五月：只是暂时的。
6月：可能达到3%，但只是过渡性的。
10月初：未来几个月会更高。
10月下旬：增加数万亿的支出将降低价格。https://t.co/BGScAa7QEa https://t.co/3UqmnVqQUS]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458434830874595337</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458434830874595337</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:38:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[突破。有报道称，恒大在30天的宽限期内没有支付债券，使他们正式陷入违约。德国公司DMSA已经对他们提出正式的破产程序。]]></title><description><![CDATA[现在关于这个问题的新闻正在不断涌现（在推特上越来越多），看起来像是
主流消息来源还没有报道，或正在淡化。在这里你可以
找到DMSA的新闻稿，http://www.dmsa-agentur.de/pressemitteilungen

据我所知，1.48亿美元的离岸债券付款 "今天 "到期...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqy68o/breaking_reports_are_coming_in_that_evergrande/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqy68o/breaking_reports_are_coming_in_that_evergrande/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:22:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;News is trickling in on this right now (gaining steam on Twitter), looks like mainstream sources haven&amp;#39;t picked it up yet or are downplaying. Here You can find DMSA&amp;#39;s press release, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dmsa-agentur.de/pressemitteilungen&quot;&gt;http://www.dmsa-agentur.de/pressemitteilungen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From what I gather, a $148 million offshore bond payment due &amp;quot;today&amp;quot; still hasn&amp;#39;t been paid, triggering formal bankruptcy proceedings against the company.  I believe that the deadline was midnight in China timezone, and the press release was filed right around there. We cannot know for sure if a last-hour payment was made. But if this is all true , it could have some pretty strong short term shocks for the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now treat this with a grain of salt until more verification and information. Either way, buckle up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**EDIT: English Press Release ** &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/evergrande-officially-defaulted---dmsa-is-preparing-bankruptcy-proceedings-against-evergrande-group-301421327.html&quot;&gt;https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/evergrande-officially-defaulted---dmsa-is-preparing-bankruptcy-proceedings-against-evergrande-group-301421327.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[通货膨胀率飙升至1990年以来最高]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.npr.org/2021/11/10/1054019175/inflation-surges-to-its-highest-since-1990

> 美国劳工部周三报告说，10月份消费者价格比去年同期高出6.2%。
> 10月份比一年前高6.2%。这是自1990年11月以来的最大幅度增长。
> 1990.
> 
> 价格上涨是广泛的，其中...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqxz18/inflation_surges_to_its_highest_since_1990/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqxz18/inflation_surges_to_its_highest_since_1990/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:22:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npr.org/2021/11/10/1054019175/inflation-surges-to-its-highest-since-1990&quot;&gt;https://www.npr.org/2021/11/10/1054019175/inflation-surges-to-its-highest-since-1990&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Labor Department reported Wednesday that consumer prices were 6.2% higher in October than a year ago. That&amp;#39;s the sharpest increase since November of 1990.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Price increases were widespread, with energy, shelter, food and vehicles all costing more. Excluding volatile food and energy costs, prices were up 4.6%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Much of the upward pressure on prices is the result of a mismatch between booming demand and limited supply, as businesses struggle to find both parts and workers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many employers have increased pay in order to attract more workers. But growing paychecks have quickly been eroded by the rising cost of gas and groceries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;For families, they&amp;#39;re feeling it right now,&amp;quot; says Mary Daly, president of the Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco. &amp;quot;If you got to a grocery store, you buy food that you usually buy, you then fill your gas tank on the way home so you can go to work or take your kids to school, you&amp;#39;re feeling this.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;When you then look at the winter coming and you realize your fuel bill for heating your home is going to rise as the winter comes, you&amp;#39;re nervous,&amp;quot; she added.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2021/11/10/business/economy/consumer-price-inflation-october.html&quot;&gt;https://www.nytimes.com/2021/11/10/business/economy/consumer-price-inflation-october.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[国税局在WSB上滚动播放钻石手的收益色情片]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqk0i1/the_irs_scrolling_through_diamond_hand_gain_porn/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqk0i1/the_irs_scrolling_through_diamond_hand_gain_porn/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[从年初开始的通胀变化...
美国：上升5.0% (1.2% --&gt; 6.2%)
欧元区：上升4.4% (-0.3% --&gt; 4.1%)
加拿大。高出3.4% (1.0% --&gt; 4.4%)
英国：上升2.8% (0.3% --&gt; 3.1%)

中央银行利率从年初开始的变化...
美联储 0%
欧洲央行: 0%
英国央行：0
英国央行：0

曲线背后]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458435864082714629</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458435864082714629</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 16:37:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[10月通胀率创30年新高，为6.2%。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqutgr/inflation_hit_30_year_high_in_october_of_62/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqutgr/inflation_hit_30_year_high_in_october_of_62/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 16:37:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[统一公司的季度收入超过预期，并收购了Weta公司。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Unity正在收购Weta，一家领先的数字视觉效果公司。他们的工具
将成为Unity创造者套件的一部分。非常令人兴奋的事情。 

他们为《指环王》和最大的Marvel电影创造了视觉效果。
仅举几例。https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ygAsQxDtXic

第三季度收益

...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqsdzh/unity_exceeds_quarterly_earning_expectations_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqsdzh/unity_exceeds_quarterly_earning_expectations_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 16:37:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unity is acquiring Weta, a leading digital visual effects company. Their tools will be a part of the Unity creator suite. Very exciting stuff. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They created visual effects for Lord of the Rings and the biggest Marvel movies, to name a few. 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ygAsQxDtXic&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ygAsQxDtXic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q3 earnings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solid quarter. Stocks dropped in the premarket, which is reasonable, the price was at an all time high. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Q3 revenue up 43% year-over-year, exceeding expectations; company raises guidance. Still operating at a 6c loss per share. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;They continue to heavily invest into the future and creating a lock-in effect with their customer base. Lots of acquisitions and more R&amp;amp;D expenditure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bottom line:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They&amp;#39;re building a substantial ecosystem and are well positioned as a top player for some of the biggest buzzwords of the next decade, the metaverse, gaming, augmented- and virtual reality. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Current price is high considering fundamentals. But in my opinion, it&amp;#39;s still being slept on. I have a gut feeling this will become a hype stock within 2-3 years, so I&amp;#39;ll continue to buy.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;d personally be very happy with buying below $120. But I think ~$135 is probably a more reasonable entry point in the next 12 months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币在过去一年中上涨了340%。

但如果你考虑到6%的通货膨胀率，实际回报率只有334%。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458441469040250882</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458441469040250882</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:47:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[去年的商品价格上涨...
WTI原油: +109%
取暖用油。+106%
汽油: +105%
布伦特原油: +101
咖啡。+88%
天然气: +74%
棉花: +71%
铜: +39%
铝: +37%
玉米。+36%
糖: +34%
小麦: +30%
木材: +15%
大豆: +9%
白银: +3%
黄金：-1%。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458441345824067590</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458441345824067590</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:47:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国通货膨胀率6.2

30年抵押贷款利率3.1

是否有一个更好的时间成为借款人？https://t.co/JUV5Got4f4]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458434239784005634</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458434239784005634</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:47:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian IPO定价为78美元/股，市值达760亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[就在几个月前，Rivian公司交付了它的第一批车辆，主要是给它自己的员工。
自己的员工。到年底，该公司在伊利诺伊州Normal的工厂将只生产大约1200辆。
它在伊利诺伊州Normal的工厂到年底只能生产约1200辆。

从这个角度来看，NIO在最近的12个月里销售了142,036辆电动汽车。
个月。

里维安的估值很高，而且...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqtrgm/rivian_ipo_priced_at_78_a_share_giving_it_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqtrgm/rivian_ipo_priced_at_78_a_share_giving_it_a/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:47:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just a couple of months ago, Rivian delivered its first vehicles, mostly to its own employees. It will only produce about 1,200 units by year-end at its plant in Normal, Illinois. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To put it in perspective, NIO sold 142,036 electric cars on the most recent 12 months. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rivian’s valuation is huge, and its $78B market cap outpaces Chinese EV maker NIO ‘s (NIO) $63 billion market value, and it is more than those of EV start-up Lucid (LCID) and XPeng (XPEV) combined. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ford has a market cap of $78.4 billion, GM&amp;#39;s is $84.4 billion and Stellantis NV, the former Fiat Chrysler, is valued at $64 billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quoting An article from a few days ago when Rivian’s was valued at $52 billion … The $52B valuation implies that Rivian will sell 2 million vehicles in 2030, or nearly 2.5 times the number of Tesla (TSLA) vehicles produced over the past 12 months and 66% more vehicles than Honda sold in the U.S. in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These manufacturing milestones are highly improbable given Rivian’s lack of manufacturing infrastructure and experience as well as the intense competition it faces in the EV market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1. 股票：历史新高
2. 房价：历史高点
3. 比特币：历史高点
4. 工资：历史高点
5. 职位空缺：历史新高
6. 通货膨胀：30多年来的最高水平
7. 美联储/政府：我们需要将利率压低到0%，并且多借/多花几万亿。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458430231715500032</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458430231715500032</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 14:35:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球通货膨胀率... https://t.co/6mNnpyO6tp]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458435460544540677</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458435460544540677</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 14:35:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[与去年相比，价格上涨（CPI报告）...
汽油。+49.6%
燃气公用事业: +28.1%
二手汽车: +26.4%
肉类/鱼类/蛋类: +11.9%
新汽车: +9.8%
电力: +6.5%
整体CPI: +6.2%
家里的食物。+5.4%
外出食品：+5.4%。+5.3%
交通运输: +4.5%
服装: +4.3%
庇护所: +3.5%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458428272384040960</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458428272384040960</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 14:35:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[去年美国消费者价格增长6.2%，是我们30多年来看到的最高通胀率。

图表来自@ycharts https://t.co/YdBRyaZGhT]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458429773760368643</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458429773760368643</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 14:35:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[10月份消费者价格指数飙升6.2%，大大超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[消费者每天购买的广泛产品的通货膨胀甚至比预期的还要糟糕。
10月份的情况比预期的还要糟糕，达到了30多年来的最高点。
劳工部周三报告说。

消费者价格指数是由一篮子产品组成的，包括汽油、保健品和其他产品。
和医疗保健到...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqukg1/consumer_price_index_surges_62_in_october/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqukg1/consumer_price_index_surges_62_in_october/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 14:21:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inflation across a broad swath of products that consumers buy every day was even worse than expected in October, hitting its highest point in more than 30 years, the Labor Department reported Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The consumer price index, which is a basket of products ranging from gasoline and health care to groceries and rents, rose 6.2% from a year ago. That compared to the 5.9% Dow Jones estimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consumer price index surges 6.2% in October, considerably more than expected &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/consumer-price-index-october.html?__source=iosappshare%7Ccom.apple.UIKit.activity.CopyToPasteboard&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/consumer-price-index-october.html?__source=iosappshare%7Ccom.apple.UIKit.activity.CopyToPasteboard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这就是为什么拥有股票是一个很好的对冲通货膨胀的工具。

投入成本上升 --gt；公司提价 --gt；消费者抱怨，但还是要支付更高的价格 --gt；公司的利润率保持不变。

@SamRo说的好 

https://t.co/ZKrUy9AkV0 https://t.co/nQLfjibYFM]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458104251796922380</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458104251796922380</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 13:44:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[真正的华尔街之狼]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qq9vgf/the_real_wolf_of_wall_street/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qq9vgf/the_real_wolf_of_wall_street/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 13:31:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[铜的目前状况令人担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在几个月前投资了一些铜的股票，看到它最近的波动情况
最近，我觉得我应该对我在上面投资的钱感到担心。
价格忽高忽低，而且随着可审查能源的需求。
一切都会变得更加混乱。已经有问题的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqs5bp/coppers_current_situation_is_concerning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqs5bp/coppers_current_situation_is_concerning/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 12:36:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I invested in some copper stocks a few months back, and seeing how volatile it is recently, I feel like I should be worried with the money I invested on it. The prices are going up and down and with the demand for reviewable energy, everything’s going to be messier. There have been issues with the supply recently as well, especially with bigger producers due to issues with miners or because of the restrictions brought about by the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now I have some I also have some &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fortitudegold.com/&quot;&gt;Fortitude Gold&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/FTCO/&quot;&gt;FTCO&lt;/a&gt;). They are a pretty small producer but has no debts and recently increased the monthly dividend they are paying 16.7% to $0.035 per common share, or $0.42 annually. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also have &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.solarisresources.com/&quot;&gt;Solaris Resources&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/SLSSF/&quot;&gt;SLSSF&lt;/a&gt;) which I got despite it being risky since it is an exploration. They have positive results with their drilling, and they recently started their maiden drilling at the Warintza South target, targeting the 4th major copper discovery. They also have a massive cash cushion and their cash burn is way under, plus they have about $60 million on the balance sheet right now. I also placed some on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.comstockmining.com/&quot;&gt;Comstock Mining Inc&lt;/a&gt;.(&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/LODE/&quot;&gt;LODE&lt;/a&gt;), and their primary focus of the company’s exploration efforts are their projects in the Dayton Resource/Spring Valley as well as the Lucerne resource area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not planning to invest on any anytime soon, since I feel a little anxious with all the investments I made seeing how volatile the situation is right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[嗯，这是官方的：这都是我们的错。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqkbbc/well_its_official_this_is_all_our_fault/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqkbbc/well_its_official_this_is_all_our_fault/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 12:36:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你建议一个年轻的投资人要有多大的多元化。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我24岁，我已经建立了一个价值约13万的投资组合。

我在大约20只不同的股票和ETF中拥有股份。我最大的赢家是
Nvidia和亚马逊。

我大概有60%的科技股，30%的ETF，10%的其他。

考虑到我的日常工作都是关于技术的，我最了解的公司是
科技。我首先...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qql530/how_diversified_would_you_suggest_a_young/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qql530/how_diversified_would_you_suggest_a_young/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 11:44:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m 24 YO and I&amp;#39;ve built up a portfolio worth about 130k. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have share in about 20 different stocks and ETFs. My biggest winners being Nvidia and Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m like 60% tech stocks 30% ETFs 10% other. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Considering my day job is all about technology the companies I know best are tech. I first purchased 5 shares of Nvidia in 2016 because they simply made superior graphic cards. Then crypto and Tesla autonomy and ARM really put the boosters on! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like the idea of being diversified but I feel like I&amp;#39;d be better off trying to pick 5 winners and just take the hits on the bad days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有些人只是被诅咒了]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqb82o/some_are_just_cursed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqb82o/some_are_just_cursed/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 11:19:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[COINBASE（COIN股票）21年第三季度的想法。COIN在盘后交易中下跌13%。]]></title><description><![CDATA[刚刚听完15分钟的电话会议，并仔细阅读了他们第三季度的
投资者信。

我认为Coinbase的风险在于对费用的依赖，因为行业会找到越来越多的
越来越多的方法来提供更便宜的交易，或免收佣金。

这里有一个好消息。

在2020年第三季度，有低...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqlmbs/coinbase_coin_stock_q3_21_thoughts_coin_down_13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqlmbs/coinbase_coin_stock_q3_21_thoughts_coin_down_13/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 10:56:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just got done listening to 15m of the conference call, and poured over their Q3 investor letter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the risk to Coinbase is reliance on fees, as the industry will find more and more ways to offer trading more cheaply, or commission free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s the good news. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During Q3 2020, there was low Crypto volitily. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That means commissions income was down 44%. Q-on-Q.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Q3 21, Y-on-Y, commissions income is up 290% from Q3 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although subscriptions/fees are only, currently, like 10%, of Coinbases revenue stream -- they&amp;#39;ve grown that revenue stream by 41% from last quarter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take away:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The price of COIN is highly correlated to the price of crypto assets rising and failing..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;.. it&amp;#39;s recent rise in price has been due to the the current rise in vaule in crypto assets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This gap will fill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be it one month or one quarter, or 2 years, barring a market crash, I think it will fill. This sell off is dumb, short sided, and backwards, not forward looking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s a dip worth holding and buying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;COIN success included recently adding more coins to compete with competitors, 24/7 phone support coming next quarter, Coin Prime &amp;amp; Coin Cloud, services recently added, to my understanding, to sell crypto to institutions (think NBA and FB deal,) and also to allow websites to accept direct payment IN crypto (Coin Cloud.) That move will continue to help Crypto become more and more mainstream, which stands to benefit Coin more than the average competitor due to their Mainstream UI/branding and first mover market share domance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I own some COIN stock.
This is my opinion.
It&amp;#39;s not investment advice. Don&amp;#39;t buy or sell things because of what people on the internet say.
I hope to provoke conversation. To have my assumptions challenged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉的市值仍然是大众集团的7倍，而大众集团的利润是5倍，销售的汽车是11倍，而且可比的电动车销售增长更快。]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至昨晚，大众汽车市值为1430亿美元，特斯拉为1.01万亿美元。

到2021年第三季度，大众汽车的利润为168亿美元，而特斯拉为32亿美元。

到2021年第三季度，大众汽车售出695.1万辆汽车，而特斯拉售出62.7万辆。

到2021年第三季度，大众汽车电动车销量为539K（到2020年期间+135%），而特斯拉为627K
(+97%).

I...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqolej/teslas_mkt_cap_is_still_7_x_vw_group_which_makes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqolej/teslas_mkt_cap_is_still_7_x_vw_group_which_makes/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 10:26:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;VW mkt cap was $143 billion as of last night vs Tesla at $1.01 trillion.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To 3Q 2021 YTD VW profits were $16.8 billion vs Tesla $3.2 billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To 3Q 2021 YTD VW sold 6.951 million cars vs Tesla 0.627 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To 3Q 2021 YTD VW EV sales were 539K (+135% to 2020 period) vs Tesla&amp;#39;s 627K (+97%).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I won&amp;#39;t torment Tesla shareholders with obvious comments - the stats speak for themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我从WSB退了出来，因为我跟着一些弱智的$WISH玩，并且全押了。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qql3bq/i_unsubbed_from_wsb_cus_i_followed_some_retards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qql3bq/i_unsubbed_from_wsb_cus_i_followed_some_retards/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 09:09:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WSB的真相]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqibxh/the_wsb_truth/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqibxh/the_wsb_truth/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 08:38:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天的特斯拉熊市（SOUND ON）。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qq9dut/tesla_bears_today_sound_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qq9dut/tesla_bears_today_sound_on/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 06:50:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克的兄弟在投票前卖出1.09亿美元的特斯拉股票]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqcb5n/elon_musks_brother_sold_109_million_in_tesla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqcb5n/elon_musks_brother_sold_109_million_in_tesla/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 05:57:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[什么假设或未来事件发生时，你准备用具体的交易来兑现？]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资电子商务（如AMZN和W）是一个伟大的举动，在大流行的开始。
大流行的时候是很好的举措。投资家庭装修店（如HD和LOW）在飓风期间可以很好地
在飓风期间是很好的。从比特币到英国脱欧，再到气候变化和covid，都有周期性的转变和发生。
有周期性的转变和发生，提供独特的机会......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqduo7/what_hypothetical_or_future_event_are_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qqduo7/what_hypothetical_or_future_event_are_you/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 05:57:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investing in ecommerce (like AMZN &amp;amp; W) was a great move at the start of the pandemic. Investing in home improvement stores (like HD &amp;amp; LOW) can be great during hurricanes. From bitcoin to Brexit, to climate change and covid, there are periodical shifts &amp;amp; occurrences that offer unique opportunities for significant returns due to some a paradigm shift or supply/demand change. &amp;quot;The future belongs to those who prepare for it today,&amp;quot; so, what change are you planning on capitalizing on in the future?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;#39;re waiting on &lt;em&gt;when&lt;/em&gt; some thing will happen or &lt;em&gt;if&lt;/em&gt; some thing will happen, what is a trade that you are prepared or plan to make come some big hypothetical future event or shift?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[r/Stocks Daily Discussion & Technicals Tuesday - Nov 09, 2021]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是每日讨论，所以任何与股票有关的都可以，但今天的主题是技术分析（TA）。
但今天的主题是技术分析（TA），但如果TA不是你的事，那么就请
忽略这个主题和/或发表你反对TA的论点......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qq0uvi/rstocks_daily_discussion_technicals_tuesday_nov/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qq0uvi/rstocks_daily_discussion_technicals_tuesday_nov/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 05:44:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the daily discussion, so anything stocks related is fine, but the theme for today is on technical analysis (TA), but if TA is not your thing then just ignore the theme and/or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+%22r%2Fstocks+semiannual+arguments+against+TA%22&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;post your arguments against TA here&lt;/a&gt; and not in the current post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some helpful day to day links, including news:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finviz.com/quote.ashx?t=spy&quot;&gt;Finviz&lt;/a&gt; for charts, fundamentals, and aggregated news on individual stocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/markets&quot;&gt;Bloomberg market news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;StreetInsider news:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Market+Check&quot;&gt;Market Check&lt;/a&gt; - Possibly why the market is doing what it&amp;#39;s doing including sudden spikes/dips&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Reuters&quot;&gt;Reuters aggregated&lt;/a&gt; - Global news&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical analysis (TA)&lt;/strong&gt; uses historical price movements, real time data, indicators based on math and/or statistics, and charts; all of which help measure the trajectory of a security.  TA can also be used to interpret the actions of other market participants and predict their actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main benefit to TA is that everything shows up in the price (commonly known as &lt;strong&gt;&amp;quot;priced in&amp;quot;&lt;/strong&gt;):  All news, investor sentiment, and changes to fundamentals are reflected in a security&amp;#39;s price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TA can be useful on any timeframe, both short and long term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intro to technical analysis by &lt;a href=&quot;https://stockcharts.com/school/doku.php?id=chart_school:technical_indicators:introduction_to_technical_indicators_and_oscillators#benefits_and_drawbacks_of_leading_indicators&quot;&gt;Stockcharts chartschool&lt;/a&gt; and their &lt;a href=&quot;https://stockcharts.com/school/doku.php?id=chart_school:chart_analysis:introduction_to_candlesticks&quot;&gt;article on candlesticks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have questions, please see the following word cloud and click through for the wiki:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/wiki/ta-themed-post&quot;&gt;Indicator - Trade Signals - Lagging Indicator - Leading Indicator - Oversold - Overbought - Divergence - Whipsaw - Resistance - Support - Breakout/Breakdown - Alerts - Trend line - Market Participants - Moving average - RSI - VWAP - MACD - ATR - Bollinger Bands - Ichimoku clouds - Methods - Trend Following - Fading - Channels - Patterns - Pivots&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See our past &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+%22r%2Fstocks+daily+discussion%22&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;daily discussions here.&lt;/a&gt;  Also links for:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Atechnicals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Technicals&lt;/a&gt; Tuesday, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Aoptions&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Options Trading&lt;/a&gt; Thursday, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Afundamentals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Fundamentals&lt;/a&gt; Friday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[伟大的一年（6千到23万--而且还没有结束）。感谢GME的开始，感谢BiG Fucking Value最近的激增...... 我会回来的，GME，别担心。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqiv8d/helluva_year_6k_to_23m_and_its_not_over_yet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqiv8d/helluva_year_6k_to_23m_and_its_not_over_yet/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 04:58:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[拥有特斯拉股票？像埃隆-马斯克一样，卖掉]]></title><description><![CDATA[来自《华尔街日报》。"通常情况下，当高管们宣布他们要在股票价格大幅上涨之后
通常，当高管们在股票价格大幅上涨后宣布出售股票时，对所有人来说都是显而易见的。
他们认为股价太高了。马斯克先生似乎已经想出了一个
狡猾的计划，试图绕过这个问题。而不是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqisap/own_tesla_stock_be_like_elon_musk_and_sell/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqisap/own_tesla_stock_be_like_elon_musk_and_sell/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 04:12:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;From Wall Street Journal: 
“Usu­ally when ex­ec­u­tives an­nounce they are sell­ing stock af­ter a sharp run-up in the price, it is ob­vi­ous to every­one that they think the share price is too high. Mr. Musk seems to have dreamed up a cun­ning plan to try to get round this prob­lem. In­stead of an­nounc­ing he was sell­ing stock, he noted the plan by Sen. Ron Wyden to tax un­re­al­ized cap­i­tal gains, and held a Twit­ter poll on whether he should sell 10% of his Tesla hold­ing. When the Twit­terati duly voted for him to dump shares in the elec­tric-car maker, that con­fused the ques­tion of whether this is an in­sider sig­nal about the share price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Per­haps Mr. Musk thinks that it’s in­sane that Tesla added $440 bil­lion to its value in the past month alone, a rise—just the rise, not the to­tal—equiv­a­lent to the com­bined mar­ket cap­i­tal­iza­tion of Ford, Gen­eral Mo­tors and Toy­ota.
…
Tesla sits at the in­ter­sec­tion of three strong trends, and a change in any one of them could lead to a rapid fall back in the stock. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first are meme stocks. Tesla is the orig­i­nal meme stock, sup­ported by in­di­vid­u­als who’ve done very well by fol­low­ing Mr. Musk, and who don’t take kindly to any­one who dis­agrees. No mat­ter the re­al­ity of sales, com­pe­ti­tion, mar­gins, sub­si­dies or any­thing else, Mr. Musk has at­tracted sup­port­ers who not only buy, but ac­tively pro­mote Tesla shares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sec­ond is the will­ing­ness of in­vestors to bet on the far dis­tant fu­ture. Tesla doesn’t make very much money, or in­deed very many cars, at the mo­ment. It is val­ued at $1.3 mil­lion for each of the 900,000 or so cars it is fore­cast to de­liver this year be­cause of the po­ten­tial for growth. The value of the com­pany doesn’t lie in this year or next year’s sales, but on hopes for sales and prof­its far in the fu­ture…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The third sup­port­ive trend is the de­sire for green tech­nol­ogy. It’s great to be an elec­tric-car maker at the mo­ment. Gov­ern­ments are push­ing elec­tric cars and the rest of the in­dus­try is stuck with the wrong sort of fac­to­ries, has the wrong sort of re­search ex­per­tise and hasn’t yet built ve­hi­cle-charg­ing net­works. Tesla is on the right side of gov­ern­ments and in­vestors pledg­ing ac­tion to re­duce car­bon emis­sions. Yet, if the share price change was about Tesla beat­ing the gaso­line-fu­eled com­pe­ti­tion, the shares of tra­di­tional ri­vals should be suf­fer­ing. In­stead, the value of the other car mak­ers has been ris­ing too. It would be great if the stock were do­ing well be­cause in­vestors ra­tio­nally worked out that elec­tric cars will take mar­ket share. In­stead, there has been an un­think­ing rush to buy stock in elec­tric-ve­hi­cle mak­ers, with many of the spec­u­la­tive pure-elec­tric-ve­hi­cle stocks that fell hard from a peak early this year leap­ing again in the past month (and Ford, with a new elec­tric F-150 on the way, soar­ing).”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source (James Mackintosh): &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/own-tesla-stock-be-like-elon-musk-and-sell-11636462480?st=n4vpidtxcyp9454&amp;amp;reflink=article_copyURL_share&quot;&gt;https://www.wsj.com/articles/own-tesla-stock-be-like-elon-musk-and-sell-11636462480?st=n4vpidtxcyp9454&amp;amp;reflink=article_copyURL_share&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PLTR收益]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qq2o88/pltr_earnings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qq2o88/pltr_earnings/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 04:12:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[好吧，让你的爸爸看看]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqhdsv/ok_show_yourself_dad/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqhdsv/ok_show_yourself_dad/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 03:51:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian公司IPO价格为78美元，公司估值为700亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.barrons.com/articles/rivian-ipo-stock-price-valuation-51636504468

Rivian汽车公司将其备受期待的首次公开发行定价为每股78美元。
一位熟悉情况的人士说。

78美元的价格高于Rivian上周设定的价格范围。这家全电动卡车制造商
制造商曾...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqi0ok/rivian_prices_ipo_at_78_valuing_the_company_at_70/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqi0ok/rivian_prices_ipo_at_78_valuing_the_company_at_70/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 03:38:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/rivian-ipo-stock-price-valuation-51636504468&quot;&gt;https://www.barrons.com/articles/rivian-ipo-stock-price-valuation-51636504468&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rivian Automotive priced its much anticipated initial public offering at $78 a share, a person familiar with the situation said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The $78 is above the price range Rivian set last week. The all-electric truck maker had filed to offer 135 million shares at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/amazon-backed-rivian-to-go-public-next-week-51635855897?mod=article_inline&quot;&gt;$57 to $62&lt;/a&gt;. It boosted the price range to $72 to $74 a share on Nov. 5, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1874178/000119312521321716/d157488ds1a.htm#toc157488_15&quot;&gt;according to a prospectus.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rivian will trade Wednesday on the Nasdaq under the ticker RIVN.  Morgan Stanley, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/market-data/stocks/gs&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs &lt;/a&gt;, and J.P. Morgan are the lead underwriters on the deal. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rivian is valued at nearly $70 billion based on the 873.1 million shares outstanding if the underwriters exercise the so-called greenshoe. (The greenshoe allows underwriters on a deal to buy shares in the IPO at the offer price.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rivian’s near $70 billion valuation would surpass the market capitalization of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/market-data/stocks/hmc?mod=article_inline&quot;&gt;Honda Motor &lt;/a&gt;(ticker: HMC), which ended Tuesday with a $51 billion market cap, bringing Rivian closer to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/market-data/stocks/f?mod=article_inline&quot;&gt;Ford Motor &lt;/a&gt;(F), an investor in Rivian, whose valuation was $80 billion. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/market-data/stocks/gm&quot;&gt;General Motors &lt;/a&gt;(GM) had an $85.1 billion market cap Tuesday. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2009, Rivian makes all-electric pickup trucks and SUVs. It employed 9,195 people as of Oct. 30. The Irvine, Calif., company is considered one of the more serious rivals to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/market-data/stocks/tsla&quot;&gt;Tesla &lt;/a&gt;(TSLA), the leading EV manufacturer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[喂，熊？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqg72g/sup_bears/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqg72g/sup_bears/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 03:38:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMD已经准备好接管另一个宇宙了]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/08/amd-shares-jump-after-company-wins-meta-partnership.html

虚拟现实、增强现实和元空间。我敢说这些仅仅是
通往一个全新的另类宇宙的起点。

AMD与微软和索尼在游戏机方面有合作关系...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qpvzy6/amd_is_well_poised_to_take_over_the_alternate/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qpvzy6/amd_is_well_poised_to_take_over_the_alternate/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 03:21:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/08/amd-shares-jump-after-company-wins-meta-partnership.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/08/amd-shares-jump-after-company-wins-meta-partnership.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Virtual reality, augmented reality and metaverse. I daresay these are just the starting points to the entrance to a whole new alternate universe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AMD has partnerships with Microsoft and Sony for gaming console chips and now has signed up Meta (Facebook) as a new customer. We all know what Facebook was planning when it changed name to Meta and AMD is going to benefit tremendously from this partnership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s gradually taking away market share from Intel and soon we will reach a point where Intel might not even be a competitor to AMD. While the need for CPUs is here to stay, most future tech would be based on GPUs, a sector where AMD has a strong footing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a long position in AMD, bought at 115. Would buy more before it hits 200.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: adding a section to explain why GPUs would support future AI and VR tech more than CPUs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GPUs are better at performing mathematical and geometric calculations than CPUs. That&amp;#39;s why they are crucial for AI/ML and VR.
This is also why GPUs are used intensively for crypto mining. 
CPUs are crucial for putting everything together and perform code and logic processing. That&amp;#39;s why GPUs won&amp;#39;t replace CPUs but as we move towards more complex requirements for altverse, we would need powerful CPUs but we would need much more advanced GPUs. For instance take high end pc games. High end games can run on a mid-end I5 CPU but need a high end GPU.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://towardsdatascience.com/what-is-a-gpu-and-do-you-need-one-in-deep-learning-718b9597aa0d&quot;&gt;https://towardsdatascience.com/what-is-a-gpu-and-do-you-need-one-in-deep-learning-718b9597aa0d&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[难道只有我一个人感到无聊吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我每周自动投资150美元100%到VTI，自动滴注，我甚至不知道我投资了多少
我甚至不知道我投资了多少，因为我不再检查它了。我知道这个策略是这样的
但我是唯一对它感到厌烦的人吗？它已经变得像
就像呼吸空气一样，很无聊，但又很需要。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qqik5u/am_i_the_only_one_who_is_bored/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qqik5u/am_i_the_only_one_who_is_bored/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 02:40:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I auto invest $150 100% into VTI weekly, auto drip, I don’t even know how much I have invested because I stoped checking on it. I know this so how the strategy is suppose to go, but am I the only who is bored of it? It has become like breathing air, so boring but needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[F]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqamoz/f/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqamoz/f/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 02:07:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是今天的市场回顾，星期二，2021年11月9日]]></title><description><![CDATA[心理市场回顾 - 2021年11月9日，星期二

股市喘了口气，暂停了这一破纪录的涨势。
所有三个主要指数都在当天收低。在最近几周，市场
市场参与者在好于预期的乐观情绪的影响下，掀起了一波长期的
盈利季节，...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqdy4r/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_tuesday_nov_9/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqdy4r/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_tuesday_nov_9/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 01:12:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Tuesday, November 9, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stock market took a breather, putting a pause on this record-breaking rally, with all three major indexes closing the day lower. In recent weeks, market participants have rode an extended wave of optimism amid better than expected earnings season, new, better than expected economic data, the passage of the $1.2 trillion infrastructure bill in Congress, and a new antiviral coronavirus pill from Pfizer (PFE). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With roughly 89% of companies in the S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) having already reported earnings, 81% of those have so far posted better than expected earnings per share and 75% of those reported better than expected revenue. FactSet projects that the year-on-year earnings growth rate for the index stands at 40%, though this number has continued creeping higher as earnings season unfolds. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_110521.pdf&quot;&gt;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_110521.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marci McGregor, Bank of America Merryl Lynch Senior Investment Strategist said, “I still think it’s all about corporate profits.  I know a lot of my peers are concerned that peak earnings growth is behind us. But I think peak earnings isn’t even a 2022 story. We’re seeing solid consumer demand, a strong U.S. economy, and I think we’re going to have a capex cycle in 2022. And I think that’s all positive for corporate profits, and that underpins this market, in my view.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, despite positive earnings, a host of companies have cited constraints around raw materials, labor shortages, and general supply-chain disruptions affecting the bottom line. According to Bank of America, mentions of supply chains on quarterly earnings calls have surged by 360% compared to last year, underscoring the widespread nature of these pressures. These supply-related issues have also contributed to still-elevated inflationary trends. Tuesday&amp;#39;s Producer Price Index from the Bureau of Labor Statistics showed that producer prices rose by 8.6% over last year, matching October&amp;#39;s rate for the fastest on record in data going back to Nov. 2010. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kristina Hooper, Chief Global Market Strategist at Invesco, said “I would expect inflation to peak by mid-year 2022. It should remain elevated but it should move lower in the back half of 2022. So while this is certainly an issue, it is part of what we should expect coming out of the pandemic. We have gotten out of a burning building, but we should expect that there is a little smoke and water damage as a result. That’s really what we’re experiencing with elevated inflation and supply chain disruptions”. I agree with this position and think the analogy is very apt. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tesla (TSLA) stock fell more than 10%, pushing down the entire EV sector with it, as the stock price feels the effect of Elon Musk’s poll where he said he would be selling 10% of his stake in Tesla. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;President Biden interviewed Federal Reserve Governor Lael Brainard for the job of Chairperson, signaling a serious rival to Jerome Powell Powell as Biden is set to nominate a new leader to the Fed in the coming weeks. I really hope Powell is re-assigned, the market does not need a shakeup right now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Peloton (PTON) continued its sharp drop following earnings, dispute the company revealing a new product designed to track your performance on the bike and give you feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roblox (RBLX) stock gapped up hard today while PayPal (PYPL) fell after reporting earnings yesterday afternoon. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Twitter (TWTR) launched a new subscription service, called Twitter Blue for $3 a month that allows one to undo or correct tweets, among other mostly aesthetic upgrades.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NVIDIA (NVDA), my favorite stock, said it was partnering with a range of self-driving sensor companies, including lidar firm Luminar Technologies (LAZR), to put together a system for autonomous driving as soon as 2024.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Moreover, NVIDIA also announced it was releasing a set of tools, called “Omniverse Enterprise”. Their Omniverse, which was beta launched in December, is a simulation and collaboration platform which “serves as the connective tissue for physically accurate 3D virtual worlds,” according to the company. In prepared remarks, Nvidia Chief Executive Jensen Huang said in his keynote address that with Omniverse, “we now have the technology to create new 3D worlds or model our physical world.” Omniverse Enterprise, which costs $9,000 a year, is also available to customers in a 30-day trial. Just another example of how NVIDIA is going key to powering technology of the future.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Netflix (NFLX) is launching a new TikTok-like short clip feature for kids called “Kids Clips” as soon as this week. Netflix said it would add new shirts based on its current and future offerings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current stock price was written premarket and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) with two target raises. Stock currently around $149

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Susquehanna from $145 to $175 at Positive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wedbush from $140 to $165 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apollo Global Management (APO) target raised by Argus from $76 to $90 at Buy. Stock currently around $76&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Five9 (FIVN) with two target raises. Stock currently around $167

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;KeyCorp from $200 to $208 Overweight&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wells Fargo from $200 to $210 at Overweight&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Humana (HUM) target raised by Citigroup from $510 to $528 at Buy. Stock currently around $450&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take-Two Interactive (TTWO) target raised by Deutsche Bank from $218 to $225 at Buy. Stock currently around $185&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zscaler (ZS) target raised by BTIG Research from $324 to $401 at Buy. Stock currently around $353&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Always remember that you are absolutely unique. Just like everyone else.” - Margaret Mead&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>