<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 00:52:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[美国第五次大的covid-19浪潮已经开始... https://t.co/0buCAhNvGW]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461811842188296200</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461811842188296200</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 23:44:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你不能理性地相信，美国股票的预期回报率比国际股票高，同时它的风险比国际股票低。ESG/清洁能源也是如此。你必须选择一个。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这只是一个关于市场如何运作以及相对安全如何降低预期收益的简单事实。
预期收益。令人震惊的是，我发现几乎所有超额持有美国股票的人
都会自觉地看着你的眼睛说，很明显，美国股票的风险较低。
股票的风险较低，正是因为风险较低，所以美国...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxpe52/you_cannot_rationally_believe_that_usa_stock_has/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxpe52/you_cannot_rationally_believe_that_usa_stock_has/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 23:30:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just a simple fact about how markets work and how relative safety lowers expected returns. Shockingly, I find almost everyone who overweights USA stock will consciously look you in the eyes and say that it is quite obvious that USA stock is less risky, and it is because of that lower risk that USA stock will bring a higher return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People often make the mirror claim as well: They point out that investing in Chinese or EM companies is far riskier than investing in the USA, and therefore if you want long term high returns you&amp;#39;d be a fool to overweight China/EM!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And another related claim: Some say that ESG/clean energy companies are obviously the safe future bet, and at the same time they say that ESG/clean energy companies will obviously outperform the rest of the market going forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In all of these cases, -you can only pick one.- Given that in none of these instances is the person claiming to be a subject matter expert who is knowledgeable beyond the total knowledge of the market. They will in all cases give basic, known information such as: &amp;quot;America has long been the center of corporate innovation, and maintains a business friendly environment regardless of political party, whereas China is becoming increasingly controlling of their market.&amp;quot; Or ESG folks will say, &amp;quot;Fossil fuel consumption is down across the board, and solar energy is now cost competitive or cost superior in most areas of the globe.&amp;quot; This is day-one minute-one basic information for any institutional investor or fund manager. Since they all know that the risk of Chinese stock is higher than the risk of American stock, then they will demand a lower price and therefore a higher expected return to take on that risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, if you are tempted to believe USA stock is safer and less risky due to it&amp;#39;s superior environment, or sector positioning, or technological foundation, or whatever, then the next words out of your mouth should be, &amp;quot;and that&amp;#39;s why USA stock is expensive and I expect it to underperform.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特公司放弃了以Rivian为动力的电动车计划。]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.theverge.com/2021/11/19/22791984/ford-rivian-ev-canceled-investment-ipo-jim-farley

任何持有这支股票的人都是抱着一颗定时炸弹。福特的锁定期
6个月后结束，他们不是对冲基金。他们不打算把一个
直接...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxq0e5/ford_drops_plan_for_rivianpowered_ev/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxq0e5/ford_drops_plan_for_rivianpowered_ev/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 23:09:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2021/11/19/22791984/ford-rivian-ev-canceled-investment-ipo-jim-farley&quot;&gt;https://www.theverge.com/2021/11/19/22791984/ford-rivian-ev-canceled-investment-ipo-jim-farley&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone holding this stock is holding onto a ticking time bomb. Ford&amp;#39;s lockup ends in 6 months and they aren&amp;#39;t a hedgefund. They aren&amp;#39;t going to baghold a direct competitor. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/jimcramer/status/1461797200460070912&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/jimcramer/status/1461797200460070912&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球通货膨胀率... https://t.co/qOlu4vYcSB]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461804771866730501</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461804771866730501</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 21:43:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[低于高点%...
$PYPL: -37%
$TWTR: -38%
$SNAP: -38%
$DKNG: -50%
$PINS: -50%
$ROKU: -51%
$PAGS: -51%
$BIDU: -55%
$ZM: -56%
$BABA: -56%
$TDOC: -60%
$CRSP: -61
$PENN: -61%
$BYND: -67%
$PTON: -71
$Z: -71%
$LMND: -71
$SFIX: -73
$CHGG: -76
$AI: -77%
$STNE: -79
---
纳斯达克100指数：0]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461769545849487365</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461769545849487365</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 20:40:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克："我是世界上最富有的巨魔"

肯-格里芬："持有我的宪法"]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461791683327283203</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461791683327283203</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 20:40:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你认为有哪些替代Boglehead投资的方法令人信服？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我遇到了Hedgefundie的优秀冒险（55% 3x SPY + 45% 3x 20年国债
几年前，我遇到了Hedgefundie的出色冒险（55%的SPY + 45%的3x 20年国债），并在最近将我的投资组合的一小部分分配到
的一小部分。它并不完全符合Boglehead的口号，但我认为它有潜力
胜过正常的指数投资。这将是一个很好的例子。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxjj5a/what_alternatives_to_boglehead_investing_do_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxjj5a/what_alternatives_to_boglehead_investing_do_you/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 19:46:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I came across Hedgefundie&amp;#39;s excellent adventure (55% 3x SPY + 45% 3x 20 Year Treasury) a few years ago and recently allocatrd a small portion of my portfolio to it. It doesn&amp;#39;t exactly fit the Boglehead mantra but I think it has potential to outperform normal index investing. It will be an interesting experiment. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are there any other strategies around that you think have have the potential to complement a Boglehead portfolio? I can&amp;#39;t think of anything else aside from maybe crypto.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[基于社区的加密货币中的价值创造与贪婪]]></title><description><![CDATA[在几乎所有与钱有关的游戏中，我都是带着这样的假设进入游戏的
它已经被操纵了。即使你看不出来，总是有一个房子，而这个房子......我们知道这个房子是做什么的，它不会输。
房子......我们知道房子会做什么，它不会输。

我觉得这就是市场上的大玩家们的情况。即使是最潮的人
或...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qxml71/value_creation_vs_greed_in_community_based_crypto/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qxml71/value_creation_vs_greed_in_community_based_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 19:33:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;In pretty much any game where money&amp;#39;s a concern, I enter it with the assumption it&amp;#39;s already rigged. Even if you can&amp;#39;t see it, there&amp;#39;s always a house, and the house...we know what the house does, and it ain&amp;#39;t losing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel that&amp;#39;s where the market&amp;#39;s at with the big players. Even the most boomer or normie-tier investors have, at the very least, HEARD of these. It&amp;#39;s been made extremely available, too. It&amp;#39;s almost easier to buy it than not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;#39;s what people are doing. They&amp;#39;re hearing the buzz and forking over the dough. But why? Is it the low price? Is it the success stories? Is it the easy access? Is it the presence in the cultural zeitgeist?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Probably all of these, really. But in all of these things, one critical element is missing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honest, real discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just try to have any real discussion about these types of coins with anyone who holds, or is purported to hold, a big-ass bag. Or a small bag. Whatever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You start talking about market cap, inflation, burn - honestly, any real concern that any reasonable buyer or holder may have, and watch how far you get. Watch how quickly your reasonable questions or concerns get swallowed up by the fervor of the irritated hivemind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ever wonder what it feels like to be one of those huge hornets that gets vibrated to death by a bunch of bees? Just do the above. Closest human approximation there is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s no actual reason for the few of these tokens to have succeeded beyond pure novelty and greed, but that won&amp;#39;t be enough for long. They&amp;#39;re simply vehicles by which the illusion of potential riches are delivered to the hungry, wanting masses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Truly disheartening to see how many people there are who are so eager to march to the beat of any drum, even if that march is gonna take them right off a cliff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve spent some time lurking many, many crypt-communities. All are largely what I&amp;#39;ve described above: willing masses easily duped into closing their minds and opening their wallets, and their attitude reflects it. There&amp;#39;s no real sense of community or belonging. It&amp;#39;s simply &amp;quot;I put my money here, and now I must defend my money.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That shit don&amp;#39;t work. Money&amp;#39;s no sufficient coagulating agent for the commingled blood of men. Pursuit of money and wealth alone are, by nature, selfish and isolating. Any community built around those as a central principle are doomed either to fail honestly or - worse - succeed dishonestly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now, no one really gives a shit about these tokens. Nobody in those communities, or any others like them, gives a shit about each other on an individual level either. You&amp;#39;re a drone. You&amp;#39;re a Wallet. You&amp;#39;re not Steve or Jane or William or Kate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To them, you&amp;#39;re a Nobody. You&amp;#39;re only as good as your ability to buy or sell, because there is no other element to their culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All that said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you think they will all always be like this, I think you&amp;#39;ve got the wrong of it. The next generation will be those that have a culture and community in in which the making of money is NOT the central element.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s mostly about content&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Truly. If a true community can be created, one where creating content on its behalf is the fun of it, it can be an extremely powerful flywheel. When the basis of the coin is community and fun, a self-reinforcing and bootstrapping process can occur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The money comes because of content, the creativity, and the enjoyment everyone gets from it. This is what attracts and retains new holders. It isn&amp;#39;t the other way around. If participating in the community is a fun thing to do, generating money just happens to be a convenient side effect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么支付宝每天都在低价交易？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的支付宝成本基础约为235美元，支付宝和Venmo被许多人广泛使用。
许多人使用。但该股每天都在不断走低，现在它正在
从2020年11月开始创下52周新低。有没有人知道这是一个宏观趋势
问题还是来自于支付宝本身的原因。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxjgcu/why_is_paypal_keep_trading_lower_everyday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxjgcu/why_is_paypal_keep_trading_lower_everyday/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 19:33:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My Paypal cost basis is around $235, paypal and venmo are very widely used by many people. But the stock just keep trading lower everyday and now it is hitting 52 week low from November 2020. Does anyone know is this a macro-trend issue or reasons from paypal itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tilray +4000% (Citadel & Legalisation)]]></title><description><![CDATA[正在发生的事情

昨天，德国宣布了一项政府范围内的协议，使大麻合法化。
仅此一项，预计将有50-100亿的市场。全球大麻是一个1000-1000亿美元的
市场。
合法化正在美国、南美、欧洲，甚至亚洲的一些地方发生，"就在我们说话的时候
亚洲的一些地区。

Tilray...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxcn0g/tilray_4000_citadel_legalisation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxcn0g/tilray_4000_citadel_legalisation/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 19:03:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ITS HAPPENING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday Germany announced a government wide agreement to legalize marijuana.&lt;br/&gt;
That alone is projected to be a 5-10b market. Worldwide weed is a 100-1000b usd market.&lt;br/&gt;
Legalisation is happening &amp;quot;as we speak&amp;quot; in US, South America, Europe and even some parts in Asia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/NASDAQ-TLRY/&quot;&gt;Tilray &lt;/a&gt;is the number one leading international company in the cannabis game.&lt;br/&gt;
They already have operations in Canada, US and Europe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would compare weed today to where tobacco were for 100 years ago.&lt;br/&gt;
Investing in weed right now is a opportunity of a life time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add the fact that &lt;strong&gt;ROTTEN CITADEL INC&lt;/strong&gt; just increased their short position in Tilray with +20%. Shoutout to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/UMNMURTY/&quot;&gt;u/UMNMURTY&lt;/a&gt; for finding that out! Here is his thread for reference: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx0rxy/citadel_is_up_to_no_good_again/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx0rxy/citadel_is_up_to_no_good_again/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Edit: For informational purposes Citadel Inc is actually NET LONG on Tilray. They however massively increased their short position the stock on 18th of November in order to bring the price down, before the German legalisation news hit the market).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/fyghn8t1ui081.png?width=1390&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c56565a587ba44395ffff788842c31833f1de955&quot;&gt;Boys. We have to do this.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DISCLAIMER:&lt;/strong&gt; Im not a financial advisor. I&amp;#39;m a hobby investor but i do make +30% yearly from stocks and have done so for 10 years. I have recently opened a 10000 stock position in Tilray at 9.99 usd. I also own Curaleaf for better exposure to the US market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2件事是真实的。

(1) 汽油价格比一年前高60%。

(2) 油价仍比13.5年前的2008年7月低16% https://t.co/DTId5yUUNV]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461695640669413376</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461695640669413376</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 18:49:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[每天早上打开WSB]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxfxkc/opening_up_wsb_every_morning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxfxkc/opening_up_wsb_every_morning/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 18:29:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在这个网站和其他投资子网站上，有一个极其明目张胆的天马行空的努力，以促进采矿相关的股票。]]></title><description><![CDATA[(我从我在/r/investing上的帖子中复制了这个帖子。
[https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qxjwg0/theres_an_extremely_blatant_astroturfing_effort/]
因为我似乎不能交叉发帖。我想提高意识，因为这个
子论坛是一个...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxknuz/theres_an_extremely_blatant_astroturfing_effort/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxknuz/theres_an_extremely_blatant_astroturfing_effort/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 18:29:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;(I&amp;#39;m copying this post from my post on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/investing&quot;&gt;/r/investing&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qxjwg0/theres_an_extremely_blatant_astroturfing_effort/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; since it seems like I can&amp;#39;t cross-post. I want to raise awareness because this subreddit is a target.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qxeym8/buying_copper_stocks_now_that_prices_are_taking_a/&quot;&gt;This&lt;/a&gt; post about copper miners just hit the top of &lt;a href=&quot;/r/investing&quot;&gt;/r/investing&lt;/a&gt;, and it&amp;#39;s a good example of the obvious astroturfing effort that&amp;#39;s going on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a look at this account&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/KatheKnuth/submitted/&quot;&gt;post history&lt;/a&gt; and you&amp;#39;ll see a common pattern: a few karma-farming posts from a couple of months ago that invariably come in subreddits like &lt;a href=&quot;/r/aww&quot;&gt;/r/aww&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/r/nextfuckinglevel&quot;&gt;/r/nextfuckinglevel&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/r/MadeMeSmile&quot;&gt;/r/MadeMeSmile&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/r/funny&quot;&gt;/r/funny&lt;/a&gt;, etc. Then nothing, then a submission to a stock subreddit. Anybody with experience moderating subreddits can pick this out as a bought account immediately. This is an extremely common pattern where people build up some easy karma on a clean account and then sell it for use in various promotional campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a look at the post content and you&amp;#39;ll see a pattern that will repeat: one or two paragraphs of content-free &amp;#39;analysis&amp;#39; about events in whatever mining sector, then a series of &amp;#39;pitch&amp;#39; paragraphs where they link to a random junior miner and include the ticker. Presumably this is an attempt to pump/draw attention to these stocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been noticing this happening in &lt;a href=&quot;/r/investing&quot;&gt;/r/investing&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;/r/stocks&quot;&gt;/r/stocks&lt;/a&gt; over the past few months, here are a few examples that I picked up in just 15 minutes by searching for recent posts about &amp;#39;mining&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;copper&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;gold&amp;#39;, and other such keywords. On each of these posts note the exact same post framework and then click on the username -&amp;gt; &amp;#39;posted&amp;#39; tab to see the exact same type of post history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qvx11z/is_investing_in_junior_mining_stocks_worth_it/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 2 days ago, &amp;#39;junior mining&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qqs5bp/coppers_current_situation_is_concerning/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 8 days ago, &amp;#39;copper&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qb8e3y/going_big_on_some_gold_stocks/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 1 month ago, &amp;#39;gold stocks&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/q8le51/investing_in_gold_mining_stocks_after_the_recent/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 1 month ago, &amp;#39;gold mining&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/peh0q5/mining_companies_and_engaging_with_communities/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 1 month ago, &amp;#39;mining companies&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/qudym9/why_do_copper_prices_still_go_down_despite_the/&quot;&gt;/r/stocks, 4 days ago, &amp;#39;copper prices&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/qlsbil/im_about_to_invest_in_some_copper_and_lithium/&quot;&gt;/r/stocks, 16 days ago, &amp;#39;copper and lithium&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/q3vsf4/will_the_recent_fall_in_copper_production_affect/&quot;&gt;/r/stocks, 1 month ago, &amp;#39;copper prices&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is just quickly scanning over posts in these two subreddits over the past month - it&amp;#39;s been going on longer than that and I&amp;#39;m guessing is probably in other investing-related subreddits as well that I just don&amp;#39;t see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I don&amp;#39;t have any personal opinion on the stocks or sectors in question, but I do feel it&amp;#39;s good to point this out and to remind everybody that when you&amp;#39;re reading stuff on Reddit you are not necessarily reading agenda-free or good faith discussions, you are being marketed to. So be suspicious about this stuff. Not sure how much the moderators can realistically do but maybe good for them to be aware of this as well (&lt;a href=&quot;/u/Fauster&quot;&gt;/u/Fauster&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/u/CriticDanger&quot;&gt;/u/CriticDanger&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/u/ScottyStellar&quot;&gt;/u/ScottyStellar&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你不了解你的股票，你不知道它们的价值。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在这个子栏目中，最受欢迎的短语是为长期投资。
长线投资。从字面上看，每个共享的投资组合、尽职调查和股票意见
都是以 "我是为了长期投资 "作为结尾，所以我并不真正关心
价格的波动。

然而，纯粹的恐慌和情绪变化......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxg8e6/you_do_not_understand_your_stocks_and_you_do_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxg8e6/you_do_not_understand_your_stocks_and_you_do_not/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 18:29:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most popular phrase to see reading posts in this sub is the investing for the long term. Literally every shared portfolio, due diligence and stock opinion is finshed with the I invest for the long term, so I do not really care about the price fluctuations. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet the sheer panic and mood changes on stocks are made after every small dip, missed earnings or change in analyst estimates. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The thing is, that the value of company and mass concensus here is not made by anything, but simple price change. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company’s stock rose singnificantly in the last year?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a complete beast and literally everyone needs it in their portfolio!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They missed earnings by 50 basis points, there is small change in the estimates for next year and the stock had not changed in a 6 months?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Immediately sell the company, because you are lacking after the last year biggest homeruns!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason why this thing is happening is, because most people do not know or have the slightest idea about how much they value their business! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would have a strong opinion on how much you value your business, you want sell it after you believed that you have paid 50 cents on a dollar for it. Most of you are valueing business on the market price that is quoted last second. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other thing is that you do not understand the businesses you own!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, saying Iunderstand Coca-Cola because i know it sells Coke is not understanding business. How many of you know the balance sheet of KO, how many of you read the 10Q and 10K, do you know that KO’s payout ratio of their dividends is above 80% and often was 100% plus? Do you know the management? Can you give a pricetag on these cash flows, that KO will make? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this is talking about KO, which is relatively easy to understand company, that nearly everyone has some experience with. I really do not believe that even 0,1% of people who read palantirs reports, looked at its valuation, and most importantly understand the business of the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Answer honestly to yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you really know the business you own?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly i would want to say a story about mass opinions on companies. Microsoft and Apple were for many years considered mature companies with limited growth. Apple was even considered with negative growth rate. After last three years rally in their prices, the opinion on them changed so much that literally everyone believes that they must have them in their portfolio. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would you also consider this if the price of the stock did not change?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在这个网站和其他投资子网站上，有一个极其明目张胆的天马行空的努力，以促进采矿相关的股票。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这个
[https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qxeym8/buying_copper_stocks_now_that_prices_are_taking_a/]
关于铜矿工的帖子刚刚登上了这个分论坛的顶部，它是一个很好的
这是一个很好的例子，说明了正在进行的明显的天马行空的努力。

看一下这个账户的帖子...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qxjwg0/theres_an_extremely_blatant_astroturfing_effort/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qxjwg0/theres_an_extremely_blatant_astroturfing_effort/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 17:32:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qxeym8/buying_copper_stocks_now_that_prices_are_taking_a/&quot;&gt;This&lt;/a&gt; post about copper miners just hit the top of this subreddit, and it&amp;#39;s a good example of the obvious astroturfing effort that&amp;#39;s going on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a look at this account&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/KatheKnuth/submitted/&quot;&gt;post history&lt;/a&gt; and you&amp;#39;ll see a common pattern: a few karma-farming posts from a couple of months ago that invariably come in subreddits like &lt;a href=&quot;/r/aww&quot;&gt;/r/aww&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/r/nextfuckinglevel&quot;&gt;/r/nextfuckinglevel&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/r/MadeMeSmile&quot;&gt;/r/MadeMeSmile&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/r/funny&quot;&gt;/r/funny&lt;/a&gt;, etc. Then nothing, then a submission to a stock subreddit. Anybody with experience moderating subreddits can pick this out as a bought account immediately. This is an extremely common pattern where people build up some easy karma on a clean account and then sell it for use in various promotional campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a look at the post content and you&amp;#39;ll see a pattern that will repeat: one or two paragraphs of content-free &amp;#39;analysis&amp;#39; about events in whatever mining sector, then a serious of &amp;#39;pitch&amp;#39; paragraphs where they link to a random junior miner and include the ticker. Presumably this is an attempt to pump/draw attention to these stocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been noticing this happening in &lt;a href=&quot;/r/investing&quot;&gt;/r/investing&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;/r/stocks&quot;&gt;/r/stocks&lt;/a&gt; over the past few months, here are a few examples that I picked up in just 15 minutes by searching for recent posts about &amp;#39;mining&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;copper&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;gold&amp;#39;, and other such keywords. On each of these posts note the exact same post framework and then click on the username -&amp;gt; &amp;#39;posted&amp;#39; tab to see the exact same type of post history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qvx11z/is_investing_in_junior_mining_stocks_worth_it/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 2 days ago, &amp;#39;junior mining&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qqs5bp/coppers_current_situation_is_concerning/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 8 days ago, &amp;#39;copper&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/qb8e3y/going_big_on_some_gold_stocks/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 1 month ago, &amp;#39;gold stocks&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/q8le51/investing_in_gold_mining_stocks_after_the_recent/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 1 month ago, &amp;#39;gold mining&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/peh0q5/mining_companies_and_engaging_with_communities/&quot;&gt;/r/investing, 1 month ago, &amp;#39;mining companies&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/qudym9/why_do_copper_prices_still_go_down_despite_the/&quot;&gt;/r/stocks, 4 days ago, &amp;#39;copper prices&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/qlsbil/im_about_to_invest_in_some_copper_and_lithium/&quot;&gt;/r/stocks, 16 days ago, &amp;#39;copper and lithium&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/q3vsf4/will_the_recent_fall_in_copper_production_affect/&quot;&gt;/r/stocks, 1 month ago, &amp;#39;copper prices&amp;#39;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is just quickly scanning over posts in these two subreddits over the past month - it&amp;#39;s been going on longer than that and I&amp;#39;m guessing is probably in other investing-related subreddits as well that I just don&amp;#39;t see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I don&amp;#39;t have any personal opinion on the stocks or sectors in question, but I do feel it&amp;#39;s good to point this out and to remind everybody that when you&amp;#39;re reading stuff on Reddit you are not necessarily reading agenda-free or good faith discussions, you are being marketed to. So be suspicious about this stuff. Not sure how much the moderators can realistically do but maybe good for them to be aware of this as well (&lt;a href=&quot;/u/MasterCookSwag&quot;&gt;/u/MasterCookSwag&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/u/dvdmovie1&quot;&gt;/u/dvdmovie1&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/u/kiwimancy&quot;&gt;/u/kiwimancy&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[小丑经济中的退休账户]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxgyxf/retirement_accounts_in_clown_economy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qxgyxf/retirement_accounts_in_clown_economy/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 17:03:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这是你如何F****短裤的。联华电子宣布有意加速回购以代替之前宣布的二次发行。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx7at0/thats_how_you_f_the_shorts_uwmc_announces_intent/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx7at0/thats_how_you_f_the_shorts_uwmc_announces_intent/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 17:03:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[调查：你的目标是什么年龄退休？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在另一个主题中，出现了退休年龄的话题，让我想知道什么是
年龄的人的目标

编辑：退休或能够退休，而不是必须继续工作，如果你不愿意的话。

查看投票 [https://www.reddit.com/poll/qxhbyd]]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxhbyd/poll_what_age_you_are_targeting_to_retire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxhbyd/poll_what_age_you_are_targeting_to_retire/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 17:03:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;in another thread, the topic of time to retire age came up, made me wonder what age bogleheads are aiming at&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: retire or be able to, not HAVE to keep working if you don&amp;#39;t want to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/poll/qxhbyd&quot;&gt;View Poll&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我受够了......我从不满足于利润，所以我从不获利和回落。而且我买期权就像买彩票一样。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx6pjd/im_done_i_am_never_satisfied_with_profits_so_i/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx6pjd/im_done_i_am_never_satisfied_with_profits_so_i/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 16:37:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[37岁的Roth IRA分配]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是博格尔哲学的新手，也是一般投资的新手；至少在关注市场投资方面是如此。
至少在关注市场投资方面是如此。

我有一个大通银行的个人退休账户（因为我20多岁时恰好在那里开了账户），里面有3.2万美元。
因为我在20多岁的时候刚好在那里开的），里面有3.2万美元。绝大多数投资于
SAGPX，完全是因为...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qx0g5x/roth_ira_allocation_for_37_year_old/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qx0g5x/roth_ira_allocation_for_37_year_old/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 15:59:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m new to the Bogle philosophy, as well as investing in general; at least as far as paying attention to market investing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a roth IRA with Chase (because that’s where I happened to be when I opened it in my mid 20’s) with $32k in it. The vast majority is invested in SAGPX, entirely because that’s what they decided to do based on my age and tolerance risk at the time. I’m told it’s doing “well” but Bogle makes sense to me and I think things could use alterations. My question is- should I be investing in 70% stocks, or more/less than that? What portfolio/stocks/bonds would more educated people recommend? Is Chase garbage or pretty average? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m risk tolerant and intend to work til 68+. I have a 403B that’s invested via Fidelity in an age based plan. I have two young kids for whom I save in 529’s for school. I don’t know what I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我只想让它上升，PLEASE!!!!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx9gs2/i_just_want_it_to_go_up_please/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx9gs2/i_just_want_it_to_go_up_please/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 15:27:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[惊人的编辑技巧在这里
https://t.co/lta9mcmNkk]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461580296873287683</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461580296873287683</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 14:35:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[去他妈的澳大利亚 
https://t.co/X8yNGH1Wxq]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461456571570040843</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461456571570040843</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 13:44:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在价格下跌的情况下买入铜股]]></title><description><![CDATA[铜价刚刚下跌，因为中国的工业产出强劲，尽管
他们的房地产行业疲软。形势仍然动荡，但我正
计划买入铜股，因为我知道对铜的需求会不断增加。
铜的需求将继续增加。

我已经买了一些在中国的股票。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qxeym8/buying_copper_stocks_now_that_prices_are_taking_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qxeym8/buying_copper_stocks_now_that_prices_are_taking_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 13:31:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Copper prices just fell because of China’s strong industrial output despite the weakness in their property sector. The situation is still volatile but I am planning to buy copper stocks because of the dip knowing that the demand for copper will just keep on increasing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have already placed some in&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.southerncoppercorp.com/&quot;&gt; Southern Copper Corporation&lt;/a&gt; (SCCO) since they are paying a dividend of $2.70 per share. I’m thinking of placing in Fortitude Gold, since they’re also paying a dividend which they just increased recently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also into getting some juniors seeing how these companies might have some future once the demand for copper increases even more. I’m thinking of getting &lt;a href=&quot;https://cumtn.com/&quot;&gt;Copper Mountain Mining&lt;/a&gt; (CMMC), since they are already producing approximately 100 million pounds of copper equivalent. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.threevalleycopper.com/&quot;&gt;Three Valley Copper&lt;/a&gt; (TVC) is also promising especially after their upsize with a recent deal financing up to $16 million. Their second quarter results are also remarkable and they are expected to start annual production by the end of next year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The copper demand is rising and will probably increase and even double in the next few years so I’m taking my chance on this metal. I didn’t put much anyways since I’m making sure I only invest the money I know I might lose in the end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么新的Vanguard应用程序如此糟糕？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qx3aqt/why_is_the_new_vanguard_app_so_bad/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qx3aqt/why_is_the_new_vanguard_app_so_bad/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 13:04:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有没有人像我一样在没有太多研究的情况下投资股票？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我有超过10万的股票，大约2.5万多的涨幅。我没有做任何深入的研究
对公司的投资。

这就是我的投资方式。- 我主要依靠YouTube上的股票推荐
频道，我经常关注。- 然后我阅读他们的产品，大约几
分钟（最多一两个小时），然后看看...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx8lvt/anyone_like_me_invest_in_stocks_with_not_much/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx8lvt/anyone_like_me_invest_in_stocks_with_not_much/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 11:46:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have more than 100k in stocks and about 25k+ up. I don&amp;#39;t do any deep research on the company invest. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is what I do to invest.
- I rely mostly on YouTube stock recommendation channels I regularly follow. 
- Then I read about their product for about a few minutes (max an hour or two) and see whether I like their product. 
- Make sure that company have no much debts.
- See whether they grew 100+% in last 10 years.
- Continue to do DCA whenever their a dip in the stocks I hold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If above are met then I&amp;#39;ll just invest. That&amp;#39;s it. Have been doing this for last 2 years. I feel like I do very little personal research and taking a big risk&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are there people who invest like me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[出售股票以购买I型债券并最终购买土地]]></title><description><![CDATA[请批判我的逻辑过程，让我知道这是否有意义。我想
想在未来一年左右购买土地。这并不急于求成，但它是
我想在短期内做到这一点。我有很多过去几年的股票收益。
所以我想卖掉一些来买......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qx6vdr/selling_stocks_to_buy_ibonds_and_eventually_buy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qx6vdr/selling_stocks_to_buy_ibonds_and_eventually_buy/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 11:46:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please critique my logical process and let me know if this makes sense.  I would like to buy land in the next year or so. There is no real rush on it, but it&amp;#39;s something I&amp;#39;d like to do in the near term.  I have plenty of stock gains from the last couple of years, so I&amp;#39;m thinking of selling some to buy a property.  However, real estate prices are also high right now and so is inflation, so my plan was to sell stocks and buy I-bonds then wait until the right time to buy a property.  Is this a reasonably wise strategy?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Draftkings是否值得投资？]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以我在前一阵子以53元左右的价格买入了Draftkings，他们已经下跌了，但我一直持有。
但我一直持有，等待疯狂三月的收益。现在，随着所有的交易被
的传闻，迪斯尼和ESPN可能是一个好时机或不值得。因为
投资于更安全的东西，如SPYG或苹果，可能有...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qx8j7c/draftkings_worthy_of_investment/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qx8j7c/draftkings_worthy_of_investment/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 10:47:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So i bought in on draftkings at about 53 a while back and they have tanked but i have been holding for march madness earnings. Now with all of the deals being made and rumors of disney and espn could it be a good time or not worth. Since investing in something safer like SPYG or apple might have more guaranteed returns but if i bought in right now and it just returned to 60 which is below its 52 week high by alot i would essentially double my money but theres a lot of uncertainty with DKNG. So i came here for more informed opinions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR; Question is do i buy in more while its below 40 or do i hold on what i have and just try to get what i can back and invest my money somewhere else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在美国，辞职的工人比例从未如此之高。https://t.co/bxpywwdRz4]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461459482895130640</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461459482895130640</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 06:52:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有些人只想看着世界燃烧]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx4mfy/some_people_just_want_to_watch_the_world_burn/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx4mfy/some_people_just_want_to_watch_the_world_burn/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 05:48:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这里有加拿大人吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是100%的XEQT，这相当于VT。没有任何加拿大版本的这个
子，而且这是我最喜欢的一个，所以我想我应该把它扔出去!]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qwt6fa/any_canadians_here/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qwt6fa/any_canadians_here/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 05:35:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m 100% XEQT, which is the equivalent of VT. Not any Canadian versions of this sub, and it’s my favourite one so thought I’d throw it out there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔的芯片恢复计划可以恢复美国制造业的实力 - Cnet独家报道。]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnet.com/features/intels-chip-recovery-plan-could-restore-us-manufacturing-prowess/

> 芯片制造商的后发制人战略是有风险的，将需要数年时间，即使有政府补贴。
> 有政府补贴。
> 
> 英特尔下一代Meteor Lake CPU、Sapphire Rapids Xeons和Ponte初探
> Vecchio...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx59wj/intels_chip_recovery_plan_could_restore_us/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx59wj/intels_chip_recovery_plan_could_restore_us/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 05:22:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnet.com/features/intels-chip-recovery-plan-could-restore-us-manufacturing-prowess/&quot;&gt;https://www.cnet.com/features/intels-chip-recovery-plan-could-restore-us-manufacturing-prowess/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The chipmaker&amp;#39;s come-from-behind strategy is risky and will take years, even with government subsidies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First Look at Intel’s Next-Gen Meteor Lake CPUs, Sapphire Rapids Xeons &amp;amp; Ponte Vecchio GPUs Fresh Out of Arizona’s Fab 42&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Summary of products and charts: &lt;a href=&quot;https://wccftech.com/first-look-at-intel-next-gen-meteor-lake-cpus-sapphire-rapids-xeons-ponte-vecchio-gpus-fresh-out-of-arizonas-fab-42/&quot;&gt;https://wccftech.com/first-look-at-intel-next-gen-meteor-lake-cpus-sapphire-rapids-xeons-ponte-vecchio-gpus-fresh-out-of-arizonas-fab-42/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局要求联邦法官让公众等到2076年才披露它在许可辉瑞公司COVID-19疫苗时所依赖的所有数据和信息。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461469163839447041</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461469163839447041</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 04:47:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[专业建议：只有当你的持有期限长于基金的期限时，才可以将钱投资于债券基金。债券不是**现金的替代品! 如果你的持有期在一年以下，现金是你最好的选择。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qx4ycu/pro_tip_only_invest_money_in_bond_funds_if_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qx4ycu/pro_tip_only_invest_money_in_bond_funds_if_your/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 04:47:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特公司计划到2023年将电动车产量提高到60万辆。基于这一消息，你明天对这只股票的立场是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[关键点

 * 福特计划将其电动汽车的生产能力提高到
   首席执行官Jim Farley表示，到2023年，全球电动汽车的产能将增加到60万辆。
 * 这位高管预计，这将使该公司成为美国第二大电动汽车制造商。
   该高管预计，这将使该公司成为美国第二大电动汽车生产商，仅次于特斯拉。
 * 目前还不清楚60万辆是否会成为美国电动车市场的主流。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx5wkv/ford_plans_to_increase_ev_production_to_600000/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx5wkv/ford_plans_to_increase_ev_production_to_600000/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 04:21:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KEY POINTS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ford plans to increase its production capacity of electric vehicles to 600,000 units globally by 2023, according to CEO Jim Farley.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The executive expects that would make the company the second-largest U.S.-based producer of EVs, behind Tesla.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s unclear if 600,000 would place it second behind Tesla. General Motors plans to sell 1 million electric vehicles globally by 2025.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/18/ford-plans-to-increase-ev-production-to-600000-vehicles-in-2023.html&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/18/ford-plans-to-increase-ev-production-to-600000-vehicles-in-2023.html&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[QQQ--如果你今天是新人，它能涨到多高？]]></title><description><![CDATA[假设你21岁，开始你的职业生涯，并选择你未来30年的投资。
未来30年的投资。

众所周知，科技绝对是 "大杀器"，但这种涨势能保持多久？
能维持多久？考虑到世界上的FAANG's已经是绝对的领导者，他们还需要多少创新呢？
他们已经是绝对的领导者。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwuosp/qqq_if_youre_new_today_how_high_can_it_go/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qwuosp/qqq_if_youre_new_today_how_high_can_it_go/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 04:21:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s say you&amp;#39;re 21 and starting your career and choosing your investments for the next 30 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tech is absolutely &amp;quot;killing&amp;quot; it as we all know, but how long can this rally be upkept? How much more innovation do the FAANG&amp;#39;s of the world need considering they are already the absolute leaders in their fields?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or do these securities just continue to become more expensive over time due to inflation?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I&amp;#39;m really getting at is what is the &amp;#39;room to grow&amp;#39; factor with these mega-cap FAANGs?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我们在感恩节]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx6hr6/us_at_thanksgiving/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx6hr6/us_at_thanksgiving/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 04:21:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你吃过的最大的亏是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我最近刚刚在我的30K账户上损失了10K，这真的很伤人，因为我已经涨了2K。
然后偏离了我的交易策略，导致我损失惨重。
但我并没有就此罢休，因为我用我的游戏冒险，试图把钱赚回来。
现在我发现自己只剩下2万块了。我知道这不是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qx0aft/whats_the_biggest_loss_youve_taken/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qx0aft/whats_the_biggest_loss_youve_taken/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 03:53:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I recently just lost 10k on my 30k account and it really hurts as I was up 2k and then varied away from my trading strategy causing me to take a massive L, but it didn&amp;#39;t stop there as I got risky with my plays to try and make the money back and now I found myself with only 20k left. I know it&amp;#39;s not the end of the world but geez does it feel like it. So how much have you guys lost? and how did you get over it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[通缉：至少14名嫌疑人在芝加哥附近的橡树溪中心购物中心的路易威登商店进行 "抢购；逃跑"；警方估计有价值10万美元的商品被盗 - WGN https://t.co/mEaVnCA7x8]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461539188063588362</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461539188063588362</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 03:41:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[自2020年5月以来，S&amp;P 500 ETF没有收于200天移动平均线以下。这是自1993年成立以来第5长的连胜纪录。$SPY https://t.co/1MFbVfnHPK]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461359161506074638</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461359161506074638</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 03:41:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[52周低点......真希望我没有发现这只股票......享受吧]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwronc/52_week_lows_wish_i_never_found_this_stock_enjoy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwronc/52_week_lows_wish_i_never_found_this_stock_enjoy/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 02:08:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果电动车]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwvbr5/apple_ev/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwvbr5/apple_ev/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 02:08:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[除了那些把☹️]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx0azv/except_for_the_people_who_had_puts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qx0azv/except_for_the_people_who_had_puts/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 02:08:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你们是如何处理看到大的损失的？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一名大学生，最近决定在股票市场上尝试一下。
我只是把股票搬来搬去，赚点小钱，很是开心。
然后几周前，我决定尝试一下期权。我买了一个苹果看涨期权，涨了
涨了几百块钱。我很惊讶于它是多么容易......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwswdf/how_do_you_guys_deal_with_seeing_big_losses/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qwswdf/how_do_you_guys_deal_with_seeing_big_losses/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 02:08:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am a college student who recently decided to try my hand in the stock market. I was having fun just moving shares around and making small amounts of money. Then a few weeks ago I decided to try options. I bought an apple call that went up a couple hundred bucks. I was amazed at how easy it was to make money with options. Then I decided to put a bunch of money into Delta Airlines calls expiring in January and February. Initially they went up, and I was making more money than ever before. But then they started to go down. As I&amp;#39;m writing this, my weekly chart is down almost 20%. This is all the money I had in my saving account. I&amp;#39;m not sure when I will crack, but at this rate it will be sometime soon. I&amp;#39;m still holding, but I can&amp;#39;t focus on school or anything else because all I can think about is how much money I&amp;#39;m losing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My question is, how do you guys deal with waking up in the morning and seeing huge losses? How do you keep going?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Thanks for all the great advice guys! So many responses! For now my plan is to keep holding because my &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/uV6mzeO&quot;&gt;fortune cookie &lt;/a&gt;from lunch told me to, and I still have a few months till the calls expire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我分析了$NVDA，所以你不必去分析。]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好，今天我将分析$NVDA，也就是Nvidia。I
也对其他公司进行了分析。请随时查看
在我的个人资料中! 对于那些不知道的人来说，Nvidia是一家位于美国的公司。
美国，设计图形、处理单元和芯片。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx1l1a/i_analyzed_nvda_so_you_dont_have_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx1l1a/i_analyzed_nvda_so_you_dont_have_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 02:08:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone, Today I will be analyzing $NVDA otherwise known as Nvidia. I also have done analysis for other companies as well. Feel free to check them out on my profile! For those that don’t know, Nvidia is a company based in the United States that designs graphics, processing units, and chip units. They reported earnings for Q3 on 11/17. They did good overall reporting revenue of $7.1 billion, which is a 50.1% Increase from the same quarter last year, and beat estimates by $290 Million. They also reported record Data Center revenue of $2.94 Billion, and record Gaming revenue of $3.22 billion. At the time of this post, NVDA is sitting at just about $316.75, gaining over $24 today alone. Some of you are probably looking for the next stock similar to TSLA in terms of growth and are thinking that this might be it, especially after their recent run up. They are up $93.85 in the last month alone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the press release, they talked about a lot of great things NVDA has done or is in the process of doing. For example NVDA discussed plans to build something which they call Earth-2, Earth-2 is an AI supercomputer which will be made specifically to predict climate change. Another cool thing they’re doing which I’m sure some of you have heard of is the Omniverse avatar, Omniverse is a technology platform which generates interactive AI avatars. The avatars that are created through this platform will be 3-D. According to NVDA they will be able to see and speak. The avatar will be able to talk about a very wide range of subjects. In the Automotive sector, They released AI technology which allows safe autonomous driving on streets and a computer architecture and sensor set made specifically for self-driving systems. I could go way more in depth on the other great advancements this company is doing but these were my favorite and I think you guys get the point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let&amp;#39;s talk about their evaluation…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nvidia beat expectations, and they had pretty strong revenue growth in Q3, however, percentage wise, they did fall short compared to their semiconductor competitors, such as AMD and TSM. Their EBITDA margins are also looking pretty good. However, compared to other competitors in the space, once again they fall short, other companies in the space captured a larger portion of the market. Overall, Nvidia’s multiples are leading more than any other company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management believes that there is a lot more growth in store. They are growing at a tremendous rate right now. In the earnings call, The CEO of NVDA said that they are finally transitioning into becoming a software company. Nvidia is the dominant leader in creating GPU hardware and now they are also becoming a leader in AI tools and virtualization technology. NVDA wants “Every transaction that goes over the internet to touch a GPU” While also selling the best software available to utilize their GPU’s.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nvidia&amp;#39;s current market cap is very substantial. This stock has had extreme hype as of recently, especially because of the anticipation regarding the Omniverse. It’s definitely possible that this company could see great growth over the coming years. Especially since they basically have a monopoly on GPU hardware and also very extensive experience in visualization and AI, but they will be fighting a lot of competition from companies that want in on the action. Furthermore, Uk regulators have been pushing back on Nvidia’s $40 billion acquisition of the chip designer Arm and if this transaction is hindered then it could put a pretty big crater in Nvidia&amp;#39;s plans. Overall, I believe their company is very overvalued right now and people should wait for a dip if they want to buy into this company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you all learned something from my analysis of this company. Thanks for reading everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EBITDA&lt;/strong&gt;, or earnings before interest, taxes, depreciation, and amortization&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[记住，股票不是公司，公司也不是股票!]]></title><description><![CDATA[在我开始之前，让你知道我没有任何公司的空头头寸
任何东西。正如有人大大向我解释的那样。

问题是，做空头，你不是在赌股票被低估，而是在赌
你是在赌人们会在很短的时间内意识到它被低估了
时间内意识到它被高估了......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qww4qv/remember_the_stock_is_not_the_company_and_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qww4qv/remember_the_stock_is_not_the_company_and_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 02:08:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before I start, letting you know I have no short positions on any company whatsoever. As someone greatly explained it to me,   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The problem is that with shorts you are not betting that the stocks is undervalued, you are betting that people will realize within a short span of time that it is overvalued which is more risky than the former.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, I been seeing and hearing lately a lot of people looking for long-term investments during 2021. Don&amp;#39;t mean to be a bear, but it&amp;#39;s important to understand that the stock is not the company and the company is not the stock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are plenty of companies out there going mainstream with potential for a bright future. EV sector, Renewable sector, Crypto, Fintech &amp;amp; Tech, etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I agree. I firmly believe renewables, electric vehicles, and internet-based payments are, in fact, the future. EV vehicle sales are growing at exponential paces. Solar panels will be seen more and more in your neighborhoods. ATMs probably won&amp;#39;t even exist in 2030. Major cities are pushing for 100% electric buses by 2035. Major car dealerships are expecting to sell only EVs by 2040. Crypto is making a push as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what&amp;#39;s important is also hopping in the stock at the right price. Now, I&amp;#39;m not advocating for market timing. But hopping into Rivian, whose currently valued at $100B with 0 sales is just insane. Lucid being another one whose valued at $75B with a QUARTER of a MILLION in sales. Don&amp;#39;t even get me started on $PLUG. $PLUG is a leader in hydrogen fuel cells for forklifts that reported negative revenue (wtf) and is valued $23B. We all know Tesla is a leader in its sector as well, but the price is outrageous. History has shown prices will always correct based on the company&amp;#39;s fundamentals. Too many posts on $TSLA so I won&amp;#39;t go into this. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s no doubt we are in a bubble. Lots of &amp;quot;Stock Gurus&amp;quot; on Instagram promoting all these overvalued stocks just because their &amp;quot;future looks bright&amp;quot;, and here come all these people commenting talking about how they just invested for the long term. Not saying their future isn&amp;#39;t bright, but it&amp;#39;s important to know when a stock is reasonably priced as opposed to just hearing a pitch line and going all in if they convince you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have no ounce of doubt the prices will drop substantially. I&amp;#39;m not worried about missing out on these hyped stocks. And no, I&amp;#39;m not talking about a 30% correction. Check the dot com bubble companies. I&amp;#39;m talking 95% corrections. Several bankruptcies across the globe. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The 2000 dot-com market collapse was triggered by technology stocks. Investors&amp;#39; interest in internet related companies increased to a frenzied level following massive growth and adoption of the internet.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;It was the unprecedented rise in equity valuations of internet-based tech companies during the bull market of the late 1990s&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The dotcom bubble burst when capital began to dry up. In the years preceding the bubble, record low interest rates, the adoption of the Internet, and interest in technology companies allowed capital to flow freely, especially to startup companies that had no track record of success.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not here to spark rage or scare you. It&amp;#39;s just the hard truth, lots of inexperienced investors have no idea how crazy the outcome could get. Once the big banks and heads at Wall Street realize its insanely overvalued, the rug pull will come. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me know if I&amp;#39;m wrong. Curious to hear everyone&amp;#39;s thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SROs、复杂性和市场结构]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周，由于对目前的市场自律结构感到沮丧和愤怒，我实际上失眠了。
市场的自我监管结构而感到沮丧和愤怒。虽然这有点傻，有点
虽然这有点傻，有点荒唐（尽管它确实发生了！），但我认为这是值得研究和解释的。
一个自我监管的营利性公司的激励机制如何导致...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qww9zu/sros_complexity_and_market_structure/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qww9zu/sros_complexity_and_market_structure/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 02:08:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week I actually lost sleep due to frustration and anger at the current self-regulatory structure in markets. While this is kind of silly and a bit absurd (though it did happen!), I think it’s worth examining and explaining how the incentives for a self-regulatory, for-profit company lead to extreme complexity and subsidization in US markets. It’s easy to say “self-regulatory BAD!” but harder to understand the web of complexity that such perverse structures create.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a long post. By the end, I hope you understand what the self-regulatory structure is, why it exists, why it creates perverse incentives, and how I think it should be fixed. I’ll do my best to explain the context of these archaic structure, why it leads to unnecessary complexity, and reduces competitive forces. Most importantly, throughout the piece think about how such perverse incentives leads to lax enforcement and wrist slaps, and a cozy relationship with the industry being regulated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The financial services industry is the only industry in America (that I am aware of) in which for-profit, publicly traded firms are “self-regulatory.” What does “self-regulatory” mean and where did it come from? The structure came about from the member-owned stock exchanges that existed prior to 1934. In 1934 these exchanges were brought into partnership with federal regulators in the Exchange Act of 1934. This actually made a lot of sense. There was nobody better positioned to monitor and enforce the rules of a stock exchange (where trading happened in a physical location, on the floor of the exchange) than the exchange itself. There were conflicts-of-interest, of course, but there were also practical considerations of what technology and communication systems looked like in the early 1900s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what does “self-regulatory” mean? Now of course, I’m no lawyer, so take everything I say with that in mind. Essentially the self-regulatory structure gives the regulation arm of the exchange quasi-governmental powers (it’s been explained to me that this structure means the exchange is supposed to act as an extension of the SEC) – and gives the exchange itself immunity from prosecution when carrying out regulatory functions. It basically means that US exchanges set the rules for trading in US markets, and for interacting with their business, are then in charge of enforcing those rules and have no legal liability in the operation of that business. Those rules include things like fee structure, order types, matching priority model, co-location and data feed costs, and many other things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That means each for-profit exchange is setting its own rules, and responsible for enforcing those rules. Each exchange is responsible for monitoring its own market for manipulation (called “market surveillance”). In reality, the responsibility for market surveillance is outsourced to FINRA. FINRA is another SRO – they are not a for-profit exchange, but they are responsible for setting the rules and policing broker/dealers. You may have heard of some of the other SROs – the DTCC, the OCC, the NSCC and others listed &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/rules/sro.shtml&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FINRA, DTCC, OCC and NSCC are not for-profit, of course, but they are deeply conflicted. They operate on the fees generated by their members, who they police and regulate; stock exchanges do too – their best customers are high-speed speculators (aka HFT), who submit 95% of all orders, and are a party to ~90% of all trades. These speculators also pay for expensive, proprietary data feeds, high-speed connections and cross-connects, and other exchange services. SROs are supposed to police these customers, and are charged with ensuring that their best customers follow the rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gee Dave, that sounds like a conflict-of-interest! At least it’s not for anything important, like the foundation of the US economy, right?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is generally the SROs that have made breaking the rules a cost of doing business (naturally following the lead of the SEC, of course). While they don’t have the authority to press criminal charges (again, not a lawyer) they could easily make referrals and work with the DOJ, who does have that authority. Instead, nearly all of Wall St has decided that breaking the rules is nearly always only worth a fine, very rarely an industry ban, and practically never a perp walk and prison.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like nobody lost their banking license for fraud following the Great Financial Crisis, can you remember a time when a major broker/dealer had their license revoked? Robinhood has been fined well over $100M by FINRA and the SEC for lying to their customers, failing to provide best execution, and underinvesting in compliance, technology and any system for protecting their customers. For some reason, none of this was enough to lose their license to operate. Those guys are laughing all the way to the bank. Fine after fine is charged to every broker on Wall St, paid by the shareholders, and everyone keeps collecting their bonuses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First SRO Problem: Reluctance to exact severe consequences because the fees being collected from the perps are paying for SRO operations and bonuses.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, there’s another side to all of this. Let’s take a concrete example to start. In 2014, BATS and DirectEdge merged. Together, they represented approximately 20% of trading in the US. Each of them operated 2 copycat exchanges – a maker/taker exchange (BZX and EDGX) and an inverted exchange (BYX and EDGA). In any other industry, such a merger would result in the consolidation of these exchanges so that the resulting company would only operate 2 exchanges. But that didn’t happen here. They continued to run 4 exchanges and do to this day. Why would they do that when it costs way more to run 4 exchanges rather than 2? The answer is actually quite simple and obvious – money. To understand why, we have to take a quick step back, and reference another law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 1975 Amendments to the 1934 Exchange Act established the need (and gave the SEC the authority) to create the Securities Information Processor (SIP). It was groundbreaking at the time. The SIP is the “ticker” – a record of quotes and trades on all national securities exchanges. Ultimately the SEC did NOT create such a system though, it delegated the authority to the exchanges. The exchanges created the NMS Committees, which are responsible for managing the SIP and setting fees. From last year’s SEC press release announcing changes to the SIP:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In  1975, one of Congress’s principal objectives for the national  market  system was to assure the availability of information with respect  to  quotations for, and transactions in, securities.  The national   securities exchanges and the Financial Industry Regulatory Authority   (“FINRA” and collectively, the “SROs”) have acted jointly to collect,   consolidate, and disseminate information for NMS stocks.  For each NMS   stock, the SROs were required to provide specified NMS market data to   exclusive securities information processors (“SIPs”).  The SIPs then   consolidated that information and made it available to the public.  The   rules adopted today are designed to modernize and improve upon that   historical infrastructure, by expanding the content of NMS market data   and replacing the historical “exclusive SIP” model with a decentralized   model of “competing consolidators.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ALRIGHT ENOUGH HISTORY DAVE, WTF IS THE SIP??&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry, it’s hard to talk about this stuff without getting deep in the weeds. The SIP is generally referred to as the “public data feed” – at the moment (though this is changing), it provides top-of-book quotes across all US exchanges, calculates the NBBO and publishes it, communicates regulatory halts and other information, and publishes all trades both on- and off-exchange.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And guess what? You pay for it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s right – you are paying for the SIP. Nearly every retail broker subscribes to the SIP, and generally speaking when you see the prices that a stock is being quoted at, or trading for, you’re seeing SIP data. This public data feed costs $4 per user, per month, for non-professional, display-only users – if you’re not a financial professional, and you’re only seeing the data with your eyes (rather than programming a trading system that will automatically look at the data), then you are a non-professional, display-only user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are all of those user fees worth? Something on the order of &amp;gt; $300M per year. That money is collected by the operators of the SIP (NYSE and Nasdaq), and distributed according to a very complicated formula to each of the exchanges. On the whole, it gets divided up based on quoting and trading market share, and means that approximately $100M every year goes to CBOE, NYSE and Nasdaq (with much less going to the smaller exchanges). That’s why BATS/DirectEdge (and now CBOE, which acquired them in 2016) was incentivized to continue to operate 4 exchanges, because it meant that more of this public subsidy would go to them. Talk about perverse – it’s the exact opposite of what the 1934 Exchange Act was established to do:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(5)  The rules of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.law.cornell.edu/definitions/uscode.php?width=840&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;iframe=true&amp;amp;def_id=15-USC-1989774883-482320172&amp;amp;term_occur=999&amp;amp;term_src=title:15:chapter:2B:section:78f&quot;&gt;exchange&lt;/a&gt;   are designed to prevent fraudulent and manipulative acts and  practices,  to promote just and equitable principles of trade, to foster   cooperation and coordination with&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.law.cornell.edu/definitions/uscode.php?width=840&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;iframe=true&amp;amp;def_id=15-USC-991716523-482320180&amp;amp;term_occur=999&amp;amp;term_src=&quot;&gt; persons &lt;/a&gt;engaged   in regulating, clearing, settling, processing information with respect   to, and facilitating transactions in securities, to remove impediments   to and perfect the mechanism of a free and open market and a national   market system, and, in general, to protect investors and the public   interest; and are not designed to permit unfair discrimination between   customers,&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.law.cornell.edu/definitions/uscode.php?width=840&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;iframe=true&amp;amp;def_id=15-USC-1179159879-482320179&amp;amp;term_occur=999&amp;amp;term_src=title:15:chapter:2B:section:78f&quot;&gt; issuers,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.law.cornell.edu/definitions/uscode.php?width=840&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;iframe=true&amp;amp;def_id=15-USC-1380616231-482320175&amp;amp;term_occur=999&amp;amp;term_src=title:15:chapter:2B:section:78f&quot;&gt; brokers,&lt;/a&gt; or&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.law.cornell.edu/definitions/uscode.php?width=840&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;iframe=true&amp;amp;def_id=15-USC-1335779815-482320176&amp;amp;term_occur=999&amp;amp;term_src=title:15:chapter:2B:section:78f&quot;&gt; dealers,&lt;/a&gt;   or to regulate by virtue of any authority conferred by this chapter   matters not related to the purposes of this chapter or the   administration of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.law.cornell.edu/definitions/uscode.php?width=840&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;iframe=true&amp;amp;def_id=15-USC-1989774883-482320172&amp;amp;term_occur=999&amp;amp;term_src=title:15:chapter:2B:section:78f&quot;&gt;exchange&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It gets even worse (No way Dave! How can it be worse than this??). Each exchange sells private data feeds that are faster and contain more information than the SIP. So the exchanges are incentivized to ensure that the SIP remains slow, and has less data, so they can make more money selling their private feeds. Pretty sweet gig if you can get it, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I’ve simplified the issue, of course. It gets even more complex with Reg NMS and order protection, which requires all exchanges to connect and route to one another, and brokers to manage that complexity as well. It means that CBOE gets double the revenue for private market data, and other connectivity fees, all of which ensures that CBOE earnings per share are robust and growing, and which accomplishes the opposite of the intention of the 1934 Act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Second SRO Problem: SRO structure is a classic example of regulation and subsidy creating inefficient and costly complexity.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The BATS/DirectEdge example is only one of so many that highlight the unnecessary complexity at the heart of US markets. I’ve talked many times about the need for regulators to understand complex systems and systems theory, to understand evolving regulatory structures in that context, and to focus on simplifying markets rather than making them more complex. Unnecessary complexity leads to several problems:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opacity – it becomes very difficult to understand these complex systems. That leads to mistrust, and potentially loss of confidence. We are seeing that play out right now in the retail community, and for good reason. Nobody trusts Wall St.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fragility – unnecessary complexity can lead to fragility. For example, the segmentation in US markets that diverts retail order flow to the duopoly of Citadel and Virtu leaves exchanges as toxic cesspools that discourage market making. This both widens spreads and reduces market making diversity, leading to behavior that can result in illiquidity contagions (mini flash crashes).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rent Seeking and Concentration – unnecessary complexity incentivizes a select few firms to master the complexity. This puts them in a privileged position, and creates economies of scale where the more of the market they master and control, the more information they have that others don’t, and the more they’re able to master and control. They push SROs to create ever more complexity to maintain their incumbent position, and are able to extract rents as a result. The SROs listen to these firms because they are responsible for more and more trading activity, which means they are the SROs’ best customers. Instead of SROs following their duties under the 1934 Act, they act in the interests of their shareholders to maximize revenue. This cycle continues unabated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Third SRO Problem: Unnecessary complexity makes markets opaque, fragile and leads to a feedback loop of rent seeking and concentration of power. The for-profit motive overrides the SRO’s duty to create fair and efficient markets.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mentioned before that SROs have legal immunity. This means many things, but primarily it means that the brokers who are members of the exchange don’t have legal recourse when something goes wrong. It is for this reason that retail brokers who don’t accept PFOF still route to the off-exchange duopoly of Citadel and Virtu, because they want someone’s neck to wring when something goes wrong. The legal immunity that exchanges enjoy is one of the reasons that we have dramatically segmented markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fourth SRO Problem: Legal immunity for for-profit, publicly traded companies leads to perverse incentives and terrible outcomes.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what’s the result? A huge amount of unnecessary complexity, enforcement becoming a cost of doing business, and ultimately fragile markets with low participant diversity delivering poor outcomes for investors as the for-profit SROs focus on creating churn and volume to increase earnings per share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More complexity means more fragmentation. More fragmentation means more complex order types. More fragmentation and complex order types means more unnecessary trading and churn. More unnecessary trading and churn means more earnings for publicly traded SROs. Rinse and repeat. It ultimately means that we end up with so much complexity that it’s impossible to keep track of. Take a look at the results of this 2018 RBC study on exchange fee structure (the picture is awesome, but I can&amp;#39;t seem to add pictures to a post in this sub-reddit):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exchanges have at least 1,023 pricing “paths”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3,762  separate pricing variables across the exchanges – “strongly suggest  that exchange prices are tailored and offered on a bespoke basis”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extreme complexity, customized for specific firms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extreme routing distortion (TD’s “virtually all” limit orders routed to EDGX)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fee-agnostic brokers had 7x better VWAP performance (Clearpool)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If someone can explain how this fee structure “promotes just and equitable principles of trade,” “protects investors and the public interest,” and is “not designed to permit unfair discrimination between customers, issuers, brokers or dealers” I’m all ears. Go ahead, give it a try!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, let’s take this convoluted, inefficient structure, add in a regulatory revolving door, corrupt campaign contribution system and corrupt politicians, mix it all together, and out comes the US crony capitalist system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GET OFF THE SOAP BOX DAVE, WHAT DO WE DO?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So glad you asked. I’ve been asked a bunch of times what I think should change about US market structure, what I would do if I was SEC Chair (imagine that), etc. My answer is nearly always the same – reduce complexity. When I say reduce complexity, this post is what I’m talking about:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· End the self-regulatory structure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· Build a proper regulator (complete overhaul of the SEC) with experts who are compensated appropriately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· Prioritize handcuffs, not wrist slaps and fines. Make the industry fearful of regulatory and enforcement consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· Reduce the number of exchanges, end public subsidy through SIP fees, get rid of every copycat exchange.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· Create a burden for off-exchange trading to compensate for the damage that segmenting and diverting flow does to the price discovery mechanism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;· Simplify, Simplify, SIMPLIFY!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tldr;&lt;/strong&gt; Wall St cannot regulate itself. It leads to unnecessary complexity, and lax enforcement and fines instead of perp walks. It’s time to overhaul the regulatory structure, send people to jail, and simplify market structure dramatically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[互联网上股票邪教的兴起]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reddit、twitter和stocktwits都允许世界各地的人更容易地交流。
世界各地有类似兴趣的人之间的交流。然而，基于
这些网站的设计（关注特定的社区，而这些社区往往是
痴迷于任何话题），它也可能导致伪装。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx1fex/the_rise_of_stock_cults_on_the_internet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qx1fex/the_rise_of_stock_cults_on_the_internet/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 02:08:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reddit, twitter, and stocktwits all have allowed for easier communication between anyone around the world who share a similar interest. However, based on the design of these sites (following specific communities that are often obsessive over whatever topic it is about), it can also lead to pseudo-cults (and circlejerks), especially with money involved. For stocks, the community will often be heavily in favor on the stock and will down vote or attack anyone who disagrees it is not the next big thing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is depressing seeing the amount of outright shaming that goes on. For example, after a rough few weeks of trading, one of the top posts on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/shroomstocks&quot;&gt;/r/shroomstocks&lt;/a&gt; (a subreddit dedicated to stocks having to do with psychedelics) is &amp;quot;Seriously, who are the losers selling at these prices right now?&amp;quot; Does this seem like healthy behavior to you? Implying your stock is a test of courage and you will be rewarded for your patience. If you are not completely faithful in the stock (which can lead to even worshipping the management), you are attacked for questioning what is obviously true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recall about a year ago and the obsession with Cathie Woods, also viewed by many to be infallible. After a couple successful years she was viewed as the next Buffet and if you dared to complain on a down day you would constantly be reminded of how it&amp;#39;s a five-year hold. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m sure many of those who were on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/PSTH&quot;&gt;/r/PSTH&lt;/a&gt; can relate. Questioning the company was seen as questioning Bill Ackman himself. Over time the sub shifted to humor as a means of getting over the losses (although there were still people who fervently believed in the SPACman!). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you think? I find some &amp;quot;communities&amp;quot; to be outright manipulative for those with dissenting views.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你如何阻止自己每天检查你的投资组合？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在两个月前开始了我漫长的退休之旅，已经得到了每月的
自动缴款的设置。我知道我应该设置它，然后忘记它，但
这很难。说真的，几小时后打开一次手机，看着
图表上上下下，让人上瘾。你们是怎么做的？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qx17te/how_do_you_stop_yourself_from_checking_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qx17te/how_do_you_stop_yourself_from_checking_your/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 01:13:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I started my long journey towards retirement two months ago, already got monthly automatic contributions set up. I know I&amp;#39;m supposed to set it and forget it, but it&amp;#39;s hard. Seriously, turning on your phone once a couple of hours to watch the chart go up and down is addicting. How do you guys do it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师在下调评级时说，PayPal "现在有被竞争对手破坏的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝宝(PayPal Holdings Inc.)以颠覆支付生态系统而闻名，但据一位分析师称，它 "现在有被颠覆的危险"。
但据一位分析师称，它 "现在有被破坏的风险"。伯恩斯坦的
Harshita Rawat周三将该股评级从优于大盘下调至市场表现。
他说，数字支付的各种竞争压力使其面临着巨大的挑战。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwqllz/paypal_now_risks_getting_disrupted_by_competitors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qwqllz/paypal_now_risks_getting_disrupted_by_competitors/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 01:13:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PayPal Holdings Inc. has a reputation for disrupting the payments ecosystem, but it “now risks getting disrupted” itself, according to an analyst. Bernstein’s Harshita Rawat downgraded the stock to market perform from outperform Wednesday, citing various competitive pressures for the digital payments giant. Shares of PayPal PYPL, -4.36% are off 2.5% in premarket trading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rawat worries about the “increasing aggregation” of e-commerce activity on large platforms like Amazon.com Inc. AMZN, +0.23% and Shopify Inc. SHOP, -2.24%, which she estimates are together responsible for about 32% of U.S. commerce. “Amazon currently doesn’t accept PayPal and just agreed to accept Venmo starting in 2022,” she wrote. “Shopify has ambitions of creating its own payments business and has been pushing its merchants aggressively to convert to Shopify payments platform (and also towards the Shop Pay button).”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Smaller merchants “are PayPal’s bread and butter, and Shopify’s meteoric rise and push towards its own payments platform is particularly problematic,” Rawat continued. PayPal’s transaction economics are better with smaller businesses than with very large ones, she argued. Shopify Inc. represents an “unassailable competitor” when it comes to the small-business demographic, in her view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rawat is also concerned that PayPal’s market-share gains will slow. The company has typically won share at the expense of manual card entry onto a website, but fewer consumers are entering their card information this way, she said, meaning there is less available land to grab there. She estimates that manual card entry now accounts for about 20% of e-commerce checkout, down from roughly 33% four years back. More broadly, she thinks that share gains could slow “by a thousand cuts” thanks to the rise of a number of technologies that separately eat away at opportunities for PayPal. These include the growth of buy-now pay-later (BNPL) services, the ability to auto-fill credit-card information on some web browsers, and the threat of Apple Pay as ever more commerce shifts online. “It is an understatement to say that the payments landscape is rapidly evolving with many powerful trends emerging,” Rawat said in her note to clients. “While PayPal is actively investing and evolving, it simply has more turf to defend versus peers in our view.” Rawat acknowledged that her thesis could prove incorrect if PayPal delivers upbeat surprises with its efforts to drive more revenue from its Venmo app and its “superapp” redesign that focuses on features beyond just payments. “After years of false starts, we believe Venmo is finally on the cusp of getting monetized,” she wrote. While Rawat has “historically been skeptical of aggressive monetization estimates for Venmo,” she feels more “constructive” now. “Venmo monetization is now less about following the PayPal playbook and more about following Cash App’s journey,” she wrote, referencing Square Inc.’s SQ, -2.78% mobile wallet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shares of PayPal have declined 20% over the past three months as the S&amp;amp;P 500 SPX, -0.26% has risen about 6%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/paypal-now-risks-gettingdisrupted-by-competitors-analyst-says-in-downgrade-11637160014?mod=mw_quote_news&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/paypal-now-risks-gettingdisrupted-by-competitors-analyst-says-in-downgrade-11637160014?mod=mw_quote_news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>