<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 19:58:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[我所接觸的一切]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/npasxm/everything_i_touch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/npasxm/everything_i_touch/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 22:19:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果我不是來自美國，我是否仍應投資於標準普爾500指數，因爲我對當地市場根本不感興趣？]]></title><description><![CDATA[這個問題是不言自明的，但是否有額外的稅和其他東西，或者我可以通過DCA在10-15年內獲得平均10%的回報？
通過10-15年的DCA投資獲得平均10%的回報？我來自一個第三世界
我來自一個第三世界國家，所以基本上還沒有很多好的全球機構，因此ETF不是很有趣，也沒有罪。
因此，ETF不是很有趣，從一開始我就...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/nozzic/if_i_am_not_from_us_should_i_still_invest_in_sp/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/nozzic/if_i_am_not_from_us_should_i_still_invest_in_sp/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 16:06:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Question is self explanatory but are there extra taxes and stuff or i can benefit the average 10% return by DCAing over 10-15 years? 
I am from a third world country so basically there are not many good global institutions yet and hence the ETF are not very interesting and since the beginning i have only researched about US and its market.
Is it possible to do that?
Any explain will be appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[乍得錢。第2集]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/np25gk/chad_money_episode_2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/np25gk/chad_money_episode_2/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 14:30:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對Pinterest的看法？]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pinterest是我目前最大的持股，我對它有強烈的信念。
的堅定信念。我喜歡它是一個以女性爲主導的投資，在全球範圍內快速增長，並擁有5億月度活躍用戶，令人印象深刻。
我喜歡它是一個以女性爲主導的投資項目，在全球範圍內快速增長，月活躍用戶達到5億。

領導層稱該公司是一個個人媒體應用和一個
搜索...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/noia7g/thoughts_on_pinterest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/noia7g/thoughts_on_pinterest/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 14:30:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pinterest is currently my biggest holding and I have a strong conviction about it. I love that it&amp;#39;s a women-driven investment that is growing impressively fast around the world and sits at 500M monthly active users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The leadership refers to the company as a personal media application and a search engine for ideas. Their two biggest changes has been the introduction of Shops,  which has pressured Instagram to release its own influencer version of shops and the release of Livestreams with tickets/waitrooms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really love the direction that this company is going in and it in some ways it kind of reminds me of the intention of YouTube. Mostly women are going on the platform with an intent to plan or search, so the need for influencing is not nearly as high as it is on platforms like Facebook or Bytedance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the short term, I&amp;#39;m bullish on Pinterest with respect to travel. I think we will see continued growth because people are planning their trips and it&amp;#39;s a lucrative market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the long-term I&amp;#39;m bullish on it being one of the more effective forms of social media with respect to e-commerce and advertising effectiveness. A user may go on Instagram and spend more time, resulting in no net gain for an advertiser. A user on Pinterest is almost guarunteed to enter and exit with an attempted plan or shop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are your thoughts on Pinterest?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[關於 "大空頭 "投資者邁克爾-伯利被美國證券交易委員會訪問並隨後被迫關閉其微博的原因的意見]]></title><description><![CDATA[我有點困惑，爲什麼大空頭投資者Michael Burry會被美國證券交易委員會訪問？
被美國證券交易委員會訪問。在翻閱他的推文檔案時，他抨擊特斯拉。
我不明白的是，爲什麼他會因爲表達自己的觀點而被美國證券交易委員會訪問？
我不明白的是，爲什麼他因爲表達了自己的觀點而被美國證券交易委員會訪問？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nok7pa/opinions_on_why_the_big_short_investor_michael/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nok7pa/opinions_on_why_the_big_short_investor_michael/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 10:33:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m a little confused about why the big short investor Michael Burry was visited by the SEC. When going over his archive of tweets he rails against tesla, robinhood and warns of a bubble in the market; what I don&amp;#39;t understand is why he would be visited by the SEC for expressing his opinion on twitter. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Isn&amp;#39;t this literally what the pundits on CNBC do all day? All I ever hear on that channel is &amp;quot;Buy, Buy, Buy,&amp;quot; whereas Burry&amp;#39;s tweets have substance behind them. For example, he warned about inflation in February and as of April 2021 it has begun to hit the markets. Also, when does someone become to big to express their opinion about the market?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[人們對伯利的5.34億美元特斯拉空頭的看法是錯誤的]]></title><description><![CDATA[人們沒有看到Michael Burry做空TSLA背後的全部想法。每一篇
文章都是關於他如何在推特上抨擊馬斯克爸爸，以及他如何認爲該公司
是他把玻璃眼睛掉進貓砂盆後最糟糕的事情。

他不認爲特斯拉會內爆。他不認爲它是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nosznl/people_are_missing_the_point_on_burrys_534m_tesla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nosznl/people_are_missing_the_point_on_burrys_534m_tesla/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 10:33:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;People don&amp;#39;t see the full idea behind Michael Burry&amp;#39;s TSLA short. Every single article is about how he tweeted at papa Musk and how he thinks that the company is the worst thing since he dropped his glass eye into his cat&amp;#39;s litter box.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He doesn&amp;#39;t think that Tesla will implode. He doesn&amp;#39;t think it&amp;#39;s a failing company. He just sees the reality, which is that all of their profits/revenues are way in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s just say you win a time-delayed lottery and get $1,000,000 in 15 years. Not bad! Now let&amp;#39;s say you won the same lottery in Venezuela in 2005. It&amp;#39;s not even worth cashing the ticket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s the same deal with companies. Growth companies, however promising, have most of their expected profits in the future. Those profits have to be discounted by the &lt;strong&gt;interest rate&lt;/strong&gt; to be turned into todays dollars. In other words, it doesn&amp;#39;t matter how much money Tesla is going to make in the future if interest rates surge today. Well... it does matter... it&amp;#39;s just worth a lot less.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So how does this relate to the Burry bet? You just have to scroll down a few lines on his 13F filing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Burry has almost as many GOOG/FB calls as he does TSLA puts. Around ~$330MM of them. Why does this matter? These are big tech companies that are actually printing out metric shit-tons of profit today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interest rates stay the same but big tech goes up? Break even. Big tech goes down? Break even. Interest rates rise? Burry makes more money in a year than all of your wives boyfriends combined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Burry TSLA short isn&amp;#39;t a bet against Tesla, it&amp;#39;s a bet on interest rates rising (AKA inflation).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我應該投資20 000美元在標準普爾500指數上嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是投資界的新手。我在一年內存了2萬塊錢，我在尋找
一個安全/小風險的投資，我可以獲得一些被動收入。標準普爾是一個
好的選擇嗎？你知道有什麼更好的或更有利可圖的風險小的選擇嗎？
機會？我也一直在投資加密貨幣作爲樂趣，不希望...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/noxl2g/should_i_invest_20_000_in_sp_500/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/noxl2g/should_i_invest_20_000_in_sp_500/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 10:33:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am new to the investing world. I have saved 20k over a year and I&amp;#39;m looking for a safe/small risk investment where I can get some passive income. Is S&amp;amp;P a good option? Do you know any better or more profitable options with small risk chances? I&amp;#39;ve been also investing in crypto for fun, not looking to invest any further or bigger amounts of money. I live in Europe so I&amp;#39;m not looking for options that aren&amp;#39;t available here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$BB | 5月28日星期五的空頭獲勝--下週牛市有了新的機會! | 12美元的阻力位是成功或失敗的邊界線!]]></title><description><![CDATA[🍇 $BB的圖表更新 🍇

上週五，我們看到了開始一個新的上升趨勢的第一次嘗試。第一個價格
目標（12美元）在不到24小時內就達到了。隨後，價格被
在12美元的阻力位被嚴重拒絕，形成一根看跌的蠟燭。

週五的成交量遠遠高於上週五。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/no5gqd/bb_shorts_won_on_friday_28th_may_next_week_bulls/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/no5gqd/bb_shorts_won_on_friday_28th_may_next_week_bulls/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 07:05:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;🍇 Chart update for $BB 🍇&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last friday we saw a first attempt to start a new uptrend. The first price target (12$) was reached in less than 24 hours. Subsequently the price got heavily rejected at the resistance level of 12$, forming a bearish candle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The volume on Friday was much higher than the average. The short sellers tried to push the share price down below the resistance at 12$ in order to avoid a further surge. I assume they are really  scared to see the price above that level because chartwise that means a bullish trend reversal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next week Blackberry needs to break the resistance around 12$. Beyond 12$ there is almost no resistance besides the ATH. Furthermore the short interest rose during the consolidation since February. The percentage of float shorted is around 9% now (5/14/2021) which provides additional fuel for a squeeze. That means we could see a fast acceleration of the new uptrend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the share price of $BB falls below the support at 8.5$ the bullish scenario is &lt;strong&gt;not valid&lt;/strong&gt; anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price targets:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;#1 12$ ✅ 28th May&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;#2 25$&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;#3 48$&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;#4 🚀🚀🚀&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;d like to quote the user IncognitoCumShot here:  &amp;quot;Anything under $140 is a dip&amp;quot; ❤&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is no financial advice - I am just sharing my opinion. Please do your own due diligence!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/qd9qf54ac7271.png?width=1518&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=4c239eb9dc85d2879ba73145fe976a299e6480b6&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/qd9qf54ac7271.png?width=1518&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=4c239eb9dc85d2879ba73145fe976a299e6480b6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just to make it more clear - I think the price action is going to repeat as you can see in the following chart:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/6lw9v7clk9271.png?width=2158&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=b691a9132220de9109aeb70283165579e3cc5c63&quot;&gt;Bearish candle along with a volume spike&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YOLO的力量!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nol0ei/power_of_the_yolo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nol0ei/power_of_the_yolo/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 00:07:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我的投資與華爾街。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/noi60w/my_investment_vs_wall_street/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/noi60w/my_investment_vs_wall_street/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 20:51:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[蘋果公司在CarPlay上的巨大成功爲汽車業的野心鋪平了道路。]]></title><description><![CDATA[蘋果在2014年推出了CarPlay，作爲整合iPhone和汽車儀表盤的一種方式。
儀表盤。從那時起，它在新車中已經變得無處不在。

蘋果公司去年表示，在全球範圍內，超過80%的新售汽車支持CarPlay。
去年說的。這相當於約600種新車型，包括來自大衆的汽車。
寶馬、...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/no1uzz/apples_massive_success_with_carplay_paves_the_way/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/no1uzz/apples_massive_success_with_carplay_paves_the_way/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 19:56:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;#39;Apple introduced CarPlay in 2014 as a way to integrate the iPhone and a car’s dashboard. Since then, it’s become ubiquitous in new cars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Around the world, over 80% of new cars sold support CarPlay, Apple said last year. That works out to about 600 new models, including cars from Volkswagen, BMW, and Chrysler. Toyota, one of the longest holdouts, started including CarPlay in 2019 models.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s also a top feature for many drivers and car buyers. Twenty-three percent of new car buyers in the U.S. say they “must have” CarPlay and 56% percent are “interested” in having CarPlay when buying a new vehicle, according to a 2017 Strategy Analytics study. When Ford’s highly anticipated electric F-150 goes on sale, it will support CarPlay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple was able to insert itself in between customers and car companies and make sure that its interface was the one that every iPhone user wants while driving. It’s an under-appreciated triumph for one of the world’s most successful companies. CarPlay doesn’t contribute direct Apple revenues or profits. But it ensures ongoing loyalty of iPhone users and gives Apple a pathway into the auto industry if it wants to expand.&amp;#39;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source and remainder of article:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/29/apple-carplay-massive-success-paves-way-for-automotive-entry.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/29/apple-carplay-massive-success-paves-way-for-automotive-entry.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我收益越多，就越貪婪。你們是如何處理那些在賣出獲利後仍不斷上漲的股票的？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在我早期的交易生涯中經歷了一系列的損失後，我認爲我應該謙虛地認識到，任何收益都是好的收益。
意識到任何收益都是好的收益，無論股票的軌跡如何。
股票。即使在今年早些時候深陷虧損，並最終意識到
一些利潤，我還是忍不住想 "可以"。

I...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nohefp/the_more_i_gain_the_more_i_get_greedy_how_do_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nohefp/the_more_i_gain_the_more_i_get_greedy_how_do_you/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 19:56:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a series of losses in my early trading career, I thought I&amp;#39;d be humbled enough to realize that any gain is a good gain, no matter the trajectory of a stock. Even after being in deep red earlier this year, and finally realizing some profits, I can&amp;#39;t help but think about the &amp;quot;could haves&amp;quot;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need to realign and shift perspectives, even though I know that&amp;#39;s the path to heavy losses, how do you guys deal with?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[哦，好吧，我只是失去了一切]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nodg7m/oh_well_i_only_lost_everything/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nodg7m/oh_well_i_only_lost_everything/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 19:56:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有人專門購買行業ETF嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[上個月我一直在增加X-ETF的數量；XLF、XME、XLI、XLE、XLT。
等。我確實擁有幾隻我深信不疑的股票，但我在想
我確實擁有幾隻我有信心的股票，但我在考慮削減並進入更多特定行業的ETF。

這是否完全沒有意義？只是買入SPY有意義嗎？

我已經能夠...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/nodibt/does_anyone_buy_exclusively_sector_etfs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/nodibt/does_anyone_buy_exclusively_sector_etfs/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 16:32:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been adding more of the X-Etf&amp;#39;s in the last month; XLF, XME, XLI, XLE, XLT, etc. I do own several stocks I have conviction about, but I&amp;#39;m thinking of trimming and going into more sector specific ETFs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is this completely pointless? Does it just make sense to just buy in SPY?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been able to out-perform SPY recently so I&amp;#39;m just curious if this is a complete waste of effort or what others opinions are. thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這是官方消息。美國新的covid-19病例已經下降到大流行開始以來的最低水平，比1月份的峯值下降了92%。🙏https://t.co/gOyJ2V41Fe]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1398994673708978179</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1398994673708978179</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 15:03:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[保留AMZN股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，夥計們，我想知道我是否應該繼續持有亞馬遜，或者我是否應該賣掉它。
並將這些錢重新投資於其他股票，如GOOGL或SMH。AMZN在過去幾個月一直
過去幾個月一直停滯不前，感覺我錯過了增長的機會，我應該
賣出AMZN還是持有它？根據CFRA的報告，AMZN是公平的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nnq8y8/keep_amzn_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nnq8y8/keep_amzn_stock/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 13:35:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey guys I was wondering if I should keep holding Amazon or if I should sell it and re invest that money into other stocks such as GOOGL or SMH. AMZN has been stagnant for the past few months, feel like I’m missing out on growth, should I sell AMZN or hold it? AMZN according to CFRA report is fair valued at 4,500$ approx, should I just hold and wait for the stock to jump? Have about 13 shares.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMC的市值爲160億美元，剛剛超過惠而浦。

去年的收入超過...
惠而浦$WHR: 205億美元
AMC: 4.49億美元

去年的淨收入...
$WHR: 13.6億美元
AMC: -29.8億美元

數據來自@ycharts https://t.co/A9jjwPtB1f]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1398273955794984967</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1398273955794984967</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 06:46:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[整個加密貨幣市場處於災難的懸崖邊上；北京的早晨即將到來*。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1398808288112881668</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1398808288112881668</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 04:42:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[菲利普-西摩-霍夫曼（Philip Seymour Hoffmann）因《波利來了》（Along Came Polly）和《我將死在這山上》（I will die on this hill）獲得奧斯卡最佳男配角獎，實至名歸

(它在Peacock上) https://t.co/GIgNM81B55]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1398481694525640707</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1398481694525640707</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 02:44:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMC成交量價格分析]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，交易員朋友們。今天，我將向你介紹一個關於AMC的非常強大的牛市案例。
這不是簡單地放一個火箭表情符號（順便說一句，我喜歡這個表情符號）就能解釋的。
順便說一下，我喜歡這個表情符號），或者因爲其他人在該股上發佈了一個強有力的YOLO賭注。以下是我的
基於成交量、價格走勢和強大的模式的分析...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nnriwg/amc_volume_price_analysis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nnriwg/amc_volume_price_analysis/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 02:44:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey fellow traders. Today, l’ll present to you a very strong bull case on AMC that is not explained by simply putting a rocket emoji (I love this emoji by the way) or because someone else posted a strong YOLO bet on the stock. Here is my analysis based on volume, price action, and a powerful pattern named the flag, high and tight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/5bruexp383271.png?width=570&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=f679d9584a983071eaf036df2e4c5be14069eaae&quot;&gt;Weekly chart&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Firstly on the weekly chart, we see a high tight flag that started developing from the low on January 5th at $1.91 (#1) to the high of the pattern which was achieved on January 27th at a staggering price of $20.36 (#2). In 17 trading days, the stock soared 1065.96%. It’s an understatement that this price action caught my attention. The following months saw the stock consolidate in a flag, high and tight on falling volume. Bulkowski studied this pattern extensively and it’s one of his favorites. HTF is characterised by a rise of at least 90% (aim for double) in less than 2 months followed by a consolidation period on ideally falling volume. I think we easily meet these criteria! The performance rank of this pattern in his work is 1 on 23 in a bull market (1 being the best) with an average rise of 69% and throwbacks happening 54% of the time. Price meets target 90% of the time. The measure rule helps us acquire a potential price target for this trade. In his work, Bulkowski tells us to measure the rise and project it 50% past the breakout point. With the measure rule, using the breakout point at $12, we would have a theoretical price target of $63.96 (1065.96/100/2*12)). Now to the analysis based on volume and price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the weekly chart, we have the breakout on #3 with rising and above average volume. This confirms the breakout is not fake, but supported by the professionals. After the minor pullback, we see the momentum exploding and the price action ripping past $20 on very high volume. Like we will see on the daily chart, the last trading day of the week saw some heavy selling which can be seen with the long upper wick on the weekly chart. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I attribute this to two things. First, the stock rose to overbought levels and a pullback was imminent. Two, the stock hit the ATH of around $35 and many market participants saw this as a good point to take profits.  While it is true the SI rose in this period, I do not believe shorts created this long upper wick. Seems more likely professionals were taking money off the table. This being said, I do not think we are witnessing a trend end since strong momentums like this one cannot be broken in a single day. Like a big cargo ship, it cannot be stopped simply by turning off the engine. More effort will be necessary to break this rocket for sure. On top of that, the most conservative assessment would bring us to $63.96 in less than 30 days (around June 10th) following the breakout and we have a 90% chance of hitting this target according to Bulkowski. If these are not good odds, I don’t know what is. I truly believe this is an opportunity of a lifetime!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/wslu122983271.png?width=570&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=0a1d2f718d41538d8bfad7ffad44ade99c796356&quot;&gt;Daily chart&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can see the flag, high and tight develop from January 27th on #2 to the breakout at #3 on May 13th. Developing this cause is important according to Wyckoff’s law of cause and effect. The development of a cause will be proportional to the subsequent effect. On May 14th (breakout day (#4)), we see rising and above average volume that confirms the start of a new trend. Then, the test of supply on the pullback at #5, we see falling volume until the stock reaches $12 which means there is no interest in selling at these prices. The rally resumes on very nice long white candles on steadily rising volume which means volume and price are in harmony fully supported by the great professionals. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the second to last candle, we see some selling happening as shown with the upper wick. On #6, we see a tall black candle that closes very close to the prior day’s close. I associate this candle with the bearish meeting lines candle. Bulkowski’s work establishes the candle to be a continuation pattern 51% of the time in a bull market, which is pretty much as valid as a coin toss. If the next day’s close is below this candle, Bulkowski tells us there is a 70% chance the candle acts as a reversal. So this is to be looked at closely for next week. The long upper wick and shorter lower wick associated with very high volume tells me there was more selling happening Friday by the professionals. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We must remember that stocks do not trend in a straight line. Volatility is cyclical, and all this is normal price action. Even in the event that Friday’s price action is stopping volume by the great professionals and the beginning of a distribution phase, Wyckoff’s work tells us this is associated with a potential preliminary supply and this stopping action ALWAYS fails and thus the rally WILL continue. Ladies and gents, I cannot stress enough how AMC is trading currently at a discount and any entry point is a good one at this point in time. We do not choose our seats on a rocket ship! You get in, strap on, and enjoy the ride! Trying to perfectly time the bottom on any pullback is a fool’s errand! Looking back at the daily chart on AMC, #1 (hanging man) and #3 (dark cloud cover) shows us that any bearish candle in the recent history of this stock is likely to be very short lived. Shorting this stock based on the bearish meeting lines (weak bearish candle by the way) would be a very dangerous endeavour indeed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/erdc846b83271.png?width=570&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=5ec91557abfecf685c4af681eaf68f0da6a1fd9b&quot;&gt;30 minutes chart&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, on the 30 minutes chart, friday we see at #1 strong buying pressure as seen with the long lower wick and high volume at $25.50. #2 was a retest on falling volume meaning falling interest to sell at this price. I do believe we have strong support at this level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No one has a crystal ball and this could go either way, but the odds are that we reach $63.96 by the end of June with a 90% probability according to Bulkowski. I am adding to my position at any dip in this stock. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/qbs706tc83271.png?width=570&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=8669186d98ef0792b216b50992969cd1d08fe785&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/qbs706tc83271.png?width=570&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=8669186d98ef0792b216b50992969cd1d08fe785&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If history is of any guide, I expect AMC to have a short consolidation period with falling volume like we saw with GME before the great run up. Thus, I believe we have another week to add to our positions before this really takes off. Any close above 35$ will be extremely bullish&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been reading many posts explaining the short squeeze potential and this adds to the excitement of a strong bull run in this stock way past $63.96. AMC is currently the most shorted stock in the market as we speak. Though I have doubts that AMC will reach 500k like many claim, I do believe we have a strong squeeze potential in this stock as shown by the candles and volume recently printed on the charts. Ultimately, volume and price will tell us when it is time to close our positions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheers,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;20$ 07/16C AMC&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;30$ 07/16C AMC&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Just to be clear, Bulkowski’s HTF gives us a 90% chance to hit the target in the next 30 days after the breakout. This target is his CONSERVATIVE target not MY target. I do NOT plan to sell at this target. I have no price target at this time since it could squeeze to 10k for all I know. More price action is needed to accurately assess a higher target.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在過去20年中，美國和國際SCV的表現都超過了它們的大盤指數。現在的標準普爾500指數非常昂貴，因爲有大盤增長的風險，它甚至比2000年還要昂貴。但今天美國和國際SCV的估值大致相同。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/nnu9x5/both_us_and_international_scv_outperformed_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/nnu9x5/both_us_and_international_scv_outperformed_their/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 02:44:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你認爲自己是一個投資人嗎？想象一下，"賣出 "按鈕在5年內都不存在。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你想做波段交易，試圖在空頭擠壓中套現，不管怎樣，那麼
好吧。你做你的。否則，如果你真的想投資，那麼讓我給你一個竅門，幫助你正確對待市場。
讓我給你一個技巧，幫助你正確對待市場......

想象一下，"賣出 "按鈕是灰色的，直到一個證券被持有了5
年。

 *...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nnzuwg/consider_yourself_an_investor_imagine_the_sell/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nnzuwg/consider_yourself_an_investor_imagine_the_sell/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 02:44:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you want to swing trade, try to cash out on short squeezes, whatever, then fine: You do you. Otherwise, if you actually want to &lt;em&gt;invest&lt;/em&gt;, then let me give you a trick to help you approach the market correctly...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Imagine that the &amp;quot;sell&amp;quot; button is greyed out until a security is held for 5 years.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;#39;ll be holding this for 5+ years, so the time and effort spent on research and DD is fully justified.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You won&amp;#39;t be &amp;quot;missing out&amp;quot; if you buy it tomorrow, or next week, or whenever you fully understand it and feel ready to commit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&amp;#39;s worth the commitment, so it&amp;#39;s completely reasonable to increase your position gradually over time (DCA).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Market dips are lame, but who cares? It&amp;#39;s not the 5d chart, it&amp;#39;s the 5y -- and it&amp;#39;s a 5y chart that has yet to be drawn.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are only three situations in which the &amp;quot;sell&amp;quot; button becomes available.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;During your research, you find something that makes you lose faith in the security (e.g., you discover something that makes you doubt the company&amp;#39;s leadership during an earnings report).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You discover a competing security that you wish you would have known about previously. In this case, &lt;em&gt;roll your investment over&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You absolutely, positively need the money for an emergency. You should have enough money on hand to be able to weather a storm, but there are some extraneous circumstances where you absolutely must liquidate investments. (If this happens more than once, it&amp;#39;s a sign that you do not have a sufficient emergency fund.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: I&amp;#39;m getting burned in the comments. Honestly, I&amp;#39;m not backing down -- this is good advice for the typical newbie. I also appreciate the thoughts people are sharing, no matter how critical they are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我越來越多地看到YT內容創作者在新的頻道上提供半懂不懂的股票投資分析。我稱其爲 "兄弟投資"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這些渠道開始蓬勃發展，雖然我很贊成增加非專業人士、YOLO者和所有其他業餘愛好者的參與。
雖然我贊成增加非專業人員、YOLO'ers和所有其他業餘人員的參與，但我認爲
但我認爲其中一些渠道弊大於利。這就像大量的半吊子的
營養和健身的人在YT上提供科學知識。這些金融...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nnyfep/more_and_more_i_see_yt_content_creators_with_new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nnyfep/more_and_more_i_see_yt_content_creators_with_new/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 02:44:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;These channels are starting to flourish, and while I’m all for increased participation by non-professionals, YOLO’ers, and all other amateurs, I think some of them do more harm than good. It’s a lot like the flood of half-assed nutritional and fitness guys offering broscience on YT. These financial bros I’m not sure are a great help to educating folks new to this movement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你通常的 "我不幹了！"的通話收益百分比是多少？]]></title><description><![CDATA[目前非常難過，我以450美元賣出了我的羅技7/16美元的看漲期權（250%的利潤）。
而不是目前的1200美元的價格。這種情況最近經常發生在我身上。
我知道我是個好孩子，但是在過去的3個月裏，我已經在桌子上留下了大約1.5萬美元的資金。
在過去的3個月裏，我保守地獲利。

你們都有...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nnx710/what_is_your_usual_im_out_percentage_gain_on_calls/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nnx710/what_is_your_usual_im_out_percentage_gain_on_calls/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 02:44:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currently very sad I sold my Logitech 7/16 $110 calls for $450 (250% profit) instead of the current $1200 price. This has happened a lot to me recently and I know I’m being a good boy, but FML I’ve left about 15k on the table in the last 3 months with my conservative profit taking. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you all have a specific target profit you look for before bailing on a call?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[加入船員隊伍]]></title><description><![CDATA[就像標題所說，我打算走Boglehead路線。我已經厭倦了壓力過大的
和所有試圖追逐個別股票的謊言。優秀的
但是，我已經厭倦了看，也厭倦了對優先股的壓力。
每隔5分鐘就對價格變化感到緊張。我只想做聰明的事。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/nnv574/joining_the_crew/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/nnv574/joining_the_crew/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 23:14:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like the title says, I’m gonna go the Boglehead route. Am tired of the stressed and all the BS trying to chase individual stocks. Nothing wrong with good DD/blue chips/ stuff you believe in but I am gosh darn tired of looking at and stressing over price changes every 5 min. Imma just make smart investments and use the time I spent worrying to work hard and get better at my job, rather then hope to basically win the lottery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[遷移到Boglehead投資組合已經完成。請告知分配的情況]]></title><description><![CDATA[我有一個超級風險的投資組合，並且正在將所有的東西轉移到
Boglehead風格的基金
[https://old.reddit.com/r/Bogleheads/comments/mnmzf5/my_portfolio_is_healing_transition_is_in_progress/]。
現在遷移已經完成，但由於我不想實現收益，所以我保留了
同樣的股票和...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/nnr5z0/migration_to_boglehead_portfolio_is_complete/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/nnr5z0/migration_to_boglehead_portfolio_is_complete/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 23:14:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had a super risky portfolio and was in &lt;a href=&quot;https://old.reddit.com/r/Bogleheads/comments/mnmzf5/my_portfolio_is_healing_transition_is_in_progress/&quot;&gt;the process of moving everything to Boglehead style funds&lt;/a&gt;. Now migration is completed but since I didn&amp;#39;t want to realize gains I kept the same stocks and just moved them to Fidelity.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is my current individual account:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/eox2lyba73271.png&quot;&gt;https://i.redd.it/eox2lyba73271.png&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand SPY and VOO are the same but I don&amp;#39;t want to realize any more gains this year. Already realized $500k due to IPO. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My question is, how do I calculate my allocations based on the 3 fund  portfolio philosophy and how do I balance it a bit more? I don&amp;#39;t have any bonds and not much international.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: 
more about me: 34 years old. Single. Expected income for the next 3 years ~$1.4m (IPO) then $450k. Planning to retire by 40. Saving aggressively. Spending $120k/yr. 401k: $110k. IRA: $100k. Real Estate $700k.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[關於蘋果的思考]]></title><description><![CDATA[股價今年仍然下跌6%，我想知道是否還有人在增加
添加更多。你們是怎麼想的？是否有任何重大的擔憂，人們正在
擔心，所以股價一直在130美元以下交易？我仍然認爲
股價將在年底前達到150美元。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nntgg0/thoughts_on_apple/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nntgg0/thoughts_on_apple/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 21:57:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The stock price is still down 6% ytd, I am wondering if anyone else is still adding more. What do you guys think? Is there any major concerns that people are worried about so the stock price keep trading under $130? I still think that the stock price will hit $150 before the end of the year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ARKK賣的是槓桿而不是阿爾法，他們的收費過高。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想了解你們對這個問題的看法，我只是在大聲思考，並歡迎不同的意見。
歡迎不同的意見!

看一下ARKK的年度百分位數回報（通過晨星，業績
與同行的百分位數）。)

2015: 第75位 2016年。第98位 2017年: 第1名 2018年。第17名 2019年：第57名 2020年：第1名 2021年：第100名

ARKK是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/nnv7be/arkk_sells_leverage_not_alpha_and_they_overcharge/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/nnv7be/arkk_sells_leverage_not_alpha_and_they_overcharge/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 21:19:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wanted to get all your thoughts on this, I’m just kind of thinking out loud and would welcome a different opinion!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking at ARKK annual percentile returns (via Morningstar, performance percentile vs peers):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2015: 75th 
2016: 98th 
2017: 1st 
2018: 17th 
2019: 57th 
2020: 1st 
2021: 100th&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ARKK is selling themselves as alpha generators, but they don’t consistently capture alpha. In fact, These kind of swings implies that the fund has excessive risk not excessive skill. Market does well, fund does great; market does poorly, fund tanks. Leverage is totally fine but it’s cheap, especially these days.  if they are just loading up on volatility then it’s not worth the management fee. You can get that on your own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Probably a lot of funds fall into this bucket….&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你必須把你所有的錢放在一家公司身上，讓它在100年後仍然存在。

你會選擇誰？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1398380353920905219</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1398380353920905219</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 20:52:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我想知道擠壓的感覺，所以我現在和你一起堅守着AMC到月亮🚀🚀。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nnqfmm/i_would_like_to_know_what_a_squeeze_feels_like_so/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nnqfmm/i_would_like_to_know_what_a_squeeze_feels_like_so/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 19:59:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[高通公司（QCOM）--熊市的情況是什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我很喜歡高通公司（QCOM）。我認爲他們的價值被極大地低估了，因爲他們目前的前景。
目前的前景，但也因爲他們的持續增長潛力和他們在5G市場上即將出現的優勢。
他們在5G市場上即將出現的優勢（我就不說了，這樣就不會被人
誤認爲是抽水馬桶的帖子）。)

基本上，我知道牛市的情況。I...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/nnr3pu/qualcomm_qcom_whats_the_bear_case/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/nnr3pu/qualcomm_qcom_whats_the_bear_case/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 19:59:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m big into Qualcomm ($QCOM). I think they’re massively undervalued for their currents prospects, but also for their continued growth potential and their upcoming superiority in the 5G market (I’ll leave it at that so this doesn’t get mistaken for a pump post).  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically, I know the bull case. I am long shares and I have LEAPs. But hoping someone can give me the bear case just so I know I’m not missing anything. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any and all thoughts welcome. Thank you in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在富達公司的羅斯IRA裏面買什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好，我將盡量保持簡短。最近收到了3萬塊錢，我想把它
通過富達公司把它放入羅斯IRA（已經有富達公司的賬戶，想把所有的東西放在一起）。
保持所有的東西在一起）。)

我將立即投入6千，一旦我被允許，將再投入6千。
允許再次投入，直到完全投入....]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/nnpds8/what_to_buy_inside_roth_ira_with_fidelity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/nnpds8/what_to_buy_inside_roth_ira_with_fidelity/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 19:59:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello I&amp;#39;ll try to keep this short. Recently received 30k and am looking to put it into a Roth IRA through Fidelity (already have fidelity account and want to keep everything together). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will be putting in 6k immediately and will put in another 6k as soon as I&amp;#39;m allowed again until fully invested. My question is what would be the best fund for aggressive growth? 31 years old and looking to set it and forget it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see people buying vanguard VTI through Fidelity but wondering what the best choice is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我認爲小米在物聯網領域有巨大的長期潛力--市值僅850億美元的科技巨頭]]></title><description><![CDATA[小米（HK: 1810）僅有11年曆史，直到2018年才上市--同年實現盈利。
同年，他們實現了盈利，但是他們是一個知名的品牌，已經在全球智能手機銷量中排名第三。
在全球智能手機銷售中排名第三。

幾天前，該公司發佈了一份相當邪惡的財報...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nnn1og/i_think_xiaomi_has_huge_long_term_potential_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nnn1og/i_think_xiaomi_has_huge_long_term_potential_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 15:44:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xiaomi (HK: 1810) is a mere 11 years old and didn&amp;#39;t go public until 2018 - the same year they turned profitable, yet the are a well known brand and already third in global smartphone sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few days ago the company delivered a pretty wicked &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.mi.com/en/2021/05/26/xiaomi-posts-record-results-as-2021-q1-revenue-and-profit-hit-historical-high-levels/&quot;&gt;earnings report&lt;/a&gt; with an adjusted net profit increase of 163%. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two days prior I wrote a &lt;a href=&quot;https://jesbaek.com/2021/05/23/xiaomis-future/&quot;&gt;piece&lt;/a&gt; of how their unique &amp;#39;AIoT&amp;#39; and &amp;#39;Internet Services&amp;#39; strategy will eventually allow the company to make much larger profits on revenue in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xiaomi commands one of the largest product portfolios with smart enabled devices of every category. In the West we don&amp;#39;t yet see their smartphones too often - but their robo vacuum cleaners and electric scooters (They own Ninebot and Segway) and other smart home equipment is everywhere. They are basically taking the opposite route of Google and Apple in providing the hardware before the software - which also means they currently have higher costs and lower return on revenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet they are already profitable and sit on a cash pile of 5.6 billion. About 60% of their revenue right now is however attributed to their smartphones - which are doing extremely well. Their phones receive high praise (though their Android fork is not liked by all) and offer unbeatable performance for the price. They do well in every price category and own several well known sub brands like Redmi, Poco and Blackshark. As an example Mrwhosetheboss (huge tech YT channel) picked Xiaomi brands for all top 3 spots for his best phones of 2021 out of 22.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xiaomi holds the top spot in market share in several emerging markets: India, Russia and most of Eastern Europe and soon South America. In Scandinavia where I live, they just recently entered local carrier stores, began advertising actively and opened a local &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mistore.dk&quot;&gt;official webshop&lt;/a&gt;. The ban on Huawei left a HUGE gap in the European market for Xiaomi to just freely gobble up and it seems like they are doing it. Xiaomi themselves have been &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.androidauthority.com/xiaomi-us-remove-blacklist-1224721/&quot;&gt;removed&lt;/a&gt; from a similar (but much less severe) blacklist by the US government this week as well. They do not pose the same threat as Huawei did, as they do not build infrastructure telecom equipment&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are rumors of the company designing their own SoCs (chips) in collaboration with OPPO and just last month they &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/30/chinas-xiaomi-to-launch-electric-car-business-and-invest-10-billion.html&quot;&gt;invested $10 billion&lt;/a&gt; into the Electric vehicle space. They already financially back Xpeng too and I think with the insane growth in the Chinese EV market they really have an opportunity to add even more value to their ecosystem integration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company is founded by Lei Jun and former Vice President of Google China and Zhou Gaungping then Senior Director at Motorola’s Beijing R&amp;amp;D Center. All three still lead the company today with Lei Jun as CEO. Xiaomi and their CEO has a huge following in China and a very dedicated loyal fan base. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company trades at a P/E of 23 and a share price of 28.6 HKD (~3.69 USD). The price to earnings is pretty typical for a tech stock but I think the benefits in profit of Xiaomi&amp;#39;s strategy and investments are yet to be seen. I began buying up a few months ago and just doubled my investment after the earnings report. I will continue to buy in over atleast the next year and truly think this is a case of a company working hard for the future and with the right strategy. I saw the same patterns in Microsoft 6 years ago when Sadya Nedella took over and that position I&amp;#39;m up over 500%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please let me know what you think and if you feel like there is anything you feel like I need to address. I&amp;#39;m really bullish on this company and it helps balance my portfolio with exposure towards Asia. I know Chinese stocks can be effy and at least for me it was also quite the challenge to find a brokage where I could buy them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[女士們，先生們，週末了。https://t.co/EubSCmPUEo]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1398622072490844161</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1398622072490844161</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 13:24:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對BABA的看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好。

BABA最近一直處於下降趨勢中，我想知道是否有其他人認爲這是一個
一個機會。在這個~200美元的區域，它非常吸引人。

你們怎麼看？有什麼我應該擔心的主要問題嗎？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nnl9c5/thoughts_on_baba/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nnl9c5/thoughts_on_baba/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 13:24:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi guys,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BABA has been in a downtrend lately, was wondering if anyone else sees this as an opportunity. It is very appealing in this ~200$ zone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you guys think? Any major concerns I should be worried about?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這波通貨膨脹不是由增長驅動的，而且剛剛開始]]></title><description><![CDATA[我將解釋我是如何得出這些結論的。
雖然對你們中的一些人來說，這可能是顯而易見的，但我認爲再次強調通貨膨脹的影響是很重要的。
通貨膨脹的影響。

通貨膨脹可以是好的、壞的或中性的。這背後的邏輯相當簡單。

如果通貨膨脹是由生產性增長驅動的，...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/nnk43e/this_inflation_wave_is_not_driven_by_growth_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/nnk43e/this_inflation_wave_is_not_driven_by_growth_and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 12:07:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m going to explain how I came to these conclusions, and although for some of you it may be obvious, I think that it is important to re-emphasize the effects of inflation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inflation can be good, bad or neutral. The logic behind this is pretty simple:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If inflation is driven by productive growth, it is good because the economy is benefiting. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If however, there is no real growth but money in circulation expands, than businesses will need to adjust their prices to match the stagnating purchasing power of consumers. This is bad because not everyone has the (pricing) power to adjust prices accordingly. In fact the people with the least pricing power are wage earners, hence an even bigger problem as people can&amp;#39;t afford to buy things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inflation can be much worse than this, but let&amp;#39;s focus on the current situation in the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this article &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thinkvalue.co/reports-tools/inflation-dashboard&quot;&gt;https://www.thinkvalue.co/reports-tools/inflation-dashboard&lt;/a&gt; I try to illustrate visually where we are in regards to inflation. My main points are these:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inflation is about to catch up with all the currency injecting the FED started doing in 2020&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are at the beginning of the inflation &amp;quot;wave&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our inflation is NOT driven by growth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wont schil for you to buy gold because there are also other investment strategies and commodities to look at, but if you didn&amp;#39;t get a chance, take a look at Damodaran&amp;#39;s recent video on inflation &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p0vqmjgF3E4&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p0vqmjgF3E4&lt;/a&gt; if you want to know which asset classes have &lt;em&gt;historically&lt;/em&gt; performed best during inflation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally I am not jumping on the gold wagon at least until I see next month&amp;#39;s CPI (release on 10th of June)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[100% VT與VTI + VXUS的對比]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近我看到很多人在推薦VTI+VXUS。我只是想知道
這不是和100%的VT幾乎一樣嗎？

爲什麼不選擇100%的VT以節省經紀人費用呢？

編輯：謝謝你的回答。然而，我想指出的是，經紀人
對我來說是不可避免的，因爲我來自東南部...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/nnh3vj/100_vt_vs_vti_vxus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/nnh3vj/100_vt_vs_vti_vxus/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 10:26:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lately I have seen a lot of people recommending VTI+ VXUS. I am just wondering isn&amp;#39;t it almost the same thing as 100% VT? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why not go 100% VT to save the broker fee?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Thanks for the response. However I would like to point out that the broker fee is inevitable for me as I am from South East Asia and invest through tradestation global (whitelabel of IBKR), I am paying 1.5usd per trade and no fractional share allowed. All the broker here has a fee and I can&amp;#39;t sign up for a Vanguard/fidelity. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Secondly there&amp;#39;s no capital gain tax in my country here. So I guess it doesn&amp;#39;t make much difference for me. The only benefit  for choosing VTI + VXUS is that I am able to customize the ratio of them when I feel like it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for answering my questions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[尋求幫助的起步 (23M)]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好! 我在做一些研究，而Boglehead的方法真的
與我產生了共鳴。我今年23歲，很快就會開始我的第一份工作。
不幸的是，我的父母在COVID期間去世了，但給我留下了一些錢。
我真的不想浪費他們的錢，爲自己準備...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/nn0b02/looking_for_help_starting_out_23m/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/nn0b02/looking_for_help_starting_out_23m/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 10:26:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone! I was doing some research and the Boglehead approach really resonated with me. I am 23 years old and will be starting my first job soon. Unfortunately, my parents passed away during COVID, but left me with some money. I really do not want to waste their money and prepare myself for retirement. Current plan is to throw my money into my company&amp;#39;s Roth 403b to max the 5% match and then throw some money into a Roth IRA. I guess these are my non-taxable accounts. I guess my question is, with my inheritance would it be best to just open a Vanguard account and throw it all into VTSAX? This is my taxable account? Thank you so much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[它已經開始了]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nnh1lx/it_has_begun/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nnh1lx/it_has_begun/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 09:34:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[公牛在遊行!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nn27e9/bulls_on_parade/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nn27e9/bulls_on_parade/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 07:11:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我們都能感受到的迪普...]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nn2ese/the_dip_we_all_can_relate_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nn2ese/the_dip_we_all_can_relate_to/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 07:11:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天的WSB討論]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nnb4d1/wsb_discussion_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nnb4d1/wsb_discussion_today/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 07:11:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你的盡職調查標準是什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想，當我們大多數人開始投資的時候，情況是這樣的：買入很酷的股票，買入代表理想的股票，買入你認爲合適的股票。
購買很酷的股票，購買代表理想的股票，購買你認爲好的企業的股票
購買你認爲是好企業的股票，學習收益，學習市盈率。
學習一系列的比率，學習財務知識......。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/nnb85e/what_is_your_due_diligence_criteria/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/nnb85e/what_is_your_due_diligence_criteria/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 07:11:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I assume when most of us started investing, it went something like; buying the cool stock, buying a stock that represents an ideal, buying a stock of what you think is a good business, learning about earnings, learning about the PE ratio, learning about a bunch of ratios, learning about financial statements, learning about how to read financial statements, copying a famous investors criteria, and so on until eventually you have your own set of metrics and criteria.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you guys look for?
What is your criteria and this scenario and your criteria in that scenario?
What metrics do you focus on?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼我喜歡$STIC即將成爲$BARK aka BarkBox 風險範圍是7美元到30美元。]]></title><description><![CDATA[披露我擁有10.5美元的股票。

BarkBox是一個spac，今天批准了合併。股票代碼$stic將變成$bark
6月2日。

許多這樣的訂閱盒公司得到了不好的聲譽，因爲有
許多雜貨公司多年來虧損數十億，而寵物公司沒有賺到錢
因爲...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/nn4wvf/why_i_like_stic_soon_to_be_bark_aka_barkbox_risk/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/nn4wvf/why_i_like_stic_soon_to_be_bark_aka_barkbox_risk/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 05:38:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclosure I own shares at $10.50. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BarkBox is a spac that today approved the merger. The Ticker $stic will be $bark on June 2nd.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many of these subscription box companies get a bad reputation because there were so many grocery ones that lose billions for years and the pet ones made no money because all they did was get existing products and package them where the margins were horrible. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, barkbox is different. They own all of the products they put in the box, we call that vertically integrated. Have a retail store and sell the products at target and other online and offline stores. So, given the higher Margins, vertical integration, new revenue channels and fast growth I think the valuation should be more expensive than chewy on a price to sales multiple. Lets not discount that the subscription model will evolve over time churn is around 5% to 6% which is excellent. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company actually has a few revenue channels: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;buy subscription (you can customize as well), &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;add on products to the box, &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;dental (medical and preventative is new and will grow), &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;meal plan (sends you monthly box of daily meals; crazy but people/dogs can be picky about food), &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ecommerce/retail where they sell the products on amazon, pet stores etc. this is an interesting business because it is not just ecommerce or subscription because they own a lot of the products they sell as their brand where they have exclusive supplychain and distribution agreements. They also have licensing with plush toys with NBA (example). They realized customers are crazy and treat dogs like people so do stuff accordingly. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No doubt they will sell clothes, costumers, more medical stuff like fleak tick products to help keep the customes within the ecosystem. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ceo is actually new started in september 2020 and has options priced at $16 a share. He came from amazon and ebay and before that consultant at infosys. I think the management hire was an excellent decision as it allows then to scale their ecommerce business and get new customers into the ecosystem via subscriptions or not. I see the subscription revenue as potentially amazon prime stuff where people will just fill it up with what they need and not just junk all the time and people will be happy with that and some add-ons here and there. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pet business is a fantastic long-term business as boomers age, etc. strategy for this is to buy and either hold or sell when it hits $20 to $30 if there becomes too much hype. This range of valuation is based in Price to Sales. The bottom I used was 2 times given Its growth rate and almost double the gross margin of chewy and even pet supermarket stores. The guidance for this year has room for upside &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I built a ten year model and see then becoming profitable by 2023, however, all of their cash flow is going into growing the business as I think they can sustain a 30% revenue per year for a few years. I do think there are some potential risks such that the Barkeats business could do poorly if the pricing is not competitive or people change the product mix of the box to less profitable products or cancel all together. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested in hearing your thoughts on this below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[結婚後你的人均支出是否會減少？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我目前是單身（20多歲），正在計劃我的財務未來。我希望的一個重大生活變化是結婚。
我希望能有一個大的改變，那就是結婚，這在稅收上有好處，而且我相信會有
一些 "規模經濟 "的好處。

我知道這取決於任何生活方式的改變（如生孩子等）。
但你是否有任何...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/nn6dou/do_your_expenses_per_person_decrease_when_married/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/nn6dou/do_your_expenses_per_person_decrease_when_married/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 03:26:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m currently single (late 20s), and planning my financial future.  One big life change I hope to have is getting married, which has tax benefits, and I&amp;#39;m sure some &amp;quot;economies of scale&amp;quot; benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know this is dependent on any lifestyle changes (such as having kids, etc.), but do you have any guidance and &amp;quot;rules of thumb&amp;quot; on what I should expect my expenses should be after marriage?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是今天星期五，2021年5月28日的市場回顧]]></title><description><![CDATA[心理市場回顧 - 2021年5月28日，星期五

週五股市上漲，市場參與者受到新的經濟數據的鼓舞。
市場參與者受到消費者支出、收入和通貨膨脹方面的新經濟數據，以及強勁的每週失業報告的鼓舞。
失業報告。市場已經取得了顯著的復甦，特別是在
技術方面，在市場...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nn7etx/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_friday_may_28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/nn7etx/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_friday_may_28/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:25:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Friday, May 28, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks gained on Friday, with market participants encouraged by new economic data on consumer spending, income and inflation, and a strong Weekly unemployment report. The market has made a remarkable recovery, particularly in technology, after the market tumbled 4% following the April Consumer Price Index roughly two weeks ago. In my view, as I have said for weeks, the recovery in the market confirms that the initial sell-off driven by inflationary fears forcing the Federal Reserve to tighten monetary policy sooner than expected was overblown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New government data on Friday showed personal income fell less than expected in April, but still pulled back after March&amp;#39;s stimulus-fueled surge. Personal income fell by 13.1% in April compared to March, less than the 14.2% drop expected. This follows a 20.9% increase during March which had been buoyed by the distribution of $1,400 stimulus checks to most Americans. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In another report, the Department of Commerce reported core personal consumption expenditures increased 3.1% in April from a year earlier, blowing past the Fed’s traditional 2% target. Federal Reserve members consider the core PCE to be the gauge of inflation. The strong inflation readings reported by the Commerce Department on Friday had been widely anticipated as the pandemic&amp;#39;s grip eases, thanks to vaccinations, and will have no impact on monetary policy. Fed Chair Jerome Powell has repeatedly stated that higher inflation will be transitory. Supply-chain constraints combined, labor shortages in certain industries, and rising demand as the US economy recovers from the coronavirus-induced recession have all contributed to higher inflationary readings. These are all factors that are widely considered transitory, meaning not permanent. In an April 28 statement, Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell said, “An episode of one-time price increases as the economy reopens is not likely to lead to persistent year-over-year inflation into the future. Clogged supply-chains won’t affect Federal Reserve policy because they’re temporary and expected to resolve themselves.” Moreover, he said “For inflation to move up in a persistent way that moves expectations up, that would take some time, and you would think it would be likely we would be in very strong employment for that to happen.” In other words, Powell is saying he expects issues driving inflation higher to resolve themselves moving forward and doesn’t expect inflationary pressures to materialize until the labor market further improves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In remarks this week, members of the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC), reiterated their stance that they were not yet concerned that new inflation data would force the Fed to tighten monetary policy sooner than expected. St. Louis Federal Reserve President James Bullard said he believed increases in inflation would be “mostly temporary” and that the Fed was “not quite there yet” when it came to discussing tapering its asset purchase program. In separate comments, Kansas City Federal Reserve President Esther George said she did not want the Fed to be “overly reliant on historical relationships and dynamics in judging the outlook for inflation.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Richard Clarida, Vice Chairman of the Fed, offered a slightly different view but one that is in-line with what the Federal Reserve has already said publicly in the past. Clarida said, “there will come a time in upcoming meetings” when the Fed would consider tapering the asset purchase program but that “it is going to depend on the flow of data”. The Fed is currently buying $120 billion a month in government-issued and government-backed securities, and has pledged to continue doing that until the economy is more fully recovered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This reaffirms the market that the Fed is not on a set timeline when it comes to rolling back current accommodative policies and will, as they have said time and again, wait for concrete data before any considerations are made. This follows a similar statement from Jerome Powell back in April 14, which proves market participants shouldn’t worry about quantitative easing tapering, in my opinion. Powell said, “We will reach the time at which we will taper asset purchases when we have made substantial further progress towards our goals from last December. That would in all likelihood be before, well before, the time we would consider raising interest rates. We have not voted on that order but that is the sense of the guidance.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Department of Labor’s Weekly Unemployment Report showed jobless claims fell for the fourth straight week to yet another pandemic-era low, an encouraging sign that the labor market is improving following the extremely disappointing April Jobs report, which showed 266,000 new jobs added in the month, far below estimated of more than 1 million and a sharp deceleration in job growth compared to March. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Initial jobless claims, week ended May 22:&lt;/strong&gt; 406,000 vs. 425,000 expected and 444,000 the week prior&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continuing claims, week ended May 15:&lt;/strong&gt; 3.642 million vs. 3.680 million expected and a revised 3.738 the week prior&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Meme-stocks”, particularly AMC, were absolutely on fire this week, as the battle between wallstreetbets and hedge funds continues. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;President Joe Biden unveiled a budget that would hike federal spending to $6 trillion for the coming fiscal year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Boeing (BA) agreed to pay at least $17 million to settle enforcement cases with the Federal Aviation Administration over production issues with its 737 jets. Stock reacted positively to the news. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Durable goods orders, or orders for manufactured goods intended to last at least three years, unexpectedly declined in April, ending an 11-month streak of increases, the Commerce Department said Thursday, an encouraging sign. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amazon (AMZN), Microsoft (MSFT) and Alphabet (GOOG, GOOGL) are all involved in a bidding process to provide cloud services to Boeing, according to multiple reports. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disney’s (DIS) California-based parks will welcome non-California natives starting June 15.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current price target was written pre-market and does not reflect intraday changes*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AutoDesk (ADSK) target raised by Barclays from $335 to $340 at Overweight. Stock currently around $287&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Burlington Stores (BURL) with a host of target raises. Average price target $365 at Overweight. Stock currently around $325&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Costco (COST) with three target raises. Stock currently around $388

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Barclays from $400 to $450&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stifel Nicolaus from $390 to $410 &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Telsey Advisory Group from $395 to $415&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salesforce (CRM) with three target raises after crushing earnings. Stock currently around $226

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mizuho from $270 to $290&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Barclays from $276 to $285 &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Moness, Crespi &amp;amp; Hardt $275 to $290&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dell Technologies (DELL) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $127 to $130 at Overweight. Stock currently around $100&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dollar General (DG) target raised by Citigroup from $250 to $260 at Buy. Stock currently around $205&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medtronic (MDT) with two target raises. stock currently around $125

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deutsche Bank from $134 to $149 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oppenheimer from $134 to $147 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ulta Beauty (ULTA) with a host of target raises after crushing earnings. Average price target $400 at Buy. Stock currently around $328&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“To bear trials with a calm mind robs misfortune of its strength and burden.” - Seneca&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YOLO AMC全員參與! 敬月亮！🚀🚀🚀🚀🌕🌕🌕。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nn4spa/yolo_amc_all_in_to_the_moon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nn4spa/yolo_amc_all_in_to_the_moon/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:25:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[沒有白銀空頭擠壓發生。沒有。永遠不會。]]></title><description><![CDATA[白銀可能會在一段時間內很好地上漲，但不要對希望太高，這是不可能的。
這不是要去在100s。

https://twitter.com/michaeljburry/status/1356111612759789568

> 白銀市場的一個角落以前就被嘗試過--我們要清楚，那就是
> 就是現在正在嘗試的。在1980年，一個規...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nn36fw/there_is_no_silver_short_squeeze_happening_none/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nn36fw/there_is_no_silver_short_squeeze_happening_none/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 23:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Silver might go up nicely and for a time but don&amp;#39;t get high on hopium, this is not gonna go in the 100s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/michaeljburry/status/1356111612759789568&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/michaeljburry/status/1356111612759789568&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A corner in the silver market has been tried before - and let&amp;#39;s be clear, that is what is being attempted now.  In 1980, a rule change by the government destroyed the corner.  #silverthursday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.britannica.com/topic/Silver-Thursday&quot;&gt;https://www.britannica.com/topic/Silver-Thursday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Silver Thursday, the dramatic fall in the price of silver on March 27, 1980, following the Hunt brothers’ attempt to corner the market on the metal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apart from a handful of reigning monarchs and despots, Nelson Bunker Hunt (1926–2014) was the richest man in the world at the start of the 1960s. Like his father, the legendary oilman H. L. Hunt, Bunker gambled big and got lucky. By 1970, although his wealth was accumulating faster than he could spend it, he foresaw a volatile economic future. Prevented by Franklin Roosevelt’s 1933 prohibition on U.S. citizens owning gold, Bunker and his younger brother William Herbert (b. 1929) chose silver, then standing at $1.50 per ounce, as their speculative hedge. Their initial caution vanished after Colonel Muammar al-Qaddafi nationalized the Bunkers’ Libyan oil fields in 1973. Furious, and paranoid that paper money would soon be worthless, the Hunt brothers then bought futures contracts on 55 million ounces of silver, eventually accumulating an estimated 100 million ounces of the precious metal. But instead of selling the contracts like normal commodity traders, they took delivery of the bullion and chartered three Boeing 707s to air-freight it to Switzerland.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By 1979, they had engineered a genuine shortage of the metal. The Hunts owned $4.5 billion-worth of shiny, glittering silver, safely stashed in Swiss vaults. Still the price climbed, until on January 17, 1980, an ounce cost $49.45. Such rampant speculation and profits triggered new government oversight, prompting the Federal Reserve to suspend trading in silver. The boom was suddenly over, but the Hunts still had to honour contracts to buy at prices over $50. The day the market plunged—March 27—silver fell to $10.80, the metal’s biggest single collapse. Upon losing some $1.7 billion, prompting Bunker to quip, “A billion dollars isn’t what it used to be,” the Hunts had become the (then) greatest debtors in financial history, and though New York banks allowed them $1.1 billion credit towards clearing their obligations, they were personally bankrupted and later convicted of illegally trying to corner the market on the precious metal; the brothers were fined $10 million each, in addition to the millions they owed to the IRS, and banned from future trading on the commodities market. The Hunts had gambled that silver was undervalued, but they failed because they had made the price of silver too attractive for its own good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To pay off his staggering debt, Bunker was forced to sell off his beloved stable of thoroughbred horses, three of whom were named Extravagant, Goofed, and Overdrawn. William Herbert remained a billionaire into the 21st century. The character of J. R. Ewing in the original TV series Dallas (1978–91) and the Duke Brothers in the movie Trading Places (1983) all drew inspiration from the Hunt family and their larger-than-life careers and personalities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[期權交易的10條戒律]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 1.  你應始終採取100%的每日收益或200%的所有時間收益。
 2.  2.不要陷入誘惑，不要在開市的前30分鐘內買入。
     開盤時買入。賣出頭寸仍是允許的）。
 3.  3.不得在綠日買入看漲期權。
 4.  4.不得在紅日買入看跌期權。
 5.  5.避免...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nn268r/10_commandments_of_options_trading/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nn268r/10_commandments_of_options_trading/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 22:55:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thou shall always take 100% daily gains or 200% all time gains.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not fall into temptation and buy during the first 30 minutes of market open. (Selling positions is still permitted)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thou shall not buy calls on green days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thou shall not buy puts on red days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid greed and do not buy consecutive options on 1 company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Give thyself at least 3 weeks time to play the option.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;End your suffering and sell if down 50% all time on an option play.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid gluttony and do not day trade options. (Unless it interferes with #1 and #7, Swing trades allowed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be fruitful, multiply earnings and sell covered calls if holding any.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Celebrate and binge drink after big gains (or losses)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bb]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nmvnmr/bb/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/nmvnmr/bb/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 22:55:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>