<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 07:55:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[$PLTR 美國空軍新合同]]></title><description><![CDATA["加利福尼亞州帕洛阿爾託的Palantir USG Inc.獲得了一份價值32,500,000美元的固定價格合同。
的固定價格合同，爲兩個獨立的任務領域提供數據即服務平臺。
額外的任務領域提供數據即服務平臺。第一個是 "棕鷺項目"，該項目擁有
Palantir Gotham平臺被配置爲自動攝取來自...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n2468b/pltr_new_us_air_force_contract/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n2468b/pltr_new_us_air_force_contract/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 23:26:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Palantir USG Inc., Palo Alto, California, has been awarded a $32,500,000 firm-fixed-price contract that provides data-as-a-service platform for two separate mission areas. The first is the Project Brown Heron effort that has the Palantir Gotham platform configured to automatically ingest data from across the Department of the Air Force (DAF) that continually push personnel, equipment, planning, health, and other readiness data sources into their common data foundation. This readiness information is a critical component to DAF-wide COVID-19 analysis and decision making. The second is to provide mission-critical space situational awareness and command and control capabilities to operational users at the National Space Defense Center and the Combined Space Operations Center. Work will be performed in Palo Alto, California, and is expected to be completed Nov. 30, 2021. This award is the result of a sole-source acquisition. Fiscal 2021 operation and maintenance funds in the amount of $12,857,144; and fiscal 2021 research, development, test and evaluation funds in the amount of $4,000,000 are being obligated at the time of award. Space and Missile Systems Center, Los Angeles Air Force Base, California, is the contracting activity (FA8806-21-C-0010).&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.defense.gov/Newsroom/Contracts/Contract/Article/2591938/&quot;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[提醒大家考慮獲取一些利潤。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你在未來12個月以上都持有你的股票，那麼請不要理會這篇文章。

這不是關於微型股（投機性遊戲），而是關於大型股
公司。我意識到電動車、雜草和微型股有多受打擊（儘管它們本週確實
本週反彈了）。) 我們正處於季度末。大盤股和小盤股都是如此。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n1xnv9/reminder_to_think_about_taking_some_profits/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n1xnv9/reminder_to_think_about_taking_some_profits/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 21:15:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are holding your shares for the next 12+ months then disregard this post. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is less about micro caps (speculative plays) and more about the large cap companies. I realize how beat up EV, weed and micro caps are (though they did bounce this week).  We are at the quarter end. The big earnings week is coming to a close. Earnings were &amp;quot;as expected&amp;quot; even though the spin is &amp;quot;exceeded expectations.&amp;quot; The expectation of investors was that these companies would exceed expectations which is why the beginning of the month had so many buyers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is going to be selling pressure over the next few days (maybe weeks). Lots of people sell after earnings simply because they don&amp;#39;t want to hold for another three months and there are no positive catalysts in the near term to move the stock. This doesn&amp;#39;t mean the company did anything wrong but the share price does come down. If there are enough buyers on the sidelines the prices won&amp;#39;t move much but there will definitely be an increase of sellers out of some positions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moving on to next quarter. There are a lot of supply issues and increased costs that many companies noted in their earning calls. We all know about the semi-conductor issue. Raw material costs are approaching all time highs in many sectors. Companies are raising their sale prices. The full impact of these issues won&amp;#39;t be fully realized until the next earnings call but in preparation for that people are moving out of some of those stocks that they feel are most vulnerable. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also of note, as many in this forum have noted, the investments made over the &amp;quot;Covid crash&amp;quot; are now at their &amp;quot;long term&amp;quot; status and profit taking due to this will occur (is occurring) as well. &amp;quot;Sell in May and go away&amp;quot; is a load of crap but many people know the saying and CNBC (among others) will be using it liberally. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are just facts I am pointing out that are working against the market in the near term. It is your decision whether it matters or not to you. Among this will also be the &amp;quot;jobs, inflation, rate hike, covid, stimulus, etc&amp;quot; drama over the next few weeks (as is the usual). That can go either way and nobody knows anything for sure. There will definitely be a lot of reporting about summer travel after Covid! This will boost the re-opening plays from time to time. Also the infrastructure package will be a talking point to look forward to. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR There will be selling pressure over the next couple of weeks which could escalate if there are not enough buyers rushing in quick enough. These buyers would hold off if &amp;quot;bad news&amp;quot; comes out during that time which would push share prices lower. There is definitely quite a bit of cash waiting for a buying opportunity but that usually takes an 8-10% correction to move in. It will recover over time (as always) but if you were looking to sell in the next few months there is nothing wrong with taking SOME profit at this level. If you are in it for over a year disregard this post. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not telling you what to do. I am reminding you to think about what to do. You are responsible for your own decisions. Good luck out there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[所有在#GME]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n1z8yy/all_in_gme/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n1z8yy/all_in_gme/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 20:27:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[點亮他們]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n205h8/light_em_up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n205h8/light_em_up/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 20:27:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[致向向我介紹這支股票並寫出有說服力的DD的WSB墮落者。去你的，謝謝你的教訓。我的起始成本基礎是10.50美元，我降了三倍。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n1xtux/to_the_wsb_degenerate_who_introduced_me_to_this/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n1xtux/to_the_wsb_degenerate_who_introduced_me_to_this/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 20:27:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美國的個人收入在去年增長了29%，是歷史上最高的增幅。https://t.co/fw9Ef0zSvZ]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1388177279981871104</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1388177279981871104</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 19:41:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[B.Riley將Cleveland Cliffs (CLF)的評級調高至33美元！Biden Infra計劃之後]]></title><description><![CDATA[B. Riley將Cleveland-Cliffs的目標價從24美元上調至33美元，並更新了長期的
價格假設，保持買入評級。

04/30/2021 (MT Newswires) -- (MT Newswires報道了來自北美、亞洲各大銀行和研究機構的股票、商品和經濟研究。
報道了北美、亞洲和歐洲的主要銀行和研究機構的股票、商品和經濟研究。
研究...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n1ubal/cleveland_cliffs_clf_rating_upgraded_by_b_riley/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n1ubal/cleveland_cliffs_clf_rating_upgraded_by_b_riley/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 19:03:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;B. Riley Raises Cleveland-Cliffs&amp;#39; PT to $33 from $24 After Updating Long-term Price Assumptions on Commodities, Keeps Buy Rating&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;04/30/2021 (MT Newswires) -- (MT Newswires covers equity, commodity and economic research from major banks and research firms in North America, Asia and Europe. Research providers may contact us here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mtnewswires.com/contact-us&quot;&gt;https://www.mtnewswires.com/contact-us&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Price: 17.09, Change: -0.30, Percent Change: -1.73&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME回到了菜單上，3.3萬美元YOLO。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n1xp4r/gme_is_back_on_the_menu_33k_yolo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n1xp4r/gme_is_back_on_the_menu_33k_yolo/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 18:39:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴倫週刊》的這篇文章可能解釋了特斯拉今天的突然飆升。特斯拉股價走高，因爲銷售和交付量可能超出預期]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.barrons.com/articles/earnings-lift-restaurant-brands-its-ceo-says-its-a-post-pandemic-growth-story-51619801175

最近幾天，一波悲觀情緒傷害了特斯拉[https://www.barrons.com/quote/TSLA]
股價在最近幾天可能開始消退。

電動汽車公司的股價已經開始下跌。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/n1z80f/this_barrons_article_might_explain_teslas_sudden/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/n1z80f/this_barrons_article_might_explain_teslas_sudden/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 18:39:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/earnings-lift-restaurant-brands-its-ceo-says-its-a-post-pandemic-growth-story-51619801175&quot;&gt;https://www.barrons.com/articles/earnings-lift-restaurant-brands-its-ceo-says-its-a-post-pandemic-growth-story-51619801175&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A wave of pessimism that has hurt  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/quote/TSLA&quot;&gt;Tesla&lt;/a&gt;  stock in recent days may be starting to recede. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stock in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/tesla-could-save-the-auto-business-by-disrupting-it-heres-how-51614442967?mod=article_inline&quot;&gt;electric-vehicle&lt;/a&gt;  pioneer was on its way to a fourth consecutive daily decline when the  shares turned around in midday trading Friday. Two factors—both related  to 2021 performance—may be making investors more upbeat heading into  May.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla (ticker: TSLA) stock started out the week at about $729  and closed Monday at $738.20, ahead of the company’s first-quarter &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/teslas-earnings-ticked-all-the-boxes-big-questions-remain-51619469933?mod=article_inline&quot;&gt;earnings report&lt;/a&gt; that afternoon. Earnings were higher than Wall Street expected, but questions about the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/teslas-earnings-were-a-gift-to-doubters-a-fine-result-wasnt-good-enough-51619539342?mod=article_inline&quot;&gt;quality&lt;/a&gt;  of the reported earnings—the degree to which trading in Bitcoin and  sales of regulatory credits for producing zero-emission cars lifted the  number–sent the stock lower. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/tesla-stock-headline-headaches-wall-street-weighs-in-51619449789?mod=article_inline&quot;&gt;Lingering concern&lt;/a&gt; over a recent crash of a Tesla vehicle in Texas dragged on the price too.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The  stock opened Friday at about $668, $71 lower than Monday’s close, and  down 1.4% from Thursday’s final level. By early afternoon, though,  shares were up about $43, or 6.5%,  from the daily low, at $709.55. The  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/quote/SPX&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/a&gt;  and  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/quote/DJIA&quot;&gt;Dow Jones Industrial Average&lt;/a&gt;, for comparison, were each down about 0.6%.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The  stock-price bounce might just be a relief rally marking the end of the  post-earnings selling spree. But two bits of news, both communicated via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/quote/TWTR&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; (TWTR), appear to be at work as well.    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New Street Research analyst &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/tesla-stock-can-hit-1-200-analyst-says-51602108860?mod=article_inline&quot;&gt;Pierre Ferragu&lt;/a&gt; tweeted out Thursday that  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/quote/STM&quot;&gt;STMicroelectronics&lt;/a&gt; (STM) believes its revenues from sales of silicon carbide will  hit $550 million in 2021. The company said as much on its April 29  earnings conference call. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It matters because according to  Ferragu, STMicro is Tesla’s sole supplier of silicon carbide,. He says  Tesla accounts for 80% of the company’s silicon-carbide sales, and that  sales of $550 million imply Tesla would produce as many as 1 million  vehicles.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wall Street is looking for 800,000 Tesla deliveries in 2021. A million vehicles would be an enormous surprise. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/nikola-stock-tesla-electric-trucks-manufacturing-hydrogen-elon-musk-trevor-milton-gary-black-51591908953?mod=article_inline&quot;&gt;Gary Black&lt;/a&gt;, an influential market watcher, also tweeted out something he uncovered in Tesla’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/tesla-notes-a-new-risk-quarterly-report-51619640537?mod=article_inline&quot;&gt;recent 10-Q&lt;/a&gt; quarterly filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the filing, Black noted, Tesla’s board of directors said it  is “probable” that Tesla’s annualized sales will hit $55 billion, a  milestone that would trigger the grant of stock options to CEO        Elon Musk.        &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wall Street analysts believe Tesla’s 2021 sales will be  less than $50 billion, so a figure of $55 billion would be a second  enormous surprise for investors. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Black  is a former Wall Street analyst and money manager who has amassed  almost 74,000 followers tweeting about stocks, including Tesla. Ferragu,  for his part, rates Tesla share at Buy and has a $900 price target for  the stock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$NAPA - 估值爲折價]]></title><description><![CDATA[我通過一個低市盈率篩選器發現了這隻股票，並意識到我已經熟悉他們的許多產品。
熟悉他們的許多產品。他們從事酒精飲料
業，擁有葡萄園，並生產廣泛的葡萄酒品牌組合，在50個國家銷售。
國家銷售。我是德科的忠實粉絲，因爲他們生產價格便宜但...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/n1ttyy/napa_valued_at_a_discount/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/n1ttyy/napa_valued_at_a_discount/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 18:00:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I came across this stock via a low PE screener and realized that I am already familiar with many of their products. They&amp;#39;re in the alcoholic beverages industry, own vineyards, and produce a wide portfolio of wine brands sold in 50 countries. I&amp;#39;m a big fan of Decoy for producing cheaply priced but great tasting reds. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They had their IPO last month and their price seems to be stabilizing after yoyoing between $16-20. Facts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Market Cap: $2.1b&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares: $18.58&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PEG: 0.01&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PE: 0.04&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This seems like an absolute steal. Competitors in the beverages industry have an average PE of 32.5 and PEG of 0.05 (per TD Ameritrade analytics, anyway). Its a profitable company that has great margins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The primary downside is their tiny market share in a competitive industry. In 2020, their total revenue was $270mil, versus the industry total of $326&lt;strong&gt;bil&lt;/strong&gt; (0.08%). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What else am I missing? Why is $NAPA valued at such a discount?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Edit&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bad data. Thanks for the replies, everyone. I actually checked the PE data on three different sources but they all said the same thing. I should&amp;#39;ve known. &amp;quot;When it sounds too good to be true, it usually is...&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[接種了Covid-19疫苗/1個以上劑量的人口百分比...
以色列：62
英國：51%。
美國：43
匈牙利：40%。
加拿大: 32%
德國: 27%
西班牙: 25%
法國: 24%
意大利：22
波蘭：22
愛爾蘭：21
土耳其：16
阿根廷: 15%
巴西: 15
墨西哥: 10%
印度: 9%
俄羅斯: 8%
韓國: 5%
日本：2%。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1388118727275601925</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1388118727275601925</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 17:22:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[第一季度收入增長，同比百分比變化...
特斯拉 $TSLA: +73.6
蘋果公司 $AAPL: +53.6
Facebook $FB: +47.5%
亞馬遜 $AMZN: +43.8
谷歌 $GOOGL: +34.4
Netflix $NFLX: +24.1%
微軟 $MSFT: +19.1%
S&amp;P 500 $SPY: +5.6%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1388176386670596100</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1388176386670596100</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 17:22:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[肯-格里芬獲得保證金調用的機會]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n1ucaz/ken_griffin_gets_margin_called/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n1ucaz/ken_griffin_gets_margin_called/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 15:28:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我分析了自2013年以來所有Motley Fool Premium的建議，並將其與S&P500的回報率作爲基準。下面是結果!]]></title><description><![CDATA[序言。這是沒辦法的事。我們絕大多數的Redditors絕對
討厭The Motley Fool。我覺得這是有道理的，因爲他們的點擊率標題
或 "5只不能錯過的世紀股票"，或將1,000篇文章變成100,000篇文章
目的只是爲了給他們的網站帶來流量。另一位Redditor...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n1t0yz/i_analyzed_all_the_motley_fool_premium/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n1t0yz/i_analyzed_all_the_motley_fool_premium/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 14:47:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preamble:&lt;/strong&gt; There is no way around it. A vast majority of us Redditors absolutely hate The Motley Fool. I feel that it’s justified, given their clickbait titles or “5 can&amp;#39;t miss stocks of the century” or turning 1,000 into 100,000 posts designed just to drive traffic to their website. Another Redditor summed it up perfectly with this,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/&quot;&gt;r/wallstreetbets&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/&quot;&gt;r/stocks&lt;/a&gt; can agree on one thing, it’s that Motley Fool is utter trash&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that that’s out of the way, let’s come to my hypothesis. There are more than 1 million paying subscribers for Motley Fool’s premium subscription. This implies that they are providing some sort of value that encouraged more than 1MM customers to pay up. They have claimed on their website that they have 4X’ed the S&amp;amp;P500 returns over the last 19 years. I wanted to check if this claim is due to some statistical trickery or some outlier stocks which they lucked out on or was it just plain good recommendations that beat the market. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically, &lt;strong&gt;What I wanted to know was this - Would you have been able to beat the market if you had followed their recommendations?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where is the data from:&lt;/strong&gt; The data is from Motley Fool Premium subscription (Stock Advisor) in Canada. Due to this, the data is limited from 2013 and they have made a total of 91 recommendations for US-listed stocks. (They make one buy recommendation every 4th Wednesday of the month). I feel that 8 years is a long enough time frame to benchmark their performance. If you have seen my previous posts, I always share the data used in the analysis. But in this case, I will not be able to share the data as per the terms and conditions of their subscription.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Analysis:&lt;/strong&gt; As per Motley Fool, their stock picks are long-term plays (at least 5 years). Hence for all their recommendations I calculated the stock price change across 4 periods and benchmarked it against S&amp;amp;P500 returns during the same period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a. One-Quarter&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;b. One Year&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;c. Two Year&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;d. Till Date (From the day of recommendation to Today)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another feedback that I received for my previous analysis was starting price point for analysis. In this case, Motley Fool recommends their stock picks on Wed market close, I am considering the starting point of my analysis on Thursday’s market close price (i.e, you could have bought the share anytime during the next day).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/oo61ht373bw61.png?width=623&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=8c8d785445785475c739f84ea3638bb820420bb2&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/oo61ht373bw61.png?width=623&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=8c8d785445785475c739f84ea3638bb820420bb2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we can see from the above chart, Motley Fool’s recommendations did beat the market over the long term across the different time periods. Their one-year returns were ~2X and two-year returns were ~3X the SPY returns. Even capping for outliers (stocks that gained more than 100%), their returns were better than the S&amp;amp;P benchmark.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/qo4xaop93bw61.png?width=623&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=8bf4985e21430a811827242ce9b3587e9a4ae25a&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/qo4xaop93bw61.png?width=623&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=8bf4985e21430a811827242ce9b3587e9a4ae25a&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it’s not like all their strategies were good. As we can see from the above chart, their sell recommendations were not exactly ideal and you would have gained more if you just stayed put on your portfolio and did not sell when they recommended you to sell. One of the major contributors to this difference was that they issued a sell recommendation for Tesla in 2019 for a good profit but missed out on Tesla’s 2020 rally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How much money should you be managing to profitably use Motley Fool recommendations?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stock advisor subscription costs $100 per year. Considering their yearly returns beat the benchmark by 13%, to break even, you only need to invest $770 per year. Considering a 5x factor of safety as historical performance cannot be expected to be repeated and to factor in all the extra trading fees, one has to invest around $4k every year. You also have to factor in the mental stress that you will have to put up with all their upselling tactics and clickbait e-mails that they send.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Limitations of analysis:&lt;/strong&gt; Since I am using the Canadian version of Motley Fool’s premium subscription, I have only access to the US recommendations made from 2013. But, 8 years is a considerably long time to benchmark returns for the service. Also, I am unable to share the data I used in the analysis for cross-verification by other people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I am definitely not the first person to independently analyze their recommendations. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/321057021_Evaluating_the_performance_of_the_Motley_Fool%2527s_Stock_Advisor/fulltext/5a0af7be458515e482743bf9/Evaluating-the-performance-of-the-Motley-Fools-Stock-Advisor.pdf?origin=publication_detail&quot;&gt;This&lt;/a&gt; peer-reviewed research publication in 2017 came to the same conclusion for the time period that was before my analysis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We find that the Stock Advisor recommendations do statistically outperform the matched samples and S&amp;amp;P 500 index, since the creation of Stock Advisor in 2002 regarding both short-term and long-term holding periods. Over a longer holding period, the Stock Advisor portfolio repeatedly outperforms the S&amp;amp;P 500 index and matched samples in terms of monthly raw returns and risk-adjusted measures. Although the overall performance of the Stock Advisor portfolio benefits from remarkable recommendation performances between 2002 and 2006, the portfolio still exceeds the benchmarks regarding risk-adjusted measures during the subsequent period between 2007 and 2011&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have some theories on why Motley Fool produces content the way they do. The free articles of the company are just created to drive the maximum amount of traffic to their website. If we have learned anything from the changes in blog headlines and YouTube thumbnails, it’s that clickbait works. I guess they must have decided that the traffic they generate from the headlines and articles far outweigh the negative PR they get due to the same articles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever the case may be, rather than hating on something regardless of the results, we could give credit where credit is due! I started the research being extremely skeptical, but my analysis, as well as peer-reviewed papers, shows that their Stock Advisor picks beat the market over the long run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: I am not a financial advisor and in no way related to Motley Fools.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[股市回報率不是平均水平

https://t.co/eSX2JaCtZE https://t.co/tmj20S8bMU]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387821728798322695</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387821728798322695</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 14:35:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有時選擇市場時機是有效的。在6天內從$MVIS上賺了5萬美元（僅股票）。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n1hbde/sometimes_timing_the_market_works_made_50k_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n1hbde/sometimes_timing_the_market_works_made_50k_on/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 13:53:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[亞馬遜的收入在過去一年中增長了44%，這是其連續78個季度的收入同比增長。自2011年以來的最高增長率。$AMZN

數據來自@ycharts https://t.co/ZOJh5XMYmv]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387861736087343106</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387861736087343106</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 12:42:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[推特第一季度。收入10.4億美元（同比增長28.8%）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[推特下滑11%，第一季度用戶和收入基本符合預期

- 第一季度非美國通用會計準則EPS爲0.16美元，超出0.02美元；美國通用會計準則EPS爲0.08美元，超出0.10美元。

- 收入爲10.4億美元（同比增長28.8%），比預期高出1000萬美元。

- 推特（NYSE:TWTR）在盤後早盤下跌11%，此前
第一季度財報顯示，該公司的收入比上年同期增長了11%。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/n1i2a5/twitter_q1_revenue_of_104b_288_yy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/n1i2a5/twitter_q1_revenue_of_104b_288_yy/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 12:42:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twitter slides 11% as Q1 users, revenue come in largely as expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Q1 Non-GAAP EPS of $0.16 beats by $0.02; GAAP EPS of $0.08 beats by $0.10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Revenue of $1.04B (+28.8% Y/Y) beats by $10M.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Twitter (NYSE:TWTR) is 11% lower in early postmarket trading after first-quarter earnings showed a beat on profitability, but revenues and user numbers that were in line with expectations - a tough sell in a quarter of tech earnings blowouts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• The company also offered subdued Q2 revenue guidance in line with expectations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Revenues rose 29% to $1.04B, largely as expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Those gains reflected &amp;quot;accelerating year-over-year growth in MAP revenue and brand advertising that improved throughout the quarter,&amp;quot; says Chief Financial Officer Ned Segal. &amp;quot;Advertisers continue to benefit from updated ad formats, improved measurement, and new brand safety controls, contributing to 32% year-over-year growth in ad revenue in Q1.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• And monetizable daily active users grew about 20% to 199M, vs. expectations that the company would hit the 200M mark this quarter. That figure was up 7M sequentially.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Average U.S. mDAU came to 38M, vs 33M a year ago; international mDAU were 162M, vs a previous 133M.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Costs and expenses rose just 21% to $984M, and so operating income swung to a gain of $52M vs. a year-ago loss of $7M. Operating margin was 5%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• And net income swung to a gain of $68M, vs. a year-ago loss of $8M.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Net cash from operations rose to $390M from a prior-year $247M.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• For Q2, it&amp;#39;s guiding to revenue of $980M-$1.08B (vs. consensus for $1.05B), and a GAAP operating loss of $170M to $120M.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[擁有200萬美元的投資組合是否比擁有一個企業更好？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我問這個問題是因爲如果你的200萬美元投資組合的平均收益率是10%左右
的回報，這意味着你賺了20萬美元，加上你的工作收入，這是
真棒。這在某種程度上會不會像擁有一個企業，除了它是
與管理企業相比，完全是被動的，比如......。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n1os7z/is_have_a_2_million_portfolio_better_than_owning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n1os7z/is_have_a_2_million_portfolio_better_than_owning/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 11:25:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I ask this because if your $2 million portfolio were to make an average ish 10% return, that means you made $200K plus whatever you make for your job, which is awesome. Would this be like owning a business in a way except that it is completely passive in comparison to managing a business such as a owning a restaurant?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any restaurant owners here? How much are you taking home a year? I don’t care about revenue, I wanna know how much free cash flow and money in your pockets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我的朋友想買入紅利股票，然後賣出這些股票的覆蓋式看漲期權。這是個好主意嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[例如，他正在考慮購買Telus的股票。他想在記錄日期前至少裝入
100支，以便收取股息。然後他計劃
爲他的100股股票寫一份覆蓋性看漲期權，希望能獲得更多的收益。
如果他的行權價格設定得很好，而且人們買了他的股票，那麼，他就可以獲得更多的收益。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n1iva8/my_friend_wants_to_buy_dividend_stocks_then_sell/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n1iva8/my_friend_wants_to_buy_dividend_stocks_then_sell/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 09:30:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example he is looking at buying Telus shares. He wants to load up at least 100 of them before the record date in order to collect dividends. He then plans on writing a covered call on his 100 shares in hopes to get some boosted gains. If his strike price is perfectly set, and people buy his option but then expires worthless, he makes gains on the share price going up, as well as dividend payments AND the premium of the call option. Seems juicy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My counter argument is that it limits his upside, and also potentially covers some losses if he sells the option and the stock drops. But besides those two factors, wouldn’t it just be better to buy and hold the same stock? That way you at least have the option to hold your shares or sell them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對於在480美元買入的GME團伙。謝謝你成爲我們的支持級別]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n1k8rq/for_the_gme_gang_that_bought_at_480_thank_you_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n1k8rq/for_the_gme_gang_that_bought_at_480_thank_you_for/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 04:32:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[他們不想讓你知道的口服科維德疫苗! 閱讀DD!]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，夥計們，我打算花時間寫這篇文章給所有日間交易員。
投資者，以及那些受到冠狀病毒影響的人。現在是你們
你們有機會奪回你們失去的東西。

這家名爲vaxart（VXRT）的公司是一家位於灣區的公司，它專注於
口服重組疫苗，...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n18pj8/the_oral_covid_vaccine_they_dont_want_you_to_know/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n18pj8/the_oral_covid_vaccine_they_dont_want_you_to_know/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 03:35:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Okay guys, I am going to take the time to write this to all day traders, investors, and those who have been affected by coronavirus. Now is your opportunity to take back what you lost. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This company called vaxart (VXRT) is a company based in the Bay Area who focuses on oral recombinant vaccines, such as influenza, norovirus, hpv, and most importantly at this time, coronavirus. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The crazy thing is that not many people care to understand science, but if you read the presentation from 3/25/2021, it may help profusely:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://investors.vaxart.com/static-files/560116e8-db25-42df-865e-0ed57b8d129a&quot;&gt;https://investors.vaxart.com/static-files/560116e8-db25-42df-865e-0ed57b8d129a&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company released an 8k on February 3rd, 2021, which highlights the Janssen collaboration agreement. This collab agreement let&amp;#39;s Janssen (owned by JnJ) use their influenza antigen and put it in vaxart pill. The final sentence reads, &amp;quot;Upon delivery of the report, Janssen has a three-month option to negotiate an exclusive worldwide license to the Company’s technology encompassing the Janssen antigens. Janssen has not notified the Company whether it will exercise this option.&amp;quot; 3 months is 90 days. 90 days from Feb 3 is May 4th (&lt;a href=&quot;https://investors.vaxart.com/news-releases/news-release-details/vaxart-enters-research-collaboration-janssen-evaluate-oral&quot;&gt;https://investors.vaxart.com/news-releases/news-release-details/vaxart-enters-research-collaboration-janssen-evaluate-oral&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pill was put the test against the leading injectable for the flu, sanofis fluzone . Studies showed that even though Sanofis Fluzone had 10x more antibodies, Vaxarts/Janssens flu pill worked 8% better at preventing influenza because of the heavy amount of T-cells and activating mucosal membranes. Oh yeah, this was funded by BARDA also, so the government knows all about them. 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://investors.vaxart.com/news-releases/news-release-details/results-influenza-challenge-study-published-lancet-infectious&quot;&gt;https://investors.vaxart.com/news-releases/news-release-details/results-influenza-challenge-study-published-lancet-infectious&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back to may 3rd...vaxart last week announced that they are having a Stanford University T-cell expert to discuss cross-protection against variants. &lt;a href=&quot;https://investors.vaxart.com/news-releases/news-release-details/vaxart-host-key-opinion-leader-webinar-importance-t-cell&quot;&gt;https://investors.vaxart.com/news-releases/news-release-details/vaxart-host-key-opinion-leader-webinar-importance-t-cell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The NEXT DAY, may 4th, Vaxarts Chief Scientific Officer, Sean Tucker, Ph.D., will present at the upcoming World Vaccine Congress Washington that will be held virtually from May 4-6, 2021. The World Vaccine Congress is the largest, most established meeting dedicated to vaccines. From basic research to commercial manufacture, this one meeting covers the whole vaccine value chain where science, government and manufacturers all come together to create groundbreaking progress. Here is a link of speakers : &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.terrapinn.com/conference/world-vaccine-congress-washington/speakers.stm&quot;&gt;https://www.terrapinn.com/conference/world-vaccine-congress-washington/speakers.stm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These room temperature stable tablets can be shipped overseas to India and Brazil, and all other spots of the world cheaper, easier, without vaccination sites, without fear of needles, (which accounts for 18% of the population of the US alone.), which enables cross variant protection while activating musocal immunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another benefit is they are environmentally friendly. No need for disposal of hundreds of million plastic syringes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is much more Due diligence you could find, such as googling &amp;quot;richetti brothers vaxart&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;lodi&amp;amp;the world s2e1&amp;quot; &amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt; Atwill claiming 1 billion pills by years end, and much much more, but that&amp;#39;s enough for now. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another important note is that on February 3rd, 2021, vaxart dropped 60% and continued to fall from 25 to 5. This was due to investors knowing about money, not the science. Once they realize they can&amp;#39;t compare MRNA technology to their VAAST technology, this thing will BLOW. Example: the influenza studies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Side note: HUGE MISCONCEPTION. MERCK, PFIZER(pill), RIDGEBACK, REMDESIRIVIR, all those are THERAPEUTICS AND ANTIVIRALS. THEY WORK SYSTEMICALLY. THIS IS A VACCINE. A PREVENTION FROM THE VIRUS ENTERING YOUR SYSTEM IN THE FIRST PLACE. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Side note 2: their building is connected to Janssen with a skybridge. Literally. AND they&amp;#39;ve increased their employee headcount by 500% in a year with 34 pending positions on LinkedIn. Once those positions are filled, 825% increase in employees. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VAXART HR TRACKER (check this out, super fucking in depth) (thank you option papa) &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/12R8GJ6sUS6nCGm5eA_KRxeYFNzNfxJfTR9iNjZChhtA/edit?usp=drivesdk&quot;&gt;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/12R8GJ6sUS6nCGm5eA_KRxeYFNzNfxJfTR9iNjZChhtA/edit?usp=drivesdk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Please share, let&amp;#39;s make this known. *&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I should also mention this is the most heavily shorted biotech stock at nearly 40%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somebody else&amp;#39;s in depth research: &lt;a href=&quot;https://ftresearch.substack.com/p/vaxart-deep-value-analysis&quot;&gt;https://ftresearch.substack.com/p/vaxart-deep-value-analysis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: I will update on Monday with more information. Tomorrow is the day, we need to squeeze them and close above 9$. We close above 9, we&amp;#39;re in for a major treat next week. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*I am not a financial advisor, and I take no responsibility for anybodys position but my own. I wish you all the best of luck and hope to go back to normalcy soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[北京對脆弱的房地產開發商的擠壓正在變得真實 - 華爾街日報文章]]></title><description><![CDATA[在這裏閱讀這篇文章。
https://www.wsj.com/articles/beijings-squeeze-on-fragile-real-estate-developers-is-getting-real-11619682390

在當前瘋狂的牛市中，人們完全忽略了這樣一個事實，即中國的市場和經濟一直在發展。
市場和經濟已經開始再次出現裂痕和跡象。
弱點....]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/n1bg9z/beijings_squeeze_on_fragile_realestate_developers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/n1bg9z/beijings_squeeze_on_fragile_realestate_developers/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 02:25:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read the article here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/beijings-squeeze-on-fragile-real-estate-developers-is-getting-real-11619682390&quot;&gt;https://www.wsj.com/articles/beijings-squeeze-on-fragile-real-estate-developers-is-getting-real-11619682390&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting completely lost in the current wild bull market is the fact that China&amp;#39;s markets and economy have been starting to once again show cracks and signs of weakness. A lot of that is a product of the government starting to restrict their stimulus efforts in an attempt to keep the growth in debt and leverage in check. China has been the first market to really pull back stimulus, which probably isnt surprising since they were the first to be hit by and recover from Covid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the above linked article, there are some very.... interesting happenings relating to the Chinese property market. I don&amp;#39;t for one second believe that China would ever purposefully burst their property bubble, since that would be a self-inflicted wound that would do a massive amount of damage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said, as with any credit-fueled bubble, you tend to see these catch-22 situations pop up where regulators are forced to decide between:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allowing the bubble to grow larger and larger, losing any type of control over how it behaves and worsening the fallout when the bubble inevitably bursts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clamping down on credit expansion, preventing the bubble from growing larger, but also risking being the pin that pops the bubble itself.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They seem to be going for option 2 right now. China recently tried to curb credit growth in 2018, and that played a major role in the markets that year, where both bonds and stock indexes saw a mild decline on the year. Despite the impact, China didn&amp;#39;t even end up actually reducing the debt in the system, but just slowed the level of growth.... until Covid hit and the floodgates were once again reopened to credit growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously, the thing to watch for is whether China can walk the tightrope of reducing leverage growth without triggering a cascading failure of the very fragile economy. One thing to keep in mind here is that China has greater ability to manage debt issues like this due to their economy not really being market-based, and the level of control the Gov&amp;#39;t has over all the pieces in the puzzle. That&amp;#39;s not to say that&amp;#39;s all good - the ability to stall a forced deleveraging also means that the problems tend to metastasize quicker and to a far greater extent since the cans typically just get kicked down the road further. It&amp;#39;s the classic moral hazard dilemma.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Good Twitter Thread On This Article&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quoting from Michael Pettis, who is always astute, and is a reasonably non-biased source on China&amp;#39;s economy. &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/michaelxpettis/status/1387831939353153537&quot;&gt;Read thread here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Important article by &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Birdyword/&quot;&gt;@Birdyword&lt;/a&gt;, who discusses the shift from bank loans to buyers&amp;#39; deposits in the liabilities of Chinese property developers. As usual I&amp;#39;m especially interested in the balance-sheet impact: as long as things are going well, the shift barely matters, but it matters a great deal if the developer ever gets into trouble and is unable to finish a project.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This creates at least two problems. First, a default by a large developer can cause what is effectively a &amp;quot;run on the bank&amp;quot; as other buyers around the country become reluctant to put up further deposits with other property developers.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This process can be highly self-reinforcing as it forces property developers to cut back further on operations, and so alienate even more deposits. Of course the more developers rely on deposits to fund their operations, the more likely it is that a problem with one large developer spreads to other developers around the country. Regulators can force banks to lend, but they can&amp;#39;t force households to put up deposits.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, Beijing will have to choose either to let households take the loss or to force banks to step in and make them whole. The former seems politically unlikely, but the latter means that what had looked like a reduction in banks&amp;#39; exposure to real estate developers was never a meaningful reduction at all but rather the conversion of direct liabilities into contingent liabilities. For all the regulatory agitation, in other words, there was never an improvement in financial-sector risk.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For many years we&amp;#39;ve seen that &amp;quot;deleveraging&amp;quot; in China has meant reducing leverage in one part of the economy while increasing it in another. This isn&amp;#39;t incidental. It is fundamental to the way the growth model works. &amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some other general thoughts &amp;amp; notes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Shanghai Composite index is down 6% in RMB terms (ASHR etf is down 13% in US markets). In general, there has been emerging weakness in Chinese indexes compared to US stock indexes. Obviously this can reverse, but it&amp;#39;s worth noting the divergence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The USDCNY exchange rate reversed in February for the first time since Covid hit in any meaningful way before starting it&amp;#39;s fall again in recent weeks. Could be a sign that a durable trend reversal is coming, which tends to signal Chinese economic weakness from a market perspective.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;China has been putting curbs on developers for a little while now ( since end of 2020) due to excessive speculation &amp;amp; credit growth - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/5bdab1f8-3285-41ca-b964-bf3ce6b2c7fb&quot;&gt;read more here on some of the details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chinese property is the primary means of savings for Chinese citizens.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beijing recently reduced restrictions on capital being allowed to leave their borders. This may potentially have an effect on property values and the exchange rate, although it&amp;#39;s tough to say if and how much this will matter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Discuss Below&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在喫香菇的時候，向MNMD投入了23萬美金。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n1hr56/yolod_230k_into_mnmd_while_on_shrooms/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n1hr56/yolod_230k_into_mnmd_while_on_shrooms/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 02:25:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Facebook的收入比Twitter略高https://t.co/bvf1FLlXsR]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387916138881892353</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387916138881892353</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 01:18:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Peloton現在從高點下跌了41%。

我喜歡這個產品，但這是迄今爲止我認爲最難預測的大流行後的股票。

健身界幾乎所有的東西最終都會成爲一種時尚，所以這隻股票屬於我的太難堆https://t.co/eXgdRlURd9]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387792096225120261</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387792096225120261</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 01:18:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[去年的社會媒體...

臉書（MAUs）：26億 -&gt; 28.5億（同比+10%）。

Pinterest (MAUs): 3.67億 -&gt; 4.78億 (+30% YoY)

Spotify（MAU）：2.86億 -&gt; 3.56億（同比增長27%）。

Snapchat (DAUs): 2.29億 -&gt; 2.80億 (同比增長22%)

推特（可盈利的DAU）：1.66億 -gt; 1.99億（同比增長20%）。

$fb $pins $spot $snap $twtr]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387868609792315394</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387868609792315394</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 01:18:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[剛把3.8萬美金投入MNMD。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n16t5n/just_yolod_38k_into_mnmd/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n16t5n/just_yolod_38k_into_mnmd/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 01:18:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIO正在爲大事情做準備]]></title><description><![CDATA[NIO Inc. (NIO)宣佈開始建設NeoPark，這是一個智能電動汽車產業園。
宣佈其與合肥市政府共同開發的智能電動汽車產業園區NeoPark開始建設。
在這家中國汽車製造商週四收盤後發佈季度財報之前，宣佈NeoPark開始建設。
週四收盤後，中國汽車製造商將發佈季度財報。 

發生了什麼。尼歐公司表示，NeoPark的工作已經啓動...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n1gpdx/nio_is_ramping_up_for_big_things/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n1gpdx/nio_is_ramping_up_for_big_things/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 01:18:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NIO Inc. (NIO) is announcing the beginning of construction of NeoPark, a smart electric vehicle industry park it is co-developing with the Hefei government, ahead of the Chinese automaker&amp;#39;s quarterly earnings release after the close Thursday. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What Happened: Work on NeoPark has kicked off, Nio said in a Thursday press release.
The opening ceremony was attended by several officials from Anhui province, where Hefei is located, as well as William Li, Nio&amp;#39;s founder, chairman and CEO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nio&amp;#39;s China headquarters are situated in Hefei. The collaboration agreement with the Hefei municipal government for NeoPark was signed in early February.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NeoPark is conceived as a smart EV industry cluster, encompassing R&amp;amp;D of vehicles, core parts and components and autonomous driving. It was envisioned to evolve as a pioneering innovation chain with global competitiveness and a hub for hundreds of key supporting industries and a highly clustered, full-fledged industry chain, the company said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 16,950-acre park features three main function areas — smart manufacturing, R&amp;amp;D and living space, and Eco park. NeoPark will likely contribute to peaking carbon emissions and achieving carbon neutrality, according to the company.
The park, according to company, will accommodate over 10,000 R&amp;amp;D personnel and 40,000 technical workers. It&amp;#39;s expected to have an annual production capacity of 1 million vehicles and 100 GWh. The annual gross output from the park is expected to reach 500 billion yuan ($77.3 billion).
Why It&amp;#39;s Important: Nio has embarked on a broad push to drive volumes as it comes up against fierce competition in a crowded EV market. The company has announced innovation in battery technology, charging infrastructure and services, while also announcing new models.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company confirmed Wednesday that it is setting up operations in Norway, terming it as the first leg of its international expansion.
The investment in Neo Park is also seen as a payback from Nio to the Hefei city, which bailed it out with financial assistance when the company was running out of cash in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[100%的投資組合在AAPL。這是個好主意嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[標題基本上說明了一切。我今年18歲，不是超級金融專家。
我繼承了幾千美元，買了一堆蘋果股票。今年
我有一份暑期工作，每週能賺500美元左右。我計劃
用每份工資來購買更多的股票。這是否是一個堅實的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n183fl/100_of_portfolio_in_aapl_is_it_a_good_idea/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n183fl/100_of_portfolio_in_aapl_is_it_a_good_idea/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 23:59:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The title basically says it all. I’m 18 years old and not super finance savvy. I’ve inherited a few thousand dollars and I bought a bunch of Apple shares. This summer I have a summer job and will be making about $500 per week. I plan on using every paycheck just to buy more shares. Is this a solid idea? I don’t plan on needing any of the money anytime soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是今天的市場回顧，2021年4月29日，星期四]]></title><description><![CDATA[PsychoMarket Recap - 2021年4月29日星期四

股市創下新的紀錄高點，因爲市場參與者考慮了一批強於預期的企業盈利報告和來自政府的新建議。
強於預期的企業盈利報告，以及美國總統奧巴馬的新提議，股市創下新高。
拜登總統提出的旨在改造美國的基礎設施和支持家庭、兒童和青少年的新建議。
改革美國的基礎設施並支持家庭、兒童和...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n1d2c6/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_thursday_april/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n1d2c6/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_thursday_april/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 22:57:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Thursday, April 29, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks hit fresh record highs as market participants considered a batch of stronger-than-expected corporate earnings reports and new proposals from President Biden aimed at revamping the US’ infrastructure and supporting families, children, and students. The S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) hit a new intraday record, driven by gains in mega-cap stocks like Facebook (FB) and Apple (AAPL), both of which reported blowout earnings. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last night, President Biden addressed a joint session of Congress, during which he said “America was back on the move again” following the coronavirus pandemic that devastated the economy. In his address, President Biden touted his $2 trillion infrastructure plan and unveiled a new $1.8 trillion proposal aimed at supporting children, students, and families. This proposal, called the American Families Plan, would be funded in part with the newly proposed tax increases on the wealthy. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2021/04/28/fact-sheet-the-american-families-plan/&quot;&gt;Read the details of the proposal here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earnings season continues to deliver blowout results, with Apple and Facebook massively outperforming analyst expectations. Facebook’s stock, in particular, gapped up more than 7%. The strong results from these companies adds to a parade of mega-cap companies that have vastly outperformed estimates, driven by a surge in demand as the US economy gradually reopens thanks to effective vaccine distribution. According to FactSet, as of early Wednesday, companies comprising nearly half of the S&amp;amp;P 500&amp;#39;s market capitalization had reported earnings results, with 83% of these corporations topping estimates, and by an average of 21.7%. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Market participants also digested recent commentary from members of the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC), which included no major changes to policy but did highlight recent improvements in the US economy. FOMC members said the effective distribution of the vaccine in the US has improved economic conditions but reiterated interest rates will remain near-zero and the current pace of the asset purchasing program in place. The Fed said, “Amid progress and strong policy support, indicators of economic activity and employment have risen.” The committee remains optimistic about the rebound in economic activity, describing the most affected sectors as “having shown improvement”, but shows no signs of slowing quantitative easing or raising interest rates. With more than 8 million people still out of jobs compared to pre-pandemic levels, FOMC reiterated its commitment to supporting the economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Labor Department released its Weekly Unemployment Report, which shows fresh pandemic-era lows as the economy gradually reopens.

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Initial jobless claims, week ended April 24:&lt;/strong&gt; 553,000 vs. 540,000 expected and an upwardly revised 566,000 during the prior week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continuing claims, week ended April 17:&lt;/strong&gt; 3.660 million vs. 3.590 million expected and a downwardly revised 3.651 million during the prior week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Uber, Lyft and Doordash (DASH) fell sharply after Reuters reported that Labor Secretary Marty Walsh supported reclassifying gig workers as employees. This change would give workers additional benefits at a large cost to companies. Recall the battle last year over Proposition 22 in California, which eventually passed in favor of companies in the gig-economy. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;US gross domestic product (GDP) increased at a 6.4% quarter-over-quarter, seasonally adjusted annualized rate in the first three months of 2021, &lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-economy-accelerated-robust-6-123644612.html&quot;&gt;the Bureau of Economic Analysis said Thursday in its first estimate on GDP. &lt;/a&gt;This marked an acceleration from the 4.3% annualized growth rate from the fourth quarter of 2020&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New York City &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Morning_Joe/status/1387733678093127684&quot;&gt;Mayor Bill de Blasio said &lt;/a&gt;that NYC would open with full capacity beginning July 1. &amp;quot;Our plan is to fully reopen on July 1. We are ready for stores to open, for businesses to open, offices, theaters, full strength,” de Blasio said. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) said Thursday it is auditing Boeing Co&amp;#39;s process for making minor design changes across its product line after a 737 MAX manufacturing issue grounded dozens of planes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**&lt;strong&gt;Please note that current stock price is written premarket and does not reflect intraday changes*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple (AAPL) with a host of target raises following their blowout earnings report. Consensus price target $180 at Buy. Stock currently around $137&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Align Technology (ALGN) with two target raises. Stock currently around $615

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stifel Nicolaus from $650 to $750 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robert W Baird from $655 to $745 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DR Horton (DHI) target raised by BTIG Research from $108 to $124 at Buy. Stock currently around $100&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brinker International (EAT) target raised by Telsey Advisory Group from $65 to $85 at Outperform. Stock currently around $68&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facebook (FB) with a host of target raises following a blowout earnings report. Consensus price target $400 at Buy. Stock currently around $330&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fortinet (FTNT) target raised by KeyCorp from $195 to $233 at Overweight. Stock currently around $198&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alphabet (GOOG $GOOGL) target raised by BMO Capital Markets from $2350 to $2600 at Outperform. Stock currently around $2359&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Olin (OLN) with two target raises. Stock currently around $42

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;KeyCorp from $50 to $53 Overweight&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Royal Bank of Canada from $56 to $63 Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OshKosh (OSK) with a host of target raises. Consensus price target $145 at Overweight. Stockcurrently around $128&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Palo Alto Networks (PANW) target raised by KeyCorp from $450 to $469 at Overweight. Stock currently around $360&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qualcomm (QCOM) with three target raises. Stock currently around $137

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Morgan Stanely from $167 to $173&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Piper Sandler from $160 to $175&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mizuho from $170 to $175&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snapchat (SNAP) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $74 to $75. Stock currently around $62&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ultra Clean (UCTT) target raised by Stifel Nicolaus from $65 to $71 at Buy after reporting great earnings. Stock currently around $55&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Patience is bitter, but its fruit is sweet.” Aristotle&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[致決定做空南非國家的那個人]]></title><description><![CDATA[我只想問他，他的做空頭寸做得如何，考慮到
考慮到南非股市已經並繼續超過美國、歐洲和亞洲股市的表現。
歐洲和亞洲股市的表現，因爲南非經濟現在正在走出衰退，而投資者也在等待。
衰退，投資者紛紛湧向南非。

你是否...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n16wga/to_the_guy_who_decided_to_short_the_country_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n16wga/to_the_guy_who_decided_to_short_the_country_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 22:57:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just want to ask him, how his shorting positions are doing, considering that the South African Stock Market has and continues to outperform the American, European and Asian stock markets as the South African economy is now coming out of recession and investors are streaming to South Africa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you plan on holding your short positions and hoping for the best (Well, worst for the country, best for you), or have you already, or are you at least planning to sell your short positions if things continue to improve for the South African Stock Market and economy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, to other investors, do you think that he has made a huge blunder with his decision, or do you think he should hold as he made a possibly good decision?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[亞馬遜粉碎了盈利預期]]></title><description><![CDATA[關鍵點 亞馬遜週四發佈的第一季度業績超過了
分析師的預期。

亞馬遜股價在週四的延長交易中攀升至5%，此前該公司發佈的第一季度財報
該公司發佈了第一季度財報，超過了華爾街的預期。
盈利和收入。

以下是該公司的盈利情況...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n1czad/amazon_smashed_earnings_expectations/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n1czad/amazon_smashed_earnings_expectations/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 21:15:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;KEY POINTS
Amazon released first-quarter results on Thursday that trounced analysts’ expectations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amazon shares climbed as much as 5% in extended trading Thursday after the company released its first-quarter earnings, beating Wall Street’s expectations for earnings and revenue. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s how the e-commerce giant fared, relative to analyst estimates compiled by Refinitiv:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earnings: $15.79 per share vs. $9.54 per share expected
Revenue: $108.52 billion vs. $104.47 billion expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Few companies have benefited from the pandemic-fueled surge of online shopping as much as Amazon. The company notched record profits and revenue last year, while CEO Jeff Bezos announced earlier this month that Amazon crossed more than 200 million Prime subscribers, up from 150 million at the start of 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2020, Amazon invested heavily on coronavirus-related measures like safety protocols and wage increases for front-line workers. As a result of these costs, Amazon last quarter forecast operating income of $3 billion to $6.5 billion in the current period. Those coronavirus-related costs are expected to slow this year, although on Wednesday, Amazon said it would spent more than $1 billion on pay raises for more than half a million of its U.S. operations workers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/29/amazon-amzn-earnings-q1-2021.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/29/amazon-amzn-earnings-q1-2021.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[亞馬遜收入（十億
2021年（估計）：478
2020: 386
2019: 281
2018: 233
2017: 178
2016: 136
2015: 107
2014: 89
2013: 74
2012: 61
2011: 48
2010: 34
2009: 25
2008: 19
2007: 15
2006: 11
2005: 8.5
2004: 6.9
2003: 5.3
2002: 3.9
2001: 3.1
2000: 2.8
1999: 1.6
1998: 0.6
1997: 0.15
AMZN]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387862284270194689</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387862284270194689</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 20:45:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[蘋果、微軟、亞馬遜和谷歌的總市值爲7.5萬億美元，比世界上除美國和中國以外的每個國家的GDP都要高。

$aapl $msft $amzn $googl

圖表來自@ycharts https://t.co/HHhN6aJKL7]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387866688289484802</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387866688289484802</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 20:45:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[第一季度收入增長，同比百分比變化...
特斯拉 $TSLA: +73.6
蘋果公司 $AAPL: +53.6
Facebook $FB: +47.5%
亞馬遜 $AMZN: +43.8
谷歌 $GOOGL: +34.4
Netflix $NFLX: +24.1%
微軟 $MSFT: +19.1%
S&amp;P 500 $SPY: +5.6%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387865015118614529</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387865015118614529</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 20:45:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shopify第一季度收益報告]]></title><description><![CDATA[第一季度業績

收入。988.6美元（同比增長110%）。

GMV擴大到373億美元（同比增長114%）。

淨收入爲12.5億美元，但其中包括Affirm的13億美元收益和
如果你把它拿出來，公司損失了大約4200萬，這意味着損失
實際上比上年同期略有擴大。

商店正在採取...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/n117k6/shopify_earnings_report_q1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/n117k6/shopify_earnings_report_q1/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 20:28:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Q1 Results &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revenue: 988.6 (110% YoY)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GMV expanded to 37.3 Billion dollars (114% YoY)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Net income is 1.25 Billion but that includes an 1.3 Billion gain on Affirm and if you take that out the company lost around 42 Million which means loss actually expanded slightly from last YoY. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shop is taking off&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the end of Q1 2021, Shop had more than 107 million registered users, including buyers using Shop Pay as well as the Shop App, of which more than 24 million were Monthly Active Users.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outlook&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are predicting that Q1 will be the smallest quarter in the year, which means the expect more the 3.9 Billion in revenue for FY21 which is a 106% growth. Really great. This is a very strong business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[諾基亞在5G專利方面名列前茅]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n11u70/nokia_ranked_as_number_one_in_5g_patents/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n11u70/nokia_ranked_as_number_one_in_5g_patents/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 19:27:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天，美聯儲會告訴你，任何地方都沒有通貨膨脹的跡象，還需要幾年的寬鬆貨幣來提振資產價格並刺激更高的通貨膨脹。你知道他們在撒謊，他們也知道這一點。https://t.co/wGr1YOT1Du]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387402492737163268</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387402492737163268</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 18:43:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[傳說中的牆頭堡查爾斯-德-沃克斯顯然是自殺身亡的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是個艱難的遊戲。即使是專家也會被殺。這位基金經理自殺了
本週早些時候自殺。從200億美元下降到10億美元。他是一個鐵桿的價值投資者
在一個目前傾向於增長型股票的世界中（正在輪流回到價值型）。

這裏有一篇關於他的基金的文章，來自...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/n17cea/legendary_wall_streeter_charles_de_vaulx_dies_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/n17cea/legendary_wall_streeter_charles_de_vaulx_dies_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:25:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a tough game. Even the pros get slayed. This fund manager took his own life earlier this week. From $20B down to $1B. He was a hardcore value investor in a world that currently favors growth stocks (and rotating back into value). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s a piece on his fund from MS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.morningstar.com/articles/708457/behind-the-rise-and-fall-of-an-esteemed-value-shop&quot;&gt;https://www.morningstar.com/.../behind-the-rise-and-fall...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I took away from this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you don&amp;#39;t need to be a professional wall street guy to be a good investor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;don&amp;#39;t over subscribe to any investing ideology (eg. growth, value, small cap, etc.). be able to be pivot and be flexible to adapt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[新的Schwab ETF -SCHY- Swhwab國際紅利增長指數]]></title><description><![CDATA[施瓦布的新國際ETF今天下跌。費用率爲0.14。看起來像是
是VXUS的有力替代品

https://www.schwabassetmanagement.com/products/schy
https://www.schwabassetmanagement.com/resource/schy-fact-sheet

" 該基金的目標是儘可能密切跟蹤，在費用和...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n13xi5/new_schwab_etf_schy_swhwab_international_dividend/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n13xi5/new_schwab_etf_schy_swhwab_international_dividend/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:25:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;New international etf from Schwab drops today. 
Expense Ratio of 0.14. Looks like a strong alternative to VXUS&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.schwabassetmanagement.com/products/schy&quot;&gt;https://www.schwabassetmanagement.com/products/schy&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.schwabassetmanagement.com/resource/schy-fact-sheet&quot;&gt;https://www.schwabassetmanagement.com/resource/schy-fact-sheet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“ The fund’s goal is to track as closely as possible, before fees and expenses, the total return of an index composed of high dividend yielding stocks issued by companies outside the United States. Invests in non-U.S. high dividend yielding stocks with a record of paying dividends for at least 10 consecutive years, financial strength and screened for lower volatility”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[儘管多米諾披薩公司的資產負債表上早在2005年就出現了負資產，但該公司的股票卻表現良好。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在網上訂了比薩餅後，在等待送餐的過程中瞥了一眼他們的財務狀況。
我沒有深入研究，所以也許我錯過了什麼。
也許他們的負資產是會計技巧的結果。我知道他們自2005年以來
自2005年以來，他們每年都是盈利的，我最遠看了......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/n0wtio/how_has_dominos_pizza_done_well_as_a_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/n0wtio/how_has_dominos_pizza_done_well_as_a_stock/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 16:26:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I kind of glanced at their financials after ordering pizza online while waiting for the delivery, I didn&amp;#39;t go too in depth so maybe I am missing something, maybe their negative equity is a result of accounting tricks. I know they have been profitable every year since 2005, I looked as far back as 2005 on macro trends since that is the earliest It allows. Their cash from operations is positive and they buy back shares, Maybe I don&amp;#39;t fully understand what negative equity means, but as far as I know this means the business should fail and the shareholders have claim to nothing, any explanations?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[UFC確認將進行IPO--誰在其中？]]></title><description><![CDATA[誰在跳上這趟車？購買你所理解的 "UFC "最近一直很火爆。
最近，我不認爲人氣會很快下降。像我這樣的凡人如何才能
像我這樣的凡人如何在早期獲得一些股票？我從來沒有在首次公開募股日購買過，但
但股票似乎在開盤的幾個小時內就會飛速上升......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n15vvg/ufc_is_confirmed_for_ipo_whos_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n15vvg/ufc_is_confirmed_for_ipo_whos_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 16:26:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Who&amp;#39;s jumping on this train? &amp;#39;Buy what you understand&amp;#39;  UFC has been blowing up lately and I don&amp;#39;t see any decline in popularity any time soon. How can a mere mortal like me secure some stocks early on? I&amp;#39;ve never purchased on IPO day, but the stocks seem to just catapult upwards in the opening hours every time IPO happens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[亞利桑那州衆議員Alma Hernandez（D-Tucson）在全面接種疫苗後對COVID-19檢測呈陽性。

經典案例]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387609237459775493</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387609237459775493</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 15:54:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[木材的價格比10年前高出5倍。

美聯儲。"不要理會，只是過渡性的。" https://t.co/ffR2CKvvQZ]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387775816289984525</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1387775816289984525</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 15:54:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Palantir公司的新合資企業希望打破癌症研究的數據孤島]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://twitter.com/PalantirTech/status/1387764219060293649?s=20

7:42 AM - 2021年4月29日

總部位於波士頓的Syntropy公司將創建一個數字平臺，使癌症研究人員能夠分享和分析來自許多不同組織的數據。
研究人員分享和分析來自許多不同組織的數據。

位於達姆施塔特的默克公司和硅谷地區的大數據...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n14tdv/palantirs_new_joint_venture_looks_to_tear_down/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n14tdv/palantirs_new_joint_venture_looks_to_tear_down/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 15:29:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/PalantirTech/status/1387764219060293649?s=20&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/PalantirTech/status/1387764219060293649?s=20&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7:42 AM - Apr 29, 2021&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boston-based Syntropy will create a digital platform that allows cancer researchers to share and analyze data from numerous different organizations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Merck KGaA, Darmstadt, and Silicon Valley-area big data company Palantir Technologies announced a joint venture that will focus on building an analytics and collaborative technology platform for cancer researchers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Called Syntropy, the Boston-based effort will rely on Palantir Foundry to power its data integration platform. Any research data shared across participating groups will be transparent and secure, according to the companies, with the participating institutions maintaining ownership of their data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Unlocking the power of scientific data is critical to advancing the fight against cancer,&amp;quot; Alexander Karp, Palantir cofounder and CEO, said in a statement. &amp;quot;Syntropy aims to help researchers collaborate securely to realize the value of this data, driving discoveries that will deliver better treatments to patients faster.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why it matters&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Numerous hospitals and research institutions are actively conducting cancer research, but the data they are generating is often limited to their own organization. Syntropy’s collaborative platform would looks to be a collective ecosystem that houses these research data and facilitates cross-institution analyses to drive new breakthroughs in cancer research and care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美國食品和藥物管理局藥品審批程序的基本概述]]></title><description><![CDATA[歡迎來到我的醫藥股指南的第一部分。我看到很多人對
我的目標是爲人們提供更多的信息
這樣他們就可以做出一個明智的決定。今天的主題將是。美國食品和藥物管理局的藥物
審批程序

美國食品和藥物管理局（FDA）的藥品審批程序可以分爲4個部分...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n13hwg/basic_overview_of_the_fda_drug_approval_process/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n13hwg/basic_overview_of_the_fda_drug_approval_process/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 14:47:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Part I of my Pharma Stocks Guide. I see a lot of interest in pharmaceuticals and my goal is to provide people with a little more information so they can make an informed decision. Today&amp;#39;s topic will be: The FDA Drug Approval Process&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The FDA Drug Approval Process can be broken down into 4 main sections: Pre-Clinical, Clinical Trials, Post Clinical, and Post Approval.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Pre-Clinical&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A drug&amp;#39;s journey begins in the lab where researchers will look at thousands of compounds and eventually select a few that they believe are promising.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After gathering initial data on the compound the next step is further testing. This will be done either In Vitro (testing done in a petri dish/ test tube) or In Vivo (animal testing).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After successful testing, the pharmaceutical company will submit an Investigational New Drug (IND) application to the FDA. This includes all of the data gathered so far and a plan for testing the drugs on humans (clinical trials).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The FDA has 30 days to review the IND application and ensures human lives aren&amp;#39;t at unreasonable risk. If the FDA accepts the IND, we move on to section 2 (Clinical Trials)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Clinical trials&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Phase 1&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; studies consist of 20-100 &lt;strong&gt;healthy volunteers&lt;/strong&gt; that last for &lt;strong&gt;several months&lt;/strong&gt;. The exception being a drug used in cancer patients will be studied in patients with that type of cancer. The goal is to assess &lt;strong&gt;safety&lt;/strong&gt; by monitoring how the drug affects the body as a whole, how long it lasts in the body, and any side effects that may appear. Results of &lt;strong&gt;Phase 1 studies do not indicate effectiveness&lt;/strong&gt;. I’ll repeat this because I believe it’s important: results of Phase 1 studies do not indicate effectiveness. As of 2018, the FDA states roughly &lt;strong&gt;70% of drugs will pass phase 1.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Phase 2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; studies consist of &lt;strong&gt;several hundreds of people with the disease/condition.&lt;/strong&gt; Studies here typically take &lt;strong&gt;months- 2 years&lt;/strong&gt;. The goal here is to observe &lt;strong&gt;effectiveness&lt;/strong&gt; of the drug in the intended patient population. This is where we first get to see if the drug truly works. Safety and side effects are monitored further as well. Approximately &lt;strong&gt;33% pass phase 2.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) FDA and pharmaceutical company meet to discuss plans for large scale Phase 3 studies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Phase 3&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; consists of &lt;strong&gt;several&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;thousands of participants&lt;/strong&gt;. These studies typically last &lt;strong&gt;1-4 years.&lt;/strong&gt; The goal here is to continue to observe effectiveness and safety as well as seeing how different doses of the drug or in combination with other drugs affects the outcome. It is important to note that because the &lt;strong&gt;studies are larger and for a longer duration, the results are more likely to show long term or less common side effects.&lt;/strong&gt; Should either happen, it almost always affects the stock negatively. &lt;strong&gt;Approximately&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;25-30% of drugs will pass Phase 3.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Post Clinical&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9) The pharmaceutical company files a New Drug Application (NDA). The NDA tells the FDA everything about the drug up to this point. This includes Pre-Clinical data, data from all clinical trials, as well as how the drug will be manufactured, and proposed labeling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10) The FDA has 60 days to decide if they will accept the NDA or reject it. If accepted, the drug is now under FDA review by a review team. Each team member will review their particular portion of the NDA. For example, the medical officer reviews all clinical data, the pharmacologist reviews all Pre-Clinical data, a chemist evaluates the drug&amp;#39;s chemical compound and stability, etc. If the NDA is rejected, the company and FDA will have to work together to resubmit a new NDA at a later date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;11) An inspection team is sent to the manufacturing site of where the drug will be made to assess for any issues that may affect the production of the drug.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;12) After a thorough assessment of the reports from each review team member and the inspection team (&lt;strong&gt;typically 6-10 months&lt;/strong&gt;), the FDA will either approve the drug or issue a Complete Response Letter (CRL) stating the drug and the application cannot be approved in its current form. This isn’t the end of the drug’s journey however, a company can work with the FDA and resubmit a NDA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Post Approval&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13) &lt;strong&gt;Phase 4&lt;/strong&gt; Clinical trials (often referred to as post marketing surveillance trial). These are studies conducted in a large scale (thousands of people) to continue to monitor the safety and efficacy of the drug after FDA approval. The company is required to send periodic updates on safety and efficacy to the FDA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Looking at some General Numbers&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;· From start (Preclinical research) to finish (FDA approval) &lt;strong&gt;a drug’s journey typically takes 10 years&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;· Some studies suggest the overall chance a drug gets approved is 10%. Other studies suggest 14%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;· If we go by the FDA numbers, lets say we have 100 potential drugs. 70% will make it to phase 2. We now have 70 hopeful drugs and only 33% make it to phase 3. We now have 23 hopeful drugs and only 25% make it to pass phase 3. So now only 5-6 drugs have made it this far (5-6%).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;· These numbers don’t exactly match because certain drugs like say for your skin are easier to get approval than cancer drugs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;· Regardless of which approval percentage you go with, studies show 2 common themes: The &lt;strong&gt;FDA drug approval percentage is low&lt;/strong&gt; and the drug &lt;strong&gt;approval chance for cancer drugs is extremely low (usually around 3%). Also, fuck cancer.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;In Summary&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preclinical Trials: the company does lab research on the drug via petri dishes or animal testing. No humans yet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IND (Investigational New Drug) application is sent to FDA. If approved we move on to clinical trials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phase 1: small group of healthy volunteers. Goal to observe safety. Timeline several months. 70% pass rate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phase 2: medium sized group of people with the intended disease/condition. Goal to observe safety AND efficacy. Timeline months - 2 years. 33% pass rate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phase 3: Large scale study for long duration. Goal to further assess safety and efficacy. Timeline 1-4 years. 25-30% pass rate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company then files NDA and will undergo FDA review. Hopefully approval after that.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phase 4: Studies safety and efficacy of the drug after FDA approval and in a large population.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From start to finish, drug’s typically take 10 years to make&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The overall approval chance for a drug is quite low (10-14%)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please please be careful/contain your excitement when you see positive Phase 1 results. It really doesn’t mean much.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a general overview of the FDA drug approval process. I hope this has been informative to some and if so, I may try to write some more quick guides in the future regarding pharmaceuticals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[第一次購買選擇就像...]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n133ay/first_time_buying_options_be_like/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n133ay/first_time_buying_options_be_like/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 14:47:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[更新：$HGEN (Humanigen) - 短期COVID遊戲，在CAR-T癌症治療方面有巨大的長期潛力（以及更多！）。5倍以上的潛在投資回報率]]></title><description><![CDATA[**TL;DR：短期的COVID遊戲在CAR-T療法中具有巨大的長期潛力
還有更多）。Lenzilumab最近的P3結果使其成爲目前住院COVID患者的第一大治療方法。
住院的COVID患者的第一治療方法。提交緊急使用許可的申請
緊急情況下使用授權（EUA）的申請隨時會到來（也許是今天！），並且...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n11qxi/update_hgen_humanigen_short_term_covid_play_w/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/n11qxi/update_hgen_humanigen_short_term_covid_play_w/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 14:34:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**TL;DR:&lt;/strong&gt; Short term COVID play with great long term potential in CAR-T therapy (and more). Lenzilumab&amp;#39;s recent P3 results cements it as the #1 current therapeutic in hospitalized COVID patients. Application submission for emergency use authorization (EUA) will come any day now (maybe today!) and cause a greater spike than when it went from $14-&amp;gt;$29 following P3 topline data release. &amp;gt;5x ROI based on potential COVID sales and CAR-T implications is very possible. Great entry point currently at $18.60 (1bil market cap).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may or may not have seen my original post on Mar. 25 (copy and pasted below) talking about Humanigen&amp;#39;s variant agnostic COVID drug Lenzilumab, which is primed to have a significant role in hospitalized COVID patients, CAR-T (cancer therapy), and more! Since my post, there have been plenty of positive catalysts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Humanigen released positive topline data in it&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://s27.q4cdn.com/938944131/files/doc_presentations/Lenzilumab-Phase-3-Results-v8-RXMD-032921-0555h.pdf&quot;&gt;phase 3 clinical trial&lt;/a&gt; studying Lenzilumab in hospitalized COVID patients. Lenzilumab met the studies primary endpoint (ventilator free survival through day 28) with a &lt;strong&gt;54% relative improvement&lt;/strong&gt; in VFS over and above current standard of care (remdesevir and/or steroids). Tocilizumab, a significantly inferior (but similar - works downstream of GM-CSF) immunomodulator is currently used often in hospitalized COVID patients. It only produced a &lt;strong&gt;18%&lt;/strong&gt; relative improvement in VFS, and yet has made Roche a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fiercepharma.com/manufacturing/novartis-inks-third-covid-19-production-pact-time-for-roche-s-arthritis-med-actemra&quot;&gt;boatload of money&lt;/a&gt; and continues to be produced for COVID treatment. The drug generated 2.9bil in sales, which is a 32% increase from last year, and that increase is largely due to COVID. Simply put, this study has shown that Lenzilumab is currently the &lt;strong&gt;best therapeutic for hospitalized COVID patients.&lt;/strong&gt; Next step is to file for EUA application, which will c&lt;strong&gt;ome any day now&lt;/strong&gt;. For reference, the last COVID therapeutic (Eli lilly&amp;#39;s baricitinib) took just over a month from topline P3 data release to EUA submission. Also, Merck&amp;#39;s (now discontinued) COVID therapeutic was given the stop sign by the FDA approx. 20 days after P3 data release saying that they needed more data before submission. Basically, if there was an issue w/ Lenzilumab, I expect we would&amp;#39;ve heard by now. &lt;strong&gt;I expect successful application submission and eventual approval&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Humanigen reported positive phase 1b) results w/ Lenzilumab in it&amp;#39;s CAR-T study &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20210419005250/en/Humanigen-Reports-Positive-Data-With-Lenzilumab-in-the-ZUMA-19-CAR-T-Phase-1b-Study-in-DLBCL-and-Plans-to-Initiate-a-Potential-Registrational-Study&quot;&gt;Zuma-19&lt;/a&gt;. One big issue with CAR-T is its side effects - cytokine release syndrome and severe neurotoxicity. Lenzilumab prevents this, and the results of this study showed that. All 6 patients had an objective response rate (4 of them being complete), and no patients had severe CRS or NT at the recommended phase 2 dose. Given the promising results, $HGEN terminated their collaboration with KITE and plans to initiate a phase 2 study with &lt;strong&gt;all commercially available&lt;/strong&gt; CD19 CAR-T therapies in diffuse large b-cell lymphoma (DLBCL).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Following the Zuma news, Humanigen brought on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20210421005213/en/Humanigen-Appoints-Dr.-Adrian-Kilcoyne-to-the-role-of-Chief-Medical-Officer&quot;&gt;Dr. Adrian Kilcoyne&lt;/a&gt; to be their CMO. Dr. Kilcoyne has a long history with big pharma (and was previously working for AstraZeneca), and has had extensive experience in CAR-T. Interestingly, he worked for Celgene corporation when they were acquired by Bristol-Myer Squibb. He oversaw the development of a DLBCL drug and was the US lymphoma CAR-T lead supporting the clinical development and launch preparation of Breyzani. Extremely bullish move for an expert in CAR-T to leave his cushy big pharma job and join Humanigen (his first small biotech company venture) following promising CAR-T clinical trial results imo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More CAR-T news: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/8ZiAr74&quot;&gt;Recent Abstract&lt;/a&gt; released (both CEO and CSO are authors) showing CAR-T cells w/ GM-CSF knock out ameliorates CAR-T cell early activation, reduces activation-induced cell death, and enhances antitumor activity. This is good. Another article &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nature.com/articles/s41421-021-00255-4&quot;&gt;(published in nature&lt;/a&gt;) shows that GM-CSF knockout in CAR-T cells significantly improves side effects and maintains good efficacy: 0/3 patients exhibited neurotoxicity, and no CRS was observed in 2 patients (the third had grade 2 CRS). All 3 patients had complete responses. As I mentioned, Humanigen has a massive IP portfolio in GM-CSF neutralization, including GM-CSF knock out cells (&lt;a href=&quot;https://money.cnn.com/news/newsfeeds/articles/globenewswire/7673719.htm&quot;&gt;exclusive license w/ Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt;). ARK investments believes the cellular therapy TAM is &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/TrumanFalkner/status/1382747618913046528&quot;&gt;absolutely massive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eversana, one of Humanigen&amp;#39;s partners, is actively recruiting for account manager positions across the United States for commercialization of Lenzilumab. (search on Lin$%^#%.com)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/humanigen/status/1380556227302854660?s=20&quot;&gt;Milestone payment&lt;/a&gt; from KPM Tech and Telcon RF Pharma (HGEN&amp;#39;s Phillipines/Korean partner) for their successful P3 results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.clinicaltrials.gov/ct2/show/NCT04583969&quot;&gt;NIH ACTIV-5 trial&lt;/a&gt; has added recruitment sites since release of P3 data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Humanigen also announced &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20210409005083/en/Humanigen-Announces-Positive-Results-From-Phase-1-Study-of-Ifabotuzumab-in-Glioblastoma-Multiforme&quot;&gt;positive phase 1 results&lt;/a&gt; for their solid tumor targeting drug (different drug!) Ifabotuzumab in glioblastoma. Additional studies are planned to evaluate ifabotuzumab as an antibody-drug conjugate in solid tumor patients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nasdaq.com/market-activity/stocks/hgen/short-interest&quot;&gt;8.5mil shares short as of April 15&lt;/a&gt;. About 25% of the float and approx. 6 days to cover given the low volume trading. Given the illiquidity, there is a bit of a short squeeze potential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/market-data/quotes/HGEN/research-ratings&quot;&gt;average price target&lt;/a&gt; of analysts for $HGEN is $34.29 ($21-$43)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After P3 results were released Mar. 29, HGEN shot up to $29 dollars and eventually settled around $22 dollars. HGEN then had a 5m share offering at $18.50 to increase funds for manufacturing. This dilution, along with a rough downtrend for the biotech market and the susceptibility to shorting given it&amp;#39;s low volume, HGEN fell to around $13 dollars (admittedly, I was very wrong about the response to P3 data release in my original post). It has since rebounded and is still at a &lt;strong&gt;great entry point&lt;/strong&gt; at $18.60 (anything sub-20 is a steal imo), close to it&amp;#39;s recent offering. As mentioned in my original post, Humanigen has consistently stated the goal to produce 100k doses in the next year with an approximate $1bil revenue. This doesn&amp;#39;t include stockpiling or potential ex-US partnerships. With a current market cap of about $1bil, Humanigen &lt;strong&gt;can absolutely 5x their current value&lt;/strong&gt; based on COVID sales alone, and CAR-T implications massively increases $HGEN&amp;#39;s ceiling as a long term hold. Humanigen is also a prime buyout target and their CEO Dr. Durrant specializes in these turnarounds. Given the market response to the P3 release, I expect the successful filing of EUA application to cause an even greater spike in the &lt;strong&gt;$40ish+ range.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/u/weentown/&quot;&gt;u/weentown&lt;/a&gt; also posted some great DD yesterday about $HGEN: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbetsOGs/comments/n0hhzn/hgen_humanigen_due_diligence/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbetsOGs/comments/n0hhzn/hgen_humanigen_due_diligence/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other catalysts to watch out for: News regarding government orders of Lenzilumab, full release of P3 data in a peer-reviewed journal, ACTIV-5 updates, CAR-T updates&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------Originally posted Mar. 25 on &lt;a href=&quot;https://old.reddit.com/r/stocks&quot;&gt;r/stocks&lt;/a&gt;: Humanigen ($HGEN), led by CEO Cameron Durant and CSO Dale Chappell, is a clinical stage biopharmaceutical company currently trading at $13.76 (market cap approx $740 million) that most notably makes the Anti-GM-CSF drug **Lenzilumab. It&amp;#39;s phase 3 study for severe COVID has been completed and results will be out by end of march. With a successful phase 3 trial, Humanigen will apply and likely be granted Emergency Use authorization (EUA) for production and use of Lenzilumab&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**What is it?**:&lt;/strong&gt; Lenzilumab is a proprietary ( +100 Patents in GM-CSF, CAR-T, CRS, GvHD) Humaneered® anti-human granulocyte macrophage-colony stimulating factor (GM-CSF) monoclonal antibody that is designed to prevent and treat an immune hyper-response called cytokine storm, a complication considered to be a leading cause of COVID-19 death. Lenzilumab targets severe COVID – patients hospitalized w/ COVID and O2 saturation &amp;lt;94% on room air (90% of hospitalized patients).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**How does it work?**:&lt;/strong&gt; GM-CSF is an inflammatory signaling protein that causes a multitude of downstream effects. Blah blah blah, the details don’t matter, but what does matter is that this shit kills people with COVID. Here’s a recent bombshell article from &lt;a href=&quot;https://immunology.sciencemag.org/content/6/57/eabg9873&quot;&gt;Science Immunology&lt;/a&gt; that shows the distinct role of GM-CSF in severe COVID-19. What’s also very important is that this is produced by OUR BODIES. Not the virus. Lenzilumab doesn’t target the virus – it is not susceptible to resistance from mutant strains (#variantagnostic). From the article: “GM-CSF is elevated early, scaled with severity, and is central to the inflammatory response in COVID-19.”… “Our findings support therapeutic targeting of GM-CSF, as previously suggested on theoretical grounds”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s another recent study that further implicated GM-CSF in COVID: &lt;a href=&quot;https://jlb.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/JLB.3COVCRA0920-628RR&quot;&gt;Journal of Leukocyte Biology&lt;/a&gt;. From the article: &amp;quot;Our findings fully support the emerging notion that GM‐CSF might be a key feature of SARS‐CoV‐2‐induced cytokine storm in COVID‐19 patients&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Does it work?**:&lt;/strong&gt; We will find out soon. The company consistently stated Phase 3 results will be released by end of March. 60 days from last date of patient enrollment will be Mar. 29, and with some secondary endpoints being at the 60 day mark, I would not be surprised if data is released on the Monday. Until that day comes, there has been a lot of evidence suggesting that it will be successful. I’ve already talked about GM-CSF and studies implicating it&amp;#39;s involvement and role in severe COVID lung pathology, and here&amp;#39;s more:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mayoclinicproceedings.org/article/S0025-6196(20&quot;&gt;Open-label study published by the Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt;30989-7/fulltext) --&amp;gt; Study showed Clinical Improvement (defined as improvement of at least 2 points on the 8-point ordinal clinical endpoints scale) in 11 of 12 (91.7%) patients treated with lenzilumab and 22 of 27 (81.5%) untreated patients. The time to clinical improvement was significantly shorter for the lenzilumab-treated group compared with the untreated cohort with a median of 5 days versus 11 days (&lt;em&gt;P&lt;/em&gt;=.006)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An interim analysis of HGEN’s Phase 3 RCT (&lt;a href=&quot;https://clinicaltrials.gov/ct2/show/NCT04351152&quot;&gt;NCT04351152&lt;/a&gt;) showed promising results – with a 37% increase in recovery rate at Day 28 vs. Standard of care treatment. Study size (small sizes being an issue w/ many COVID therapeutics thus far) was increased to help maintain power of the study at 90% based on these results. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.biospace.com/article/releases/humanigen-announces-positive-interim-phase-3-data-of-lenzilumab-in-patients-hospitalized-with-covid-19/&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Otilimab – a drug from $GSK that also targets GM-CSF – recently failed their Phase 3 study. How is that good? Well, despite it being severely underdosed (single 90mg dose w/ shorter half life vs. 1800mg total dose of lenzilumab w/ longer half life) and including patients already on mechanical ventilation (further in disease course), they STILL proved statistical significance in their age 70+ group of patients. Lenzliumab has approx.. 45% of their patients age 65+ (which have a 35-80x risk of hospitalization and 1100-7900x risk of death compared to adolescents as per CDC) as per their interim phase 3 report as compared to 22% in the otilimab trial. The increased dose, greater drug half-life, and better patient population bodes very well for Lenzilumab’s chance of success&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Here’s a recent bullish letter to the editor from [&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7833532/?fbclid=IwAR3RqXf3i6T9xPnFja_mb5b6p86rLF51SyOXOGimPD5Kgoij0QpBJW87tBs&quot;&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt;]: “Aware of the good safety profile of lenzilumab in this current study and previous analysis, the treatment is feasible and safe and the ongoing randomized phase III trial will extensively confirm the lymphocyte recovery in SARS-CoV-2 infection and the impact of the drug on coronavirus disease 2019 clinical improvement”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ACTIV-5 / Big Effect Trial (BET-B) for the Treatment of COVID (NCT04583969): Funded and selected by the NIH – this studies Lenzilumab combined with Remdesvir for the treatment of COVID. Not hard evidence of lenzilumab’s efficacy, but evidence that Lenzilumab has showed enough promise to warrant being chosen for such a trial&lt;strong&gt;Competition&lt;/strong&gt;- There is none right now. All COVID therapeutics that target severe COVID have been dropping like flies. It’s all for the taking if this phase 3 study succeeds and Emergency Use approval Is granted&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COVID – getting worse:&lt;/strong&gt; As many of you might’ve heard, COVID isn’t going away. In fact, there are multiple new variants that are more infectious, more deadly, and more resistant to current vaccinations. Across the globe, COVID cases are rising again and certain areas are being hit especially hard. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ctvnews.ca/health/coronavirus/india-detects-double-mutant-coronavirus-variant-1.5360271&quot;&gt;CTV news article re: India w/ it’s new double mutant variant&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/19/europe/coronavirus-europe-third-wave-intl/index.html&quot;&gt;CNN&lt;/a&gt; re: Europe dealing with a surge in cases, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://globalnews.ca/news/7720211/brazil-record-cases-covid-19/&quot;&gt;global news&lt;/a&gt; re: Brazil hitting record number COVID cases, to name a few. New COVID cases in the US remain pretty low, but between lax restriction and the rise of variant strains &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-021-00564-4&quot;&gt;as this nature article shows&lt;/a&gt;, we could be seeing another wave in the US as well. How deadly are these new strains? Still much to be learned, but it’s looking like current vaccines leave a lot to be desired. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMc2100362&quot;&gt;Here’s a study from the New England Journal of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, which studied viral neutralization of some new variants w/ our current vaccines (refer to Table 1). $PFE has decreased (in vitro) efficacy by 2x, 6.7x, &amp;lt;6.5x vs. B117, P1, 501YV2 variants. $MRNA vaccine has decreased efficacy by 1.8x, 4.5x, &amp;lt;8.6xGoogle cases worldwide and you will see the # of new COVID cases/day have started to rise after hitting a trough in mid-Feb. Between COVID fatigue and places easing restrictions and the new variants mentioned above, COVID is here to stay and will be for years to come. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-021-00396-2&quot;&gt;Here’s an article from nature&lt;/a&gt;, which talks about COVID being a endemic virus that we will be dealing with on a year to year basis. Unfortunately, the market is huge for #lenzilumab&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Partnerships&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Humanigen was the only micro cap company chosen for &lt;strong&gt;Operation Warp Speed&lt;/strong&gt; (an initiative to facilitate and accelerate the development, manufacturing, and distribution of COVID-19 vaccines, therapeutics, and diagnostics) -&amp;gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://ir.humanigen.com/news/news-details/2020/Humanigen-Announces-Cooperative-Research-and-Development-Agreement-with-the-US-government-to-Develop-Lenzilumab-for-COVID-19/default.aspx&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;. Humanigen in collaboration with BARDA to increase manufacturing capacity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;License agreement with KPM Tech/Telcon RF Pharamceutical company for Lenzilumab production in South Korea and the Phillipines. [&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20201103005167/en/Humanigen-Executes-Licensing-Agreement-for-Lenzilumab%E2%84%A2-in-COVID-19-with-KPM-TechTelcon-RF-Pharmaceutical-for-South-Korea-and-the-Philippines&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partnership with Thermo Fisher to scale up manufacturing. [&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fiercepharma.com/manufacturing/humanigen-thermo-fisher-reach-agreement-to-scale-up-manufacturing-monoclonal-antibody&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partnership with Emergent Biosolutions for development and manufacturing. [&lt;a href=&quot;https://investors.emergentbiosolutions.com/news-releases/news-release-details/humanigen-and-emergent-biosolutions-announce-contract-0&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partnership w/ Avid Bioservices for manufacturing agreement. [&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20210203005204/en/Humanigen-and-Avid-Bioservices-Enter-Into-cGMP-Manufacturing-Agreement-for-COVID-19-Therapeutic-Candidate-Lenzilumab-in-Support-of-Potential-EUA-Filing&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not a partnership, but $HGEN recently announced an $80million loan w/ Hercules Capital on Mar. 10 to support manufacturing and commercialization. Bullish move close to P3 data release imo. [&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20210310005879/en/Humanigen-Announces-80-Million-Loan-Facility-from-Hercules-Capital&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR - lots of partnerships and agreements in place for manufacturing if EUA approval granted&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Market:&lt;/strong&gt; Here’s a PDF PowerPoint of $HGEN corporate presentation: &lt;a href=&quot;https://ir.humanigen.com/events-and-presentations/default.aspx&quot;&gt;Humanigen&lt;/a&gt;. The whole presentation gives a great overview of the company and I recommend a look through, but skip to slide 18 and you can get a rough sense of the market potential. There are 3 sources of incomes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stockpiling – US and ex-US&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;US market&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outside the US market&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;US market: Conservative estimates from the company believes there will be 1,000,000+ hospitalizations in the US this year, with approximately 100,000 patients as a market for Lenzilumab treatment. At 10k per dose, an approximate 1bil of revenue is up for the takingOutside the US market:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The market is there with cases numbers rising across the globe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Humanigen has been in discussion with ex-US governments already about production of lenzilumab (skip to 24:00 on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://ir.humanigen.com/events-and-presentations/default.aspx&quot;&gt;Mar 16 fireside chat webcast&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price forecasting:Conservative estimates from the company project 100k doses for the US alone in 2021 if given EUA approval. This gives approximate revenue of 1bil. This doesn’t include any non-US sales or stockpiling.With positive phase 3 trial data, I see the price share easily shooting up to 50-60+. The next step would be applying for Emergency Use Approval, with acceptance likely if P3 study is successful. If granted, and going by the very conservative estimate of $1billion in revenue, I think $HGEN’s market cap will easily be $5bil+, giving it a PPS of roughly $100+&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BONUS -&amp;gt; HIGH SHORT INTEREST: $HGEN short interest has almost doubled from Feb 26-&amp;gt;Mar 15!!!. Yahoo finance estimates a 26% short interest as of Mar 15 w/ a Short ratio of 4.12 given the stock’s low trading volume. With the recent drop in price the past couple days, I would not be surprised if this number was higher. TL;DR -&amp;gt; more fuel for the rocket ships&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BONUS BONUS – CAR-T implications and more:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lenzilumab is a cytokine storm drug, not a COVID drug. It is also in a phase 1b/2 study (ZUMA-19) where it is paired w/ a CAR-T drug Yescarta (by $GILD) for the treatment of relapsed/refractory Large B-Cell lymphoma. Car-T therapy is basically genetically engineered T-cells that can target a specific protein, or cancer. The main issue with CAR-T therapy is that it has significant side effects via cytokine storm and neurologic toxicity. Early studies have already shown that Lenzilumab significantly reduces cytokine storm side effects in CAR-T and actually IMPROVES overall efficacy. The readout for this study is planned for this year and there is precedent for CAR-T FDA approval based on phase 2 studies. I don’t have the energy to go into detail so I will leave it at that, but this has HUGE long term possibilities and gives $HGEN significant long term value outside of COVID&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**Edit to expand on CAR-T a bit more: I don’t want to downplay this, I think it’s very promising and I’m very bullish on it, but I’m admittedly not as researched on the minutia and writing up covid stuff tired me out XD. There’s 3 main players in the Car-T space and Lenzilumab (which has the patent for preventing Cytokine storm and neurotoxicity related to T cell therapy) could be the missing piece to make this therapy safer. $GILD had dropped another anti-GM-CSF drug from $KNSA and decided to go ahead with just lenzilumab, as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lenzilumab also is in a phase 2/3 study for preventing/treating acute GvHD and also CMML phase 2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$HGEN also has ifabotuzumab, a drug for treating solid tumors, which is currently in phase 1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**TL;DR: Short term covid play w/ ++high upside (potential 5-10x ROI) and high short-interest w/ long term CAR-T potential.*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imo, $HGEN is a very appealing short term, high risk phase 3 COVID trial play with extremely high reward. With successful P3 studies, I see the PPS skyrocketing to 60+ and w/ EUA to 100+ (5bil+ market cap) as a conservative estimate. With stockpiling and ex-USA partnerships, the PPS will soar past 100 and w/ CAR-T the potential is even greater. Of course, the downside is a failed trial and price plummets to around $6 I think. Given the stocks low float and low trading volume, it is very volatile and subject to easy price manipulation. It has dropped approx. 25% the past month down to $13.76 and is extremely appealing at this price range. There is downside, but the upside is much much greater.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;POSITION: 1250 @ $16.30&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[雖然不多，但這是一個開始。$MNMD LETS GO.]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n0jus8/its_not_much_but_its_a_start_mnmd_lets_go/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/n0jus8/its_not_much_but_its_a_start_mnmd_lets_go/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 13:53:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>