<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 06:41:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[试图与华尔街的鲨鱼一起游泳的猿人]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/pfdpqc/apes_trying_to_swim_with_wallstreet_sharks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/pfdpqc/apes_trying_to_swim_with_wallstreet_sharks/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 23:55:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在应税账户中持有共同基金是否总是坏事？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想在应税账户中获得更多的国际风险，但我不确定是选择ETF（VT）还是共同基金（FZILX）。
我不确定是选择ETF（VT）还是共同基金（FZILX）。

什么更有意义？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/pfdohf/is_it_always_bad_to_hold_mutual_funds_in_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/pfdohf/is_it_always_bad_to_hold_mutual_funds_in_a/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 23:55:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am trying to get more international exposure in a taxable account but I&amp;#39;m not sure whether to go for an ETF (VT) or a mutual fund (FZILX).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What makes more sense?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[三次接种疫苗的以色列登记了创纪录的丙型肝炎病例，11,000 *。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432788188620279812</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432788188620279812</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 23:42:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[心理市场回顾 - 2021年8月31日，星期二]]></title><description><![CDATA[今天股市的涨势有所降温，所有三个主要指数都在今天的交易中小幅飘红。
今天交易小幅收红，但有望结束一个出色的月份，其中
标准普尔500指数（SPY）在8月份的涨幅超过2.5%，连续7个月上涨。
涨幅。到目前为止，标普500指数今年迄今的涨幅达到了惊人的20%。市场...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pfeb4x/psychomarket_recap_tuesday_august_31_2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pfeb4x/psychomarket_recap_tuesday_august_31_2021/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 23:30:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rally in equities somewhat cooled today, with all three major indexes trading modestly red today but are on track to close out a stellar month, with the S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) gaining more than 2.5% in August, its seven straight month of gains. So far, the SPY is up a staggering 20% year-to-date. Market participants continue to digest the Federal Reserve’s annual Jackson Hole Symposium and a key speech by Chairman Jerome Powell on Friday. Looking ahead, market participants await a busy week for new economic data, with the August Jobs Report due out on Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BMO Capital Markets became the latest financial firm to raise its end of the year price target for the SPY. Brian Belski, the company’s Chief Investment Strategist, wrote in a note to clients that he now expects the index to end the year at $480, up from his original estimate of $450. He cites the “blistering rate” of corporate earnings amid a strengthening economic backdrop. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite hawkish statements by other Federal Reserve members in the July meeting minutes, in his speech Powell remained highly accommodative, suggesting he was more inclined to wait to see further progress in the economy before tapering QE, especially in light of surging infections due to the Delta variant. Powell said, “At the FOMC&amp;#39;s recent July meeting, I was of the view, as were most participants, that if the economy evolved broadly as anticipated, it could be appropriate to start reducing the pace of asset purchases this year. The intervening month has brought more progress in the form of a strong employment report for July, but also the further spread of the Delta variant. We will be carefully assessing incoming data and the evolving risks. Even after our asset purchases end, our elevated holdings of longer-term securities will continue.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Powell once again urged caution since the economic recovery in the market is still undergoing, saying effects from an ill-timed policy shift would “arrive after the need has passed” and “could be particularly harmful. Here is the full quote, “The main influence of monetary policy on inflation can come after a lag of a year or more. If a central bank tightens policy in response to factors that turn out to be temporary, the main policy effects are likely to arrive after the need has passed. The ill-timed policy move unnecessarily slows hiring and other economic activity and pushes inflation lower than desired. Today, with substantial slack remaining in the labor market and the pandemic continuing, such a mistake could be particularly harmful. We know that extended periods of unemployment can mean lasting harm to workers and to the productive capacity of the economy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the full transcript from the speech, I encourage everyone to read it fully. It’s not very long and is extremely insightful to see exactly what the main monetary policy-maker thinks of the current state of the economy&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/speech/powell20210827a.htm&quot;&gt;https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/speech/powell20210827a.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Liu, Founder and CEO of Clearnomics, said of Powell’s speech, “We do think that tapering, in general, will be a non-event, most likely because first, the market has had time to react throughout this year. The Fed has done a great job telegraphing this. Whether it’s September or November for the announcement of taper will really depend on the jobs report coming up and some more economic data. But regardless, the market seems to expect it at this point. This is very different from 2013 when the market had to adjust very abruptly to taper.” In my humble opinion, I totally agree with this sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;U.S. home prices surged by the most in 30 years at the beginning of this summer as tight inventory levels and elevated demand combined to drag on affordability. The S&amp;amp;P CoreLogic Case-Shiller national home price index jumped 18.6% in June over last year, accelerating from a 16.8% rise in May. This also marked the 13th straight month of accelerating price increases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Footwear startup Allbirds, which is known for making shoes with only environmentally safe and sustainable materials, filed to go public via IPO. Its backers include Oscar-winning actor Leonardo DiCaprio and Adidas, which has partnered with the company to make a range of sustainable sneakers. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The intense regulatory crackdown in China continues. Yesterday, the Chinese Communist Party announced minors were forbidden to play video games for more than three hours a week (only on the weekends). Recently, state media has been rallying against video games, calling them “spiritual opium”. The restrictions apply to any devices including phones and are a massive blow to the global gaming industry that caters to tens of millions of young players in the world&amp;#39;s most lucrative market.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Zoom (ZM, the defining work from home stock, slid more than 15% after reporting earnings due to concerns of growth slowing down.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tesla (TSLA) received regulatory approval from the Indian government that certifies all car models as “roadworthy”. This is big as India is the world’s second-most populous country.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current stock price was written during the session and may not reflect closing prices.*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple (AAPL) target raised by Fundamental Research from $144 to $164 at Buy. Stock currently around $152&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anthem (ANTM) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $459 to $468 at Overweight. Stock currently around $375&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BlackRock (BLK) target raised by Jefferies Financial from $1001 to $1075 at Buy. Stock currently around $942&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Catalent (CTLT) with a host of target raises. Average price target $150 at Buy. Stock currently around $130&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CVS Health (CVS) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $99 to $114 at Overweight. Stock currently around $86&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generac (GNRC) target raised by Piper Sandler from $480 to $510 at Overweight. Stock currently around $437&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Humana (HUM) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $500 to $513 at Overweight. Stock currently around $405&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Li Auto (LI) target raised by Bank of America from $39 to $42 at Buy. Stock currently around $30&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LabCorp (LH) target raised by $273 to $368 at Overweight. Stock currently around $304. Stock currently around $305&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lowe’s (LOW) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $230 to $240 at Overweight. Stock currently around $204&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Knowing yourself is the beginning of all wisdom.” - Aristotle&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[疫苗接种后的心肌梗塞（样本量900） https://t.co/BQVr3IJcG3]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432830751607767040</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432830751607767040</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 22:40:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝登称美国历史上最大的国家尴尬--撤离阿富汗是 "非凡的成功" *。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432787952472633357</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432787952472633357</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 21:37:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国房价升值与整体通胀之间的差距从未如此之大。https://t.co/2bDKu02OS3]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432762948695515139</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432762948695515139</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 21:37:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者要像...]]></title><description><![CDATA[ * 过去的表现并不保证未来的结果... 你应该回测
   每个投资组合
 * 你为什么要使用该ETF？你应该使用这个ETF，它有相同的
   持有的股票
 * 太多的科技产品... MSFT和AAPL是最好的公司
 * 赚了钱就要交税！!
 * 这...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pfbgkx/investors_be_like/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pfbgkx/investors_be_like/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 21:23:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Past performance is not a guarantee of future results... You should back test every portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why are you using that ETF? You should use this ETF that has the same holdings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Too much tech... MSFT and AAPL are the best companies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have to pay taxes when you earn money!!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;That expense ratio is 0.6%!!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The market is going to crash... Buy and hold forever&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do your due diligence... Just buy index funds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Warren Buffet says...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是否应该利用雇主的股票发行计划？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在一家大型电信公司工作，该公司的股票在每个季度的最低交易额时提供15%的折扣。
每季度交易的美元数额。(编辑：我刚刚仔细检查，他们
改变了这一点... 它不再是基于最低的一天，而是基于开盘和收盘之间的哪一个
季度开盘和收盘之间较低的金额...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/pfciqs/should_i_utilize_an_employer_stock_offering/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/pfciqs/should_i_utilize_an_employer_stock_offering/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 21:23:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I work at a large telecom company that offers 15% off its stock at the lowest dollar amount it traded for each quarter. (EDIT: I just double checked and they changed this... It&amp;#39;s no longer based off the lowest day, but rather whichever amount was lower between the opening and closing day of the quarter.) So, for example, each paycheck I can select to debit x% from my paycheck and have that held within my Fidelity account, and then at the end of the quarter that money I&amp;#39;ve accumulated is put toward the stock with the discount included.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seems like a pretty good deal, but the stock itself has only increased 84% in the past 5 years looking at the charts on Robinhood. I say &amp;quot;only&amp;quot; because relative to some other growth stocks that&amp;#39;s nothing to write home about... but I feel like it&amp;#39;s a pretty stable company that probably won&amp;#39;t be going anywhere any time soon given its diversification, and with the discount included, obviously those gains would be a little higher, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it were you, would you enroll in this program? How much would you put into the employee stock versus a 401k / other investment accounts? Right now I put 6% into 401k (which is what they match), only 1% into the employee stock, and I&amp;#39;ve been doing some Robinhood ETFs/index funds/single stocks on the side as well as Coinbase for crypto... I&amp;#39;m just trying to figure out how much to diversify across these in terms of percentages. My income is about $100k this year but I&amp;#39;m in sales so it fluctuates. Last year was lower due to COVID. I was thinking of upping the employee stock to 3% but I&amp;#39;m just not sure long-term what my best bet would be... I guess the other nice advantage with this is that the funds are able to be sold after 1.5 years unlike a 401k, so it is relatively liquid in case of a rainy day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么中联重科的股价会跌得这么厉害？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我上个月买了ZM的股票，它一直在下跌。今天它自己是16.23%
下跌。有什么事情发生吗，有什么消息吗？我是一个新的投资者，在美国以外的地方投资
来自美国以外的地方。

你认为我应该持有吗？我在雅虎财经上看到，尽管收益报告不错，但它还是在下跌。
一个好的收益报告。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pf8wyc/why_is_zoom_share_price_falling_so_much/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pf8wyc/why_is_zoom_share_price_falling_so_much/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 20:36:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I bought ZM shares last month and it&amp;#39;s been falling. Today its self is 16.23% down. Is there anything happening any news? I am a new investor and investing from outside of the US.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you think I should hold? I saw on yahoo finance that it&amp;#39;s going down despite a good earnings report.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[房地产的繁荣仍在继续，美国房价再次创下历史新高，在过去一年中上涨了18.6%。这是有史以来最高的年度增长速度。https://t.co/EtYfKDzgYU]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432727558647394305</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432727558647394305</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 19:43:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[绿色鞋子和生活方式品牌Allbirds申请IPO，计划以 "BIRD "的名义在纳斯达克上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[绿色生活方式品牌公司Allbirds申请进行首次公开募股。
周二，计划在纳斯达克上市，股票代码为 "BIRD"。摩根
摩根士丹利、摩根大通和博鳌亚洲论坛证券是17家银行中的主承销商。
银行中担任主承销商。募集资金将用于一般...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pf5ov4/green_shoe_and_lifestyle_brand_allbirds_files_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pf5ov4/green_shoe_and_lifestyle_brand_allbirds_files_for/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 19:43:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Allbirds, a green lifestyle brand company, filed for an initial public offering on Tuesday with plans to list on Nasdaq under the ticker symbol &amp;quot;BIRD.&amp;quot; Morgan Stanley, JPMorgan and BofA Securities are lead underwriters among a team of 17 banks working on the deal. Proceeds are to be used for general corporate purposes and working capital. &amp;quot;Allbirds is a global lifestyle brand that innovates with naturally derived materials to make better footwear and apparel products in a better way, while treading lighter on our planet,&amp;quot; says the company&amp;#39;s prospectus. The company, based in San Francisco, had a net loss of $21.5 million in the first six months of 2021, wider than the loss of $9.3 million posted in the year-earlier period. Revenue rose to $117.5 million from $92.8 million a year before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局的顶级疫苗监管人员格鲁伯、克劳斯，卸任**。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432741331147890697</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432741331147890697</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 18:48:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BABA是上一季度美国最大投资者中买入最多的股票。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dataroma是一个跟踪72位所谓的 "超级投资家 "的网站，看看他们在做什么。
他们一直在做什么。每个季度它都会收集每个投资者的13F文件
并编制一份所谓的 "聪明钱 "的前10名股票名单。
目前购买的股票。这些投资者是一些最大和最...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pf97f1/baba_is_the_most_bought_stock_amongst_the_biggest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pf97f1/baba_is_the_most_bought_stock_amongst_the_biggest/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 17:57:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dataroma is a website that tracks 72 so called &amp;#39;superinvestors&amp;#39; to see what they&amp;#39;ve been up to. Every quarter it takes every 13F filing for each investor and compiles a list of the top 10 stocks that so called &amp;#39;smart money&amp;#39; is currently buying. These investors are some of the biggest and most influential investors in the world today including: Warren Buffett, Charlie Munger, Bill Gates, Seth Klarman , Bill Ackman, Carl Icahn, Michael Burry, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The number #1 ranked stock that big investors have bought this last quarter is &lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/MxzqV4N.png&quot;&gt;Alibaba&lt;/a&gt;. It is ranked past Google, Facebook, Amazon, Netflix and so many other companies. Thought this was interesting so I wanted to share. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dataroma.com/m/g/portfolio_b.php?q=q&amp;amp;o=c&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[可以停放的红利股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，我从买入期权，到卖出期权（目前仍在卖出一小部分投资组合），再到现在忙于工作，想直接买入期权，已经走过了很长的路。
我的投资组合中的一小部分），到现在忙于工作，想把我的钱存入银行。
把我的钱停在可靠的长期分红公司里。目前我有
部分INTC、TAK、VZ、MPW、K。我正在考虑Walgreens、...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pf5iaf/dividend_stocks_to_park_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pf5iaf/dividend_stocks_to_park_in/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 16:26:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I’ve come a long way from buying options, to selling options (still do with a small portion of my portfolio), to now being busy with work and wanting to just park my money in solid long term dividend paying companies. Currently I have portions of INTC, TAK, VZ, MPW, K. I am considering Walgreens, STAG, and SONY. I am also considering O but it’s a bit high right now. What are some recommendations?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[新手投资者。我持有股份的公司正在经历一场恶意收购。我应该持有还是出售？]]></title><description><![CDATA[请原谅我对术语的无知。我有一家公司的股票
公司，该公司的平均交易价格通常在0.40左右。另一家公司正在
试图通过出价0.75来接管。
显然，与另一家公司有某种竞标战。该公司的董事会已经建议...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/pf5v06/novice_investor_company_i_have_shares_in_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/pf5v06/novice_investor_company_i_have_shares_in_is/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 15:54:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#39;ll have to excuse my ignorance on the terminology. I have stocks in a company that typically trades around 0.40 on average. Another company is attempting a take over by bidding 0.75. apparently there is some sort of bidding war with another company.  The board of the company has recommended shareholders sell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stock price seems to be flatlined at 0.77.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not sure if I should hold or sell. Just in terms of the share price is not quite where it is because of growing market interest, but because of a specific bid by one larger buyer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币市场很疯狂。索拉纳的市值今年已经翻了9倍。开始是7400万美元，现在是350亿美元。

我不知道我们是否曾见过这么多人在这么短的时间内赚了这么多钱。https://t.co/JGnIeMwTK4]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432669814380711942</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432669814380711942</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 15:42:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CRSR：沉睡的巨人，第二回合]]></title><description><![CDATA[昨天，由于一个新的reddit帖子，它再次获得了流行，并且是在
目前处于趋势的前三位。

https://preview.redd.it/p33hk6ilhnk71.png?width=1432&format=png&auto=webp&s=046ca3e0a12b67ad135921d8644051cd3a60ebd5

说一下背景。

太多的人仍然认为他们是RGB和一些...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/pf1lmc/crsr_the_sleeping_giant_round_two/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/pf1lmc/crsr_the_sleeping_giant_round_two/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 15:42:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday it gained popularity again thanks to a new reddit post and is currently in the top 3 trends:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/p33hk6ilhnk71.png?width=1432&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=046ca3e0a12b67ad135921d8644051cd3a60ebd5&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/p33hk6ilhnk71.png?width=1432&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=046ca3e0a12b67ad135921d8644051cd3a60ebd5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To put some context:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Too many people still think they are RGB and some peripherals (mouse, keyboard and headphones).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corsair is a video game holding company. They do pretty much everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corsair has acquired several companies the last 3 years: ScuffGaming, Origin, GamersSensei, Elgato, Visuals By Impulse....&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All that&amp;#39;s left is to enter the mobile gaming world and they will literally dominate the entire gaming market. And seeing their pace of acquisitions, I&amp;#39;m sure they will sooner or later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company is focusing lately on the streaming world (elgato, Visuals By Impulse), which as I&amp;#39;m sure you all know, is growing at an unstoppable pace, competing head to head with traditional television. It is only a matter of time before it becomes the most popular way to consume content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is also looking to improve its service and subscription revenues (ICUE).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the last few months alone they have launched 84 products, shipped 33 million around the world and acquired 3 new companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/1pfyp61vink71.png?width=1865&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=551d205ac2be82b9957d72b3122eea1feb340bef&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/1pfyp61vink71.png?width=1865&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=551d205ac2be82b9957d72b3122eea1feb340bef&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are expanding very aggressively, and currently sell products in 26 categories:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/bgivrap5jnk71.png?width=2126&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=54decbc4db9edf04e461d8c399cb91ec3898fcdd&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/bgivrap5jnk71.png?width=2126&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=54decbc4db9edf04e461d8c399cb91ec3898fcdd&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They have some of the largest communities of all video game brands:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/n5tj29fajnk71.png?width=2153&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=cd9a8f86b39f82507fcc676535f9c711f21b829f&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/n5tj29fajnk71.png?width=2153&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=cd9a8f86b39f82507fcc676535f9c711f21b829f&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of its segments are growing at an astounding rate, but as you can see, the content creators segment is simply incredible. Elgato has a virtual monopoly in the capture, spotlight, streamdeck, green screen and they have just launched a facecam that is getting very good sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/3z1m6txgjnk71.png?width=2224&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=176d3133b42aeaafbca8e71adee6fd8b57e84890&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/3z1m6txgjnk71.png?width=2224&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=176d3133b42aeaafbca8e71adee6fd8b57e84890&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These spectacular results have been achieved at a rather adverse time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shipping costs have risen dramatically due to inflation, especially for container shipments from China.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chip shortages have also been a big problem and, let&amp;#39;s not forget, corsair has a leading position in ram memory, power supplies, magnetic levitation fans, RGB... and nowadays it is very expensive to buy a graphics card. Which has prevented many people from building their own computers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also come from a period of pandemic, many people thought that its sales were going to plummet, but in spite of all this, it has produced very good results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/bficnarjknk71.png?width=919&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=b1f537f44e3f0af2704073175ea1b73c87bc947a&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/bficnarjknk71.png?width=919&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=b1f537f44e3f0af2704073175ea1b73c87bc947a&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do have 500 Shares and few 9/17 30 Calls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[对于20多岁的Boglehead投资者来说：你的投资组合中有多少百分比包括债券？]]></title><description><![CDATA[此外，在这轮牛市中，你的投资组合是否更多地转向了债券？
债券？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/peu4uy/for_the_boglehead_investors_in_their_20s_what/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/peu4uy/for_the_boglehead_investors_in_their_20s_what/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 15:22:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, has your portfolio shifted more towards bonds at all during this bull run?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你认为是隐藏的宝石的股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[按照标题，这个话题要讨论的是那些还不是主流的股票
但你会发现它们在未来5年内会有很好的表现。

像Moderna（MRNA）或Sea limited（SE）这样的公司，今天还没有被发现。
迄今还没有被发现。

你认为什么将是下一个大戏？

对于...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pf35fq/stocks_that_you_consider_hidden_gems/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pf35fq/stocks_that_you_consider_hidden_gems/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 15:22:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As per title, this topic is to discuss about stocks that are not mainstream yet but you&amp;#39;d see that would be having a great performance in the next 5 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Companies like Moderna (MRNA) or Sea limited (SE), that today have not been discovered yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you think will be the next big play?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, AFRM, been holding since IPO, sold a bounce after the initial spike but despite being in red for most of the time is gaining confidence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如何在一个没有随机漫步迹象的弱无效率的市场中进行长期投资？]]></title><description><![CDATA[从本网站推荐的许多初学者书籍（Bogleheads, Random walk down
华尔街》、《投资的四大支柱》），长期指数投资的论据是
投资的论点在于假设市场是有效的，股票的
价格特征是随机漫步。会发生什么...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/pez3qm/how_to_longterm_invest_in_a_weakly_inefficient/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/pez3qm/how_to_longterm_invest_in_a_weakly_inefficient/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 13:42:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;From many beginners books recommended on this site (Bogleheads, Random walk down Wall Street, The Four Pillars of Investing), the argument for long-term index investing lies on the assumption that the market is efficient and the stock price characteristic is that of a random walk. What would happen then, if that wasn&amp;#39;t the case anymore, as in many frontier markets? Does long-term investment in stock still makes sense? Is index ETF still a good choice when the extra TER in active funds eats up the larger return? Or it&amp;#39;s better to find less volatile forms of investment? How can it be that the large cap index is weakly efficient and shows signs of random walk, while the rest of the market isn&amp;#39;t?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For context, in Vietnam - a frontier market, saving interest has for the first time dip below the average index return of the last decade and current corporate bond rate. The stock market trading volume has doubled in less than 2 years, with a huge influx of new, inexperienced investors and is on the second largest rally in the mere 20 years of its existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[期权不适合新投资者]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/pf3xee/options_are_not_for_new_investors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/pf3xee/options_are_not_for_new_investors/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 13:42:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[遇到了4万块钱的黑钱，考虑将其投资于股票。辞掉工作是因为我想做日间交易。]]></title><description><![CDATA[几周前去了拉斯维加斯，在黑色上打了4万块。我回来后辞去了工作
并考虑买一些股票。我在想，也许日间交易
GME或AMC，这些似乎是最受欢迎的。我只需要1400美元/月的费用
我的开支，我打算也许再拿出2万......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/pevi5k/hit_40k_in_black_and_thinking_about_investing_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/pevi5k/hit_40k_in_black_and_thinking_about_investing_it/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 13:28:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Went to Vegas a few weeks ago and hit 40k on black. I quit my job when I got back and was thinking about buying some stocks. Was looking at maybe day trading GME or AMC, those seem to be the most popular. I only need about $1400/month for my expenses and I’m planing on maybe taking out another 20k loan so I can really go all in on this. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s what I got:
40k winnings + 40k I initially bet with
20k loan from the bank
10k cash advance on my moms credit card&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was thinking an even split on GME and AMC might send me to the moon. My expenses aren’t too bad so I can hold over if nothing is gonna hit just yet plus I’ll have to start paying this cash advance back monthly. Maybe I can get some pointers on other stocks y’all think is worth looking into. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also when do y’all think I should pay off the cash advance? Once I’m bringing in the bags I might just pay it off at once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: my wife’s boyfriend is actually gonna loan me the 10k so I’ll pay him back interest free. No need to advance on my moms card 🙏&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT 2: I’m moving to Vegas, just talked it over with the wife. She said her bf is also moving there too so it’s all falling into place. Y’all are the best ✊&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT 3: Talked to my priest (who was the one who set up my wife and her boyfriend) and he recommended I look into investing in alt coins. It allows me to night trade, so that&amp;#39;s a huge plus. I also see a lot of influencers coming out with their own coins, maybe I can get there someday. Thanks for the help guys!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[九月快到了.....]]></title><description><![CDATA[9月，这个在历史上对股市来说最糟糕的月份即将到来。
几乎是在我们面前。自1950年以来，道琼斯指数在9月份的平均跌幅为0.8%，而标准普尔指数在9月份的平均跌幅为0.5%。
而标准普尔500指数的平均跌幅为0.5%。有些人
这是一个世界性的现象；它并不...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pesdp6/september_is_almost_here/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pesdp6/september_is_almost_here/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 09:17:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;September, the month that is historically the worst for the stock market is almost upon us. Since 1950, the Dow Jones has averaged a decline of 0.8% in September, while the S&amp;amp;P 500 has experienced an average decline of 0.5%. Some call it the &amp;quot;September effect&amp;quot; It&amp;#39;s a worldwide phenomenon; it doesn’t only impact the U.S. markets. Some analysts believe this negative market effect can be attributed to a seasonal behavioral bias created by investors deciding to make changes to their investment portfolios or raising cash at summer’s end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some analysts believe that this negative effect is attributable to a seasonal behavioral bias as investors make changes to their portfolios at summer’s end by “cashing in” on some of their year-to-date gains. Other investors may be preparing for both the end of the current year and positioning investments for next year as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another reason may be that mutual funds, many of which have fiscal years ending in September – the traditional end of the 3rd quarter – and in October, may decide to harvest any short and long-term tax losses by liquidating their negative return holdings before year-end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One other theory points to the fact there are lower trading volumes during the summer months. Many investors take vacation time during the summer and refrain from actively trading their portfolios during this downtime. However, once these vacationing investors return to work, they exit positions they had planned to sell. When this occurs, the market experiences an increased level of selling pressure and, as supply exceeds demand, the markets experience an overall decline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now, not every September has been miserable, so we don&amp;#39;t know what&amp;#39;s to come for September of 2021, so due your own diligence.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[税务建议 - 今年在短线交易上损失了7万多。我应该用什么方法来弥补我的普通收入的损失？收入刚刚超过20万。不是在吹牛，需要真正的建议。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/pes1lr/tax_advice_lost_over_70k_this_year_on_short_term/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/pes1lr/tax_advice_lost_over_70k_this_year_on_short_term/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 06:17:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在$ASTS SpaceMobile上的100万美元YOLO，我通往威利-旺卡巧克力工厂的金票🚀🛰📲🍫🍭🍬。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/pein3f/1_million_yolo_on_asts_ast_spacemobile_my_golden/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/pein3f/1_million_yolo_on_asts_ast_spacemobile_my_golden/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 04:29:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我不惧怕任何人... 但这个，让我害怕]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/peeovf/i_fear_no_man_but_this_it_scares_me/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/peeovf/i_fear_no_man_but_this_it_scares_me/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 04:29:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果有两种疫苗已经被FDA完全批准，Novavax公司（$NVAX）能否获得FDA的紧急使用授权？]]></title><description><![CDATA[$PFE/$BNTX已经获得FDA的全面使用授权，而$MRNA
也应在未来几周内获得全面批准。JNJ将在年底前申请
在今年年底前获得FDA的全面批准。

由于$NVAX甚至不会在FDA的紧急使用下申请批准
许可证，直到...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/pemfe0/can_novavax_nvax_receive_emergency_use/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/pemfe0/can_novavax_nvax_receive_emergency_use/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 02:09:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;$PFE/$BNTX have already received full use authorization from the FDA and $MRNA should also be fully approved in the coming weeks. $JNJ is going to file for full FDA approval by the end of the year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since $NVAX won&amp;#39;t even file for approval under the FDA&amp;#39;s emergency use authorization untile the fourth quarter, will it be able to claim that there is an actual &amp;quot;emergency&amp;quot;. In many ways, U.S. sales are not hugely important to $NVAX but I&amp;#39;d imagine that if they don&amp;#39;t get emergency use authorization the market would react negatively. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will they still qualify for emergency use under these circumstances? How might the market react to approval or denial?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是今天的市场回顾 2021年8月30日，星期一]]></title><description><![CDATA[心理市场回顾--2021年8月30日，星期一

股市交投不一，标普500指数（SPY）和科技股的纳斯达克指数（QQQ
扩大了上周的涨幅，达到新的盘中纪录高点。另一方面
另一方面，由于金融和能源股的疲软，道琼斯指数（DIA）小幅走低。
证券和能源股的疲软，推动了道琼斯指数的小幅下跌...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/peqn8g/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_august_30/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/peqn8g/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_august_30/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 02:09:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Monday, August 30, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks traded mixed, with the S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) and tech-heavy Nasdaq (QQQ) extending gains from last week to reach new intraday record highs. On the other hand, the Dow Jones (DIA) was driven slightly lower due to weakness in financial and energy stocks while the Russell 2000 (IWM), which tracks the performance of small-caps, broke its winning streak to close 0.41% lower. Market participants continue to digest the Federal Reserve’s annual Jackson Hole Symposium and a key speech by Chairman Jerome Powell on Friday. Looking ahead, market participants await a busy week for new economic data, with the August Jobs Report due out on Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite hawkish statements by other Federal Reserve members in the July meeting minus, in his speech Powell remained highly accommodative, suggesting he was more inclined to wait to see further progress in the economy before tapering QE, especially in light of surging infections due to the Delta variant. Powell said, “At the FOMC&amp;#39;s recent July meeting, I was of the view, as were most participants, that if the economy evolved broadly as anticipated, it could be appropriate to start reducing the pace of asset purchases this year. The intervening month has brought more progress in the form of a strong employment report for July, but also the further spread of the Delta variant. We will be carefully assessing incoming data and the evolving risks. Even after our asset purchases end, our elevated holdings of longer-term securities will continue.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Powell once again urged caution since the economic recovery in the market is still undergoing, saying effects from an ill-timed policy shift would “arrive after the need has passed” and “could be particularly harmful. Here is the full quote, “The main influence of monetary policy on inflation can come after a lag of a year or more. If a central bank tightens policy in response to factors that turn out to be temporary, the main policy effects are likely to arrive after the need has passed. The ill-timed policy move unnecessarily slows hiring and other economic activity and pushes inflation lower than desired. Today, with substantial slack remaining in the labor market and the pandemic continuing, such a mistake could be particularly harmful. We know that extended periods of unemployment can mean lasting harm to workers and to the productive capacity of the economy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regarding inflation, Powell once again reiterated the need for caution but suggested he was prepared to act if incoming data deems it appropriate. He said, “Central banks have always faced the problem of distinguishing transitory inflation spikes from more troublesome developments, and it is sometimes difficult to do so with confidence in real time. At such times, there is no substitute for a careful focus on incoming data and evolving risks. If sustained higher inflation were to become a serious concern, the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) would certainly respond and use our tools to assure that inflation runs at levels that are consistent with our goal. Incoming data should provide more evidence that some of the supply–demand imbalances are improving, and more evidence of a continued moderation in inflation, particularly in goods and services prices that have been most affected by the pandemic. We also expect to see continued strong job creation. And we will be learning more about the Delta variant&amp;#39;s effects.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the full transcript from the speech, I encourage everyone to read it fully. It’s not very long and is extremely insightful to see exactly what the main monetary policy maker thinks of the current state of the economy&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/speech/powell20210827a.htm&quot;&gt;https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/speech/powell20210827a.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regarding Powell’s speech, BTIG Chief Equity and Derivatives Strategist Julian Emanuel said, “Powell &amp;quot;did three things very, very right, and obviously the markets are celebrating that. First was keeping the speech succinct. Second thing he did risht is, he sent the rest of the Fed governors out over the prior four weeks to basically tell us all that the taper was coming. He merely had to reiterate, and reiterate softly, that message, which he did very effectively. The third thing is he really tackled inflation head on. He knew that’s been the preoccupation of the markets for these last couple of months. While he didn’t give any new real evidence as to why he views inflation as transitory, he did cite the ongoing moderation in commodity prices and the view that past history would indicate that inflation is likely to be temporary.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, market participants are set to receive more data on the strength of the labor market recovery this week, with the Labor Department&amp;#39;s August jobs report due out on Friday. Consensus economists are looking to see that 750,000 payrolls came back during the month, representing an eighth straight month of gains but a slight pullback from July&amp;#39;s 943,000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of buy-now-pay-later company Affirm (AFRM) gapped up more than 40% after announcing partnership with Amazon (AMZN) that will let customers buy items of $50 or more in installments. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of travel and leisure stocks slid after the European Union issued a new recommendation to restrict nonessential travel from the US due to surging coronavirus Delta cases. Here is the recommendation: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.consilium.europa.eu/en/press/press-releases/2021/08/30/covid-19-council-removes-5-countries-and-one-entity-territorial-authority-from-the-list-of-countries-for-which-travel-restrictions-should-be-lifted/&quot;&gt;https://www.consilium.europa.eu/en/press/press-releases/2021/08/30/covid-19-council-removes-5-countries-and-one-entity-territorial-authority-from-the-list-of-countries-for-which-travel-restrictions-should-be-lifted/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;July pending home sales unexpectedly dropped, according to data from the National Association of Realtors, likely due to high housing prices. Sales dipped 1.8% in July compared to June, nearly matching June’s 2% decline. Economists were looking for a gain of 0.3%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;McDonald’s (MCD) sent a notice to instruct franchisees on steps they should take to re-close indoor dining in areas where the Delta variant is rapidly spreading. Originally, barring any COVID resurgence, McDonald’s planned to fully reopen indoor dining by Labor Day (Sept 6)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple (AAPL) announced changes to its App Store regulations that will allow software developers to tell customers how to pay for services outside of Apple’s ecosystem, part of a proposed settlement of a class-action lawsuit. The shift will make it easier for some apps to steer customers toward other forms of payment, rather than using the App Store, where Apple charges a commission of up to 30%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ESPN, which is owned by Disney (DIS), is reportedly seeking to license its brand to major sports-betting companies for at least $3 billions over several years, according to sources familiar with the matter as reported by the Wall Street Journal. On offer is the right for a suitor to use the ESPN name for branding purposes and potentially rename its sportsbook after ESPN. The sports-media giant has held talks with players that own major sportsbooks, including casino operator Caesars Entertainment (CZR)&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/market-data/quotes/CZR?mod=chiclets&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;and DraftKings (DKNG) the sources said. ESPN has existing marketing partnerships with both companies already. This is huge for the sports-betting industry, will be closely following this story.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amazon-backed (AMZN) electric vehicle maker Rivian is reportedly seeking a $70-$80 billion valuation in its upcoming IPO. The company has an agreement to produce electric vans for Amazon and a pickup truck for consumers. In my humble opinion, even being backed by Amazon, this valuation is insane.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current stock price was written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Affirm (AFRM) with a host of target raises following the Amazon news. Average price target $120 at Buy. Stock currently around $99&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Albemarle (ALB) target raised by Cowen from $180 to $260 at Outperform. Stock currently around $237&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Asana (ASAN) target raised by Jefferies from $65 to $90 at Buy. Stock currently around $78&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crowdstrike (CRWD) with a host of target raises. Average price target $320 at Outperform. Stock currently around $286&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DocuSign (DOCU) target raised by Wedbush from $290 to $340 at Outperform. Stock currently around $303&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fortinet (FTNT) target raised by Wedbush from $310 to $350 at Outperform. Stock currently around $319&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eli Lilly (LLY) target raised by Cowen from $250 to $300 at Outperform. Stock currently around $262&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Workday (WDAY) with two target raises. Stock currently around $270

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wolfe Research from $270 to $300 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Loop Capital from $320 to $340 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zscaler (ZS) target raised by Wedbush from $240 to $320 at Outperform. Stock currently around $278&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Without labor nothing prospers.” - Sophocles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我在GME上赚了很多钱，并辞去了工作，但我不确定是偿还债务还是继续用大量的钱进行日间交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[编辑：我不在美国（我住在欧洲）。我每个月只需要450美元来
吃饭、付房租等。另一半是由我妻子提出的。我不需要所有
你们这些人每年被迫在应许之地挣的钱。只是需要注意的是
铭记在心。

----------------------------------------------…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/pembbo/i_made_a_lot_of_money_on_gme_and_quit_my_job_but/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/pembbo/i_made_a_lot_of_money_on_gme_and_quit_my_job_but/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 01:30:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDIT:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;#39;m not in the US (I live in Europe). All I need is $450 each month to eat, pay rent, etc. The other half is put forth by my wife. I don&amp;#39;t need all the money you guys are forced to make each year on the promised land. Just a note to keep in mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here it is, I got lucky.  I took a few loans in different ways to daytrade stocks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$20k&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$10k&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$6k from my girlfriend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$4k from credit cards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;some savings from my regular job&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason I took so many loans is that I was constantly making little money and losing (the loans were not taken all at once). At one point, I decided to put together as much money as possible and went all in on GameStop after the first squeeze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When GameStop hit $340 the second time, I sold it all literally 5 minutes before it dipped, and made $65k.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since that moment, I&amp;#39;ve been trading with $50k+ and it&amp;#39;s been really easy to make money, so I decided to quit my job. After quitting, I got my hand into $25k that they had to pay me as severance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bottom line: I extinguished all my loans BUT $27k I owe the bank, and right now I&amp;#39;m trading with $65k. I figured that, considering taxes, I have to make $1500 monthly to break even (monthly expenses + loan rate). If I pay off the bank, that amount is reduced to $700 monthly expenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, if I pay off the bank, my trading power will be reduced to $35k, which is insufficient, in my experience, to make money just trading stocks. So what do I do? Keep trading until those $65k become, lets say, $100k, and then pay off the bank? Or just extinguish debt and go back to trade with under $50k?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDIT 2:&lt;/strong&gt; and for those who wonder what happened with my job... I posted my quitting story &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/AmItheAsshole/comments/nbvbiw/aita_for_leaving_my_company_in_deep_trouble_after/&quot;&gt;three months ago here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Palantir公司被美国空军授予48,500,000美元的数据即服务平台固定价格定义修改合同。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Palantir USG公司。加利福尼亚州帕洛阿尔托市，被授予48,500,000美元的
的固定价格修改合同（PZ0004）。
FA8806-21-C-0010，用于数据即服务平台。这项工作将为政府提供
这项工作将为政府提供定期的软件许可、云主机、启用服务。
支持...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/peswr2/palantir_is_awarded_a_48500000_firmfixedprice/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/peswr2/palantir_is_awarded_a_48500000_firmfixedprice/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 01:30:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Palantir USG Inc. Palo Alto, California, was awarded a $48,500,000 firm-fixed-price definitization modification (PZ0004) to contract FA8806-21-C-0010 for a Data-as-a-Service Platform. This effort will provide the government with a term software licenses, cloud hosting, enablement services, support and training for each platform solution. The location of performance is El Segundo California; Palo Alto, California, Washington, D.C.; and New York, New York. The work is expected to be completed by Nov. 30, 2021, with three six-month options. The total cumulative face value of the contract is $91,500,000. Fiscal 2021 operation and maintenance funds in the amount of $2,000,000; and fiscal 2021 research, development, test and evaluation funds in the amount of $12,500,000 were obligated at the time of award. Space Systems Center, Los Angeles Air Force Base, El Segundo, California, is the contracting activity. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[塔利班的新武器库 https://t.co/CP2XpCUOy3]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1431997819490115587</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1431997819490115587</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 23:37:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我仍然看到在这个子上有不少人根据最近的表现分配到大盘增长倾斜、QQQ、VOOG、VGT、科技股、ARK或其他主动管理的股票基金。追溯杰克-博格尔几十年来的智慧，提醒我们这可能是个坏主意。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在重读《投资常识小书》（2017年更新版）的部分内容时，看到了下面这段话，其中提到了投资者的情况。
更新版），看到下面这段话，其中提到投资者
在几十年前网络公司和次级抵押贷款造成的崩溃中表现不佳
几十年前的泡沫。其中提到的热门基金、成长基金、技术...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/pesvkw/i_still_see_quite_a_few_folks_on_this_sub/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/pesvkw/i_still_see_quite_a_few_folks_on_this_sub/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 23:37:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was re-reading parts of &lt;em&gt;The Little Book of Common Sense Investing&lt;/em&gt; (2017 updated version) and came across the below passage referencing investor underperformance through the crashes caused by the dot-com and subprime mortgage bubbles decades ago. The mentions of hot funds, growth funds, technology funds, etc. sound like they could just as easily be written about today&amp;#39;s market. TL;DR regression to the mean will make today’s winners tomorrow’s losers - hold a passive total market index fund for the long haul and come out ahead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The evidence is compelling that (1) the long-term returns on equity funds lag the stock market by a substantial amount, largely accounted for by their costs; and (2) the returns earned by fund investors lag the market by more than double that substantial lag.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What explains this second shocking lag? Simply put, counterproductive market timing and adverse fund selection. First, shareholders investing in equity funds paid a heavy timing penalty. They invested too little of their savings in equity funds when stocks represented good values during the 1980s and early 1990s. Then, inflamed by the heady optimism and greed of the era and enticed by the wiles of mutual fund marketers as the bull market neared its peak, they poured too much of their savings into equity funds.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, they paid a selection penalty, pouring their money not only into the market at the wrong time, but into the wrong funds—funds that had provided outstanding results in the past, but, as we shall soon see, tumbled thereafter. Why? Simply because high fund returns tend to revert toward or below the mean of average returns. (We’ll discuss reversion to the mean—RTM—in Chapter 11.) With both counterproductive timing and poor fund selection, investors simply fail to practice what common sense would have told them.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This lag effect has been amazingly pervasive. For example, the returns provided to investors from 2008 to 2016 by 186 of the 200 largest equity funds were lower than the returns that they reported to investors! This lag was especially evident during the “new economy” craze of the late 1990s. Then, the fund industry organized more and more funds, usually funds that carried considerably higher risk than the stock market itself, and magnified the problem by heavily advertising the eye-catching past returns earned by the hottest funds. As the market soared, investors poured ever larger sums of money into equity funds. They invested a net total of only $18 billion in 1990 when stocks were cheap, but $420 billion in 1999 and 2000, when stocks were substantially overvalued.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s more, investors also overwhelmingly chose “new economy” funds, technology funds, and the hottest-performing growth funds, to the virtual exclusion of more conservative value-oriented funds. Whereas only 20 percent of their money had been invested in risky aggressive growth funds in 1990, investors poured fully 95 percent into such funds as those fund returns peaked during 1999 and early 2000. After the bubble burst, when it was too late, investor purchases dried up to as little as $36 billion in 2002, just before the market hit bottom. They also pulled their money out of growth funds and turned, too late, to value funds.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The underwhelming performance of fund investors returned during the financial crisis of 2008–2009 and the subsequent recovery. Fund investors have been chasing past performance since time immemorial, allowing their emotions—perhaps even their greed—to overwhelm their reason. Many investors reacted strongly—and ultimately counterproductively—to the sharp downturn in the markets during the financial crisis by getting out of stocks near the market’s nadir. Many of those investors missed part or even all of the subsequent recovery, a cumulative increase by the end of 2016 of some 250 percent from the low.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fund industry itself has compounded the problem by playing on investors’ emotions, bringing out new funds to meet the fads and fashions of the day (often supercharged and speculative), and then aggressively advertising and marketing them. It is fair to say that when counterproductive investor emotions are played upon by counterproductive fund industry promotions, little good is apt to result. The fund industry will not soon give up on its new products or its promotions, and it will take time (and first-hand experience) by investors with counterproductive short-term behavior to gain wisdom. But the intelligent investor will be well advised to heed not only the message in Chapter 4 about minimizing expenses, but the message in this chapter about removing emotions from the equation—that is, about investors improving their short-term, market-oriented behavior.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The beauty of the index fund, then, lies not only in its low expenses, but in its elimination of all those tempting fund choices that promise so much and deliver so little. Focusing on the long term, doing one’s best to ignore the short-term noise of the stock market, and eschewing the hot funds of the day, the index fund can be held through thick and thin for an investment lifetime. Emotions need never enter the equation. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The winning formula for success in investing is owning the entire stock market through an index fund, and then doing nothing. Just stay the course.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bogle, John C.. The Little Book of Common Sense Investing (Little Books. Big Profits) (p. 73). Wiley. Kindle Edition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在美国证券交易委员会主席说 "禁止为订单流付款是可能的 "之后，Robinhood下跌了。卡玛]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/peps7z/robinhood_tanks_after_sec_chair_says_banning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/peps7z/robinhood_tanks_after_sec_chair_says_banning/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 23:37:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME牛股突破! 已经重新测试并准备好飞行!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/peje3c/gme_bull_pennant_breakout_already_retested_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/peje3c/gme_bull_pennant_breakout_already_retested_and/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 22:13:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[S&amp;P 500指数今年第53次收于历史新高。如果以目前的速度持续到年底，它将超过1995年的77个记录。$SPX https://t.co/h7dBsrqnxP]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432433479082553345</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432433479082553345</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 21:40:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[401k看起来像一个烂摊子。是这样吗？帮助!]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好。

我查看了我的401k，它在John Hancock的保护伞下。我不知道
我不知道这些基金是什么。你们对这些有什么看法，我是否应该做
一次性的重新平衡？我不能从约翰-汉考克移出。我想说......这看起来
像一个烂摊子。非常感谢您的任何反馈意见....]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/penb05/401k_looks_like_a_mess_is_it_help/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/penb05/401k_looks_like_a_mess_is_it_help/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 20:52:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi All,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I checked out to see my 401k that is under the John Hancock umbrella. I have no idea what these funds are. What are your thoughts on these and should I do a one-time rebalance? I cannot move out of John Hancock. I will say... this looks like a mess. Any feedback is greatly appreciated. Edit: I am 33. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blue Chip Growth Fund: JIBCX 11.8%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Euro Pacific Growth Fund: RERFX 10.2%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Invesco Developing Markets: ODVXY 2.55%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mid Cap Index Fund: JECIX 10.4%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Real Estates Securities Fund: JIREX: 3.76%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Small Cap Index Fund: JESIX 5.29% &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;500 Index: JFIVX: 14%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;T Rowe Price Equity Fund: PRFDX 15.42%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Total Stock Market Index Fund: JETSX 10.99%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PIMCO Global Bond Opp Fund: PADMX 5.56%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fidelity Advisor Total Bond: FEPIX 5.65%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;T Rowe Price Spectrum: RPSIX 5.1%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会的Gensler说 "禁止为订单流付款已经摆在桌面上 "后，HOOD下跌了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[刚刚由CNBC报道。罗宾汉、查尔斯-施瓦布、Virtu金融公司的股价在美国证券交易委员会批准后触及
在证券交易委员会主席Gary Gensler
告诉《巴伦周刊》，禁止为订单流量付款的做法 "正在讨论中"。

HOOD股价下跌，-4.15美元（8.8%），报42.745美元

SCHW交易下跌，-1.93美元（...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pepk5p/hood_drops_after_secs_gensler_says_banning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pepk5p/hood_drops_after_secs_gensler_says_banning/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 20:39:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just reported by CNBC: Robinhood, Charles Schwab, Virtu Financial shares hit session lows after Securities and Exchange Commission chairman Gary Gensler tells Barron&amp;#39;s that banning payment for order flow is &amp;#39;on the table&amp;#39;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HOOD is trading down, -$4.15 (8.8%)     at 42.745&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SCHW is trading down,  -$1.93 (-2.54%)   at 73.91 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/CNBCnow/status/1432428167227129857&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/CNBCnow/status/1432428167227129857&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GameStop（GME）本周的目标是240美元]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/peiobs/gamestop_gme_is_aiming_for_240_this_week/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/peiobs/gamestop_gme_is_aiming_for_240_this_week/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 19:59:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司创下历史新高，其市值首次超过2.5万亿美元。3年前，它成为第一个达到1万亿美元的美国公司，去年是第一个达到2万亿美元的公司。$AAPL

数据来自@ycharts https://t.co/xUrYGY0wAq]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432375066851954689</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432375066851954689</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 19:35:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[非美国人的投资。]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好。

在接下来的几个月里，我将在Vanguard开设一个账户，我在美国已经有一个
在美国的银行账户，其资金已经足够开始测试
资金和如何操作。

我想，花点时间研究一下这些基金可能会有帮助。
问题是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/pelc1o/nonus_person_investments/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/pelc1o/nonus_person_investments/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 18:51:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello everybody,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the following months ill be opening an account in Vanguard, i already have a bank accountin the US, its already funded with more than enough to start testing the funds and how to operate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Im thinking that taking some time to study the funds could be helpfull and the question that is making me a tad nervous is the US tax law, i have zero knowledge about the subject and dont want to end up losing money or having legal troubles due to ignorance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you guys work with an accounting firm or do everything on your own ? Because ill be using money earned outside the US, im a non US person living outside the US and dont want to have any trouble.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where can i learn about the recquirements ?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PayPal正在为其美国客户探索一个股票交易平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/30/paypal-is-looking-to-launch-a-stock-trading-platform-for-its-customers.html

据两位熟悉计划的消息人士称，PayPal正在探索让用户交易个人股票的方法。
熟悉该计划的消息人士透露，围绕一个新的高管招聘的公开细节。

作为这种扩张的一部分，...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/peloe0/paypal_is_exploring_a_stocktrading_platform_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/peloe0/paypal_is_exploring_a_stocktrading_platform_for/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 18:51:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/30/paypal-is-looking-to-launch-a-stock-trading-platform-for-its-customers.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/30/paypal-is-looking-to-launch-a-stock-trading-platform-for-its-customers.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PayPal is exploring ways to let users trade individual stocks, according to two sources familiar with the plan, and public details around a new executive hire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of that expansion, the payment giant hired a brokerage industry veteran to lead “Invest at PayPal” -- a previously unreported division of the payments giant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The move comes amid a retail trading boom that brought millions of new investors into the stock market, and more regulatory scrutiny for some brokerage firms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a definitely good news for paypal. It is the best fintech play and the customer bases are growing very healthy. By adding the stock trading platform, it can attract more customers assets and able to generate more revenue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[RE: 疫苗增强了感染/疾病/复制的能力  
1) ADE是许多可能的机制之一。
2）没有证据并不证明没有证据。
3) 疫苗的突破有一些奇怪的地方。
4) FDA和Fauci都提到了这种风险。
5) 药厂没有研究这个问题。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432407221359595532</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432407221359595532</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 18:35:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CRSR：一个世纪的戏剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[怎么了，弱智们，我花了两个星期的时间寻找最好的股票玩法，以使你发财。
让你发财，而看起来CRSRR已经准备好上月球了!

你妻子的男朋友再也不会因为你的小鸡鸡而欺负你了。在CRSR之后
你将变得足够富有，可以接受阴茎增大手术，并最终拥有一个...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/pehp2m/crsr_the_play_of_a_century/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/pehp2m/crsr_the_play_of_a_century/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 18:34:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s up retards, I have spent the past 2 WEEKS finding the best stock play to make YOU RICH, and it looks like CRSR is ready to go to the MOON!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NO MORE will your wife’s boyfriend bully you for your micro-penis! After CRSR you will be rich enough to get penis-enlargement surgery and FINALLY have a dong BIGGER than his!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now before you retards go gamble all your life savings on the chance to get penis-enlargement surgery, let me explain why CRSR will go TO THE MOOON&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First, the Fundamentals:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now bare with me, I know you retards don’t like fundamentals… So I will make it as short and colorful as possible!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fundamentally, this company is one of the MOST undervalued companies I have EVER seen&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/mznix9b2uhk71.png?width=1380&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c29960c932cbd9af0f993eaaf0b124f918960fac&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/mznix9b2uhk71.png?width=1380&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c29960c932cbd9af0f993eaaf0b124f918960fac&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CRSR has grown at 24.3% Y/Y despite chip shortages, re-openings, supply-chain shocks, commodity inflation, and last year being especially good for them cause of lockdowns&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They also own Elgato which specializes in studio equipment for streamers, and Origin PC which builds custom pc’s&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These two additional companies have been growing rapidly and allow CRSR to capture the whole gaming peripheral market&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite being a well run, profitable company in a growing industry, they are priced at HALF the S&amp;amp;P 500&amp;#39;s P/E!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/izz273f4uhk71.png?width=825&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=efe189f52a2c6e4b7afd394465e64fb915cc0320&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/izz273f4uhk71.png?width=825&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=efe189f52a2c6e4b7afd394465e64fb915cc0320&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally the float is only around 88M... so unlike some plays on here, WSB could LITERALLY buy the ENTIRE FLOAT&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could go on for SO much longer about why CRSR is a Deep F*cking Value play... But since you retards have an attention-span worse than a goldfish, I will move on...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Option Chains:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corsair has an insanely bullish options market which is primed for a Gamma Squeeze&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/3778p8t6uhk71.png?width=1290&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=0c9838491bb87c9d27bdacb7759ff9fe87f37ae5&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/3778p8t6uhk71.png?width=1290&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=0c9838491bb87c9d27bdacb7759ff9fe87f37ae5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If CRSR gets above $35.00 by 9/17, up to 2,037,800 shares will need to be purchased! This is even before WSB has gotten their greasy hands on it. I’m sure by 9/17 the open interest will be MUCH higher&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having so many options sold just OTM is PERFECT for a gamma squeeze&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally due to delta hedging, the more IV on options and options that go ITM, the more stocks MM&amp;#39;s will need to buy to hedge against the options that they sold&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having so many options contracts sold on a smaller market cap stock is perfect for a gamma squeeze. IV will go through the roof once WSB buys in causing MM&amp;#39;s to hedge creating a feedback loop&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CRSR options are SUPER cheap which gives a good entry point for WSB retards, and makes it much easier to increase the open interest&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short sellers:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the past month, short sellers have been getting TOO greedy and have been adding a shit ton of positions around 26$. This means shorts will be underwater if the stock price increases AT ALL&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CRSR has a short interest of around 24% which, albeit still large, would not be a huge issue on its own... but because most of these short positions were opened at the literal bottom, those short sellers will be much more likely to close their positions and/or be margin called&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the past few weeks, around 40% of the volume has been sold short&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/e9foib1cuhk71.png?width=768&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=cd43fab041475611218d946812efb0dc47a2d786&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/e9foib1cuhk71.png?width=768&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=cd43fab041475611218d946812efb0dc47a2d786&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the same time as shorts have been adding positions, large institutional investors have been buying in HEAVILY&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/a7284jjduhk71.png?width=820&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=22a94571d7c932f4439a5587301cbcfca8fc41ff&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/a7284jjduhk71.png?width=820&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=22a94571d7c932f4439a5587301cbcfca8fc41ff&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This high of a short interest combined with strong financials, a bullish options market, and large institutional investors being on our side means shorts are absolutely fucked and this stock is going TO THE MOON&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to Profit:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recommend buying a mix of 9/17 ITM/OTM calls, leaps, and shares&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buy 9/17 calls if you believe this has a chance to squeeze&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buy leaps/shares if you believe in the underlying company&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Positions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10 $27.5 C 9/17, 13 $30 C 9/17, 50 $32.5 C 9/17, 20 $35 C 9/17, 106 shares, 2 $25 2/18/22 C&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TLDR:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/u1dcgm1iuhk71.png?width=1920&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=15cd932f87fe52287b37262ec396341363afc910&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/u1dcgm1iuhk71.png?width=1920&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=15cd932f87fe52287b37262ec396341363afc910&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我父亲拒绝出售他的ICT集团股票，投资公司以法律程序相威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[我父亲拥有 "ICT集团 "的股票（在阿姆斯特丹的Euronext上有记载）多年。

3个月前，他收到了一封来自他持有这些股票的银行的信。
一家投资公司NPM Capital为他的股票出价14.10欧元。
股票。在那一刻，我们决定不接受这个报价，因为...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pek6un/investment_firm_threatens_with_legal_procedures/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pek6un/investment_firm_threatens_with_legal_procedures/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 18:07:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My dad had stock of “ICT Group” (noted on Euronext Amsterdam) for years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 months ago he received a letter from the bank with which he is holding these stocks that an investment firm, NPM Capital, offered him €14.10 each for his stock. At that moment we decided to not take the offer because of the opportunity it had to go up with the offer going on. (€14.35 now at time of writing)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now 3 months later he received another letter in which the bank states that if he not agrees to the sale of the stocks before the 6th of September, NPM Capital is seeking for legal procedures to get all stock in their possession. (Yes we confirmed if the letter is legit, and it is)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it even possible for an investment group to disown people of their stocks through legal procedures? And what do you guys suggest to do?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[自2013年开始，S&amp;P已经创下328个历史新高。

这比1989-2000年S&amp;P 500指数创下327个历史高点的史诗般的运行多了一个。

$SPX https://t.co/CM96w6R62a]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432365681513844743</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432365681513844743</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 16:51:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国共产党对电子游戏的打击力度更大，未成年人只能在周五、周末和节假日玩1小时。对腾讯和网易的持有者来说，这是一个SOL。]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/30/china-cuts-amount-of-time-minors-can-spend-playing-video-games

中国监管机构周一削减了18岁以下玩家在网络游戏上的时间。
18岁以下的玩家可以在周五、周末和节假日花一个小时的时间玩在线游戏。
假期，以应对日益增长的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pehtmt/more_crackdown_by_the_ccp_on_video_games_minors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/pehtmt/more_crackdown_by_the_ccp_on_video_games_minors/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 15:50:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/30/china-cuts-amount-of-time-minors-can-spend-playing-video-games&quot;&gt;https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/30/china-cuts-amount-of-time-minors-can-spend-playing-video-games&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chinese regulators on Monday slashed the amount of time players under the age of 18 can spend on online games to an hour of gameplay on Fridays, weekends and holidays, in response to growing concern over gaming addiction, state media reported.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rules, published by the National Press and Publication Administration, said users under the age of 18 would be able to play games only from 8pm to 9pm local time on those days, according to the Xinhua news agency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Online gaming companies would be barred from providing gaming services to minors in any form outside those hours and would need to ensure they had put real name verification systems in place, said the regulator, which oversees the country’s video games market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Previously, China limited the total length of time minors could access online games to three hours on holiday or 1.5 hours on other days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new rules come amid a broad crackdown by Beijing on China’s tech giants, such as Alibaba Group and Tencent Holdings, which has unnerved investors, hammering Chinese shares traded at home and abroad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The National Press and Publication Administration also told Xinhua it would increase the frequency and intensity of inspections for online gaming companies to ensure they were putting in place time limits and anti-addiction systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["你的交易情况如何？"在一个星期六的晚上... https://t.co/vQgDQes0EP]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432009108903841795</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1432009108903841795</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 14:41:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[矿业公司与社区和环境倡导者的接触]]></title><description><![CDATA[大批采矿公司的许多矿区位于世界各地。
的很多矿区。采矿活动会影响到这些矿区的环境和社区
因此，我认为矿业公司也应该优先考虑那些能够促进负责任的采矿和孵化的项目。
因此，我认为采矿公司也应该优先考虑那些能够促进负责任的采矿和包容社区的项目。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/peh0q5/mining_companies_and_engaging_with_communities/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/peh0q5/mining_companies_and_engaging_with_communities/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 14:16:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lot of mining sites of a chunk mining companies are located in various parts of the world. Mining activities can affect the environment and the communities in these mining sites, so I think mining companies should also prioritize projects that will promote responsible mining and inclusion of the local communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For instance, Newmont Corporation (NEM) has sustainability programs that involve environmental and social responsibility. The company has environmental standards that are designed to protect the environment and prevent or otherwise minimize, mitigate and remediate the impacts of their mining activities in the mining sites’ locations. They also involve the local communities, providing jobs and provisioning local goods and services, which makes them become an important player in catalyzing the economic development and social well-being of host governments and communities. They also have the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newmont.com/IndigenousCommunityRelations/default.aspx&quot;&gt;Global Center for Indigenous Community Relations&lt;/a&gt;, whose role is to “to advocate for excellence in engagement with Indigenous Peoples, both within Newmont and across the industry.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With junior companies, Solaris Resources (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/search?q=TSE:+SLS&amp;amp;stick=H4sIAAAAAAAAAONgecRowS3w8sc9YSn9SWtOXmPU5OIKzsgvd80rySypFJLmYoOyBKX4uXj10_UNDbPiiyvjK03SeBaxcoQEu1opBPsEAwAqUS8YSAAAAA&amp;amp;sa=X&amp;amp;ved=2ahUKEwiMuov1vNHyAhXbAogKHZriDHMQsRUwIHoECDYQAw&amp;amp;biw=1280&amp;amp;bih=609&quot;&gt;SLS&lt;/a&gt;) has remarkable projects focusing on these matters. The company is very inclusive when it comes to the local miners in the community, and hired a lot of them, generating jobs for people. They also put a priority on using locally sourced products and services whenever practical, to benefit the regional economy. Also, the company has an environmental management project with the goal of minimizing the impact of mining on the environment. This is also more possible since the current president of Ecuador vowed to emphasize the enforcement of environmental protection rules and larger involvement from indigenous communities in deciding the future of mining projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somehow, a lot of corporations feel less responsible for the damage they cause to the environment and to communities with their projects, so I think it should be the responsibility of these companies to change and be more inclusive and responsible. All these globalization and the current climate of economic rationalism is making these people less human and deprived of compassion and sense of responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国共产党对电子游戏的打击力度更大，未成年人只能在周五、周末和节假日玩1小时。对腾讯和网易的持有者来说，这是一个SOL。]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/30/china-cuts-amount-of-time-minors-can-spend-playing-video-games

中国监管机构周一削减了18岁以下玩家的游戏时间。
18岁以下的玩家可以在周五、周末和节假日花一个小时的时间玩在线游戏。
假期，以应对日益增长的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/peh5er/more_crackdown_by_the_ccp_on_video_games_minors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/peh5er/more_crackdown_by_the_ccp_on_video_games_minors/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 13:42:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/30/china-cuts-amount-of-time-minors-can-spend-playing-video-games&quot;&gt;https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/30/china-cuts-amount-of-time-minors-can-spend-playing-video-games&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chinese regulators on Monday slashed the amount of time players under the age of 18 can spend on online games to an hour of gameplay on Fridays, weekends and holidays, in response to growing concern over gaming addiction, state media reported.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rules, published by the National Press and Publication Administration, said users under the age of 18 would be able to play games only from 8pm to 9pm local time on those days, according to the Xinhua news agency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Online gaming companies would be barred from providing gaming services to minors in any form outside those hours and would need to ensure they had put real name verification systems in place, said the regulator, which oversees the country’s video games market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Previously, China limited the total length of time minors could access online games to three hours on holiday or 1.5 hours on other days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new rules come amid a broad crackdown by Beijing on China’s tech giants, such as Alibaba Group and Tencent Holdings, which has unnerved investors, hammering Chinese shares traded at home and abroad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The National Press and Publication Administration also told Xinhua it would increase the frequency and intensity of inspections for online gaming companies to ensure they were putting in place time limits and anti-addiction systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>