<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 05:30:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[当你在购买后几分钟内看到绿色。🤑📈]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ob518m/when_you_see_green_within_minutes_of_buying/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/ob518m/when_you_see_green_within_minutes_of_buying/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 23:46:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[r/Stocks Daily Discussion Wednesday - Jun 30, 2021]]></title><description><![CDATA[这些日常讨论从周一到周五进行，包括在我们的主题性
帖子。

一些有用的链接。

 * Finviz [https://finviz.com/quote.ashx?t=spy] 提供图表、基本面和单个股票的汇总新闻。
   个别股票的汇总新闻
 * 彭博市场新闻[https://www.bloomberg.com/markets]
 *...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oatp7z/rstocks_daily_discussion_wednesday_jun_30_2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oatp7z/rstocks_daily_discussion_wednesday_jun_30_2021/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 23:32:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;These daily discussions run from Monday to Friday including during our themed posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some helpful links:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finviz.com/quote.ashx?t=spy&quot;&gt;Finviz&lt;/a&gt; for charts, fundamentals, and aggregated news on individual stocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/markets&quot;&gt;Bloomberg market news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;StreetInsider news:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Market+Check&quot;&gt;Market Check&lt;/a&gt; - Possibly why the market is doing what it&amp;#39;s doing including sudden spikes/dips&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Reuters&quot;&gt;Reuters aggregated&lt;/a&gt; - Global news&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a basic question, for example &amp;quot;what is EPS,&amp;quot; then google &amp;quot;investopedia EPS&amp;quot; and click the investopedia article on it; do this for everything until you have a more in depth question or just want to share what you learned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please discuss your portfolios in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?sort=new&amp;amp;q=Rate+My+Portfolio+-+r%2FStocks+Quarterly+Thread&amp;amp;t=all&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&quot;&gt;Rate My Portfolio sticky.&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See our past &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+%22r%2Fstocks+daily+discussion%22&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;daily discussions here.&lt;/a&gt;  Also links for:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Atechnicals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Technicals&lt;/a&gt; Tuesday, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Aoptions&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Options Trading&lt;/a&gt; Thursday, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Afundamentals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Fundamentals&lt;/a&gt; Friday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[15年内100%的校车可以实现电动化。Lion Electric副总裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[加上 "基础设施 "法案提供的资金，公共汽车应该开始运行。
轧制!

电动校车可能是下一波冲击商业市场的电动车。
业内一位高管说。莱昂电气（LEV）营销和通信副总裁帕特里克-杰维斯（Patrick Gervais）说。
市场营销和沟通副总裁帕特里克-杰维斯（Patrick Gervais）讨论了电动校车的进展。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ob5pos/100_of_school_buses_could_be_electric_within_15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ob5pos/100_of_school_buses_could_be_electric_within_15/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 22:54:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add the funding from the “infrastructure” bill and the buses should start rolling!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Electric school buses may be the next wave of EVs to hit the commercial market, one executive within the industry says.
Patrick Gervais, Lion Electric (LEV) VP of marketing and communication, discussed the progress made with electric vehicles on a Yahoo Finance Live segment Tuesday afternoon.
“I think there’s a really good intention to electrify 100% of school buses within the next couple of years,” Gervais said. “We could feel the hype all across the United States. I mean, we’ve delivered buses in New York, in Minnesota, all across the country.”
The infrastructure bill, which is supported by President Biden, is expected to provide an additional $15 billion to electric vehicles infrastructure. Under the framework of the bill,  $7.5 billion is to be allocated to schools and public transit organizations to help convert to electric buses.
Gervais noted that a transition to electric school buses would have a plethora of benefits besides a reduction in carbon emissions. “There’s no noise pollution, so it’s more quiet and the kids are more calm and more concentrated when they go to school,” he said. “These are the kids and the people of tomorrow [who] will drive electric cars in the future.”
Currently, less than 1% of school buses are electric. Over 400,000 school buses drive over 3.5 billion miles each year, according to a Bellwether Education Partners study. The transition to electric buses will take initiative, but with the right moves, Gervais said, the entirety of the US school bus fleet could be electrified in 10-15 years.
Abroad, electric vehicles have sparked the interest of consumers of late — 11% of the 11.6 million new cars registered in the EU, Iceland, Norway and Britain last year were either fully electric or plug-in hybrid electric vehicles. Meanwhile, EVs and plug-ins accounted for less than 3% of new car sales in the United States.
MediaNews Group/Los Angeles Daily News via Getty Images via Getty Images
Ihsaan Fanusie is a writer at Yahoo Finance. Follow him on Twitter @IFanusie.
More from Ihsaan:
This startup helps college athletes monetize their personal images
Raw material costs rising for automotive industry: BofA report
Bitcoin to tumble further: oddsmakers bet on drop to $10K
Read the latest cryptocurrency and bitcoin news from Yahoo Finance
Read the latest financial and business news from Yahoo Finance
Follow Yahoo Finance on Twitter, Facebook, Instagram, Flipboard, LinkedIn, YouTube, and reddit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是今天（2021年6月30日，星期三）的市场回顾]]></title><description><![CDATA[心理市场回顾 - 2021年6月30日，星期三

请注意：很抱歉昨天没有发送每日总结，我在我的终端遇到了技术问题。
有技术问题。值得庆幸的是，所有的问题都得到了解决。
现在是全速前进。

今天股票交易情况不一，标普500指数（SPY）和道琼斯指数（DIA）...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ob5k2v/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_wednesday_june/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ob5k2v/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_wednesday_june/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 22:54:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Wednesday, June 30, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please Note: Apologies for not sending the Daily Recap out yesterday, I was having technical issues on my end. Thankfully, all the issues were resolved, it&amp;#39;s full steam ahead.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks traded mixed today, with the S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) and Dow Jones (DIA) rising while the Nasdaq (QQQ) fell modestly after hitting record highs for many consecutives days. In short, stocks continue to hover near record highs. Market participants are encouraged a stronger-than-expected gain on private payrolls and tempered inflationary fears. Looking ahead, market participants wait for Q2 earnings season and incoming economic data. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, ADP’s June private payroll report showed private payrolls increased faster than expected&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/adp-june-private-payrolls-jobs-market-pandemic-economy-recovery-121542029.html&quot;&gt;.&lt;/a&gt; This underscores the ongoing economic recovery with the US economy reporting its sixth straight monthly increase in employment. Job openings rose by 692,000 versus the 600,000 expected. Consumer confidence has also risen and pointed to Americans&amp;#39; increased propensity to spend, with the Conference Board&amp;#39;s consumer confidence index racing to its highest level since February 2020. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;David Lefkowitz, UBS Global Wealth Management Head of Equities, said “If you look at what&amp;#39;s really been powering the economy and powering the stock market, it&amp;#39;s been the fact that there&amp;#39;s been so much fiscal stimulus poured into the economy. What&amp;#39;s really crucial though is that a lot of that fiscal stimulus has actually not been spent this year. It&amp;#39;s sitting on the balance sheets of consumers.&amp;quot; I totally agree. Consumer spending accounts for roughly 70% of US GDP. Now that the economy is reopening thanks to effective distribution of the vaccine, I expect saving-laden consumers to step out and spend big this summer after enduring social distancing guidelines for more than a year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today marks the last trading session of the second quarter of the year, so I thought it would be useful to take a look back at the performance of different assets since March. Year-to-date through Tuesday&amp;#39;s close, the S&amp;amp;P 500 has increased 14.3%, the Nasdaq by 12.7% and the Dow by 12%. The 10-year Treasury yield hit a year-to-date peak of 1.77% in March but is on track to end the quarter yielding just under 1.5%. The West Texas intermediate crude oil rebounded by 23% as demand for energy picks up. Digital currencies, on the other hand, had a very difficult quarter, with prices sharply down across the board compared to the beginning of the quarter. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pending home sales were up 8% in May month-on-month, helping reverse April&amp;#39;s 4.4% drop, according to data from the National Association of Realtors. This brought the pending home sales index to 114.7, or the highest reading for the month of May since 2005. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chinese ride-hailing giant Didi (DIDI) began trading on the New York Stock Exchange. The company sold 316.8 million shares to raise $4.4 billion, making it one of the largest initial public offerings of a Chinese company in the U.S. since Alibaba&amp;#39;s (BABA) $25 billion listing in 2014. Trading began trading at $18, roughly 29% higher than its $14 IPO price, though throughout the session the stock lost most of its IPO gains. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General Mills (GIS) said it is raising prices across nearly all its grocery categories by around 7% due to higher costs for ingredients and labor. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ford Motor (F) said it will be forced to cut output across more than a half-dozen U.S. factories in July due to continued pressure from the global shortage in semiconductors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PayPal (PYPL) is intensifying competition with Square (SQ) by launching its own physical card reader to put in stores. While both are undisputed leaders in fin-tech, PYPL has always focused more intensely on peer-to-peer transactions while SQ put more of an emphasis on consumer-to-business transactions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Twitter Inc on Tuesday named Sarah Personette as chief customer officer to oversee the social media platform&amp;#39;s global ad sales, global content partnerships and revenue operations. The company has been making a big push to increase revenue lately. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Current stock price was written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salesforce (CRM) target raised by Evercore from $290 to $300 at Outperform. Stock currently around $244&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crowdstrike (CRWD) target raised by Truist Securities from $250 to $300 at Buy. Stock currently around $252&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facebook (FB) target raised by Argus from $385 to $410 at Buy. Stock currently around $349&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hess (HESS) target raised by Wells Fargo from $98 to $104 at Overweight. Stock currently around $87.50&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paychex (PAYX) target raised by Citigroup from $1095 to $121 at Buy. Stock currently around $107&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shopify (SHOP) with two target raises. Stock currently around $1464

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Loop Capital from $1400 to $1600 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Royal Bank of Canada from $1500 to $1700 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exxon Mobil (XOM) target raised by Wells Fargo from $67 to $72 at Overweight. Stock currently around $63&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“How long are you going to wait before you demand the best for yourself?” - Epictetus&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spotify着眼于进入现场活动业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[该公司正在考虑利用其关于音乐兴趣的用户数据库
报道称，该公司正在考虑利用其有关音乐兴趣的用户数据库，举办虚拟和潜在的现场音乐会。
报道。

这可能有助于缓解其与音乐人之间的关系，因为音乐人一直抱怨他们的歌曲被流媒体传播。
他们一直抱怨流媒体对他们的歌曲造成了影响。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ob1068/spotify_eyes_entry_into_live_events_business/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ob1068/spotify_eyes_entry_into_live_events_business/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 21:36:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company is looking at using its trove of user data about music interests from streaming to host virtual and potentially live concerts, according to the report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that could help ease some strain in its relationships with musicians, who have consistently complained that streaming their songs is a poor source of revenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Touring and merchandise have long been a bigger source of income for artists than recording contracts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: NewsFilter&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[21个出售的决定，几乎都错了]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直怀疑我在投资时犯的最昂贵的错误之一是过早卖出。
我一直怀疑我在投资时犯的最昂贵的错误之一是过早地卖出，但我从来没有深入研究我的数据，以确定这是否是真的。
确定这是否是真的。所以我决定这么做。我回顾了
在过去的12-18年里，我分别做出了21个卖出股票的决定......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ob3cuw/21_decisions_to_sell_got_almost_all_of_them_wrong/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ob3cuw/21_decisions_to_sell_got_almost_all_of_them_wrong/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 20:55:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve always suspected that one of the most costly mistakes I&amp;#39;ve made when investing has been selling prematurely, but I never dug through my data to determine if that was actually true.  So I decided to do that.  I went back over 21 separate decisions I&amp;#39;ve made to sell stocks over the past 12-18 months to see what happened in the months after the sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;None of these were short-term trades, they were all intended to be long-term investments when I bought them but ended up deciding to sell.  Sometimes it was based on technical signals (new downtrends, violation of the 50 day moving average, price running up too fast and getting over-extended beyond the 50 DMA) but other times it was based on concerns about valuation.  Sometimes it was pure impatience, getting frustrated with a stock going nowhere and wanting to find a better opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of the 21 sell decisions, 18 of them turned out to be wrong in the sense that the price ended up higher than my sell price within the ensuing weeks and months.  In only 3 of the 21 cases did the decision to sell turn out to be a good one.  But the important thing is what I can learn from this to improve my decisions in the future.  Here are some observations:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) A break below the 50 day moving average is a very unreliable sell signal, especially if the stock remains in a longer term uptrend.  Price dropping below the 50 DMA theoretically signals a change in the medium term trend, which could foretell the beginning of a longer term downtrend.  But in almost every case where I sold after the stock dropped below the 50 DMA, it reversed course within days and continued up.  The only case where this turned out to be a good signal was when the stock traded below the 50 DMA for several weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Don&amp;#39;t sell stocks based on concern about valuation.  Valuing stocks isn&amp;#39;t an exact science; I&amp;#39;m not a professional and even professionals can have very different opinions about the fair value of a stock.  In every single case where I sold because I thought the stock got &amp;quot;overvalued,&amp;quot; it continued climbing.  This is where some of my biggest mistakes happened in terms of lost profits.  For example, I sold APPS last October for a 6x return at $32 only to watch it hit $100 within 5 months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Selling when the stock dropped was always a mistake.  This overlaps with (1) because the drops typically coincided with a technical signal (breaking below the 50 DMA or breaking a support level), but every time that happened the stock reversed course soon after.  Unless the selloff reflects an underlying change in the long-term prospects for the business, you should be taking advantage of drops to buy not sell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be fair to myself, some of these decisions could have turned out to be correct if I moved the money elsewhere and saw better returns than if I had left the money where it was.  But the results clearly show that premature selling is a costly mistake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[维尔京轨道公司成功发射]]></title><description><![CDATA[维珍轨道公司成功地将其第一批商业卫星送入太空
今天上午。这是在美国联邦航空局最近批准第一个
商业太空飞行许可证。

布兰森和贝佐斯之间的竞争已经公开化，最近有
人们猜测布兰森正在悄悄地...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ob26gs/virgin_orbit_successful_launch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/ob26gs/virgin_orbit_successful_launch/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 19:51:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Virgin Orbit successfully launched its first commercial satellites into space this morning. This following the recent approval from the FAA for the first commercial space flight license. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The race between Branson and Bezos has been publicized and recently there is speculation that Branson is quietly looking to edge out Branson for the first to fly. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Albeit that Branson’s attempt to fly first seemed highly speculative at the first announcement of Bezos flying it now seems like a fair expectation as there have been numerous well publicized articles declaring Branson’s secret ambition. According to SEC regulations that would require denial or clarification on part of SPCE, whom has not declared it false and ambiguously announced a flight without a passenger list. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aside from the ambiguity on part of SPCE it has several well timed catalysts that have come to fruition over the last couple months. This is speculation yes, however, it is becoming tangible in numerous ways. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/amp.cnn.com/cnn/2021/06/30/tech/virgin-orbit-launch-tubular-bells-scn/index.html&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/amp.cnn.com/cnn/2021/06/30/tech/virgin-orbit-launch-tubular-bells-scn/index.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日的准备工作 - 2021年6月30日]]></title><description><![CDATA[准备交易日 - 2021年6月30日

请注意，这只包括市值较大的股票和被认为是
畅销的股票。


显著的价格升级和降级

FactSet Research Systems（FDS）。

 * B Of A Securities维持 "跑输大盘 "评级（目标价从295美元改为...
   295美元至...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oawfor/preparation_for_trading_day_june_30_2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oawfor/preparation_for_trading_day_june_30_2021/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 18:54:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Preparation for trading day - June 30, 2021&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note that this only includes stocks with larger market cap and stocks considered popular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Notable Price Upgrades and Downgrades&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FactSet Research Systems (FDS):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B Of A Securities Maintains Underperform Rating (Price Target Changes From $295 To $310)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deutsche Bank Maintains Hold Rating (Price Target Changes From $315 To $330)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Morgan Stanley Maintains Underweight Rating (Price Target Changes From $261 To $273)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capri Holdings (CPRI):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BTIG Maintains Buy Rating (Price Target Changes From $80 To $85)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UBS Maintains Buy Rating (Price Target Changes From $82 To $90)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Credit Suisse Maintains Neutral Rating (Price Target Changes From $56 To $62)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook (FB):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Argus Research Maintains Buy Rating (Price Target Changes From $385 To $410)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shopify (SHOP):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Loop Capital Maintains Buy Rating (Price Target Changes From $1400 To $1600)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RBC Capital Maintains Outperform Rating (Price Target Changes From $1500 To $1700)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CrowdStrike Holdings (CRWD):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Truist Securities Maintains Buy Rating (Price Target Changes From $250 To $300)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Virgin Galactic Hldgs (SPCE):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B Of A Securities Downgrades To Underperform From Buy (Price Target $41)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exxon Mobil (XOM):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wells Fargo Maintains Overweight Rating (Price Target Changes From $67 To $72)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chevron (CVX):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wells Fargo Maintains Equal-Weight Rating (Price Target Changes From $110 To $111)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BP (BP):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wells Fargo Maintains Overweight Rating (Price Target Changes From $31 To $32)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unity Software (U):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Morgan Stanley Initiates Equal-Weight Rating (Price Target $115)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Roblox (RBLX):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Citic Securities Initiates Overweight Rating (Price Target $96)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Micron Technology (MU):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BMO Capital Upgrades To Outperform From Market Perform (Price Target Changes From $90 To $110)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Today&amp;#39;s Economic Calendar&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;08:00 am&lt;/strong&gt;    Atlanta Fed President Raphael Bostic speaks             &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;08:15 am&lt;/strong&gt;    ADP employment report for June&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;09:45 am&lt;/strong&gt;    Chicago PMI for June&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10:00 am&lt;/strong&gt;    Pending home sales index for May&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;01:00 pm&lt;/strong&gt;    Richmond Fed President Tom Barkin speaks            &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;IPO market (This week)&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acumen Pharmaceuticals (ABOS) Price range: $14.00 - $16.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aerovate Therapeutics (AVTE) Price range: $13.00 - $15.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AMTD Digital (HKD) Price range:   $6.80 - $8.20&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atour Lifestyle Holdings (ATAT) Price range: $13.50 - $15.50&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clear Secure (YOU)    Price range:    $27.00 - $30.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CVRx (CVRX)   Price range: $15.00 - $17.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;D-MARKET Electronic Services &amp;amp; Trading    (HEPS)  Price range: $11.00 - $13.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DiDi Global   (DIDI) Price range: $13.00 - $14.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dingdong (DDL)    Price range: $23.50 - $25.50&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;EverCommerce (EVCM)   Price range: $16.00 - $18.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intapp (INTA) Price range:    $25.00 - $28.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integral Ad Science Holding   (IAS) Price range: $15.00 - $17.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Krispy Kreme (DNUT)   Price range: $21.00 - $24.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LegalZoom.com (LZ)    Price range: $24.00 - $27.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nyxoah    (NYXH)  Price range: $31.46&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regencell Bioscience Holdings (RGC)   Price range: $8.50 - $10.50&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SentinelOne   (S) Price range: $31.00 - $32.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Glimpse Group (VRAR) Price range: $6.00 - $8.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Torrid Holdings   (CURV) Price range: $18.00 - $21.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Twin Vee PowerCats (VEEE) Price range:    $5.00 - $6.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Xometry   (XMTR) Price range: $38.00 - $42.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s all folks, have fun and stay green&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: I am not a financial advisor, and nothing in this post shall be seen as a financial advise. Always make to sure to vet the accuracy of statements and do your own research before using it in any way&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Robinhood因虚假信息和交易中断支付7000万美元，这是有史以来最大的监管罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[> "在这个问题上的罚款反映了Robinhood的违法行为的范围和严重性。
> Robinhood的违规行为的范围和严重性，包括美国金融监管局发现Robinhood向其数百万客户传达了
> 向数百万客户提供虚假和误导性信息，"监管机构说。
> 说。
> 
> 网上交易平台Robinhood将支付大约70美元。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ob2ayy/robinhood_to_pay_70m_for_false_information_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/ob2ayy/robinhood_to_pay_70m_for_false_information_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 18:32:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The fine imposed in this matter reflects the scope and seriousness of Robinhood’s violations, including FINRA’s finding that Robinhood communicated false and misleading information to millions of its customers,&amp;quot; the regulator said.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Online trading platform &lt;strong&gt;Robinhood will pay roughly $70 million in penalties for its systemwide outages and misleading communication and trading practices&lt;/strong&gt;, the Financial Industry Regulatory Authority said Wednesday.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The settlement regards the technical failures Robinhood experienced in March 2020, Robinhood’s lack of due diligence before approving customers to place options trades and purveying misleading information to customers about aspects like trading on margin.&lt;/strong&gt; The stock market was diving that month in especially wild trading amid the outbreak of the Covid-19 pandemic.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FINRA — a self-regulatory organization that oversees brokerage firms and their registered representatives — said it fined Robinhood $57 million and ordered the stock trading app to pay nearly $13 million in restitution to thousands of clients.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“FINRA considered the widespread and significant harm suffered by customers, including millions of customers who received false or misleading information from the firm, millions of customers affected by the firm’s systems outages in March 2020, and thousands of customers the firm approved to trade options even when it was not appropriate for the customers to do so,” &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.finra.org/media-center/newsreleases/2021/finra-orders-record-financial-penalties-against-robinhood-financial&quot;&gt;the statement said.&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Robinhood — expected to go public sometime this year — suffered multiple days of outages beginning in early March of 2020 during the pandemic, leaving clients unable to trade equities, options or cryptocurrency. The platform remained offline during some of the highest volume trading days amid the fastest bear market in history.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Robinhood also faced criticism over the death of a 20-year old trader who killed himself after believing he racked up huge losses on Robinhood. The suicide was mentioned in the FINRA press release.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Robinhood neither admitted or denied the charges.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Robinhood has invested heavily in improving platform stability, enhancing our educational resources, and building out our customer support and legal and compliance teams,” Jacqueline Ortiz Ramsay, head of public policy communications for Robinhood, said in response to the fine. “We are glad to put this matter behind us and look forward to continuing to focus on our customers and democratizing finance for all.”&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Robinhood said it now has approximately 2,700 customer support staff, according to a blog post. That is more than triple the staff it had during March 2020.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Menlo Park, California-based company forecasted this fine was coming and set aside $26.6 million for settlements, according to an annual audit filing with the SEC. However, the fine is more than double the amount reserved.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The fine imposed in this matter, the highest ever levied by FINRA, reflects the scope and seriousness of Robinhood’s violations, including FINRA’s finding that Robinhood communicated false and misleading information to millions of its customers,” said Jessica Hopper, executive vice president and head of FINRA’s Department of Enforcement.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FINRA also fined Robinhood $1.25 million in 2019 for best execution violations.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Robinhood is expected to go public in the coming months with a valuation north of $30 billion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nbcnews.com/business/markets/robinhood-pay-70m-false-information-trading-outages-largest-ever-regulatory-n1272722&quot;&gt;NBC News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMD对NVDA，你们现在倾向于哪一个？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我注意到，最近这两只股票成为更受欢迎的讨论点。
点，NVDA在7月中旬进行了4比1的拆分，而AMD的预期增长。
我很想知道你们对这两只股票中的哪只更喜欢，你们对自己喜欢的股票有什么看法？
你喜欢的股票的要点是什么？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oaxcj2/amd_vs_nvda_which_one_are_you_guys_favoring_right/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oaxcj2/amd_vs_nvda_which_one_are_you_guys_favoring_right/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 17:00:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve noticed that recently these two stocks becoming more popular discussion points, with NVDA having a 4 to 1 split in mid July and AMD’s projected growth. I’m curious to know which of the two you guying are liking better and what your points are for your favored stock?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[通过回溯测试，比较1997-2021年S&P500 ETF与低债券和高债券三类基金组合的表现]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好。我一直听说追踪标准普尔500指数的指数提供了一个良好的多样化组合。
但最近有人告诉我，情况并非如此，三个基金的投资组合才是王道。
三个基金的投资组合才是王道。关于这一点，有很多很好的信息
的信息。因此，我决定对它们进行比较，看看它们如何。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/oay995/backtesting_to_compare_sp500_etf_vs_lowbond_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/oay995/backtesting_to_compare_sp500_etf_vs_lowbond_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 17:00:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone. I&amp;#39;ve always heard that indices which track the S&amp;amp;P500 offer a good mix of diversification but recently I&amp;#39;ve been told that&amp;#39;s not the case and that a three-fund portfolio is the way to go. There&amp;#39;s a lot of great info about that on here. So I decided to compare them and see how it looks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Methodology&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used backtesting with PortfolioVisualizer to compare a &lt;strong&gt;100% SPY&lt;/strong&gt; approach (this is an ETF that tracks the S&amp;amp;P500 index), versus two three fund portfolios: a &lt;strong&gt;Hi-bond portfolio&lt;/strong&gt; (40% total bond index, 30% total US stock, 30% total international stock), and a &lt;strong&gt;Lo-Bond portfolio&lt;/strong&gt; (10% bond index, 45% US total stock, 45% total intl stock).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assumptions here use the default parameters of PortfolioVisualizer: starting with 10K lumpsum, no other contributions, annual reballancing, and reinvesting dividends.  This covers the dotcom bubble as well as the 2008 crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assets in the three-fund portfolios are all Vanguard mutual funds. I chose these because they are generally older and allow covering further back in time. Specifically I was aiming for before the 2008 crisis. There are newer ETFs which cover similar indices with a more favorable lower expense ratio (ER), but these all go back to ~2010. This is also why I chose SPY over VOO. Using lower ER options, which seem to generally be ETFs over mutual funds, will of course offer slight benefits over these exact options. The analysis runs from Jan 1997 to May 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The high-bond portfolio is meant to replicate a two-fund portfolio breakdown of bonds/stocks at a 40:60 ratio, but because the recommended historical stock fund there has apparently been disctontinued and cannot be viewed on PortfolioVisualizer (VTWSX), I resorted to a three-fund stock with the same stock:bond ratio and equal split of domestic and intl stocks. I think this may slightly undervalue the stock allocation in that portfolio due to double stock fund ER hit. The low-bond portfolio is 10% bonds to 90% stocks, with equal weight of US to intl total stock allocation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Results&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A more complete results slideshow is available on google slides: &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1vlA5Z8d1vqkBv4DvGd8p3RY3R9Am191UkSKwt3Aon8g/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1vlA5Z8d1vqkBv4DvGd8p3RY3R9Am191UkSKwt3Aon8g/edit?usp=sharing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The portfolio comparison results are visualized below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/gm69e95uce871.png?width=2180&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=cbdf65b22c47254acba659b3bd942b226d208e38&quot;&gt;Portfolio Visualizer Results&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The details of the three-fund portfolios are below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/g78vmbpvee871.png?width=2378&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=690be3898f6e283909cb430bb5eac8998d8f71ba&quot;&gt;Details of three-fund portfolios including tickers, allocations and expense ratios&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;These results indicate that &lt;strong&gt;S&amp;amp;P500 have given the most returns over the whole time period&lt;/strong&gt;. This is primarily because it took off starting in 2014.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The high-stock three-fund portfolio outperformed the high-bond portfolio over the whole time course. This may be because there is significant overlap with the S&amp;amp;P500.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The high-bond portfolio performed best during the 2008 crash, until ~2013.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am not showing the details, but using ETFs with lower ER (ie VOO over SPY; and Vanguard ETFs over Vanguard mutual funds in the three-fund portfolio) is always slightly better. (these were not used in the main comparison because they don;t track back far enough in time).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Discussion and Followup Questions&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These results indicate that if I had invested 10K in Jan 1997, I would have made more returns from an S&amp;amp;P500 index fund than a 3-fund strategy, this is true if I would have sold at almost any point of the time period except 2008-2013. If I had waited until May 2021, SPY clearly gives better returns largely because of  relative outperformance since 2014. For the rest of the historical record, the portfolios are more comparable. The high-bond portfolio dominates starting in 2008 through 2013, which seems consistent with a common intuition about bonds being relative safe harbors during times of crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This naturally raises a few questions in my mind:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is the S&amp;amp;P500 &amp;quot;overpriced&amp;quot; at this point?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What happened in 2014 and since then to drive the S&amp;amp;P500 overperformance?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Additionally, how would a 4-fund portfolio that also includes real-estate (REIT) compare here? I did not have time to followup on this, but this is a strategy some take.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just some concluding notes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Historical data is better than no data, but it cannot predict the future. I am currently long VOO which is a S&amp;amp;P500 ETF that is almost identical in performance to SPY. I am not a financial advisor. Would love to hear your thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我分析了过去15年的新闻报道，看看Michael Burry预测了多少次崩盘，以及他有多少次是正确的！他的预测是正确的。以下是结果。]]></title><description><![CDATA[序言。迈克尔-伯利绝对是一个有争议的人物。他一举成名
赌注是针对次贷市场的，在2000年11月至2008年6月期间为他的投资者赚取了489%的回报。
在2000年11月至2008年6月期间，他为投资者赚取了489%的回报（同期SP500的回报率仅为3%）。

但是，我最近观察到，在每一篇新闻报道/推文中，他...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oawsxf/i_analyzed_last_15_years_of_news_articles_to_see/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oawsxf/i_analyzed_last_15_years_of_news_articles_to_see/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 17:00:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preamble:&lt;/strong&gt; Michael Burry is definitely a controversial figure. He rose to fame betting against the subprime mortgage market and making a 489% return for his investors between Nov’00 and Jun’08 (SP500 returned just 3% in the same period).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, I recently observed that in every news article/tweet, he always talks about an impending crash. As recently as last week, he issued another warning stating that there would a “mother of all crashes soon due to the meme-stock and *****currency rally that will approach the size of countries”. Basically, what I wanted to analyze was&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whether Michael Burry always predicts a crash and gets lucky when there is an actual crash or does his prediction actually turns out to be true most of the time?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Analysis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The various news articles spanning over the last 15 years were obtained from Google News [1]. I flagged the date of each crash prediction and then analyzed the performance of the market/stock over the&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a. Next 1 Month&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;b. Next 1 Quarter&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;c. Till Date&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will not be including the subprime mortgage crash prediction in this analysis as we all know how that turned out and how that made him famous. Also, there are no news reports covering Burry before that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The performance figures are calculated based on the prediction. If Burry specifies a stock, then I am using that particular stock as the benchmark. If its broader prediction relating to the overall market, then the benchmark used is S&amp;amp;P 500.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/y2bct7sphe871.png?width=1028&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=0dd6d0b6163ad7ed0bfc917af373ce9f65bce71d&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a long gap of 9 years after the 2008 crash where Burry stayed out of the public view and did not make any warnings or predictions about the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His first verifiable prediction after the 2008 crisis &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lombardiletter.com/michael-burry-stock-market-crash/10895/&quot;&gt;came in May 2017&lt;/a&gt; where he warned that we can expect a global financial meltdown and World War 3. In his exact words&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I didn’t go out looking for this, I just did the math. Every bit of my logic is telling me the global financial system is going to collapse&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it’s been 4 years since the prediction and the market is chugging along just fine. S&amp;amp;P500 has returned a respectable 93% to date and there is &lt;a href=&quot;https://thebulletin.org/doomsday-clock/timeline/&quot;&gt;no imminent threat&lt;/a&gt; of a World War happening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Burry’s next prediction was in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/the-big-short-s-michael-burry-explains-why-index-funds-are-like-subprime-cdos-1.1310874&quot;&gt;Sep 2019&lt;/a&gt; where he said that index funds are the next market bubble and are comparable to subprime CDOs. He said that index fund inflows are now distorting prices for stocks and bonds in the same way that CDO purchases did for subprime mortgages more than a decade ago. He said the flows will reverse at some point, and “it will be ugly” when they do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This prediction also did not pan out as S&amp;amp;P500 has returned 50% to date over the last two years and the only crash that occurred during this period was the Covid-19 flash crash from which the market made a sudden recovery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Burry’s next target was on Tesla where he said that Tesla’s stock price is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.in/stock-market/news/big-short-investor-michael-burry-reveals-hes-short-tesla-tells-elon-musk-to-issue-more-stock-at-its-ridiculous-price/articleshow/79538731.cms&quot;&gt;ridiculous&lt;/a&gt; and that it would &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.in/stock-market/news/big-short-investor-michael-burry-predicts-tesla-stock-will-collapse-like-the-housing-bubble-enjoy-it-while-it-lasts/articleshow/80171258.cms&quot;&gt;collapse&lt;/a&gt; like the housing stock bubble. I have kept both the articles there which had only one month difference as we don’t know exactly when he shorted the stock. The returns would be substantially different if he did it in Dec’20 when compared to Jan’21 as Tesla had a phenomenal run in December.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.in/stock-market/news/big-short-investor-michael-burry-warns-the-stock-market-is-dancing-on-a-knifes-edge-and-fears-hes-being-ignored-again/articleshow/81154288.cms&quot;&gt;reiterated&lt;/a&gt; again on Feb’21 that the market is dancing on a knife’s edge and he is being ignored again. He felt the boom in day traders due to the meme stock mania and the increasing cash flow to the index trackers would cause a massive bubble. This prediction also hasn’t turned out to be right as the market has returned 11% to date over the last 4 months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Burry’s only prediction that we can say confidently was right after the 2008 mortgage crisis is that he called &lt;a href=&quot;https://moguldom.com/340499/michael-burry-who-predicted-2008-mortgage-crash-says-bitcoin-is-a-speculative-bubble-sends-prices-lower/&quot;&gt;***coin a speculative bubble&lt;/a&gt; in March’21. ***coin has since dropped 28% in around 3 months. Even in this case, we don’t have enough data to showcase how this prediction would turn out over the next one/two years.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Burry was most active in 2021 making the most number of predictions with the latest in Jun’21 stating that we are currently in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://moguldom.com/358632/investor-michael-burry-who-predicted-2008-subprime-mortgage-crisis-says-this-is-greatest-speculative-bubble-of-all-time-in-all-things/&quot;&gt;greatest speculative bubble of all time&lt;/a&gt;. Only time will tell how this one will turn out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have immense respect for Michael Burry and his skills. He was a doctor and worked as a Stanford Hospital neurology resident and then left to start his own hedge fund that became &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Michael_Burry&quot;&gt;extremely successful&lt;/a&gt;. But, as you can see from the above analysis, he is more often wrong than right with his predictions [2].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, the stock market rewards predictions disproportionately [3]. Out of the 100 predictions you make, even if you get 99 wrong but get one extremely unlikely event right your overall returns will still be extremely high.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key point here is that if you believe in Michael Burry, you will have to follow all of his recommendations [4] and not pick and choose what you feel comfortable with as most of the returns would be from an extremely unlikely scenario.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Footnotes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[1] Google News has a &lt;a href=&quot;https://researchbuzz.me/2019/07/22/if-youre-not-using-more-of-google-news-date-options-you-might-be-missing-out/#:%7E:text=As%20you%20probably%20know%2C%20Google,hours%2C%20and%20the%20past%20hour.&quot;&gt;nifty feature&lt;/a&gt; where they allow you to search news in specific time periods. Also, Google News seems to capture almost all the major publications other than the historical archives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[2] The current analysis is done using all the publicly available records. We are not considering the personal bets he made, conversations he had with his friends/family/investors, etc. This can definitely alter the&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[3] Take the classic example of Keith Gill (aka DFV). He at one point had a $50MM return using a 50K call option. Even if he had another 99 50K call options in other stocks which expired worthless, just this one right pick would have made him a net profit of $45MM. This phenomenon is known as &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.paulgraham.com/swan.html&quot;&gt;black swan farming&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[4] At that point, if you are that confident in his predictions, you can &lt;a href=&quot;https://smartasset.com/financial-advisor/scion-asset-management-review&quot;&gt;invest in his hedge fund&lt;/a&gt;. Please note that you need to have a minimum capital requirement ($1 million minimum investment and some extra regulatory requirements)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: I am not a financial advisor.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ARKG vs. GNOM - GNOM是一个更好的赌注吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在我看来，GNOM[https://www.globalxetfs.com/funds/gnom/]是一个更好的长期
与ARKG相比，在基因组学进展方面的赌注更好。GNOM的ER值较低，而且由于与Cathie Wood的狂热无关，它的波动性和膨胀性可能较小。
由于与凯西-伍德的狂热没有关系，其波动性和膨胀性较小。
GNOM也是基于一个指数（Solactive Genomics Index），它...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/oaweof/arkg_vs_gnom_is_gnom_a_better_bet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/oaweof/arkg_vs_gnom_is_gnom_a_better_bet/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 15:52:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seems to me &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.globalxetfs.com/funds/gnom/&quot;&gt;GNOM&lt;/a&gt; is a better long-term bet on genomic advances than ARKG. GNOM has a lower ER and is likely less volatile and less inflated due to no association with Cathie Wood fanaticism. GNOM is also based on an index (Solactive Genomics Index), which suggests lower expenses over the long term. What are your thoughts? Advantages and disadvantages of each? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GNOM info from Global X&amp;#39;s website:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FUND SUMMARY&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Global X Genomics &amp;amp; Biotechnology ETF (GNOM) seeks to invest in companies that potentially stand to benefit from further advances in the field of genomic science, such as companies involved in gene editing, genomic sequencing, genetic medicine/therapy, computational genomics, and biotechnology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;FUND OBJECTIVE&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Global X Genomics &amp;amp; Biotechnology ETF (GNOM) seeks to provide investment results that correspond generally to the price and yield performance, before fees and expenses, of the &lt;strong&gt;Solactive Genomics Index.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[房价的调整是否迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[这篇文章
[https://www.annettahome.com/housing-news/examining-the-foundation-whats-causing-the-rise-in-home-prices]
深入探讨了推动房价上涨的因素。根据这篇文章
[https://www.annettahome.com/housing-news/examining-the-foundation-whats-causing-the-rise-in-home...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/oawyqu/is_there_a_correction_looming_in_housing_prices/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/oawyqu/is_there_a_correction_looming_in_housing_prices/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 15:52:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annettahome.com/housing-news/examining-the-foundation-whats-causing-the-rise-in-home-prices&quot;&gt;This article&lt;/a&gt; delves into the factors driving home price increases. According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annettahome.com/housing-news/examining-the-foundation-whats-causing-the-rise-in-home-prices&quot;&gt;the article&lt;/a&gt;, they are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Limited supply&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Increased input costs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Increased demand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s worth a read, but there are a few things I think they missed:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supply chain factors impacting the supply side&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Costs other than lumber, for ex: copper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Impact of increased institutional buying&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My points 1 and 2 I think are at risk of normalizing soon which should put some pressure on home prices. What other factors should be considered when trying to assess the next move in housing prices? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is systematic leverage as high as it was in &amp;#39;08?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WSB的父亲发现他孩子的交易账户]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oaxd0y/wsb_dad_finds_his_kids_trading_account/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oaxd0y/wsb_dad_finds_his_kids_trading_account/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 15:28:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在未来12-24个月内，你预计的增长部门是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在未来12-24个月内，您预计哪些行业会有增长？

您认为哪些行业/产业将成为下一个增长/投资最多的领域？
增长/投资？

我们已经看到对电动车的大笔投资？你认为这是否会逐渐减少或继续
以同样的速度继续下去

人工智能股票、5G股票、数字......怎么样？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oav9mb/what_are_your_projected_growth_sectors_over_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oav9mb/what_are_your_projected_growth_sectors_over_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 14:46:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What are your projected growth sectors over the next 12-24 months?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What sectors/industries do you think will be next to see the most growth/investment?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve seen big investment into EVs? Do you think this will taper off or continue at the same rate &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What about AI stocks, 5G stocks, digital farming?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Put forward your ideas below with some reasoning. Thanks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[西北地区160万美元，60岁，需要供养30岁的儿子。已有20年的瘦身经验]]></title><description><![CDATA[我已经在墨西哥生活了20年，住在一个付费的房子里。
每月最多只有3500美元的预算（我可以轻松地将其降至每月2000美元）。
在这种情况下，我得到了110万美元的现金，总价值为160万美元。
包括房子。我60岁了，有一个住在我屋檐下的成年儿子......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/oad0eg/16m_nw_60_yo_and_need_to_provide_for_30_year_old/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/oad0eg/16m_nw_60_yo_and_need_to_provide_for_30_year_old/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 14:20:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been leanfire for 20 years living in Mexico in a paid for house with a budget of $3500 per month tops (I can crash this easily to $2k per month). Circumstances have put a $1.1M cash into my lap for a total NW of $1.6M including the house. I’m 60 and have an adult son who lives under my roof and whom I will need to provide for. He will continue in this house after I’m gone. He is very low maintenance - does not have expensive hobbies, tastes or needs. What’s the best way to invest this so that there are gains substantial enough to provide minimal income and conserve the wealth?  I have a fairly high tolerance for risk.  This huge lump sum just makes me nervous. Thanks in advance for any suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔公司。(INTC)的价值被低估了]]></title><description><![CDATA[我只在这个分论坛上发过两次帖，所以我还在学习如何发DD
帖子。

我成为英特尔的大牛有一段时间了，我从中学起就开始制造电脑并研究
我从中学起就开始建造电脑并学习电脑技术，所以我了解英特尔和它的
产品。

英特尔的股价在过去有一个颠簸的过程。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/oac3ox/intel_corp_intc_is_undervalued/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/oac3ox/intel_corp_intc_is_undervalued/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 13:57:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have only posted twice on this subreddit so I’m still learning to make DD posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been an Intel bull for a while, I have built computers and studied computer tech since I was in middle school so I understand Intel and it’s products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intel’s share price has had a bumpy ride over the past couple years, mostly trading sideways, and giving up gains very soon after achieving them. Intel as a business has had very poor management as intel for a long time has essentially been complacent in its innovation because of lack of competition. Intel only 5 years ago was far ahead of where AMD was (AMD being its most well recognized competitor) this has changed now that AMD has been able to outsource its chip manufacturing to TSMC, which is a Taiwan semiconductor company that produces the smallest chip and most dense chip designs that are available. This partnership has allowed AMD to eat away and Intel’s market share over the past 2-3 years, but there are many overlooked reasons for why Intel should still be considered a boof value buy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intel is it’s own manufacturer. Intel is not like AMD as intel has its own fab factories meaning they don’t have to outsource there products to other companies. This will be huge for intel as the chip trade war heats up, Intel will likely receive large subsidies from the US government as Intel is the only US based chip manufacturing company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intel is expanding into new markets.
Intel has as of this year expanded into graphics processing. A market that was completely dominated by Nvidia for decades. This is a very good and logical expansion of intel’s market. Intel is also partnering with other companies to try to create new processing technologies. Intel has also announced all new fab factories that will be completed by 2023.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intel has had a refocus and has gotten new leadership. Intel has a new ceo (Patrick Gelsinger) Gelsinger has done a fantastic job refocusing the company on innovation, and if AMD is any example of how changing leadership can rejuvenate a company, then this should be great for intel’s projected growth, as AMD’s ceo (Lisa Su) has saved AMD since she has started working as there chief executive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intel is in a exponentially growing market. The chip industry is a very high growth sector. This has helped intel as its lack of innovation has been offset by its sale performance the past few years. Investors just need reason to believe intel will grow with its completion in order to feel confident in the company as an investment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My last point is that Intel is fundamentally undervalued. The other chip companies in the industry have average P/E ratios around 35~40 intel, however, has a P/E ratio of 12. This ties into my previous point that investors just need reason to believe in intel’s long term growth, and once they have it intel will likely skyrocket. Intel also has the greatest market cap out of its competitors and has the lowest price to book value and not to mention billions in free cash flow. Intel is also a high dividend stock with a dividend of 2.48. while AMD offers no dividends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will edit this post as I find more information that I didn’t cover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading! And all criticism is welcomed!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你知道你是谁...]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oadniw/you_know_who_you_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oadniw/you_know_who_you_are/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 13:44:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[押注于市场的通货膨胀/修正]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好，我最近对所有关于通货膨胀的讨论和国债收益率感兴趣。
收益率感兴趣，因为经济从去年开始复苏了。我很想了解
更多关于债券、通货膨胀、美联储等的信息。我想在$TTT上做文章（一个
是ICE美国国债每日表现的逆向（-3倍）...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/oaiumu/betting_on_market_inflationcorrection/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/oaiumu/betting_on_market_inflationcorrection/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 13:32:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone I&amp;#39;ve been recently interested in all the inflation talk and treasury yield rates as the economy recovers from last year. I&amp;#39;m interested in learning more about bonds, inflation, the Fed etc. I want to make a play on $TTT ( an inverse (-3x) of the daily performance of the ICE U.S. Treasury 20+ Year Bond Index). Essentially I&amp;#39;d like your help with these three scenarios, is my logic incorrect or am I missing some other important factors- or both.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scenario 1: Inflation (currently around 5%, near 2008 high) continues to pick up in the following months. Does the Fed raise interest rates to combat this? I believe Powell has stated they don&amp;#39;t want hikes until 2023. So in my mind higher inflation----&amp;gt;demand for higher yields as investors don&amp;#39;t want their money eroded by inflation. In this case I would be bullish on TTT (?)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scenario 2: Lets assume there is a big selloff/correction in the general market in the following months, for any reason (i.e. overleverage). I&amp;#39;m assuming that investors would be interested in parking their money in safer treasuries/bonds, which would drive the yield down for these securities? In this case I would be bearish on TTT (?)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scenario 3: Inflation tapers off in the following months, the economy is showing a decent recovery, no major financial events occur. I&amp;#39;m guessing yield rates remain the same or edge slightly upwards towards the end of the year. So this is a more neutral stance on TTT, slightly bullish (?)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do realize that TTT is not meant for long term plays typically, I&amp;#39;m more interested in getting the market dynamics down of these possible futures down. I mostly used it as a real life example I could visualize. Feel free to comment using 1,2, and 3 for direct responses to my thought process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks in advance&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bonus: How do these scenarios affect overnight repo rates, which are currently around 800B .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你在做DD时有什么效率秘诀？从股票筛选器的设置、DCF模板等一切。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我刚刚开始工作，所以很想听听各位的意见。

 * 我目前只使用finviz，但不知道是否有更好的东西。
   有
 * 我有一个相当强大的DCF模型模板，但我已经很害怕复制粘贴10K的数据，尤其是大多数公司都有不同的数据。
   我有一个相当强大的DCF模型模板，但我已经害怕复制粘贴10K的数据，特别是由于大多数公司有不同的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/oaobil/what_are_your_efficiency_hacks_when_doing_a_dd/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/oaobil/what_are_your_efficiency_hacks_when_doing_a_dd/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 12:35:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m just starting out, so would love to hear from you folks. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I currently just use finviz but don&amp;#39;t know if there&amp;#39;s anything better out there&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have a pretty robust DCF model template, but I already dread copy-pasting the data from 10Ks especially since most companies have different formats for their P&amp;amp;Ls and across industries. How do you make sure this doesn&amp;#39;t take up too much of your time? &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When working the assumptions, do you just switch back and forth between news and create ad-hoc tables for scenarios to plug into the model?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[最高法院大法官托马斯称联邦大麻禁令 "自相矛盾且不稳定"，预示着合法化即将来临]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oak73w/supreme_court_justice_thomas_calling_federal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oak73w/supreme_court_justice_thomas_calling_federal/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:57:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NVDA对AMD。从长远来看，哪个更值得购买？]]></title><description><![CDATA[NVDA是一只野兽般的股票，最近出现了大幅上涨，并将在7月以4:1的比例进行拆分。
7月下旬4:1。许多人预计拆分后会出现飙升，因为它可以吸引
更多的投资者。AMD也有很好的发展，但似乎是两者中更有价值的。
两者中更有价值，有更大的增长空间。两者中哪一个会...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oaisr9/nvda_vs_amd_which_is_the_better_buy_for_the_long/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oaisr9/nvda_vs_amd_which_is_the_better_buy_for_the_long/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 09:58:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NVDA is a beast of a stock that has seen a huge run up lately and will be split 4:1 in late July. Many anticipate a spike after the split since it could attract more investors. AMD has also been on a nice run but seems to be the better value of the two with more room to grow. Which of the two would you buy and why?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$PLTR持袋人欢欣鼓舞!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oakw14/pltr_bagholders_rejoice/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oakw14/pltr_bagholders_rejoice/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 09:46:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这位父亲要去的地方https://t.co/Dvm1nCKqeD]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1410043879110369284</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1410043879110369284</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 08:45:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我读了《在华尔街随意走走》，阅读清单上的下一步是什么？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/oajmnm/i_read_a_random_walk_down_wall_street_whats_next/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/oajmnm/i_read_a_random_walk_down_wall_street_whats_next/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 07:49:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[万亿美元的公司，宝贝。

@Facebook #Facebook $FB https://t.co/EXKObUu2qK]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1409879499186085892</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1409879499186085892</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 07:36:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[对SoFi的长期公司研究和分析（过滤噪音）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我已经看到很多关于交易SOFI和空头挤压等的帖子，但我是为了长期投资SoFi，原因如下
投资于SoFi是长期的，原因如下。

 1. 1.SoFi在第一季度实际上有正的EBITDA，并预测2021年的EBITDA为2700万美元。
    2021年的EBITDA! 有多少高增长、近期上市的公司可以这么说！？SoFi是
    预测为2.54亿美元...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oal276/long_term_company_research_analysis_on_sofi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oal276/long_term_company_research_analysis_on_sofi/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 05:29:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve seen a ton of posts about trading SOFI and short squeezes etc. but I’m investing in SoFi for the LONG TERM and here’s why:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SoFi actually had positive EBITDA in Q1 and is forecasting $27M in EBITDA for 2021! How many high growth, recent IPO’s can say that!  SoFi is forecasting $254M EBITDA in ’22, $484M ’23 ($1.17B in ’25 but that’s a bit of a wild card since it’s so far in the future…).  That’s a 162% CAGR over 3 years and 113% CAGR over 5.  They exceeded guidance in Q4’20 and in Q1’21 !!!  Their forecast is also somewhat conservative since it excludes the impact of the pending bank charter acquisition which could increase these #’s.  It also excludes some of the new offerings that were just announced like Auto Loans and IPO investing (underwriting).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rapid revenue and customer growth! Forecast of $980M in 2021 to $2.1B in 2023 is a 29% CAGR over 3 years (28% CAGR over 5 years).  2.28M unique customers in Q1 and targeting 3M customers by the end of 2021.  They have a great track record of upselling existing customers (very low cost to upsell vs. acquire) with about 1/4 of their customers using multiple products, this should only improve as they add more product lines (like auto loans…and hopefully options soon!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Galileo technology platform actually turns a major cost center into a profit center and makes them a true Fintech vs. just an online bank like Ally etc.  Galileo is expected to grow 55% CAGR from 2020-2025 with an estimated 62% margin.  This gives them a great B2B model and de-risks a 100% banking model.  Galileo is the Fintech engine behind 70M accounts (Q1 #’s) and customers include Robinhood, Chime, Monzo, Revolt etc. Galileo’s APIs power functionalities including account set-up, funding, direct deposit, ACH transfer, IVR, early paycheck direct deposit, bill pay, transaction notifications, check balance, and point of sale authorization as well as dozens of other capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Future bank charter with the pending acquisition of Golden Pacific Bancorp will help juice profitability and revenue growth and lowers their cost of capital.  This is expected to grow profits from $484M in 2023 to $718M in 2023.  If their estimates are correct AND the acquisition goes through that would increase the 3-year earnings CAGR from 162% up to 198%!  This deal should close by the end of 2021&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid leadership:  Anthony Noto, CEO has a strong background in Finance with Goldman Sachs and the NFL (CFO) AND Technology from Twitter (COO).  Chris Lapointe, CFO also has a great mix of Tech (Uber) and finance from Goldman Sachs.  Similar story with the rest of the executive team.  Strong marketing with SoFi stadium in LA (Superbowl venue) and SoFi’s investment team is frequently on CNBC (Liz Young etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rising interest rates is actually POSITIVE for SoFi!  Banks pay customers a relatively low interest rate on short term deposits and charge customers a higher interest rate on longer term loans.  As rates rise their margins increase.  With rates at record lows, a rapidly recovering economy and inflation on the horizon rates should only go higher (maybe substantially and much faster than normal).  The bank charter only enhances this….&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I invested a little in SoFi (via IPOE) originally after it pulled back and wanted to invest more BUT before I did, I opened accounts at SoFi to verify that it’s all that they say it is.  So I opened a checking account, 2% cash back credit card, active investing account, automated investing account.  This is the real deal:  Products are SUPER competitive (2% cash back on a CC with NO annual fee!), Checking account pays 0.25% with no fees, $0 stock trades for active investing and direct access to IPOs (I participated in their 1st 4 IPOs today - 6/29) and no cost automated advisor investing.  They really treat you like a “member” and customer service has been great so far.  The mobile App is very user friendly with a ton of added features (credit score, education etc.).

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you own SoFi stock for the long term and you’re not a customer yet – you’re doing yourself a disservice.  You are an owner in the company and you should be profiting from your own banking!  Try them – you’ll love them and start consolidating all your accounts to them like I am.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post lockup period (ended Monday 6/28) we should see a lot more interest from  ETFs, Mutual Funds, Institutional investors and analysts.   Volume should dissipate and the stock held its ground even with 50M shares trading a day (10X normal volume). There is a ton of demand for not only high growth but also PROFITABLE companies and FinTech specifically.   Based on their market cap and projections for profitability they should be added to the Russell indexes next year and possibly the S&amp;amp;P Indexes if they can meet the profitability criteria etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Analyst Price Targets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oppenheimer:  Overweight $30 Price Target&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rosenblatt = BUY $25 Price Target&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I personally don’t follow Analysts too closely but it does drive institutional investor buying and helps give you a sanity check.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My 2024 Price Target is $42-$50 based on their 2024 projected revenue (with current product offerings, this should increase as they offer new products and finalize the bank acquisition).  This is based on a pretty simple comparison to other FinTech&amp;#39;s (Square and Paypal) P/S multiples.  Pretty rudimentary so I&amp;#39;d welcome other input.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are obvious risks if multiples come down or if they miss their targets and there is a very high short interest right now but so far they have delivered on all their guidance and growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve seen a ton of posts on SoFi trading with a lot of hopes and dreams of a quick hit or WSB pushing it higher and that’s not why I put my money into SoFi over the past few months.  I’m an investor not a gambler...but I have been buying some of the dips when it does on sale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclosure:  I’m long SoFI and it’s my largest holding.  I continue to buy more on dips and plan to add more in general as they meet their targets and goals, release new products.  I clearly have a vested interest in SoFi going higher but I wanted to share some of the research on the company vs. all the hype that&amp;#39;s flying out there right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有谁知道为什么FED拒绝加息，哪怕是0.25%？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我认为相当明显的是，将利率提高0.25%就可以
缓解这些所谓的 "短缺"，实际上就是他们所说的当一种商品出现
商品价格大幅飙升时的说法。我们的 "短缺 "无处不在，从木材到
二手车到房地产。



我的问题是，是否真的如此...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oakbmd/does_anybody_know_why_the_fed_refuses_to_raise/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oakbmd/does_anybody_know_why_the_fed_refuses_to_raise/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 03:59:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think its rather obvious to see that raising interest rates just .25% would ease up these so call &amp;quot;shortages&amp;quot; which are really what they say when a commodity has a huge spike in prices. We have &amp;quot;shortages&amp;quot; everwhere from wood to used cars to real estate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My question is, is it really that difficult to bump interest rates up .25% just to help ease the amount of inflation that is happening around the USA? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I noticed that other countries are also raising rates already and even India &amp;amp; china have higher interest rates than the USA right now. Why do they insist waiting until 2023-2024?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the first things u studied if you took economics was that 0% interest rates (making money free and printing alot of it) leads to hyperinflation. We are supposed to be able to put our money in the bank and collect at least 2% in interest rates. Why is money so cheap still? None of this is adding up. So I was hoping somebody could explain why interest rates are going to stay at ~ 0% for more years. I am so scared to invest in the stock market now seeing as to how pumped up it is with fake money. Its so obvious that it only goes higher because of 0% interest rates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[将亏损变成250亿美元。- 巴菲特/芒格]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特和查理-芒格今晚参加了CNBC的节目，我的主要收获之一是，在他们的旅程中，损失是他们成功的关键。
我的一个主要收获是，在他们的旅程中，损失是如何对他们的成功至关重要的。

他们举的一个例子是，他们在80年代拥有的一家百货商店正在亏损
所以他们减少了损失，挽回了约600万美元。他们估计...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oamdfz/turning_a_loss_into_25_billion_buffettmunger/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oamdfz/turning_a_loss_into_25_billion_buffettmunger/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 03:26:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warren Buffett and Charlie Munger were on CNBC tonight and one of my main takeaways was how losses along their journey were critical to their success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One example they gave was a department store they had in the &amp;#39;80s was losing money so they cut their losses and salvaged ~$6 million.  They estimated since then they&amp;#39;ve turned that single $6M into ~$25 billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Had the business/investment not failed the money could&amp;#39;ve remained tied up for years making so-so returns.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me this hit home as my first investment losses forced me to take investing more seriously.  Fingers crossed I&amp;#39;ll have the same return story in 30-40 years.  ;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[根据巴菲特的说法，以合理的价格购买一家出色的公司远比以便宜的价格购买一家普通的公司要好。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据我所知，他从未真正解释过原因。从我所看到的数据来看，廉价购买
廉价购买公司是一种表现优异的策略。请为我分析一下这个问题。为什么
或为什么不是更好？这不可能完全是由于税率的不同。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oagbeg/according_to_buffett_it_is_far_better_to_buy_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oagbeg/according_to_buffett_it_is_far_better_to_buy_a/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 02:56:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;He never really explained why, as far as I know. From the data I’ve seen, buying companies on the cheap is an outperforming strategy.  Break this down for me. Why or why is it not better? It can’t be solely due to the difference in tax rates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[简要看一下我在过去3个月中错过的每一只热门股票]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oahtji/a_brief_look_at_me_missing_out_on_every_popular/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oahtji/a_brief_look_at_me_missing_out_on_every_popular/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 02:44:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你对未来10年最有信心的游戏是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，标题说明了一切。

简单说一下，我的投资组合只包括5只股票，AMD、JPM、BA。
AAPL，和CRSRR。在清空我的ETSY头寸后，我现在有大约9%的现金。
我正在寻找一个在未来5-10年内有潜力的伟大公司，但是
我有一点...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oai5jy/what_are_your_highest_conviction_plays_for_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oai5jy/what_are_your_highest_conviction_plays_for_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 01:14:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok the title says it all. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just a quick preface, my portfolio consists of just 5 stocks, AMD, JPM, BA, AAPL, and CRSR. I&amp;#39;m about 9% cash right now after liquidating my ETSY position and I&amp;#39;m looking for a great company with potential in the next 5-10 years but I&amp;#39;m having a little bit of trouble.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost every stock I want to own is trading at too high of a multiple for me so now I&amp;#39;m turning to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are your highest conviction plays in the long term and WHY?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我要去做https://t.co/DeR2D5qJAD]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1409853625535455236</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1409853625535455236</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 22:41:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉被赶出标准普尔500指数的公司表现优于它]]></title><description><![CDATA[资料来源。
https://finance.yahoo.com/news/the-company-tesla-booted-from-the-sp-500-is-outperforming-it-over-50-202435898.html

Tl;DR。

特斯拉在2020年12月21日大张旗鼓地进入标准普尔500指数，在重新平衡的过程中
指数的重新平衡。它在第一个月就飙升了20%以上，但从那时起，它已经
下跌，...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oaeck5/the_company_tesla_booted_from_the_sp_500_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oaeck5/the_company_tesla_booted_from_the_sp_500_is/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 22:24:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/the-company-tesla-booted-from-the-sp-500-is-outperforming-it-over-50-202435898.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/the-company-tesla-booted-from-the-sp-500-is-outperforming-it-over-50-202435898.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tl;DR:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla entered the S&amp;amp;P 500 to great fanfare on Dec. 21, 2020, in a rebalance of the index. It surged well over 20% in its first month, but since then has fallen, standing now with gains of about 5%, lagging the S&amp;amp;P 500’s (&lt;sup&gt;GSPC)&lt;/sup&gt; near-16% gain in that same timeframe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla’s entry meant one company had to leave, as the S&amp;amp;P 500 does not become the S&amp;amp;P 501 when a new company joins the club. To make room, S&amp;amp;P had to kick out Apartment Investment and Management (AIV) from the index, but since that December 2020 rebalance, the company’s stock spiked almost 60% — and though it went down still stands around 40% higher than it did when it got the boot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[愿望 100% 悠乐]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/o9xfvw/wish_100_yolo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/o9xfvw/wish_100_yolo/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 22:24:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[保护你的钱。我认为经济很快就会崩溃。]]></title><description><![CDATA[说我胆小，但我的理由是这样的。

1）大银行正在增加红利。他们在2007年年中和2008年雷曼兄弟破产前做了完全相同的事情
和2008年，就在雷曼兄弟破产之前，他们也做了同样的事情。他们这样做是为了制造一种
金融安全的假象，并在兑现之前吸引小投资者。
兑现之前，吸引小投资者...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/oadncd/protect_your_money_i_think_the_economy_will_crash/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/oadncd/protect_your_money_i_think_the_economy_will_crash/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 22:00:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call me chicken little, but here&amp;#39;s my rationale:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Big banks are increasing dividends. They did the exact same thing in mid 2007 and 2008 right before Lehman brothers went bankrupt. They do this to create an illusion of financial safety, and to draw in smaller investors before cashing out the equity for institutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.barrons.com/amp/articles/big-banks-seen-increasing-dividends-by-10-on-average-51624658729&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.barrons.com/amp/articles/big-banks-seen-increasing-dividends-by-10-on-average-51624658729&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Federal reverse repo activity is extremely high. Almost 850 billion dollars right now. It signals serious liquidity issues for institutional investors, with the Fed increasing demand for UST collateral. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.newyorkfed.org/markets/autorates/temp&quot;&gt;https://apps.newyorkfed.org/markets/autorates/temp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) The economy did not recover this fast after COVID. The same UST liquidity injected through reverse repos were used by big investors to have more cash on hand because most of their trading is done with margin debt (need to meet margin requirements), and the UST money prevented a bigger crash last March. But their leverage has not gone down, and the stock market being at the peak is unjustified.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.federalreserve.gov/econres/feds/hedge-fund-treasury-trading-and-funding-fragility-evidence-from-the-covid-19-crisis.htm&quot;&gt;https://www.federalreserve.gov/econres/feds/hedge-fund-treasury-trading-and-funding-fragility-evidence-from-the-covid-19-crisis.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Fed continously pumping liquidity through stimulus checks for retail and reverse repo for institutions is dangerous. Producer price index is at an all time high. Lumber, oil, and steel futures are skyrocketing because of supply shortage. So much speculation in stocks, cryptocurrency (allows 100x leverage...), and real estate. Asset bubbles form before a crash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;amp;source=web&amp;amp;rct=j&amp;amp;url=https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-22/bubble-expert-jeremy-grantham-addresses-epic-equities-euphoria&amp;amp;ved=2ahUKEwiFstnqsb3xAhXVN30KHbFsBIEQFjABegQIAxAC&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw2FRt5rczT_Oi1lov6E-2tJ&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;amp;source=web&amp;amp;rct=j&amp;amp;url=https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-22/bubble-expert-jeremy-grantham-addresses-epic-equities-euphoria&amp;amp;ved=2ahUKEwiFstnqsb3xAhXVN30KHbFsBIEQFjABegQIAxAC&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw2FRt5rczT_Oi1lov6E-2tJ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) The yeild curve is flattening. Long term yields between 5 year and 30 year bonds have fallen, and FOMC expects overnight rate hikes in early 2023. This is typical before a recession.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/m.investing.com/analysis/is-it-already-time-to-think-about-a-us-recession-200588193%3fampMode=1&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/m.investing.com/analysis/is-it-already-time-to-think-about-a-us-recession-200588193%3fampMode=1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The news media is trying to tell everyone that everything is fine, but it&amp;#39;s not. Everything is debt, everything is overexposed to leverage, and the strain on the financial system is starting to show. Just remember, all the news was very positive right before 2008. Don&amp;#39;t listen to the news. Listen to the data and the facts. Protect your savings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你认为目前股市被高度高估，而且你预计中期回报率很低，甚至是负数，你会如何处理你的资金？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我认为很难反驳的是，目前市场总体上是
非常高的价值。许多措施，如平均市盈率、巴菲特指标。
盈利增长等都表明了这一点。然而，债券收益率处于历史
水平的低点，其他资产价格如住房甚至绘画或。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/oad95q/what_would_you_do_with_your_money_if_you_think/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/oad95q/what_would_you_do_with_your_money_if_you_think/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 21:36:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think it is hard to argue against, that the market in general is currently very high valued. Many measures like average PE ratio, Buffet Indicator, earnings growth etc. are indicating this. However bond yields are at record level lows and other asset prices like housing or even paintings or classic cars are also from historical perspective extremely high priced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you came to the conclusion, that the prices are too high what would you do with the money instead?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Staying in cah and lose it on the inflation?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[谁真正相信今年会出现崩盘，你在做什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[虽然我对股市很陌生，但我敢打赌，每年和每天总有一些人在某个地方谈论崩盘。
每一年，每一天都在谈论拐角处的崩溃。

作为新手，我知道我什么都不知道，但我确实为我的大仓位设置了止损。
仓位设置了止损，以防万一。

如果你认为我们可以期待今年的崩溃......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oafplq/who_truly_believes_a_crash_is_coming_this_year/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oafplq/who_truly_believes_a_crash_is_coming_this_year/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 21:36:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;While new to the stock market, I would bet there is always someone, somewhere  every year and every day talking about a crash around the corner. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being new I know that I know nothing, but do have stop losses set for my bigger positions on the off chance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you think we can expect a crash this year - why? And what are you doing about it? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please no bear vs bull rhetoric - I’ve seen this topic touched on in other non-crash posts and it always turns into our side/their side and I’m not looking for that. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[劳斯莱斯 (RYCEY)]]></title><description><![CDATA[我有1000股。计划是在航空业反弹时长期持有。
我不着急。但你有什么想法？我是否应该卖掉并腾出
腾出1400美元来投资其他地方（大约损失500美元），或者只是
稳坐钓鱼台，长期持有？你会怎么做？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oa9f0r/rolls_royce_rycey/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oa9f0r/rolls_royce_rycey/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 21:17:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have 1000 shares. Plan is to hold long term while the airline industry bounces back, I’m in no rush. What are your thoughts though? Should I sell and free up that 1400 dollars to invest elsewhere (taking about a 500 dollar loss) or just sit tight and hold for long? What would you do?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[📉😵💫😵💫]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oac0kd/_/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oac0kd/_/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 21:17:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[语言学习应用Duolingo申请上市，收入同比翻番]]></title><description><![CDATA[ * https://techcrunch.com/2021/06/28/duolingo-s-1/
 * https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/28/duolingo-files-s-1-for-ipo.html

你对此有什么看法？收到Robinhood关于Duolingo Inc.
(DUOL)现在被列入其 "IPO准入 "名单。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oa9do4/languagelearning_app_duolingo_files_to_go_public/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oa9do4/languagelearning_app_duolingo_files_to_go_public/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 19:38:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2021/06/28/duolingo-s-1/&quot;&gt;https://techcrunch.com/2021/06/28/duolingo-s-1/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/28/duolingo-files-s-1-for-ipo.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/28/duolingo-files-s-1-for-ipo.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are your thoughts on this ? Got robinhood notification about Duolingo Inc. (DUOL) now being on its &amp;quot;IPO Access&amp;quot; list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[High Tide公布2021年第二季度财务业绩，收入增长99%，调整后EBITDA达到470万美元，再创新高。]]></title><description><![CDATA[来源于 海潮公司公布2021年第二季度财务业绩，收入增长99%，调整后EBITDA为470万美元，再创历史新高。
收入增长99%，调整后EBITDA达470万美元，再创新高

2021年第二季度 - 财务亮点。

 * 在截至4月30日的三个月里，收入增加了99%，达到4090万美元。
   2021年4月30日为止的三个月中，收入增加了99%，达到4090万美元，与此相比...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oa4aya/high_tide_reports_second_quarter_2021_financial/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/oa4aya/high_tide_reports_second_quarter_2021_financial/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 19:12:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Source: High Tide Reports Second Quarter 2021 Financial Results Featuring a 99% Increase in Revenue and Another Record Adjusted EBITDA of $4.7 Million  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second Quarter 2021 – Financial Highlights:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue increased by 99% to $40.9 million in the three months ended April 30, 2021, compared to $20.6 million in the same quarter last year.  The second quarter of 2021 financial results incorporate the acquisition of META Growth Corp. on November 18, 2020, and Smoke Cartel, Inc. on March 24, 2021.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gross profit increased by 93% to $15.0 million in the three months ended April 30, 2021, compared to $7.8 million in the same quarter last year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gross profit margin in the three months ended April 30, 2021, was 37% compared to 38% in the same quarter last year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adjusted EBITDA(1) for the three months ended April 30, 2021, was $4.7 million compared to $1.8 million for same quarter last year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Geographically in the three months ended April 30, 2021, $35.0 million of revenue was earned in Canada, $5.7 million in the United States and $0.2 million internationally.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Segment-wise in the three months ended April 30, 2021, $38.4 million of revenue was generated by Retail, $2.5 million by Wholesale, and an immaterial amount by Corporate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cash on hand as at April 30, 2021, totaled $29.4 million compared to $7.5 million as at October 31, 2020.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SOFI--如此飞翔]]></title><description><![CDATA[什么是Sofi？

社会金融（$SOFI）是一个无所不能的金融应用程序，最近通过反向合并上市。
通过反向合并上市。Sofi的功能包括：支票账户。
信用卡、股票投资、学生贷款再融资和发放。
个人贷款，抵押贷款再融资，汽车贷款......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oa86eq/sofi_so_fly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oa86eq/sofi_so_fly/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 18:53:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Sofi?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Social Finance ($SOFI) is a jack of all trades finance app which recently went public through a reverse merger. Sofi has features such as &lt;strong&gt;Checking Accounts, Credit Cards, Stock Investing,  Student Loan Refinancing and Origination, Personal Loans, Mortgage Refinancing, Auto Loan Refinancing&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;and Early Payday, so you can blow your Wendy’s paycheck 2 days earlier.&lt;/strong&gt; The vast array of products they offer and partnerships they have formed with other companies gives them a unique ability to cross-sell their products to customers and retain customers by doing so. For example, someone may come to SOFI refinance their gender studies student loans, but end up banking and investing with them. This is because of a singular key factor. &lt;strong&gt;Convenience.&lt;/strong&gt; Sofi’s target audience for their products are millennials who are financially savvy. What do we know about millennials? They value convenience. It’s why people will use Grubhub, Doordash or Uber-Eats despite the absurd fees and cold tendies they receive; why people will use Amazon Prime to order stuff rather than go in person; why people will use Robinhood despite it going down every time something interesting actually happens in the market. This creates a dynamic where people will switch over their entire financial life to Sofi in order to simplify things, and makes Sofi in many ways, a superapp in the making, similar to that of Alipay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/pnyzn6ihf7871.png?width=1396&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c24282bb20dd3571b020b51616a3ecf5b4c23eea&quot;&gt; Sofi has worked out deals with big banks so that retail can get an equal footing in IPO’s. Provided a Sofi member has $3,000 in their Sofi Invest account, they are eligible to get in on an IPO at the IPO’s reference price, as opposed to market price.  &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Financials?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we hear the term lending, we probably think of some Big Short Michael Burry subprime fuckery, but that is not what we have here today. Sofi deals with high quality customers with good income and good credit scores, rather than degenerates like you. Because of this, they can run a business model that is beneficial to all parties involved. Sofi can charge lower interest rates due to the low risk of default on any lending they do, and customers can get low interest rates with flexible payment options. This provides a good experience for customers and helps Sofi retain them, or better yet, cross-sell them on other products. As it stands now, Sofi’s bread and butter is Business to Consumer (B2C) lending, which makes up a large portion of their revenue, however as time goes on and we see an expansion and more adoption of their financial services (Banking, Credit Cards, Investing), we will see this shift to be more diversified. Sofi projects 43% CAGR, which is far above other companies in the sector, such as PayPal and Square, who project 20.2% and 29.3% respectively. Sofi will be profitable this year as well, and by 2025 will be raking in Billions of dollars in annual profits. Overall, Sofi is in a very healthy position with a boatload of cash on hand ready to expand the business, be it through acquisitions, or building out products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/0qwveoorf7871.png?width=850&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=27edc4a721d49544074324e920856b7d8f2f7536&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/0qwveoorf7871.png?width=850&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=27edc4a721d49544074324e920856b7d8f2f7536&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/nxsb5cxsf7871.png?width=850&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=7953fca5f265f025feb036fbf02e6d8183550b90&quot;&gt; Graph go brrrr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moat?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sofi is a very unique business. Due to it’s jack of all trades nature, it is hard to pinpoint a singular company which compares to it. It shares aspects with dozens of companies, such as investing with Robinhood/Webull/Chime/Acorns, banking with legacy banks such as GS/JPM/BAC/WFC, and many other companies who parallel Sofi. With this said, Sofi has a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;massive&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; advantage over other fintech platforms. &lt;strong&gt;Galileo&lt;/strong&gt;. No, not the astronomer. &lt;strong&gt;Galileo&lt;/strong&gt; is to Sofi what AWS is to Amazon. &lt;strong&gt;Galileo&lt;/strong&gt; is a fintech API which powers many of the fintech companies we know and love (or hate) today. Companies such as Robinhood rely on &lt;strong&gt;Galileo&lt;/strong&gt; to power aspects of their business, such as issuing debit cards and opening accounts. What this means for all you smoothbrains out there, is that as those companies grow and gain members, Sofi gets a cut of that. Though Robinhood is the most well known of the companies handled by &lt;strong&gt;Galileo&lt;/strong&gt;, there are dozens of others who all rely on it to power their businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;![img](ass2c6hxf7871 &amp;quot;
&amp;quot;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price Action?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/fy6qenk0g7871.png?width=1560&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=cd43b211a2f8a431bb6ac5194bbab4d14bd26989&quot;&gt;Crayon Says Stock Go Uppies 🚀&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because some of you smooth brained degenerates might not know how to draw with crayons, I will do it for you. Sofi has been in an overall uptrend since it’s merger deal was announced earlier this year. In February, Sofi peaked at an ATH of 28.2 dollars, right before the Inflation Boogaloo made the markets throw a fit. From then it’s had some choppy price action but has continued in it’s uptrend. Recently, Sofi has dropped due to Pipe unlocking, allowing them to sell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pipe?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, not the lead thing you licked as a kid, putting your room-temp IQ ass on the path to WSB. PIPE (Private Investment in Public Equity) is when big investment firms are offered the ability to invest before a merger is announced at a favorable price. In doing this, their shares are locked up for a period of time so that they don’t immediately sell. As of last Friday, PIPE investors were able to sell their shares if they wanted. On Friday and Monday, we saw high volume price action with lots of volatility. Friday was somewhat brutal for holders, but Monday not only presented opportunities for dip buying, but had a great close. Sofi rejected the lows of 17.6 and closed at 19.4, significantly above the $18 support level. TLDR? &lt;strong&gt;Stock Goes Uppies Tomorrow.&lt;/strong&gt; 🚀🚀🚀🚀&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;![img](w8625038g7871 &amp;quot;
Sofi Pipe consists of ⅔ investors who likely have no plans on selling, and ⅓ funds who would likely sell. With over 94 million volume the past 2 trading days, it is very likely they have all sold, setting us up to 🚀&amp;quot;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short Squeeze?&lt;/strong&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sofi currently has over &lt;strong&gt;28 million&lt;/strong&gt; shares short sold, with borrow fees costing hundreds of % in fees. Admittedly, some of this is due to PIPE holders hedging their positions (Long PIPE shares, Short shares on the open market), but there is almost certainly some non pipe related shorts. There are almost no shares available to short at any given time however, and retail are getting paid &lt;strong&gt;46% interest&lt;/strong&gt; just for diamond handing shares and lending them. Pretty sweet right? With the bullish price action today and high short interest, this could be a powder keg ready to be set off with rocket fuel 🚀.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/u9mngtpcg7871.png?width=1331&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=5c82f361102f7fb7e0064e546bcb5ed6fa081a2e&quot;&gt;Screenshot from IborrowDesk shows high borrow rates with few shares available to borrow.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Catalysts?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sofi is currently in the process of becoming a chartered bank. What this means is that they have to get government approval and become an FDIC approved entity, so if they blow up like Bear Stearns, your $50.33 checking account is protected. Sofi recently purchased a bank with an existing charter so that instead of getting a brand new charter, they can simply request a transfer of control. This will speed up the process, and although the bank charter will probably be approved later this year, any positive news earlier could set this stock off. Sofi will also release earnings most likely in July, and it is seemingly likely they will smash estimates which make stock go 🚀.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/q462ix4jg7871.png?width=1415&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=84ecd9e78250c04f32e46bb58d66629ec207a887&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/q462ix4jg7871.png?width=1415&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=84ecd9e78250c04f32e46bb58d66629ec207a887&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sofi Stadium and Noto.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CEO of Sofi is simply put, a baller. Anthony Noto was a football superstar in college, an Army Ranger, and has worked in high level positions for Goldman Sachs, The NFL and Twitter before joining Sofi. Every company needs to advertise, and how did Noto choose to do this? He named a fucking stadium. That&amp;#39;s right, when your boomer dad is watching football, it could be at Sofi Stadium. Sofi stadium is situated in LA, and is home to the LA Rams and Chargers. It also facilitates lots of other venues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/sxandv9og7871.png?width=1152&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=d7841e2e3aedd3de8fcb03afb74a4f14a68fc072&quot;&gt;Noto Second From The Right&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/a4nllkdqg7871.png?width=1999&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=4c117aef6b8705229e9ce77ebf14999e3cbd65c2&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/a4nllkdqg7871.png?width=1999&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=4c117aef6b8705229e9ce77ebf14999e3cbd65c2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Options Flow?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/3u12luzrg7871.png?width=1480&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=93731f5e541ab0a13989e84c044afafe9beebbaa&quot;&gt;Lots of bullish inflow.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Monday, Sofi had a massive amount of short term call options bought with strikes between $10-$20. You know what this means? Gamma Squeeze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Positions? Ban?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ticker, Strike, Expiration. I get it. Your adhd riddled brains can’t focus on something for more than 5 seconds, so I gotchu. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/zxpf27uug7871.png?width=952&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=97f20daf9b30ab9f4beb030aa2d770ca79f99c59&quot;&gt; I&amp;#39;m long 46 SOFI 2023 10C, but if you have more risk tolerance than me (who am I kidding, you do), July calls are a good buy. If water is too spicy for you and options aren’t your thing however, just buy shares. No-one here will judge you for being as bland as white rice.  &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TLDR:&lt;/strong&gt; Good company, bullish crayons, short and gamma squeeze, stock go 🚀🚀🚀&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天大家都在谈论的金融科技颠覆者，不是别人，正是社会金融公司，又称SOFI。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我已经说了大约2-3周，我将对$SoFi做一个DD，并认为
随着今天成交量和提及率的增加，现在是时候提出我自己的牛市
论点。

SoFi于2011年由Mike Cagney、Dan Macklin、James Finnigan和Ian
布拉迪，四个在斯坦福大学研究生院认识的学生。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/o9xjby/the_fintech_disrupter_that_everyone_is_talking/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/o9xjby/the_fintech_disrupter_that_everyone_is_talking/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 18:32:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have been saying for about 2-3 weeks that I would do a DD on $SoFi and figured with the increased volume and mentions today, it is time lay out my own bull thesis.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SoFi was founded in 2011 by Mike Cagney, Dan Macklin, James Finnigan, and Ian Brady, four students who met at the Stanford Graduate School of Business. The founders hoped SoFi could provide more affordable options for those taking on debt to fund their education. &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SoFi#:%7E:text=SoFi%20was%20founded%20in%202011,debt%20to%20fund%20their%20education&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SoFi#:~:text=SoFi%20was%20founded%20in%202011,debt%20to%20fund%20their%20education&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am just a big believer in bringing personal finances to the masses and to teach people about personal finance and how to accumulate and build wealth, most parents and schools don’t teach shit on the subject matter. I absolutely love SoFi&amp;#39;s statements/mantras:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our number one goal is helping our members get their money right. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;SoFi&amp;#39;s mission is to help people reach financial independence to realize their ambitions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s go over some #s.  SoFi has been around and growing as a private company for some time now and has seen seven consecutive quarters of YoY growth w Q1 2021 producing 110% growth and ending w 2.281M members.  This is exponential to say the very least.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will be linking the data and numbers, but that is all readily available for all the see and find.  The adjusted Net Revenue and EBITDA are increasing and trending in the right direction, with 151% and 70% growth YoY respectively.  The biggest factors to me are they are scaling and accumulating data.  These 2 things are what are going to set companies apart to not only produce growth but obtain profitability to the bottom line. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal of SoFi is to be the one-stop shop for everything a person would need for finance.  Checking/savings accounts, personal loans, home loans, student loans, car loans, budgeting, investing in the markets, and on and on.  The total products used by members has grown by 121% YoY and financial products has grown 273% YoY.  It appears to this layman that they are figuring out to how grow members as well as total products used by member.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nasdaq.com/articles/sofis-q1-earnings-beat-managements-guidance-as-company-prepares-to-trade-on-nasdaq-2021-05&quot;&gt;https://www.nasdaq.com/articles/sofis-q1-earnings-beat-managements-guidance-as-company-prepares-to-trade-on-nasdaq-2021-05&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SoFi acquired Golden Pacific Bancorp Inc in its quest to get a federal bank charter, which is cumbersome and tedious process.  This would be an upcoming catalyst for sure if/when this happens &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.spglobal.com/marketintelligence/en/news-insights/latest-news-headlines/sofi-s-bank-buy-presents-blueprint-for-more-fintech-bank-deals-63129976&quot;&gt;https://www.spglobal.com/marketintelligence/en/news-insights/latest-news-headlines/sofi-s-bank-buy-presents-blueprint-for-more-fintech-bank-deals-63129976&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Galileo acquisition was a game changer and covered well by &lt;a href=&quot;/u/havocs2&quot;&gt;u/havocs2&lt;/a&gt; in his DD, I would just add that this has seen 130% YoY (everything seems to be growing triple digits) growth as well. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/o9l9x6/why_sofi_will_be_sofly_my_78000_yolo_into_sofi/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/o9l9x6/why_sofi_will_be_sofly_my_78000_yolo_into_sofi/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$SoFi was brought to market under the SPAC model and coverage of the stonk has just began.  Coverage was initiated by Oppenheimer w an outperform and was also initiated by Rosenblatt w a buy.  TipRanks has it rated as moderate buy and a price target of $27.50, about a 40% premium to today&amp;#39;s closing price.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tipranks.com/stocks/sofi/forecast&quot;&gt;https://www.tipranks.com/stocks/sofi/forecast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not a bot, nor am I a shill.  I am very active (to fucking active to be honest) in the daily and I post almost all my plays in real time.  Check my post history and you can see that I have been in this play for some time and believe in the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Current positions: 5 $12.50 2023 LEAPS, 2 $20.00 2023 LEAPS, and 155 shares and no intention of dumping or selling short term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is there a high SI? is the borrow rate high? Was this targeted because it was a Chamath SPAC?  Probably, i don&amp;#39;t know for sure and honestly don&amp;#39;t give 2 shits if it is or it is not, I like the company and the stonk and think it is undervalued and will only grow in the future.  That is what the hell I think.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be a FinTech disrupter, you obviously need an app and great user-friendly UI and SoFi has a 4.8 rating w over 48K reviews on the $AAPL app store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR There is no industry/s that need more disruption than banks and brokerages.  For far too long the poors and working class have been hit w hidden fees, outrageous fees, shit even made-up accounts.  SoFi is the just the company to do this disrupting all in one beautiful app!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shout out to &lt;a href=&quot;/u/OSRSkarma&quot;&gt;u/OSRSkarma&lt;/a&gt; as he kept pushing to post this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[18岁，3万现金，ROTH最大值，401k雇主匹配。现在在哪里？]]></title><description><![CDATA[先说一下，我工作很多，有一个生意，在*****，他提供了7%的工资匹配。
我在那里工作的时间即将结束。我有1000美元的
今年在我的罗斯401k里有1000美元，在我的罗斯IRA里有14000美元，两年的价值加上收益。
~约3万美元的现金，以及其他与此无关的资产....。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/o9urai/18_30k_cash_roth_max_401k_employer_match_where_now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/o9urai/18_30k_cash_roth_max_401k_employer_match_where_now/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 17:33:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;To preface, I work a lot and have a business, and work at ***** who offers a 7% match on my paychecks and my time working there is abt done. I have 1,000 from this year in my Roth 401k, 14,000 in my Roth IRA, 2 years worth plus gains, ~$30k cash, and other assets that don’t matter to this equation. Anyways, my family member who is a big investor recommends to wait until a turn down to invest, as I put the other 12k in on a rise. I have read all the books saying not to time it, but should I just dump a lot of my cash in? If so, in my 401k? Or like a Robinhood account? Thanks. Idk where else to put my money&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉被赶出标准普尔500指数的公司表现优于它]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/oaawxo/the_company_tesla_booted_from_the_sp_500_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/oaawxo/the_company_tesla_booted_from_the_sp_500_is/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 17:33:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我不知道谁需要听这个，但没有高于无风险利率的无风险回报。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1409899027785830404</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1409899027785830404</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 17:04:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[房地产的繁荣仍在继续，美国房价再次创下历史新高，在过去一年中上涨了14.6%。这是有史以来最高的年增长率，超过了2005年的前记录。https://t.co/KyOb5EWu16]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1409878295672393746</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1409878295672393746</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 17:04:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如何DD/分析一只股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[伙伴们都围过来。如果你厌倦了被莫特利愚弄，那就试试这个。
裂缝

这就是我对股票的判断，希望新的投资者不会被愚弄到
抽水和倾倒。显然有很多方法可以对一只股票进行尽职调查。
我认为最重要的是有一个过程......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oa5gzs/how_to_ddanalyse_a_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/oa5gzs/how_to_ddanalyse_a_stock/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 17:04:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aight blokes gather around. If youre sick of getting Motley Fooled give this a crack&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is how I DD a stock, so hopefully, new investors won&amp;#39;t get fooled into pump-and-dumps. There&amp;#39;s obviously a lot of ways to do your due diligence on a stock, I think the most important thing is having a process and not relying on trash articles, or your mates tips :|&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My Stock DD Checklist Summary&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you sick of getting &lt;em&gt;Fooled&lt;/em&gt; into terrible stocks? Stock DD or Due Diligence is probs the most important step in investing. So do your DD and don&amp;#39;t COP a Pump and Dump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step One: Identify the Stonk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first step to a stock DD is obviously finding a stonk to DD. This could be a recommendation from your dodgy mate, or maybe you got Motley &lt;em&gt;Fooled&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; The important thing to note here is the intent of the source that is mentioning the stock. Do they have a vested interest? Are they tryna pull a Jordan Belford on ya? What is their motive behind mentioning the stock?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For these reasons, it may be a good idea to identify your own stock. Have a think about companies that you interact with and see if they are publicly traded. Or browse through the listings. Although these strategies are honestly slow and probs trash you can be sure there’s no altera motive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step Two: Understand the Company. Know the Stonk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an extension on the phrase don’t invest in something you don’t understand. The same goes for individual stocks, it’s probably not a good idea to invest in a company if you don’t even know what they do PROBABLY?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search the Businesses ‘About Us’ Section&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pretty much all listed companies will have a webpage with an ‘about us’ section browsing this and their website can be a good starting point to understanding their business, and a good start to a stock DD. See if their website is trash while ur there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use Simply wall st and Read the Company Profile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SWS is decent for listed stocks, it has a Company Overview section for every stock which gives a quick synopsis (Synopsis: a bRiEf suMmaRy oR gEneRal SurVEy Of SoMEThinG) about the business and what they do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How Much Do I Need To know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Peter Lynch “Never invest in an idea you can’t illustrate with a crayon.” As a starting point you should be able to answer at least these four questions, and probs be able to use a crayon;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What sector is the company in?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What does the company do?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How does the company make money?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How long has the company been around?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step Three: What is their Market Cap&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A company’s market capitalization or (Market Cap: if you didn&amp;#39;t know) is how much the stock market determines a company is worth. it is calculated by the total market value of all outstanding shares. These are Large, mid and small cap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each category can be a good investment strategy it&amp;#39;s just important to note that each group has different companies at varying levels of maturity. You shouldn&amp;#39;t buy a micro-cap and be surprised if it gets delisted instead of paying dividends. Likewise, you probably shouldn&amp;#39;t buy a Bluechip and hope they go to the moon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step Four: Screening Software for Stock Analysis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of websites and tools available to screen the selected stocks, Here&amp;#39;s what i use:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trading View&lt;/strong&gt; great&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yahoo Finance&lt;/strong&gt; ehhh&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simply Wall St&lt;/strong&gt; decent, (lots of nice Pics if u cant read)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are we looking for?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After picking some of these tools that works well for you, perform a basic fundamental analysis on the stock. Looking for any red flags:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Earnings Per Share (EPS):&lt;/strong&gt; Positive? Growing over time? Earning?????&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price to Earnings Ratio (PE):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PE 0/NA: &lt;em&gt;The company has no earnings&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PE 1-14: &lt;em&gt;The company is undervalued/has low investor sentiment regarding growth&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PE 15-20: &lt;em&gt;Average&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PE 20+: &lt;em&gt;The company is overvalued/has high investor sentiment regarding growth&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Book Value/share:&lt;/strong&gt; The book value is the net assets of a business divided by the number of shares on issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Debt:&lt;/strong&gt; A company should have more assets than liabilities to avoid bankruptcy. We like companies with low-to-no debt. If a company has debt, ensure it is well covered by assets and earnings&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Return on Equity (ROE):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Higher ROE = The better the company are at making money from equity and vice versa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We like companies with consistently higher ROE over 10. A low ROE means low growth potential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Past Performance:&lt;/strong&gt; We all know &amp;#39;past performance is not indicative of future returns&amp;#39; but it can pay to have a quick look at the stock chart. If its going up that means money&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step Five: Financials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;find the companies latest Yearly or Half-Yearly report. Analyse its Income Statement, Balance Sheet and Cash flow statement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step Six: Cap Raise! Dilution&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therse nothing more frustrating than seeing your share getting hit with Cap Raise after Cap Raise and seeing your shares diluted to nothing. We all had that feeling when they halt and release another supplementary prospectus. FML. One easy sign that a company is constantly raising capital is through looking at it&amp;#39;s share price and number of shares on issue. IF SP is rly low and number of shares is rly high then they&amp;#39;re probs cap raising 24/7.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can also use the financials we read before to try and predict if the company is adequately capitalised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A capital raise is not necessarily a red flag, but be wary and sucks to see all those trading haults.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step Seven: Buy Sell Ratios and Volume&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See if there are a healthy number of buyers and sellers and decent trading volumes. The best way to do this is using your trading platforms. If you&amp;#39;re wanting to sell there&amp;#39;s got to be someone to buy the trash off you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step Eight: Prospects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When examining a company for your stock DD we should consider its macro and microeconomic factors. Notably regulation and future industry outlook and disruption. Are they gonna be the NExt Blockbuster? Is the gov gonna screw u over?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step Nine: Competition&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;compare the stock to it&amp;#39;s direct competitors. To do this we are going to go back to step four and compare the company&amp;#39;s fundamentals against its competitors. If the competitors are better then why not buy them instead?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do they have an economic moat?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;----------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;There are five types of generally accepted economic moat&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;s&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Low-cost production;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;em&gt;Companies that can keep their prices low can maintain market share and discourage competition&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;High switching costs;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Customers and suppliers might be less likely to change companies or providers if the move will incur monetary costs, time delays, or extra effort. e.g. banks and power providers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Network effects;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;em&gt;network effect happens when the “value of a good or service grows” as its used by existing and new customers e.g. Amazon is an excellent example&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Intangible assets;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Brand identity, patents, and government licenses are examples of intangible assets. e.g. think Nike or Coca-Cola as an excellent brand and think of the government regulation surrounding gamble and the moat this creates for gambling companies.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Efficient scale.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Companies that have a natural monopoly – or operate in markets or industries where there are few rivals&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;One thing to consider about an economic moat is they’re largely priced into a stock share price as they often relate to profits. For example Coca-Cola has an excellent brand and due to that sells more products and creates more profits. As such these factors will often be indirectly accounted for in Quantitate Analysis but it can be helpful to identify businesses with and without these moats.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step Ten: Insider Ownership and Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Insider Ownership:&lt;/strong&gt; We generally like companies with large insider ownership. This is big for small cap companies. Skin in the game helps ensure the management&amp;#39;s motives are in line with ours. U can use Simple wall St (Swear i dont work witt them, just like their stuff) which shows Insider Ownership and Trading easily. We like small cap stocks with ~30% insider ownership and history of owners buying on market. For large cap companies&amp;#39; insider ownership will be lower, 3-5% would be decent in this case. It wont be much for large caps u clearly wont see Bill G coppin 30% of Micros any time soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are management buying or selling large amounts of shares?&lt;/strong&gt; Sudden large selling by management for no apparent reason may hint that management believes the company is overvalued or peaked at that point in time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Management Experience:&lt;/strong&gt; Consider educational and professional backgrounds. One of the most important factors is their experience in the industry. Their reputation is also key. What goals has the management set out for the company? Have the leaders had successful projects in the past, or did they fail?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One case study of management is the affect that Elon Musk has had on tesla.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus Step: Speccies are Sentiment and Hype&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After going through every step and doing a thorough DD, it&amp;#39;s important to mention that the market is unpredictable trash. Even with the most advanced analyses, speccies are just sentiment and hype. By every stretch of fundamental analysis, they are trash stonks, that doesn&amp;#39;t mean you can&amp;#39;t make money off them. Just be ready for the pump-and-dump!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(reposted w/ a bit more info. Also had to remove all the links to the SWS and trading and stuff bc the subreredit didnt like. I got nothign to do with them. I just like their stuff)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheers for reading blokes. Hoepfully this saves at least someone from getting Motely Fooled into trash&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚀 🚀 TLDR🚀🚀
Motley fool is Trash.Maybe know the name of a company before YOLOing your life saving into it.... Or maybe not idk 🖍&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>