<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 19:30:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[從Robinhood轉過來？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我仍然是個年輕人，但在GameStop的失敗後開始有點認真地對待投資。
遊戲店的失敗。在沒有賺到錢之後，我決定開始做我所說的
幾年來一直在做的事情，定期向ETF捐款。我目前使用
Robinhood作爲我的經紀商，不知道這樣做是否會更好...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qzait2/switching_from_robinhood/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qzait2/switching_from_robinhood/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 18:50:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m still a young guy, but started taking investing kinda seriously after the GameStop debacle. After making no money, I decided to start doing what I said I&amp;#39;d be doing for years and make regular contributions to an ETF. I currently use Robinhood as my brokerage and wonder if it would be better to switch to a different one or not worry about it. I only have fractional shares (&amp;gt;$1000) in a few stocks, but about $2k in VOO. Any benefit to switching, assuming I just want to regularly contribute to safer investments?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Gonna be switching to fidelity and eating the taxes from RH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[5.3萬億美元，蘋果&amp; 微軟的市值現在比羅素2000指數中所有公司的市值總和（3.8萬億美元）高1.5萬億美元。

$AAPL $MSFT

數據/圖表通過@ycharts https://t.co/3JaSeLkmpO]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462826581550936065</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462826581550936065</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 18:35:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GoDaddy披露最近的安全漏洞，暴露了120萬個賬戶]]></title><description><![CDATA[根據美國證券交易委員會的最新文件，這是他們對該漏洞的說法。

 1. 多達120萬活躍和非活躍的WordPress管理客戶的電子郵件地址和客戶號碼被盜。
    電子郵件地址和客戶號碼被曝光。電子郵件地址的暴露
    帶來了網絡釣魚攻擊的風險。
 2. 原始的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qzp7gn/godaddy_discloses_recent_security_breach_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qzp7gn/godaddy_discloses_recent_security_breach_that/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 17:49:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the latest SEC filing, this is what they say about the breach:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up to 1.2 million active and inactive Managed WordPress customers had their email address and customer number exposed. The exposure of email addresses presents risk of phishing attacks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The original WordPress Admin password that was set at the time of provisioning was exposed. If those credentials were still in use, we reset those passwords.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For active customers, sFTP and database usernames and passwords were exposed. We reset both passwords.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For a subset of active customers, the SSL private key was exposed. We are in the process of issuing and installing new certificates for those customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[藍薯片可以成爲你的漢堡]]></title><description><![CDATA[對於經驗豐富的投資者來說，這已經是老生常談了，但這裏總是有新朋友。只是
想用一個真實的例子來說明你如何能在不需要任何投資的情況下獲得穩定的收益。
需要追逐新的股票。

在一年的時間範圍內，我目前在AAPL中上漲了約25%，在NET中接近400%。
400%的NET。然而，我的美元收益...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qzp37a/blue_chips_can_be_your_bangers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qzp37a/blue_chips_can_be_your_bangers/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 17:33:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Old news for the seasoned investors, but there are always new folks here. Just wanted to use a real life example of how you can make steady gains without needing to chase new stocks. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a one year time horizon, I’m currently up around 25% in AAPL, and close to 400% in NET. However, my dollar gains in both stocks are less than 10% apart. While I may not have exploded on AAPL, DCA’ing in over a year has allowed to me to net the same dollar gains as a bet on growth stock. Just something to consider for newer investors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美聯儲的資產負債表上週再創新高，達到8.675萬億美元。

圖表通過@ycharts https://t.co/YaJbeDp0j7]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462775948110139403</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462775948110139403</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 17:04:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[市值1150億美元的Rivian旨在到2023年銷售54,000輛電動汽車。市值爲770億美元的福特公司的目標是在2023年前銷售60萬輛。]]></title><description><![CDATA["截至2021年10月31日，我們在美國和加拿大有大約55,400份R1T和R1S的預購訂單，這些客戶都支付了可取消的和可接受的費用。
我們在美國和加拿大有大約55,400個R1T和R1S的預購訂單，這些客戶各自支付了可取消和可完全退還的定金。
他們每人支付了1000美元的可取消和可完全退還的定金。根據我們目前的生產預測，我們
預計到2021年，我們將完成約55,400份積壓的預購訂單。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzftqa/115_billion_mkt_cap_rivian_aims_to_sell_54000_evs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzftqa/115_billion_mkt_cap_rivian_aims_to_sell_54000_evs/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 16:26:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;As of October 31, 2021, we had approximately 55,400 R1T and R1S preorders in the United States and Canada from customers who each paid a cancellable and fully refundable deposit of $1,000. Based on our current production forecast, we expect to fill our preorder backlog of approximately 55,400 by the end of 2023.&amp;quot; Rivian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;We are now expecting to produce 600,000 electric vehicles per year globally by end of 2023.&amp;quot;. Ford.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ford is already selling Mach-E&amp;#39;s and adding F150 Lightnings in volume next year (75K+ pre-orders already).  Oh it might just sell  5 million other vehicles a year at profit too (having made $5.7 billion net income YTD 3Q 2021, whilst Rivian revealed a $1 billion dollar loss in its IPO).  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry but the figures speak for themselves. US EV start-ups are trading at absurd valuations vs existing legacy EV producers like Ford who are already in the market selling EV&amp;#39;s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登挑選傑羅姆-鮑威爾領導美聯儲的第二個任期，因爲美國正在與科威德和通貨膨脹作鬥爭]]></title><description><![CDATA[傑羅姆-鮑威爾(Jerome Powell)，他指導美聯儲和國家經濟渡過了難關。
他通過實施史無前例的貨幣刺激措施，引導美聯儲和國家經濟度過驚人的、突然的Covid-19經濟衰退。
他通過實施史無前例的貨幣刺激政策，引導美聯儲和美國經濟度過了驚人的、突如其來的衰退。
擔任美國中央銀行主席。

總統喬-拜登週一宣佈了這一消息...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzm7ni/biden_picks_jerome_powell_to_lead_the_fed_for_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzm7ni/biden_picks_jerome_powell_to_lead_the_fed_for_a/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 15:20:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jerome Powell, who guided the Federal Reserve and the nation’s economy through the staggering and sudden Covid-19 recession by implementing unprecedented monetary stimulus, has been nominated for a second term as chairman of the U.S. central bank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;President Joe Biden made the announcement Monday morning following weeks of speculation that a push from progressives might see Fed Governor Lael Brainard get the spot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brainard instead will be vice chair of the board of governors; she had been widely expected to get a separate vice chair for supervision post, which oversees the nation’s banking system. As vice chair, she would succeed Richard Clarida, whose term expires Jan. 31, 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“As I’ve said before, we can’t just return to where we were before the pandemic, we need to build our economy back better, and I’m confident that Chair Powell and Dr. Brainard’s focus on keeping inflation low, prices stable, and delivering full employment will make our economy stronger than ever before,” Biden said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The nominations next head to the Senate for confirmation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In making the decision, Biden praised the Powell Fed for its “decisive” action in the early days of the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fed rolled out an unprecedented array of lending programs while also cutting interest rates back to near zero and instituting a monthly bond-buying program that would increase the central bank’s holdings of Treasurys and mortgage-backed securities by more than $4 trillion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Chair Powell has provided steady leadership during an unprecedently challenging period, including the biggest economic downturn in modern history and attacks on the independence of the Federal Reserve,” a White House statement said. “During that time, Lael Brainard – one of our country’s leading macroeconomists – has played a key leadership role at the Federal Reserve, working with Powell to help power our country’s robust economic recovery.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Powell carried the day, it was not without controversy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fed has been under fire lately following an ethics scandal in which multiple officials engaged in trading stocks at a time when the institution was implementing policies aimed at boosting markets. Powell disclosed that he owned municipal bonds, which the Fed also was buying, and he also bought and sold funds tied to the broad stock market indexes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the same time, the Fed has been hit with inflation running faster than it had anticipated – in fact, at the sharpest pace in 30 years. Official Fed policy since September 2020 has been to let inflation run somewhat hotter than the standard 2% target if it allows for full and inclusive employment, but prices have been rising well above that level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Powell has held to the line that inflation will cool off once factors associated with the pandemic return to normal. But the recent readings have raised questions about the so-called average inflation targeting that signaled a historic turn in central bank monetary policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The inflation also has come with a rapid economic recovery and a decline in the unemployment rate from a pandemic peak of 14.8% to its current 4.6%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The White House statement said the recovery is “a testament to the success of the President’s economic agenda, and it is a testament to decisive action by Chair Powell and the Federal Reserve to cushion the impact of the pandemic and get America’s economy back on track.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brainard emerged as a key force in the race over who would carry the Fed through the next four years. She has taken point on several issues important to the Biden administration, particularly the need for the Fed to brace the banking system against disruptive climate change events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A former undersecretary of the Treasury during the Obama administration, Brainard also has been a strong proponent of a digital dollar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The White House statement stressed the importance of progressive for the Fed in the years to come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biden said that Powell and Brainard “also share my deep belief that urgent action is needed to address the economic risks posed by climate change, and stay ahead of emerging risks in our financial system.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Fundamentally, if we want to continue to build on the economic success of this year we need stability and independence at the Federal Reserve – and I have full confidence after their trial by fire over the last 20 months that Chair Powell and Dr. Brainard will provide the strong leadership our country needs,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Political pressure, and a Covid struggle
President Donald Trump appointed Powell to the position in 2018 in somewhat of a surprise. Trump chose to pass over then-Chair Janet Yellen, an unusual move in that Fed leaders are rarely removed after just one term. Former President Barack Obama initially appointed Powell to a 14-year term as governor in 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Trump nominated Powell, he later fired withering criticism at the Fed chief when the central bank raised interest rates seven times in 2017 and 2018. The former president went as far as to call the Fed policymakers “boneheads” for trying to normalize policy as the economy recovered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for Brainard, she is now widely expected to be named vice chair of supervision, a key Fed post to oversee the nation’s banking system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fed is empowered by Congress to fulfill two mandates: Maximize U.S. employment and keep inflation stable. Its leaders, known as governors, are nominated by the president and vote on how to adjust interest rates, regulate the nation’s largest banks and monitor the health of the economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To combat the spike in unemployment and recession that began in the spring of 2020, the central bank slashed interest rates and began buying some $120 billion in Treasury bonds and mortgage-backed securities every month. It also instituted a variety of lending programs aimed at keeping fixed income markets functioning after they endured significant stress at the beginning of the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Economists credit that quick and sizable response for stabilizing financial markets and later repressing long-term interest rates. Lower interest rates make it easier for corporations to take on loans to build new factories, or for individuals to buy homes or cars. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Under Powell the Fed has placed more emphasis on having the economy operate at maximum employment,” Mike Feroli, chief U.S. economist at JPMorgan, said via email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This is a goal progressive economists have long advocated and a goal which is presumably consistent with Biden’s agenda.”  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen, one of Biden’s top economic advisors and a counselor on his Fed nominations, told CNBC earlier this month that she is happy with the Fed chief’s work. Yellen was the first woman to serve as the Fed’s chair and is the country’s first female Treasury secretary. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I talked to him about candidates and advised him to pick somebody who is experienced and credible,” Yellen said. “I think that Chair Powell has certainly done a good job.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Powell is also popular on Capitol Hill, where lawmakers on both sides of the aisle have praised his leadership and amiability since he took over for Yellen in February 2018. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The news is likely a disappointment to progressives including Sen. Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., who said in September that the Fed’s role in relaxing banking regulations in recent years makes Powell a “dangerous man” and that she would oppose his renomination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["我是一個真正的Boglehead，但現在是時候提醒我了......爲什麼房地產不是更好？" [BH主題]]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qzccrf/im_a_true_boglehead_but_its_time_for_me_to_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qzccrf/im_a_true_boglehead_but_its_time_for_me_to_be/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 14:55:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[規則1："在你賣出之前，它不是一個損失"。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qziter/rule_1_its_not_a_loss_until_you_sell/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qziter/rule_1_its_not_a_loss_until_you_sell/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 14:12:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[新文章。

7張圖的星期天...

https://t.co/uZLzNqvOAy https://t.co/QJJsFAgJgh]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462770976890970115</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462770976890970115</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 13:39:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[試圖成爲一個有道德的投資者，就像從麥當勞點一份沙拉一樣]]></title><description><![CDATA[就是說，我可以尊重他們的努力，但最終毫無意義
而且有點傻？

除非你從事私人投資和/或你在個人層面上了解的小盤股，否則你永遠不會知道你把錢放在什麼地方。
個人水平，你永遠不會知道你把你的錢投入了什麼。

即使你挑選的公司有...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qzcgdm/trying_to_be_an_ethical_investor_is_like_ordering/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qzcgdm/trying_to_be_an_ethical_investor_is_like_ordering/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 08:27:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is, something for which I can respect the effort, but ultimately pointless and a bit silly?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unless you’re into private investing and/or small cap stocks which you know on a personal level, you’ll never EVER know what you’re putting your money into.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if you pick companies that have a morally good mission (like, green energies), you’ll never know if their employees are treated fairly, if they cut corners in production, if they’re involved in corruption and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can only trust people that you know personally, and even that has its limits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think that employing morals into finance achieves pretty much nothing, and damages your overall performance as an investor.
I’d rather try to maximize returns, and then use that money to increase the better being of my community on a smaller, more trusted scale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But that’s obviously only my opinion, feel free to disagree.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這個行業真的被高估了嗎？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzag3k/is_this_industry_really_overvalued/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzag3k/is_this_industry_really_overvalued/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 06:53:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我明天就要上華爾街博彩公司的名人堂了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，我有一個計劃。我，一個有一點知識的弱智大學生
在Robinhood "投資"，並在過去幾個月裏做得很好。
只損失了1000美元! 我知道這看起來像蛋糕，但失去這麼多的
我的大學學費應該是用來買食物的，這太瘋狂了。

我適合...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzb41c/im_about_to_be_on_the_wallstreetbets_hall_of_fame/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qzb41c/im_about_to_be_on_the_wallstreetbets_hall_of_fame/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 05:00:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, I have a plan. I, a retarded college student with a little knowledge of “investing” in robinhood and have done pretty good over the last few months, losing only 1000 dollars! I know that seems like cake, but losing that much of my college money supposed to be spent for food is crazy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m suited up and have robinhood gold. I am able to deposit $10,000 in instant deposits, but have nowhere close to that money in my bank. No matter what y’all retards say, i’m going to do it tomorrow morning and see what happens. Throwing all into $LCID puts because fuck Lucid. Realistically, will this work? What will happen IF i make profits? Will they just take the amount out and i’m left with the profit? Either way, i’m going to it. I have no clue what will happen to me if i lose this money, but, i’m not thinking about losing. Only thinking about drowning in pussy and blue hundreds. I’m tired of eating out of wendys garbage can. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Short: Using my instant deposit limit on robinhood with not even 30% of the money in my bank. Remember my name.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[達雷爾-E-布魯克斯（Darrell E. Brooks），黑人男性，30多歲，是在沃克薩被拘留的嫌疑人。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462629029681455105</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462629029681455105</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 04:44:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[當我想加入時，市場如何運作]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qza5m5/how_the_markets_work_when_i_want_to_join_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qza5m5/how_the_markets_work_when_i_want_to_join_in/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 04:44:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[運費是通過屋頂的。這裏是如何發揮它們的作用。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們距離西方最大的可自由支配商品的揮霍還有近一個月的時間
而聖誕老人並沒有把它們帶入洛杉磯港。

催化劑

由於 "iNflaTIOn iz TranZuhToRY "和 "沒有人看到 "的持續言論
[https://twitter.com/TheEconomist/status/1461651190144503808] it…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qz1a61/shipping_rates_are_through_the_roof_heres_how_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qz1a61/shipping_rates_are_through_the_roof_heres_how_to/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 04:44:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are nearly one month away from the West&amp;#39;s greatest splurge on discretionary goods and Santa isn&amp;#39;t the one bringing them into the Port of LA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Catalyst&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to the constant rhetoric that &amp;#39;iNflaTIOn iz TranZuhToRY&amp;#39; and &amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/TheEconomist/status/1461651190144503808&quot;&gt;no one saw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/TheEconomist/status/1461651190144503808&quot;&gt; it coming&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; many companies that have benefited greatly from the increased prices were discounted. Nobody wanted to invest in lumber, freight, and oil because these price hikes were supposed to be temporary. As many are now admitting, inflation is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fed-may-need-to-pivot-to-faster-taper-waller-says-11637336865&quot;&gt;here to stay&lt;/a&gt; and so are the aforementioned companies&amp;#39; sick margins. The catalyst is a great repricing of undervalued companies. *Think Dr. Burry buying Gamestop at $5* We literally have boomer stocks growing revenues and margins at the rates of start-ups (more on that below*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shipping Rates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a result of the decreased labor force and QE, shipping rates have climbed close to 600% over the last year. However, recently they&amp;#39;ve plateaued and haven&amp;#39;t shown any sign of returning to baseline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/6v7dj97fdz081.png?width=2474&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=7a78e8ce52437c4b66dd9c349bebfd1fa66c019f&quot;&gt;From $ZIM &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, these rates are mostly just for freight from the East to the West. Prices are incredibly low if you&amp;#39;d like to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.moneycontrol.com/news/business/explained-why-the-shipping-container-crisis-will-not-end-soon-7743451.html&quot;&gt;ship the other way&lt;/a&gt;, &amp;quot;Shanghai-Los Angeles route was over $10,000 but under $1,300 in the reverse direction in the recent weeks&amp;quot;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Demand&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consumer spending continues to hit &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.bea.gov/iTable/iTable.cfm?ReqID=19&amp;amp;step=2#reqid=19&amp;amp;step=2&amp;amp;isuri=1&amp;amp;1921=underlying&quot;&gt;all-time highs&lt;/a&gt; and the Port of LA is&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/cargo-ships-queues-pushed-150-miles-from-southern-california-coast-2021-11&quot;&gt; jakkt to the tits in congestion&lt;/a&gt; with over 100 ships queued in a conga line 100 miles south. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/q9hfrdebiz081.png?width=2636&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=844822e0824142df9b8d61f9c22a8f8f55e5a3b2&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/q9hfrdebiz081.png?width=2636&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=844822e0824142df9b8d61f9c22a8f8f55e5a3b2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/p7qqvzd7iz081.jpg?width=1300&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=0b2707167e384e315aa1cd403099073ac1dffc21&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/p7qqvzd7iz081.jpg?width=1300&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=0b2707167e384e315aa1cd403099073ac1dffc21&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;The Play&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any shipping company seems mispriced, however, I see the greatest opportunity I see is with $ZIM. &lt;a href=&quot;https://s27.q4cdn.com/416879924/files/doc_financials/2021/q3/ZIM-Q3-2021-investors-call-Final-17-11-2021.pdf&quot;&gt;Here&amp;#39;s&lt;/a&gt; the link to their latest earnings. *spoiler: they absolutely crushed it*. I have literally looked at the top 12 largest, publicly-traded shipping companies and this one seems to have the greatest mismatch on price:value. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Margins&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$ZIM has one of (if not, the) highest margins of any shipping company in the industry with a 66% EBITDA margin (that&amp;#39;s double $APPL). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rate of growth&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether it has been their shipping fleet acquisitions, the freight prices, or efficient logistics $ZIM has 18X&amp;#39;d their profit YoY. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/tri9nglhkz081.png?width=2508&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=35275a8fb7642c2953228db9bf8b7be2c00d4c6b&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/tri9nglhkz081.png?width=2508&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=35275a8fb7642c2953228db9bf8b7be2c00d4c6b&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stock Performance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$ZIM went public in January this year and has averaged a 100% return every quarter. For a &lt;strong&gt;REAL&lt;/strong&gt; company, this is unparalleled. They literally just go up and to the right. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ptd3omdjlz081.png?width=2522&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=81cc178b902e40d8a4002aff7948ff657e4d5166&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/ptd3omdjlz081.png?width=2522&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=81cc178b902e40d8a4002aff7948ff657e4d5166&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price Mismatch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After looking at the top 12 highest market cap shipping companies, $ZIM seems to be the most mispriced. The average PE of the shipping industry is  ~6.9X (nice). While $ZIM trades @ 3.3X. Even if $ZIM were to normalize at the industry&amp;#39;s average, that&amp;#39;s over a 100% return. If you look at revenue, $ZIM brings in roughly 20% of Maersk&amp;#39;s $AMKBY (the largest shipping company by MC) revenue while trading at ~10% of the valuation.  If you were to normalize $ZIM (66% margin) with $AMKBY (41% margin) based upon net profit, you&amp;#39;d expect a 130% return from the current price of $57. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/6wve2xa8tz081.png?width=1520&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=2e2984facc1c048ebec1529ea691d516ad1161cb&quot;&gt;Comparison across some shipping companies.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Next Run&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After $ZIM completely destroyed their Q3 earnings ($12.16 vs $8.99 EPS) and announced a market-leading dividend (20% of quarter&amp;#39;s net income with a 4th quarter dividend equal to 30-50% of annual net income), and heavy volume has started coming in over the last few days. People are starting to notice. If we assume a similar profit for Q4, their &amp;#39;21 annual profit is ~$4.5B. We know that based on shares outstanding divided by net income with a 20% dividend is $2.50. This means that their 4th quarter dividend (assumed at the midpoint of 40%) will be $15. At a current share price of $57, you&amp;#39;d basically get &lt;strong&gt;a 26% return just from a single dividend.&lt;/strong&gt;  If you don&amp;#39;t think boomers and pensions that love dividends aren&amp;#39;t going to jump into this stock then go YOLO into some weed stocks (RIP. Long $ROPE). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to Play&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$ZIM&amp;#39;s ex-dividend date is Dec 15th so, if you&amp;#39;d like the dividend (like me) you&amp;#39;d have to get in before that date. If you think the stock will massively skyrocket from dividend investors, here&amp;#39;s the options chain. You&amp;#39;ll notice the most volume taking place at the $60 strike calls. These calls also have the greatest #gamma and could offer a great return with a breakeven price of $62.60. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/187r26jnqz081.png?width=2574&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=a3f502b943a2717b68a7a813f87e02fb99a2d554&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/187r26jnqz081.png?width=2574&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=a3f502b943a2717b68a7a813f87e02fb99a2d554&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Positions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;100 shares @ $57.50&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*This is literally my uneducated, unlicensed opinion. Don&amp;#39;t listen to me. You&amp;#39;ll Lose money\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[百分之百做股票的投機者有多少經驗或信心？]]></title><description><![CDATA[12年的股票牛市運行，人爲地擡高了許多人的風險承受能力。
對風險承受能力的評價，更惡劣的是，它誇大並錯誤地提高了許多人對自己投資的信念。
錯誤地提高了許多人對自己投資 "技能 "的信念。

這裏的許多投資者在我們上次經歷的時候還僅僅是在小學...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qz1w1g/how_experienced_or_confident_are_speculators_who/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qz1w1g/how_experienced_or_confident_are_speculators_who/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 04:14:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twelve years of an equities bull run have artificially inflated many a person&amp;#39;s appraisal for risk tolerance, and even more perniciously, has inflated and wrongly boosted many a man&amp;#39;s belief in this own investing &amp;quot;skill.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many investors here were in mere grade school the last time we experienced any significant market downturn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[r/wallstreetbets中的生活決定]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qz9xgu/life_decisions_in_rwallstreetbets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qz9xgu/life_decisions_in_rwallstreetbets/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 04:14:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[傑羅姆-鮑威爾明天]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qz76xr/jerome_powell_tomorrow/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qz76xr/jerome_powell_tomorrow/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 03:39:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[誰在加載支付寶？]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好，我最近買了一些支付寶，因爲它在過去幾天裏下跌了
100股，總成本基礎爲198。現在我打算賣出一些
來降低我的成本基礎。

還有人看好支付寶嗎？整個行業似乎都在崩潰
桶]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz8wyi/who_is_loading_up_on_paypal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz8wyi/who_is_loading_up_on_paypal/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 03:39:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey Everyone,
I recently bought some paypal as it dropped over the last few days with 100 shares at a total cost basis of 198. Now i a plan on selling some covered calls to lower my cost basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is anyone else bullish on paypal? 
the whole sector seems to be crapping the bucket&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[20個國家的亞馬遜員工將在黑色星期五罷工以爭取更好的工作條件]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 20個國家的亞馬遜員工正準備在黑色星期五進行罷工，作爲
> "讓亞馬遜付錢 "運動的一部分。 
> 
> 該運動包括一個由70個組織組成的聯盟，其中包括綠色和平組織。
> 樂施會，和亞馬遜工人國際。
> 
> 抗議活動是在越來越多的人反對的情況下進行的。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzakmc/amazon_employees_in_20_countries_will_strike_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qzakmc/amazon_employees_in_20_countries_will_strike_on/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 03:22:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon employees in 20 countries are preparing to strike on Black Friday as part of the &amp;quot;Make Amazon Pay&amp;quot; campaign.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The campaign includes a coalition of 70 organizations, including Greenpeace, Oxfam, and Amazon Workers International.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The protests come amid mounting dissent from Amazon employees over working condition and union busting. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This seems like a one more strike that is going to have no effect on working conditions, stock or anything really. Share what you think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[⚠️🇺🇸#Update: Suspects now described as either Black OR Arab.

- 兩名嫌疑人仍然在逃
- 警方建議Waukesha的居民鎖好所有門窗
- CBS新聞現在報道有 "多個死亡 "https://t.co/vHAcNFrYEK]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462607860878254082</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462607860878254082</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 02:41:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[20個國家的亞馬遜員工將在黑色星期五罷工以爭取更好的工作條件]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 20個國家的亞馬遜員工正準備在黑色星期五進行罷工，作爲
> "讓亞馬遜付錢 "運動的一部分。 
> 
> 該運動包括一個由70個組織組成的聯盟，包括綠色和平組織。
> 樂施會，和亞馬遜工人國際。
> 
> 抗議活動是在越來越多的人反對的情況下進行的。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qza112/amazon_employees_in_20_countries_will_strike_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qza112/amazon_employees_in_20_countries_will_strike_on/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 02:41:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon employees in 20 countries are preparing to strike on Black Friday as part of the &amp;quot;Make Amazon Pay&amp;quot; campaign.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The campaign includes a coalition of 70 organizations, including Greenpeace, Oxfam, and Amazon Workers International.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The protests come amid mounting dissent from Amazon employees over working condition and union busting. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This seems like a one more strike that is going to have no effect on working conditions, stock or anything really. Share what you think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對沖基金目前擁有的前10只股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[對沖基金目前正在擊敗大盤，他們的綜合購買力
的力量可以輕易地推動股票上漲。花旗銀行剛剛發佈了一份名單，列出了截至年底最大的50家對沖基金持有的前10只
截至第三季度末，最大的50家對沖基金持有的10只股票。我不能說這個名單
名單是令人驚訝的，但它是有趣的，可以看到。



股票名稱...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz1jhq/the_top_10_stocks_owned_by_hedge_funds_right_now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz1jhq/the_top_10_stocks_owned_by_hedge_funds_right_now/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 02:41:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hedge funds are beating the broader market right now and their combined buying power can easily drive stocks higher. Citi just put out a list of the top 10 stocks held by the biggest 50 hedge funds as of the end of Q3. I can&amp;#39;t say the list is surprising, but it is interesting to see. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Ticker&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Name&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Number of funds holding as top 10 position in size&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;MSFT&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Microsoft&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;26&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;GOOGL&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;17&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;AMZN&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;17&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;FB&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;AAPL&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Apple&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;NFLX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Netflix&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;CRM&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Salesforce&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;BKNG&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Booking Holdings&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;DASH&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Doordash&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;MA&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Mastercard&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s noteworthy that just because hedge funds own these stock, that doesn&amp;#39;t mean they are completely bullish on them in the near term. It&amp;#39;s very possible they are running shorts in the various forms (covered calls, puts, etc) against their own holdings to hedge themselves. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The only thing that stuck out to me here is BKNG&lt;/strong&gt;, which seems  overvalued, given it is trading at a price that is well above pre-pandemic levels and a P/E for this year over 55. Earnings are projected to grow at 130% next year.  That means the company would have about $100 per share in earnings. BKNG has traded very richly for some time, so applying a healthy 25X multiple on earnings, that would project a stock price of $2500 next year. In this market, a p/e of 25 looks pretty low, especially if the company continues to grow revenues quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sales for Q3 came in just under $4.7B&lt;/strong&gt;, which puts it on pace to exceed 2019 revenues of $15B in 2022 IF the trajectory continues. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BKNG sold off big after its last earnings report, despite the fact they delivered a healthy beat of expectations. The drop is presumably because expectations had grown too high in advance of earnings, on concerns that COVID would impact travel, and on profit taking.  It&amp;#39;s now down over 300 points from its high. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s interesting to see the trend reversal that just occurred in the travel sector. AirBnB, BKNG, and Expedia, were all up double digits from mid-August and in the past 10 days, all 3 are down. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Attractive entry point for BKNG?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It could be, but I&amp;#39;m betting the stock will retreat further as COVID cases rise due to holiday travels.  I&amp;#39;ll be looking to buy the stock if it dips back to 2,100 again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我的投資組合應該至少與標準普爾500指數一樣好嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，夥計們，我最近找到了一份工作，今年我成功地在ROTH IRA中獲得了6000美元，並開始了401k。
ROTH IRA並開始了401k。標準普爾500指數自9月以來上漲了20%（當我開始
我的倉位）。但我的回報卻少得多。我是否應該只投資於
標準普爾500指數？對不起，我是投資新手]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz5thz/should_my_portfolio_be_at_least_as_good_as_sp_500/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz5thz/should_my_portfolio_be_at_least_as_good_as_sp_500/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 02:07:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey guys, I recently got a job and this year I managed to both get 6000 in a ROTH IRA and start a 401k. The S&amp;amp;P 500 is up 20% since September (when I started my positions). But my returns are much less. Should I just be investing in the S&amp;amp;P 500? Sorry i am noob investor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在Waukesha假日遊行中，一輛汽車剛剛衝破警戒線，衝過行人，向窗外發射子彈。我和家人都很安全。事件發生在我們前面20英尺處。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462560182857310208</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462560182857310208</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 23:43:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如何以較小的風險獲得3倍於標準普爾指數的年複合增長率 | 長期的槓桿作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2741701

對於那些想知道現在到底該怎麼辦的人，我向你們介紹一個新的
無名英雄Michael Gayed。邁克爾找到了一種方法，可以系統性地超越
在承擔較少風險的情況下，系統地超越標準普爾500指數3倍以上，這是一個極其重要的方法。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qz07zp/how_to_3x_the_sp_cagr_with_less_risk_leverage_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qz07zp/how_to_3x_the_sp_cagr_with_less_risk_leverage_for/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 23:43:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2741701&quot;&gt;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2741701&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of your wondering what the hell to do now, I introduce you to a new unsung hero Michael Gayed. Michael has found a way to systemically outperform the S&amp;amp;P 500 by over 3x while taking on less risk and it&amp;#39;s an extremely simple investment strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone says that triple leveraged ETFs have volatility decay and are not meant for long-term holding. Well guess what, those people are idiots. Let&amp;#39;s look at the data: If you invested in UPRO using this guy&amp;#39;s simple strategy, backtested all the way back to 1928, you would have returned 27% CAGR while the S&amp;amp;P did 9% and by taking on half as much risk (0.6 Sharpe ratio for this strategy vs. 0.3 for buy &amp;amp; hold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rules are simple, if the underlying index closes below the 200 day moving average, you sell. Once it crosses back above the 200 MA, then reenter. That is it. &lt;strong&gt;Investing $10k in 1928 with this strategy would have returned $28 TRILLION (with a T) while the S&amp;amp;P would have returned $39 million.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason this works is because of the lack of volatility above the 200 MA, and higher volatility below the 200 MA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the sweet taste of compounding returns my friends because this is a ticket to an early retirement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR: Read the damn paper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼我現在要投資，因爲崩潰可能會到來......]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qz63mh/why_should_i_invest_now_when_a_crash_might_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qz63mh/why_should_i_invest_now_when_a_crash_might_be/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 23:43:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[新文章。

7張圖的星期天...

https://t.co/uZLzNqvOAy https://t.co/QJJsFAgJgh]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462535662641590287</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462535662641590287</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 22:38:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[無名氏的問題。爲什麼是國際？]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以我們的投資冒險剛剛開始。我們已經見了幾個
顧問和Vanguard PAS。每個人和維基都說你應該把一些
國際股票VTIAX的3/4基金組合。PAS建議高達
在75/25的股票債券組合中，30%的國際股票。我們有一個AUM的人說...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyyhnt/noob_question_why_international/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyyhnt/noob_question_why_international/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 22:22:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So we&amp;#39;re just starting out on our investing adventure. We&amp;#39;ve met with a couple advisors and Vanguard PAS. Everyone and the wiki says you should some international stock VTIAX in a 3/4 fund portfolio. PAS recommended as high as 30% international in a 75/25 stock bond portfolio. We had a AUM guy say 8% international. Just trying to wrap my mind around this. I have no business running backtests, but when I do = portfolios with higher % international don&amp;#39;t perform as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[將價值5萬美元的指數交易到英偉達？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道，KNOW NVIDIA是改變未來的脊髓。I
我認爲在10年內，它的價值至少在1000-1500美元/股。我真的
我真的相信它，而且作爲一名計算機工程師，我很瞭解它。

我已經知道omniverse的公告有一段時間了，所以買了227股...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0x1l/trade_50k_worth_index_into_nvidia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0x1l/trade_50k_worth_index_into_nvidia/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 22:22:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know, KNOW NVIDIA is the spinal cord that&amp;#39;s going to be changing the future. I think in 10 years it&amp;#39;ll be worth at least $1000-$1500 per share. I really believe in it, and being a computer engineer I understand it well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve known about the omniverse announcement for awhile, so bought 227 shares at $220 ($49,940) two months ago. But &lt;a href=&quot;/r/bogleheads&quot;&gt;/r/bogleheads&lt;/a&gt; convinced me it was gambling so I took it out and I&amp;#39;m pissed I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, in order to get that $50k I&amp;#39;d be having to sell 50k worth of VTSAX, meaning forfeiting early capital gains. I&amp;#39;ve only been investing for like 2 years, so it&amp;#39;s not that much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or.... should I just leave the VTSAX alone, invest $500 per week in that, then another $500 per week in QQQ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMD的未來？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在AMD有一個小倉位。50股。我已經在上面賺了一點錢。
但我想知道該公司的未來到底會怎樣？我知道
他們即將與xilinx合併，並與Meta公司合作，但是否有更多的增長？
但該股是否有可能有更多的增長？我不能完全看到...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0sab/the_future_of_amd/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0sab/the_future_of_amd/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 21:44:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have a small position in AMD. 50 Shares. I&amp;#39;ve made a little bit of money on them but I&amp;#39;m wondering what exactly the future holds for the company? I know they have an upcoming merger with xilinx and they&amp;#39;ve partnered with Meta, but is more growth for the stock possible? I can&amp;#39;t exactly see Semiconductors going anywhere, so I feel like the sky&amp;#39;s the limit. What are everyone&amp;#39;s thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你什麼時候知道自己是股票投資者或股票交易員？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直在網上閱讀一堆關於我目前感興趣的不同公司的隨機帖子。
我意識到，我很高興我是一個投資者，而且我永遠都是。
永遠都是。

我不明白人們怎麼能以交易員的心態存在。這似乎是
你需要學習大量的準科學，在...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyw688/when_did_you_know_you_were_stock_investor_or_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyw688/when_did_you_know_you_were_stock_investor_or_a/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 21:44:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been reading a bunch of random posts online about different companies I&amp;#39;m currently interested in, and I realize I&amp;#39;m happy that I&amp;#39;m an investor and I always will be. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t understand how people can exist with a trader mindset. It&amp;#39;s seems like you need to study alot of quasi science, be on social media constantly, do alot of cocaine, and it really just seems stressful. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The neat thing about reddit is I can look and see when people post their &amp;quot;analysis&amp;quot; of a stock. Which for 99% of reddit, is just a trader saying voodoo witch craft nonsense about enter and exit points, resistance this and that, cutting losses, and special orders. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then you ask for their portfolio and they have none or its top secret or something. It&amp;#39;s not illegal to share your portfolio you great traders. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m an average Joe, and I&amp;#39;m not that smart. so I feel really good when I read posts from people who buy a stock like MU, three years ago, at 40-43 a share, and sell it saying they see no future in it. It&amp;#39;s trading at like $83 now. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love it when I read people saying they bought Uber near ipo at 40 and sold at 32 and say it&amp;#39;s doomed to fail. But Uber is still around, in fact it hit a height of $60 last spring and now it&amp;#39;s $44. You haven&amp;#39;t even given it a chance to grow or become something yet. Like the company is a verb, give it a few years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think traders are like fake friends in high school. They&amp;#39;re only around you if you&amp;#39;re cool. Once you&amp;#39;re not cool anymore they abandon you. But traders are onlu a small portion of money for a company a company makes stuff to sell to people and that&amp;#39;s what really draws in revenue to grow. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see alot of people talk about the &amp;quot;opportunity cost&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;oppurtuniy lost, &amp;quot; something like that when you&amp;#39;re not trading. Like if I buy something that isn&amp;#39;t moving fast, or something is in the red, it&amp;#39;s better to &amp;quot;cut my losses.&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But that&amp;#39;s like... Buying high and selling low. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That sounds like the exact opposite of what you&amp;#39;re supposed to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honestly, I&amp;#39;d rather sink with my ship if you&amp;#39;re telling me to always sell the moment my stock goes red. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;if I was so foolish as to pick a bad company, I&amp;#39;d rather just take the full loss, rather then death by a thousand cuts. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I pick companies that make more revenue every year, have increasing dividends, and are medium to large size growth companies. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m boring. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just look at the best performing companies, read their 10k and just invest. My first two companies I bought were Apple and Starbucks, I then bought Nvidia and Realty Income. I bought Pennymac and Weyerhaeuser afterward. I just sorta sit on them. I just hold them and buy more. If I somehow become broke instantly from these decisions then damn. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m investing in known companies with easy business models. I like safety and simplicity. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t believe I&amp;#39;m gonna become a multi millionaire with several cars and boats. I just want to make enough money to be the first millionaire in my family, and have my children live of my dividends so they don&amp;#39;t have to work so hard. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It just seems like people don&amp;#39;t have patience on the internet. And when you take the time to read people who argue about a particular stock, and then for those same people to be proven wrong by time. It feels good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[是否有充分的理由從富達或施瓦布轉到Vanguard？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道他們本質上可以做同樣的事情，但我喜歡Vanguard的整個精神。
但我喜歡Vanguard的整個精神，並經常想，我是否應該轉換。這只是一種偏好
還是使用Vanguard有明顯的優勢？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyy6h0/is_there_a_strong_reason_to_switch_to_vanguard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyy6h0/is_there_a_strong_reason_to_switch_to_vanguard/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 21:16:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know they essentially can do the same things, but I like the whole ethos of Vanguard and have often wondered if I should switch. Is it just a preference thing or are there clear advantages from using Vanguard?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是否應該開設羅斯退休基金？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我有一個401k，我把工資的20%放在一個星期內。我每月把大約500美元左右的資金存入
每月在應稅賬戶中存入約500美元。目前我的應稅賬戶佔我總儲蓄的23%。
退休。

我是否也應該開一個羅斯賬戶？它們聽起來非常有吸引力，有幾個原因。

我把應稅賬戶作爲一個安全網...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyu75h/should_i_open_a_roth_ira/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyu75h/should_i_open_a_roth_ira/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 20:42:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have a 401k that I&amp;#39;m putting 20% of pay in a week. I put about $500 or so a month in a taxable account. Currently my taxable is 23% of my total savings for retirement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should I open a Roth as well? They sound very attractive for several reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was using a taxable account as a safety net should I need to access some of the money. Also I was hoping to retire at 55 and use this account to bridge me over to my 401k.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But from my understanding I could open a Roth and take some or all of the principle out at anytime without penalty.  Also this money grows tax free and can be withdrawn tax free at 59.5. So essentially I could start taking the principle out early if I want to retire early.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe its best to have a combination of all 3 401k, Roth, Taxable?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有了納斯達克，爲什麼還要買SP500？]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好，我在市場上投資已經3-4年了。我只是DCA
像你們中的大多數人一樣。我知道的不多。

起初，我買了WORLD追蹤器，然後我意識到大部分的%來自於
美國（我住在歐洲），所以我換成了標準普爾500，現在我意識到大部分的
％來自...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyv4a9/why_sp500_when_there_is_nasdaq/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyv4a9/why_sp500_when_there_is_nasdaq/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 20:27:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello there, it has been 3-4 years since I&amp;#39;m investing in the market. I just DCA like most of you. I don&amp;#39;t know much tbh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At first, I bought WORLD Tracker, then I realized most of the % comes from the US (I live in Europe btw), so I switched to S&amp;amp;P500 and now I realize most of the % comes from NASDAQ100. (Yeah I&amp;#39;m not a quick learner).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, why wouldn&amp;#39;t I want to put everything in NASDAQ100? I know the drawdown is higher but the profit is as well. And inflation is just starting imo...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[關於俄羅斯準備在1月下旬攻擊烏克蘭的消息。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這裏的新聞文章
https://www.militarytimes.com/flashpoints/2021/11/20/russia-preparing-to-attack-ukraine-by-late-january-ukraine-defense-intelligence-agency-chief/

我想知道這是否值得關注？ 通常情況下，這些事情不會影響到美國的經濟。
美國股市，因爲它通常是由兩個小的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0kx4/news_about_russia_preparing_to_attack_ukraine_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0kx4/news_about_russia_preparing_to_attack_ukraine_in/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 20:27:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;news article here &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.militarytimes.com/flashpoints/2021/11/20/russia-preparing-to-attack-ukraine-by-late-january-ukraine-defense-intelligence-agency-chief/&quot;&gt;https://www.militarytimes.com/flashpoints/2021/11/20/russia-preparing-to-attack-ukraine-by-late-january-ukraine-defense-intelligence-agency-chief/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was wondering is this of any concern? normally these thinsg wouldnt affect the US stock market because it usually from 2 small countries. but this seems like a different situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vanguard在等待時間，我在1:17放棄了]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyw6vc/vanguard_on_hold_times_i_gave_up_at_117/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyw6vc/vanguard_on_hold_times_i_gave_up_at_117/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 17:53:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我們的人民https://t.co/UUuzClMemw]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461790163177295884</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461790163177295884</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 17:41:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在2月份的歷史高點購買了所有這些股票，在市場創下歷史高點時，它們仍然全部下跌。現在削減損失嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道，在市場上的時間比在市場上的時間更重要，這就是爲什麼我在所有時間的高點買入。
在所有時間的高點買入。但當納斯達克和標準普爾指數每隔一天都在上漲時
但當納斯達克指數和標準普爾指數每隔一天都在上漲時，要想在這些股票持續交易時平均下來是很困難的。
橫盤/下跌。一個人如何克服不想要的心態呢？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyx5s1/purchased_all_these_stocks_in_feb_at_all_time/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyx5s1/purchased_all_these_stocks_in_feb_at_all_time/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 17:22:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know the saying time in the market beats timing the market, which is why I bought during all time highs. But when the nasdaq and s&amp;amp;p keep going up every other day it’s tough to want to average down when these stocks keep trading sideways/ down. How does one get over the mindset of not wanting to sell for a loss?
Arkf -16%
Arkg -37%
Arkw -17%
Moon -32%
Expi -40%
Prnt -24%&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這就是你的投資方式。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyth8s/this_is_how_you_invest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyth8s/this_is_how_you_invest/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 15:40:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[第一次上萬科的網站....，真的這麼簡單嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[有人可以只開一個賬戶，購買VTI，每年拿到稅單，就可以了。
就這樣簡單了？

幾乎看起來太容易了？

挑選賬戶容易嗎？Roth/經紀公司等？我一直在想，這裏面一定有
一些棘手的地方]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyuykq/first_time_on_the_vanguard_siteis_it_really_this/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyuykq/first_time_on_the_vanguard_siteis_it_really_this/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 15:21:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Someone can just make an account, buy VTI and get the tax paper each year and that’s it in a nutshell? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost seems too easy? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is picking the account easy? Roth/brokerage etc? I keep thinking there has to be something tricky somewhere&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[將你的時間和精力過度分配給投資組合優化是次優的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不知道這種情況有多普遍，但這是我意識到的一個戰略錯誤。
我認爲這可能值得思考。

對投資組合進行研究和回溯測試等等是很有趣的，我知道。
我知道，我當然同意，花時間設計投資組合是很重要的。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyry5y/overallocating_your_time_and_effort_to_portfolio/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyry5y/overallocating_your_time_and_effort_to_portfolio/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 13:03:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not sure how common this is, but this is a strategic mistake I realized I&amp;#39;m making and I think that it might be worth thinking about. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Geeking out about portfolios and studying and backtesting and so on is fun, I know, and I certainly agree that it is important to take the time to design a portfolio that is compatible with one&amp;#39;s objectives and risk tolerance; but, as with many other things, extra effort has diminishing returns and there soon comes a time when your time (heh) and work would be better spent elsewhere. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Case in point: lately I have been obsessing about whether to increase my bond allocation by 5% now or 2/3 years from now as per my initial plan (this has nothing to do with the market being &amp;quot;high&amp;quot;, I&amp;#39;m just concerned that I might be overestimating a little my risk tolerance), and I spent way more time thinking about this than putting extra work towards a certification that could increase my wages by about &lt;strong&gt;10%&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I... don&amp;#39;t think I have to spell out why this is not the best use of my time and effort. So yeah, it might be worth it to keep in mind that it is suboptimal to overallocate one&amp;#39;s resources towards portfolio optimization. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now if I know myself, the danger is that I&amp;#39;ll spend the next four months designing and refining the perfect allocation of my time and mental efforts towards my various work and life objectives rather than doing what I am supposed to do... :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[週末，當我不持有看漲期權時，特斯拉與我持有看漲期權時，特斯拉。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qykw6v/tesla_over_the_weekend_when_i_dont_own_calls_vs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qykw6v/tesla_over_the_weekend_when_i_dont_own_calls_vs/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 13:03:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我在WSB上的第一個帖子--我應該持有還是賣出？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyedi1/my_first_post_on_wsb_should_i_hold_or_sell/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyedi1/my_first_post_on_wsb_should_i_hold_or_sell/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 12:36:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ZIM看起來還好嗎？17%的股息？]]></title><description><![CDATA[該死的，我在45點賣掉了我在ZIM的小倉位，現在又回到了57點！我還注意到他們現在有17%的股息。

我還注意到他們現在有17%的股息。這有聽起來那麼好嗎？

不管怎樣，我想週一在ZIM上投1500美元。新的目標價格是80美元
我想航運終於開始有點緩解了？

任何關於...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qykjyh/is_zim_looking_ok_17_dividend/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qykjyh/is_zim_looking_ok_17_dividend/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 11:33:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Darn I sold my small position in ZIM at 45 and now it&amp;#39;s back to 57!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also noticed they have a 17% dividend now.  Is that as good as it sounds?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways I&amp;#39;m thinking of throwing $1500 in ZIM Monday.  New price target is $80 and I guess shipping is finally starting to ease a bit?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any info on shipping? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is ZIM a good move now?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Empower對我的401k轉帳徵稅？]]></title><description><![CDATA[幫助! 我正在向IRA和Roth IRA轉帳（從401k和Roth 401k）。
我在電話中與Empower公司的代表進行了非常徹底的溝通。
我在電話中與Empower公司的代表進行了非常徹底的溝通（將其保留在IRA中，並轉爲他們的IRA經紀賬戶
產品），並將所有的東西都以實物形式滾動起來。應該不會有什麼問題。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyb85h/empower_taxed_my_401k_rollover/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyb85h/empower_taxed_my_401k_rollover/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 10:59:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Help! I’m in the middle of a rollover to an IRA and Roth IRA (from a 401k and Roth 401k) I went through everything pretty thoroughly on the phone with the rep from Empower (Keeping it with Empower in an IRA, to their IRA brokerage acct product) and rolling everything over in kind. There should be no taxes associated with the transaction, but it’s showing I’m paying state and fed taxes on this. It seems like Empower screwed something up here, hopefully they aren’t screwing me in the process. I’ve rolled over 401ks before and this has always been a pretty uneventful process, has anyone seen this happen?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[薩爾瓦多將創建 "比特幣城"，用計劃中的10億美元債券發行中的5億美元購買更多的比特幣]]></title><description><![CDATA[薩爾瓦多是唯一一個將比特幣作爲法定貨幣的國家，它將會
總統Nayib Bukele在週六晚上的薩爾瓦多比特幣週上說，他將在最大的加密貨幣基礎上建立一個完整的城市。
在週六晚上薩爾瓦多比特幣周的一次演講中說。

"比特幣城 "將位於豐塞卡灣沿岸，靠近一個...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyp4ry/el_salvador_to_create_bitcoin_city_use_500m_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyp4ry/el_salvador_to_create_bitcoin_city_use_500m_of/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 10:47:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;El Salvador, the only country in which bitcoin is a legal tender, is going to build an entire city based on the largest cryptocurrency, President Nayib Bukele said in a Saturday night presentation at Bitcoin Week in El Salvador.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Bitcoin City” will be located along the Gulf of Fonseca near a volcano. The government plans on locating a power plant by the volcano to provide energy for both the city and bitcoin mining, the president said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Bukele, Bitcoin City will be a full-fledged metropolis with residential and commercial areas, restaurants, an airport as well as a port and rail service. The city will be laid out in a circle (like a coin) and in the city center will be a plaza that will be host to a huge bitcoin symbol. The city will have no income, property, capital gains or payroll taxes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bukele also said El Salvador plans on issuing $1 billion US “bitcoin bond,” a tokenized financial instrument developed by Blockstream, on the Liquid Network. Of that amount, $500 million will be used to help construct needed energy and bitcoin mining infrastructure and $500 million to buy even more bitcoin. At the cryptocurrency’s recent trading price of about $59,000, that would bring the country’s treasury stash to just under 2,000 bitcoins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coindesk.com/business/2021/11/21/el-salvador-to-create-bitcoin-city-use-500m-of-planned-1b-bond-offering-to-buy-more-crypto/&quot;&gt;https://www.coindesk.com/business/2021/11/21/el-salvador-to-create-bitcoin-city-use-500m-of-planned-1b-bond-offering-to-buy-more-crypto/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[什麼是基本的退休Boglehead組合？]]></title><description><![CDATA[60/40股票/債券 - 假設20%的外國股票 - 使用VTI/VXUS/BND/BNDX

像這樣嗎？

VTI 48% VXUS 12% 32% BND 8% BNDX

就這樣嗎，並使用4%的規則？Bogglehead認可嗎？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyf4h9/what_is_the_basic_at_retirement_boglehead/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyf4h9/what_is_the_basic_at_retirement_boglehead/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 10:47:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;60/40 Stocks/Bonds - Assuming 20% Foreign - Using VTI/VXUS/BND/BNDX&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VTI 48% VXUS 12% 32% BND 8% BNDX&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s it? and use the 4% rule? Bogglehead approved?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這是我今晚的幸運餅乾。不過他們把位置拼錯了。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyl6pd/this_was_my_fortune_cookie_tonight_they/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyl6pd/this_was_my_fortune_cookie_tonight_they/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 10:11:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>