<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 16:29:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[充滿波動的市場......要冷靜，乘風破浪]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><a
href="https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/30/strategists-urge-investors-to-look-through-omicron-volatility-and-stay-the-course.html">https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/30/strategists-urge-investors-to-look-through-omicron-volatility-and-stay-the-course.html</p>
<p>我認爲...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r5kyaq/a_omicron_volatile_marketbe_cool_and_ride_the_wave/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r5kyaq/a_omicron_volatile_marketbe_cool_and_ride_the_wave/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 15:19:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/30/strategists-urge-investors-to-look-through-omicron-volatility-and-stay-the-course.html&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/30/strategists-urge-investors-to-look-through-omicron-volatility-and-stay-the-course.html&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I think I&amp;amp;#39;m staying put and riding this wave.  Gonna be bumpy, but stay focused, stay strong and hold the line gentlemen.  Some impulse decisions are good.  But be careful out here and don&amp;amp;#39;t be too impulsive.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在年底前，我是否應該虧損賣出以減稅，並在31天內買回？]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>我相信這些股票會反彈，但在下個月之前不太可能。
但在下個月之前不太可能，因爲圍繞着OMICRON的這段不確定性（我認爲這將在幾周內結束）。
我認爲幾周後就會結束）。</p> <p>因此，策略是
現在虧損賣出並獲得減稅，然後在31日回購......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r5e3ae/before_years_end_should_i_sell_at_a_loss_for_tax/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r5e3ae/before_years_end_should_i_sell_at_a_loss_for_tax/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 15:19:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I believe these stocks will rebound, but not likely before the next month given this period of uncertainty surrounding omicron (which I think will end in a few weeks).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So the strategy is to sell at a loss now and collect tax deduction and then buyback in 31 days to avoid wash sale rule. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Risk is that stocks could go up and would lose out on those gains, but the stocks in question seem more like long term hold and have been static lately. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Does this seem reasonable?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[幫助! 我找不到出售按鈕。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r5czjn/help_i_cant_find_the_sell_button/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r5czjn/help_i_cant_find_the_sell_button/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 15:19:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[DIS的流血事件是否有任何結束的跡象？]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>我仍然是投資的新手，在最近對我的投資組合進行了一些調整，並從我的投資中獲得了很大的利潤。
最近對我的投資組合進行了一些調整，並從迪斯尼獲得了一大塊利潤。
迪斯尼後，我的投資回報率在30%左右。自從重組後，我現在下降了17%。
在我看來，它似乎不會很快轉好......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4xrge/is_there_any_end_in_sight_to_dis_bleeding/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4xrge/is_there_any_end_in_sight_to_dis_bleeding/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 15:19:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m still fairly new to investing and after recently restructuring my portfolio a bit and taking a chunk of profits from Disney it’s sitting around 30% for me. Since the restructuring I’m now down 17% and it seems to me like it won’t turn around any time soon especially with the new Covid variant scaring people once again. I’ve heard the old adage of “don’t bet against the mouse” a million times at least and in the past it’s done very well for me. I guess I’m looking for a bit of reassurance as I’m fairly confident in them for the long run but damn if it’s not dragging my whole portfolio through the mud right now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[好了，經濟衰退取消了]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r5dqai/ok_recession_cancelled/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r5dqai/ok_recession_cancelled/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 15:19:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[新聞，我們今天都需要]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r5jhpl/the_news_we_all_need_for_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r5jhpl/the_news_we_all_need_for_today/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 15:19:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[[長帖DD]爲什麼我長期購買/持有100%的TQQQ？]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>因此，首先讓我把我的投資背景說出來。
背景的方式。我今年21歲，相對較新。我大約在今年4月開始
但我已經關注股市有一段時間了，從我17歲起就開始關注。
17歲，但由於我沒有穩定的收入來源，所以我...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r57m25/long_post_dd_why_im_buyholding_100_tqqq_for_long/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r57m25/long_post_dd_why_im_buyholding_100_tqqq_for_long/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 15:19:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, first things first let me get my investing background out of the way. I am 21, and relatively new. I started around April of this year, but I&amp;amp;#39;ve been eyeing the stock market for a while, since I was 17, but since I didn&amp;amp;#39;t have a stable income stream, I couldn&amp;amp;#39;t invest until recently. I heard about meme stocks but as I knew I wanted to be an index investor. First I bought VOO then moved to VTI. I was a boglehead at heart and still am, more or less.  Also, when I say things such as &amp;amp;quot;This cannot happen&amp;amp;quot;, it really means &amp;amp;quot;In my opinion, this cannot happen.&amp;amp;quot; I figured it&amp;amp;#39;d be obvious from now on that this is mostly just my opinion. I&amp;amp;#39;m not saying I&amp;amp;#39;m 100% right, but I figured since it&amp;amp;#39;d be annoying to constantly repeat, &amp;amp;quot;this is my opinion&amp;amp;quot;, I&amp;amp;#39;d mention this nonetheless. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Since this is a Long post, if you&amp;amp;#39;d like, just see if you find your argument in bold, as I tried to go over the main counter-arguments for them.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I, like many others, have discovered LETFs, but people scare people away from truly investing in them while spouting the same repeated things, ad nauseum. I also have seen a lot of TQQQ posts recently, which.... lowkey brings up alarm bells. If history truly does repeat itself, people used the hell out of leverage and LETFs during the dot-com bubble and the 2008 crash.. With all the talk of the market being in a bubble (And for the record, when i mention &amp;amp;quot;the market&amp;amp;quot;, I strictly mean the S&amp;amp;amp;P 500, or VOO/SPY), then then yikes..? But nonetheless I haven&amp;amp;#39;t quite seen anything thoroughly in depth, which is what I strive to do with this post. So, if I succeeded, let me know at the end. I&amp;amp;#39;m not going to cut corners, as I&amp;amp;#39;ve mentioned in the title. This will be long, so get some snacks if you&amp;amp;#39;d like.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyway, speaking of crashes, people often say stuff like:&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;What about Dot-Com crash and 2008? You&amp;amp;#39;d still be at a loss today from the dot-com crash if TQQQ existed back then!&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/1fmpmxW.png&quot;&amp;gt;True&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;... But, let&amp;amp;#39;s go over why one is not like the other: The dot-com bubble is not what TQQQ is currently. Some parts of the market, such as electric vehicle companies such as RIVN, TESLA, NKLA, meme stocks such as GME, AMC, or some penny stocks may be in a bubble, but the market as a whole is not in a bubble. It may head for a correction, but the whole reason why the Dot-Com Bubble popped was because the market was euphoric, with P/E ratios completely bonkers for the companies that are essentially garbage. Take this &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://images.thinkadvisor.com/contrib/content/uploads/sites/415/2020/12/cape.jpg&quot;&amp;gt;chart&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; showcasing how absurdly high the Shiller P/E ratio around 2001 was. It&amp;amp;#39;s *still way higher* than even now, with companies that are much more profitable, mature, and robust than ever before. Instead of random companies that have never sold anything before (Ouch, I know RIVN exists y&amp;amp;#39;all.. I already said it&amp;amp;#39;s a bubble stock. But the market as a whole...? Not at all), you have companies like Apple, Amazon, FB/Meta, Microsoft, etc. I mean, I could go on and on about the amazing companies that are currently in the S&amp;amp;amp;P 500. While yes, people thought the same about things like Blockbuster, Nokia, Enron, these companies are at completely different stages in terms of profitability, maturity, and/or diversity in assets entirely.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;While, sure, anything can happen to, say, Apple -or even multiple companies- if you take &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;index investing seriously, and buy/hold, you will statistically always come out on top in the long run.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
This is simply due to the fact that index investing in the broad market is diversified, and has great companies. It&amp;amp;#39;s so simple, yet so effective. On top of that, the risk that the majority of companies in the S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 go bankrupt like in 2001 is just so insanely small, that if that were to be the case, something *terribly, terribly wrong* is happening to America, if not the entire world due to how globalized the companies in the index are. Trust me, if your boomer stocks such as KO, JNJ, and even stuff like Microsoft and Amazon go under, it doesn&amp;amp;#39;t matter what you invested in. Everything is on fire. This is essentially the idea of investing in the index in the first place. If you are able to worry about if the market is down, you don&amp;amp;#39;t have it bad enough, and it&amp;amp;#39;s going to be alright in the long term. This, combined with everything else I said, more or less ensures that investing into something like VOO/UPRO won&amp;amp;#39;t have such a gigantic crash such as before. As cliche as it may sound, *This time truly is different*... For this anyway. Besides, due to how LETF&amp;amp;#39;s are, I would argue it&amp;amp;#39;s actually better to *DCA* instead of Lump sum, or at least continue to DCA after a huge draw-down so the draw-up roars louder and harder. There&amp;amp;#39;s a difference between DCA into an LETF just like you would with VTI and just putting all 100k of your retirement at once into a market environment with a lot of companies that never have made any profitability at all when you&amp;amp;#39;re 2 years away from retirement&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;So, Okay, what about 2008 then?&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/hXj9RnA.png&quot;&amp;gt;Well...&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; It&amp;amp;#39;s not pretty. But that&amp;amp;#39;s entirely the point of LETF&amp;amp;#39;s. They amplify, and compound gains and losses. But you&amp;amp;#39;d still have recovered through a 90% drawdown in just... in 4-5 years. If you are able to stomach it, which you *should mentally expect and prepare for* during such a thing, and continue to DCA (which this only tests a lump sum), you essentially are loading up your weapons for the next bull market. And when the bull market comes, it roars loud and clear with LETF&amp;amp;#39;s. The thing people might think with LETF&amp;amp;#39;s is that they&amp;amp;#39;re &amp;amp;quot;beginner traps&amp;amp;quot;, or that &amp;amp;quot;they seem too good to be true&amp;amp;quot;. Really, they&amp;amp;#39;re &amp;amp;quot;risky&amp;amp;quot; extremely volatile. With a lot of things in investing, risk/reward is a big thing. For example, bonds are low-risk, low-reward typically. VTI is considered low-medium risk, low-medium reward. TQQQ/UPRO is high-risk/High-reward, and managing your risk is how you can mitigate the downs, should anything like it happen again. If you&amp;amp;#39;re able to handle 90%+ drawdowns, sure, you can have 90%+ rallies. In fact, though, 2008 is one of the big reasons why QE is such a huge influence in the market. It seems like &amp;amp;quot;The Fed&amp;amp;quot; will do whatever it can to save the market. So, while 2008 probably won&amp;amp;#39;t happen again, an event similar to it (such as 2020) may happen again. But it probably won&amp;amp;#39;t be as bad, last for as long, and may recover quicker.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;But what about Volatility Decay? If the price of $100 goes up 10%, then down $10, you lost money! It&amp;amp;#39;s simple math!&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Yeah? That is just simple math. I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen this repeated so many times as an argument against LETF&amp;amp;#39;s. It&amp;amp;#39;s not really an argument as the same goes for unleveraged ETF&amp;amp;#39;s such as VTI as well. Sure, while Index XYZ would be at 99, the 3x XYZ would be at 91. But, what exactly does that look like? &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://assets.website-files.com/617960145ff34f911afe7243/617960145ff34f0fcdfe79eb_5ed6befa9e2f6d4f2c1095c7_pic-3.png&quot;&amp;gt;Well&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, it certainly looks very odd to say the least. I&amp;amp;#39;ve never had anybody bring up any real examples of decay eating away LETF&amp;amp;#39;s long term. Sure, *theoretically* if the market just goes up and down the exact same amount every single day forever then sure, but *theoretically* I can easily Mike Tyson in a fight if I just perfectly dodge every attack and never get hit. Realistically though, that will never happen. It&amp;amp;#39;s technically *possible*, but hypotheticals and theoreticals oftentimes have no place in reality. Sideways trading does happen quite a bit on a day-to-day scale, but there&amp;amp;#39;s quite a few days/months that on average in the stock market where they account for a good chunk of gains. This is why the saying, &amp;amp;quot;Time in the market beats timing the market&amp;amp;quot;, because if you do somehow get in at the perfect time, you could have missed out some really, really, REALLY great days that would have still made you go up regardless.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;What about if the market drops 34% in a day?! You lose everything&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Yes/No. Yes, theoretically/hypothetically, the math tells you you would. But realistically there are circuit breakers on basically everything. From futures, to the market, to whatever else you can think of, there are circuit breakers that stop trading so that at any point, a drawdown of such a magnitude is next to impossible at all. As far as I know, historically, such a thing has never happened. There have been some pretty nasty drawdowns, but nothing of that magnitude. Furthermore, you need to ask yourself a simple question: If we&amp;amp;#39;ve had such a crazy bull market, why haven&amp;amp;#39;t inverse LETF&amp;amp;#39;s just went tits up? Surely the math would point to them fizzling out right? I mean, take SQQQ, a 3x inverse of QQQ. But in the real world scenarios, with real world people, these LETF&amp;amp;#39;s are actively managed, which means they&amp;amp;#39;ll do whatever they can to keep it afloat. For example, SQQQ does reverse splits keep it alive. While SQQQ has basically killed all your money if you bought it and held, that&amp;amp;#39;s the same for most inverse ETF&amp;amp;#39;s. It doesn&amp;amp;#39;t have anything to do with leverage.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;So, what about a prolonged bear market such as the Great Depression??&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
So, I don&amp;amp;#39;t mean to pull the &amp;amp;quot;ThIs TiMe Is DiFFeReNT&amp;amp;quot; shlick, but truthfully, comparing 1920s america to 2020&amp;amp;#39;s america is like comparing modern cars to 1920&amp;amp;#39;s cars. Sure they both drive but they&amp;amp;#39;re entirely different beasts. Oftentimes, it&amp;amp;#39;s better to bring up averages, rather than extremes, as extremes are usually outliers. Even if they are possible, they&amp;amp;#39;re rarely ever going to happen. Again, This is why something such as 2008 is a better argument against LETF&amp;amp;#39;s than say, the dot-com bubble, but even then, 2008 eventually recovered. Combine those things, plus the willingness of The Fed to just woosh in and save the market, it&amp;amp;#39;s very unlikely such an event will happen again. One important fact to remember is that, on average:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;The average length of a Bull/Bear market is 2.7 years and 9.6 months respectively&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
This is the whole crux as to why holding something such as VTI/VOO wins long term. You simply have more up days than down days, on average. If you truly are a believer in the sentiment that bull markets will last longer and that the market will continue to be profitable, while bear markets will be significantly shorter, it&amp;amp;#39;s a no-brainer to invest in VTI/VOO, just like it is to invest in TQQQ, once you learn the risks and differences of leveraged ETF&amp;amp;#39;s compared to regular ETF&amp;amp;#39;s. This also brings me back to my next point:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;If you followed Benjamin Graham&amp;amp;#39;s book on the Intelligent Investor, &amp;amp;quot;Mr. Market&amp;amp;quot; is described as irrational and too optimistic or pessimistic.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Along with creating the fundamental investing advice, and being labelled as &amp;amp;quot;probably the most important and influential value investing book ever written&amp;amp;quot; by Warren Buffet himself, Graham describes Mr Market as an analogy for market sentiment. Use this to your advantage. On any bad news about something, the market, instead of being perfectly &amp;amp;quot;efficient&amp;amp;quot;, will be incredibly &amp;amp;quot;bipolar&amp;amp;quot;, swinging from one pendulum of extreme, either being optimistic or pessimistic. This means when the market dips, it will dip *hard*, and when it rallies, it will rally *high*. You can clearly see this currently with the current bull market. People complain that it&amp;amp;#39;s too high, or a bubble. Really, that&amp;amp;#39;s just the market sentiment. No wonder it&amp;amp;#39;s extreme. It&amp;amp;#39;s purely the collective emotion of greed compared to fear. Not &amp;amp;quot;pure raw logic and wits and math and calculations&amp;amp;quot;. The saying goes, &amp;amp;quot;be fearful when others are greedy and greedy when others are fearful&amp;amp;quot;, not &amp;amp;quot;be robotic and logical&amp;amp;quot;. Another great saying is &amp;amp;quot;The market can remain irrational longer than you can remain solvent&amp;amp;quot;. Truth is, the market is irrational. Extremely so.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With all this being said, these were most of the argument&amp;amp;#39;s I&amp;amp;#39;ve heard against LETF&amp;amp;#39;s. LETF&amp;amp;#39;s are all about risk-management. For example, when I brought up someone who is buying 100k worth of TQQQ in 2001 two years before retirement, that&amp;amp;#39;s for a reason. Due to me being 21, and somewhat little to somewhat moderate cash invested into TQQQ, &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;due to it being leveraged, even a small amount can turn into a large sum.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; For example, &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;if you invested 5k in 2010, reinvesting your little dividends you earn from TQQQ, you&amp;amp;#39;d have over 400k today.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; This is the power of leverage in great companies. with as little as 5k you can &amp;amp;quot;gamble&amp;amp;quot;, if you really think it&amp;amp;#39;s a gamble. Personally, I think a gamble is 5k in GME right now. Investing into the top companies in the nasdaq, leveraged or not, is way less of a gamble, if at all. Having a long time horizon especially helps, which for high/risk high/reward plays, is definitely an advantage. This is why I would not recommend someone who is two years from retirement to put money they need into leveraged funds. They are inherently, amplified in volatility. Entering at the wrong time, and not having enough time to DCA back in can be devastating.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;If, however, you need a hedge due to your risk tolerance, or having a large sum into TQQQ, you can use 55% TQQQ/UPRO / 45% TMF&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
This is also another thing I rarely see mentioned. It&amp;amp;#39;s more mentioned from people using TQQQ/UPRO or other LETF&amp;amp;#39;s, but people act like you just go 100% into TQQQ without a hedge and call it a day. Realistically, you can do so much with portfolios. For simplicity sake, TMF, a 3x bonds index, hedges great with TQQQ/UPRO, due to being *uncorrelated* in most timeframes. For example, when people get scared of something such as say.. I don&amp;amp;#39;t know.....? A new Covid Variant called the Omicron, they flock to save bets such as bonds. This means that as TQQQ goes down, TMF will go up. You can actually see it clear as day during last Friday, and especially other days as well. While TQQQ took a beating, TQQQ/TMF was actually up. While, sure, pure 100% TQQQ beats TQQQ/TMF, but if you can&amp;amp;#39;t handle the drawdowns or need a hedge, it&amp;amp;#39;s well, well worth it. This strategy is called &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;HedgeFundies Excellent Adventure,&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;or&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;HFEA&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; for short. I won&amp;amp;#39;t go over it much due to it being exhaustively gone over, but on the bogleheads site, there&amp;amp;#39;s a thread for it already, which you can take a look at them here, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bogleheads.org/forum/viewtopic.php?t=288192&quot;&amp;gt;Part I&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bogleheads.org/forum/viewtopic.php?t=288192&quot;&amp;gt;Part II&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; here.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyways, In short, why I&amp;amp;#39;m 100% investing in TQQQ and soon to hedge with TMF once I reach a sizable sum is simply for multiple reasons. I disagree with plenty of the arguments I&amp;amp;#39;ve heard about LETF&amp;amp;#39;s, I&amp;amp;#39;m 21, have a long time horizon, and I&amp;amp;#39;m willing to take risks such as leverage in ETF&amp;amp;#39;s to turn a small sum such as 5k, 10k, or 15k into something hopefully huge later down the line. Then once I finally hit a good amount, if I ever do, I&amp;amp;#39;ll then invest back into VTI/VOO and let the dividends compound more than I ever could DCA into. Truth be told, even I&amp;amp;#39;m terrified of holding 500k worth of TQQQ, *maybe* even with a hedge. That&amp;amp;#39;s the short of it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s also nothing stopping someone from just going 10% TQQQ as well. Even though the prospectus of every LETF says not to buy/hold as they&amp;amp;#39;re only for daily leveraged returns, nobody is stopping you from holding it and seeing what happens. Some people just want to take it farther than others, myself included.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[推特的新CEO將比@傑克更糟糕。帕拉格的時代已經來臨。$TWTR https://t.co/R41l6K7flL]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465440645703733256</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465440645703733256</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 14:50:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[6萬美元的GME YOLO，不能停止不會停止]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r56bii/60k_gme_yolo_cant_stop_wont_stop/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r56bii/60k_gme_yolo_cant_stop_wont_stop/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 06:40:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[與顧問開始時的麻煩]]></title><description><![CDATA[可能是顧問們最討厭的事情：我不知道自己在做什麼，但已經關注Boglehead幾個月了。
已經關注Bogleheads幾個月了。在過去，我一直是一個
在財務問題上完全是個白癡。最近我父親去世了，給我們留下了一筆
相當多的錢。我的妻子非常堅定地認爲她想要一個顧問和...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r5bqrk/trouble_starting_off_with_an_advisor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r5bqrk/trouble_starting_off_with_an_advisor/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 05:20:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Probably what advisors hate the most: I have no idea what I&amp;amp;#39;m doing but have been following Bogleheads for a few months now. In the past I have been a complete idiot with financial matters. Recently my dad passed away and left us a considerable sum. My wife is pretty adamant she wants an advisor and looking at my past financial mistakes I agree with her. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So I went out and researched like crazy. We met with a friend&amp;amp;#39;s trusted 1% Aum guy, a Vanguard PAS guy and an advice-only guy. I liked the AUM guy and his advice but I think Bogleheads has turned me sour on AUM. Plus the AUM guy wanted everything at his brokerage.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We initially liked the advice-only guy because he was cheaper and I thought he help me get my feet underneath me for DIY down the road. We could set everything up wherever we want. I also liked him because he set us up on their version of Mint to track all our spending. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But he constantly hmmed and hawed on allocation. We had our 2nd meeting today and for an hour and a half he talked about getting a new credit card and retirement goals and tasks and ... I finally jumped in and said if you had to invest my dad&amp;amp;#39;s money what funds in the market tomorrow and what allocation would he recommend? He pulls up his website and hits an 70/30 Risk button - hits another button and boom pops out an 11 fund portfolio. I ask him what&amp;amp;#39;s the software they&amp;amp;#39;re using and he talks about low cost ratios. I asked him if they&amp;amp;#39;re licensing a robo-advisor of some kind and he kind of yada yada&amp;amp;#39;d that one.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/0tddsua71n281.png?width=920&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=b10ab2c9e458779ecc41a882376843dc097f360a&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/0tddsua71n281.png?width=920&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=b10ab2c9e458779ecc41a882376843dc097f360a&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I got kind of mad that it took him this long to throw out how he delivers allocation advice. I&amp;amp;#39;ve been looking at 3 and 4 fund Vanguard and Fidelity portfolios and told him that&amp;amp;#39;s what I wanted. Then my wife got mad. &amp;amp;quot;I&amp;amp;#39;m so tired of hearing about Boogle Heads,&amp;amp;quot; she says. She&amp;amp;#39;s like &amp;amp;quot;what&amp;amp;#39;s wrong with this?&amp;amp;quot; - and I just shut up. I really don&amp;amp;#39;t know what I&amp;amp;#39;m doing I&amp;amp;#39;m just a guy that reads a forum who&amp;amp;#39;s messed up pretty bad in the past. Bogleheads is tough when you don&amp;amp;#39;t have a clue what you&amp;amp;#39;re doing but yet know you want something super simple but can&amp;amp;#39;t explain why that&amp;amp;#39;s better. I can&amp;amp;#39;t explain why VTI/VXUS/BND is better than this. Maybe it&amp;amp;#39;s not all that better? Maybe this is a perfectly fine portfolio?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He also said he wants to DCA this and not lump sum. So my question is - say I go along with this in a Fidelity account. How hard would it be to convert this into a VTI/VXUS/BND down the road?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[索尼的《蜘蛛俠：無路可退》讓電影票網站崩潰]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 當時間停留在11月29日的午夜時分，《蜘蛛俠：無路可走》的門票開始銷售。
>回家 "開始銷售。幾分鐘之內，國內電影票網站開始崩潰
>因爲電影觀衆急於爲今年最令人期待的電影之一搶佔座位。
> 今年最令人期待的電影之一。
> 
> 這是在票房上未曾有過的事情。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r5ba4y/sonys_spidermanno_way_home_crashes_movie_ticket/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r5ba4y/sonys_spidermanno_way_home_crashes_movie_ticket/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 05:03:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When the clock stuck midnight on Nov. 29, tickets for “Spider-Man: No Way Home” went on sale. Within minutes domestic movie ticket sites began to crash as moviegoers rushed to snag seats for one of the most anticipated films of the year.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is something that the box office has not experienced since the pandemic began and a sign that with the right releases, the movie theater industry has a “bright future,” experts say.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The pandemic battered cinemas, crushing demand and nearly bankrupting some of the industry’s largest exhibitors. The box office has been slow to rebound, but sustained momentum over the last six months has provided confidence in an eventual recovery.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Overnight, the latest installment of the Marvel Cinematic Universe, a co-production between &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/DIS&quot;&amp;gt;Disney&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/6758.T-JP&quot;&amp;gt;Sony&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, has sparked even more optimism. Ticketing sites like Atom Tickets, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/CMCSA&quot;&amp;gt;Fandango&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and MovieTickets.com alongside movie theater sites like &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AMC&quot;&amp;gt;AMC&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/CNK&quot;&amp;gt;Cinemark&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and Regal saw a surge of demand for tickets leading many to crash or place visitors in hour-long online queues.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“There are different tiers of intense fan demand when it comes to box office pre-sales, and this film is clearly showing it belongs near the top with a select few others,” said Shawn Robbins, chief analyst at BoxOffice.com. “For anyone who doubted the communal draw of the theatrical experience over the past two years, look to this enthusiasm for ‘Spider-Man’ as a major inflection point during the box office recovery period and the sign of a bright future ahead.”  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This kind of fervor has not been seen at the box office since 2019 when advanced tickets for titles like “Avengers: Endgame” and “Star Wars: The Rise of Skywalker” went on sale.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/spider-man-no-way-home-ticket-demand-crashed-box-office-sites.html&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#39;Spider-Man: No Way Home&amp;amp;#39; ticket demand crashed box office sites (cnbc.com)&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME YOLO! 終於去做了! 我賣了幾個月的csp，收集了很多溢價，週五我被分配到了，不能再興奮了。Lfg!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r526kl/gme_yolo_finally_went_for_it_been_selling_csps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r526kl/gme_yolo_finally_went_for_it_been_selling_csps/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 04:37:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[是什麼催化劑將半導體股票推得如此之高？]]></title><description><![CDATA[尤其是今天--AMD創下了新高，大多數人都像沒有明天一樣火箭般地上升了。
漲勢，就像沒有明天一樣。當你看到他們過去一個月的表現時，這很瘋狂，但我
但我知道他們的收益和所有這些好東西都是在那段時間出來的。
芯片短缺=高需求=永不倒閉似乎不是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r59rt3/what_catalysts_are_pushing_up_the_semiconductor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r59rt3/what_catalysts_are_pushing_up_the_semiconductor/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 04:37:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Especially today - AMD hit a new high and most rocketed like there’s no tomorrow. When you look at their past month performance, it’s crazy, but I understand their earnings and all those good stuff were out during that period. Chip shortage = high demand = never out of business doesn’t seem to be the main push anymore. What else is behind this crazy push?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你是怎麼找到這個分論壇的？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我個人是從我看的一個優酷網友那裏瞭解到指數基金的，這讓我找到了這個社區。
找到這個社區。你呢？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r5bcjb/how_did_you_find_this_subreddit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r5bcjb/how_did_you_find_this_subreddit/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 04:13:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Personally I learned about index funds from a youtuber I watch and it led me to find this community. How about you?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[420.69 GameStop (GME) 股票 🚀🚀🚀🚀]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r56xmz/42069_gamestop_gme_shares/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r56xmz/42069_gamestop_gme_shares/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 03:27:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我錯過了什麼嗎？試圖瞭解紅利的價值...]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，假設我有一支價值50美元的股票。它的季度股息爲每股1美元
股。這意味着在除息日，該股票的價值爲49美元/股。
所以我所有的股票價值將下降1美元，但我在支付日得到1美元的回報。
但我在支付日得到了這1美元的回報。有人怎麼能從...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r52i1y/am_i_missing_something_trying_to_understand_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r52i1y/am_i_missing_something_trying_to_understand_the/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 03:27:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Ok, say I have a stock worth $50 a share. It gives a quarterly dividend of $1 a share. This means that on the ex dividend date, the stock will be worth $49 a share, so all my stock value will drop by $1 a share, but I get paid that $1 a share back on the pay date. How does anyone make any money from dividends if the stock price drops?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[60歲退休--什麼能讓你在65歲時享受到醫療保險？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想我有足夠的錢在60歲時退休，但不確定我是否想支付一大筆健康保險費用。
不知道我是否想爲健康保險支付一大筆錢。我在考慮做非全職工作或一份輕鬆的工作，直到65歲，只是爲了福利。
勤的工作，直到65歲，只是爲了福利。

有什麼想法？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r59bmz/retire_at_age_60_what_gets_you_through_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r59bmz/retire_at_age_60_what_gets_you_through_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 03:27:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I think I will have enough to retire at 60, but not sure if I want to pay a bunch of money for health insurance. I was thinking of working par-time or a light job until 65 just for the benefits. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thoughts?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這是什麼意思？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r59os6/what_does_it_mean/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r59os6/what_does_it_mean/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 02:39:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是2021年11月29日星期一的市場回顧。請欣賞!]]></title><description><![CDATA[心理市場回顧 - 2021年11月29日，星期一

在經歷了極度動盪、假期縮短的一週後，股市在週一出現反彈。
週一，在科技股大幅反彈的推動下，股票出現反彈，因爲市場參與者
市場參與者正在努力應對新發現的 "Omicron "冠狀病毒的潛在影響。
冠狀病毒變體的潛在影響。該...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r55t5m/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_nov_29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r55t5m/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_nov_29/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:58:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Monday, November 29, 2021&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Following an extremely volatile, holiday-shortened week, stocks rebounded on Monday, driven higher by a huge bounce in technology, as market participants grapple with the potential implications of the newly discovered “Omicron” coronavirus variant. The Dow Jones (DIA) closed higher after its worst day since October 2020, as the price of oil, which suffered its worst day all year, somewhat rebounded. While it is way too early to make any conclusions, I am personally looking at this dip as a potential buying opportunity in equities that were overstretched before.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Wedbush analyst Dan Ives wrote in a note to clients, “Ultimately this is not the first or last variant scare and our tech playbook over the last 18 months has been to use these macro/risk-off events as buying opportunities to own the tech sector specifically cloud, cyber-security, and 5G winners. While we are seeing a return to normalcy, a semi-remote workforce environment we believe is here to stay which underscores our tech cloud thesis into 2022 that the digital transformation build-out will be accelerated and is not a one time COVID pull forward event&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The US and EU have banned a host of destinations to ban flights from several African countries after the new variant was discovered. But cases of the variant, which the World Health Organization (WHO) has so far designated as a &amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.who.int/news/item/26-11-2021-classification-of-omicron-(b.1.1.529&quot;&amp;gt;variant of concern&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;-sars-cov-2-variant-of-concern),&amp;amp;quot; have also detected in regions including the U.K., Hong Kong, Australia, Germany and Italy, among others.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;While there is still much that needs to be studies regarding the Omicron variant, Pfizer (PFE) and Moderna (MRNA), the two largest producers the current COVID vaccine, asid they are already working to adapt current inoculations for the new variant and that, if a tailor made vaccine is necessary, would be completed relatively quickly. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/28/moderna-says-an-omicron-variant-vaccine-could-be-ready-in-early-2022.html&quot;&amp;gt;Moderna’s Chief Medical Officer Paul Burton said a new vaccine to address the Omnicron variant &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;would be widely available in early 2022 and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/omicron-covid-19-variant-pfizer-184458407.html&quot;&amp;gt;Pfizer said it could take about 100 days to have a tailor made vaccine ready to be widely available.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;President Biden said of the new variant, “his variant is a cause for concern, not a cause for panic. We have the best vaccines in the world, the best medicine, the best scientists, and we’re learning more every single day. We have more tools today to fight the variant than we ever have before.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Despite concerns present in the market, consumer spending, which accounts for roughly 70% of US GDP, continues accelerating. While supply-chain disruptions could lead shoppers toward in-stock items at physical stores this year, I think overall spending will see a healthy increase. The National Retail Federation (NRF) is forecasting an 8.5%-10.5% increase in holiday sales this year, compared with 2020. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The latest reading shows the personal savings rate is 7.5% (savings as a % of disposable income), the third-highest rate coming into Thanksgiving in the last quarter century. While this is down dramatically from the spike during the pandemic lockdowns (when consumers were unable to consume), the savings rate remains notably above the long-term average of 6.5% (6.1% excluding 2020). We think elevated savings will be drawn down, representing additional dry powder that will power consumer-spending growth for an extended period. At 4.2%, wage growth is now the highest it&amp;amp;#39;s been since Thanksgiving of 2007, providing additional fuel for consumers. Looking back over the last 25 years, when wage growth was above 4% and accelerating, GDP growth averaged 3.2%, compared with an average of 2.5% over the entire period, according to a report by Edward Jones. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Highlights&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Chief Executive Satya Nadella sold about half of his shares in the company last week, according to a federal securities filing. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/0001513142/000106299321011647/xslF345X03/form4.xml?campaign_id=4&amp;amp;amp;emc=edit_dk_20211129&amp;amp;amp;instance_id=46511&amp;amp;amp;nl=dealbook&amp;amp;amp;regi_id=90401093&amp;amp;amp;segment_id=75585&amp;amp;amp;te=1&amp;amp;amp;user_id=b1b6731f732a5b8d7bb632a925fe64b9&quot;&amp;gt;In the filing last week&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, the Redmond, Wash.-based software company reported Mr. Nadella sold 838,584 shares over two days, down from close to 1.7 million shares.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Jack Dorsey announced he will be stepping down as CEO of social media Twitter (TWTR), giving the lead role to Chief Technology Officer Parag Agrawal. In my opinion, this is good news for Twitter, given they will now have more focused leadership. Dorsey, who is also the CEO of Square (SQ) has a lot on his plate.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Nissan Motors announced it was planning to spend $18 billion over five years to accelerate growth of their EVs.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Shares of Alibaba (BABA) stock fell to its lowest level in four years amid the continued regulatory push by the Chinese Communist Party (CCP).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Tencent (TCEHY) will further open their super-app WeChat, with over 1.2 billion users in China, and allow links to external shopping sites like Alibaba. This was a new regulation instituted by the CCP in order to encourage competition among the big tech firms. Previously, apps in China did not allow competitor links in their platforms.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Russia will continue slowing down the speed of Twitter on mobile devices until all content deemed illegal is deleted, state communications regulator&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Please note price target upgrades were written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;*&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;John Deere (DE) with three target raises. Stock currently around $350

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Evercore ISI from $354 to $415 at Outperform&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Deutsche Bank from $375 to $398 at Hold&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Stifel Nicolaus from $430 to $445 at Buy&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Marvell Technology (MRVL) with two target raises. Stock currently around $75

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;JP Morgan from $74 to $85 at Overweight&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;B. Riley from $83 to $90&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Pfizer (PFE) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $50 to $60 at Equal Weight. Stock currently around $53&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Snowflake (SNOW) target raised by BTIG Research from $353 to $421 at Buy. Stock currently around $366&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Zscaler (ZS) target raised by Needham from $345 to $390 at Strong-Buy. Stock currently around $354.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“All our dreams can come true, if we have the courage to pursue them.” - Walt Disney&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列現在報告說，歐米茄的社區傳播是由一位服用3個劑量的心臟病專家傳播給另一位服用3個劑量的心臟病專家的。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465473422817959947</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465473422817959947</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:13:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這真的很簡單，夥計們。

爲了阻止這個新的變種，我們必須做那些已經對舊變種失敗的事情。

但這次我們必須更努力地去做，以便在它再次失敗時有更多人受害。

如果這對你來說毫無意義，你就是個壞人。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465482430802968580</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465482430802968580</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:13:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[英國現在建議每3個月進行一次covid強化治療
https://t.co/UKOndcb7la]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465454012250132487</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465454012250132487</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:13:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AAPL現在是一個好的買點嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，夥計們，我剛剛開始更多的分析股票，我想我將嘗試
並在這裏發表。這是我對AAPL的第二次分析，最後一次是
5月份的。如果你對我有任何反饋意見，那將是非常好的。
感謝。如果你有問題，請隨時提出，我將盡力解決。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r576vm/is_aapl_a_good_buy_right_now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r576vm/is_aapl_a_good_buy_right_now/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:13:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey there guys, I just started analyzing stocks more and I thought I´ll try to do that and post it here. That´s my second analysis for AAPL, the last one was from May. If you have any feedback for me that would be great and highly appreciated. If you have questions feel free to ask, I´ll try to answer everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we will look through the basics of Apple´s business and then see if we can come up with a fair value for Apple´s stock using discounted free cashflow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not financial advice and I personally own shares in Apple. Nevertheless I will try to stay as unbiased and objective as I can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First let´s review their different revenue streams. Their biggest stream, around &lt;strong&gt;50%&lt;/strong&gt; of their sales comes from the &lt;strong&gt;iPhone&lt;/strong&gt;. The &lt;strong&gt;Mac&lt;/strong&gt; makes up around &lt;strong&gt;11%&lt;/strong&gt;, the &lt;strong&gt;iPad&lt;/strong&gt; around &lt;strong&gt;9%&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Services&lt;/strong&gt; around &lt;strong&gt;19%&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Wearables, Home and Accessories&lt;/strong&gt; around &lt;strong&gt;11%&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the valuation:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We take &lt;strong&gt;analyst estimates&lt;/strong&gt;, we discount that by our &lt;strong&gt;required return of 8%&lt;/strong&gt;. Then we use the &lt;strong&gt;perpetual growth rate of 2,5%&lt;/strong&gt; and that gave us a fair value for Apple´s stock of &lt;strong&gt;$99 per share&lt;/strong&gt;. But because we have to account for &lt;strong&gt;Apple´s debt&lt;/strong&gt; as well, our &lt;strong&gt;fair value of equity&lt;/strong&gt; would be &lt;strong&gt;$94 per share&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now feel free to include a margin of safety to that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Apple´s price being at &lt;strong&gt;$160&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;per share&lt;/strong&gt; right now, it´s a little too high. That´s why I don´t think buying heavily is a good idea. Although you can always dollar-cost-average. That´s where you invest every month the same amount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where I see Apple´s stock price in 5 years.&lt;/strong&gt; We can calculate where the price might be in 5 years with the &lt;strong&gt;Earnings Per Share (EPS TTM)&lt;/strong&gt;, the &lt;strong&gt;Estimated Growth Rate&lt;/strong&gt; and the &lt;strong&gt;Future P/E Value&lt;/strong&gt;. With this method I get a stock price of &lt;strong&gt;$293 per share&lt;/strong&gt; which is higher than what it is now. Almost double. That´s why you have to be careful with this analysis. Always do your own due diligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What I´ll do.&lt;/strong&gt; I believe in Apple. I think they will stay for a long time and innovate even more. That´s why, although the price is not where I would want it to be, I will continue to &lt;strong&gt;dollar-cost-average&lt;/strong&gt;. That way I don´t mind the volatile market and hold for the longterm. Even if they don´t double in 5 years, I´m rather bullish on this company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading and I hope I´ll see you again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[傑克-多爾西辭職，專注於他的鬍鬚]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r51mb7/jack_dorsey_resigns_to_focus_on_his_beard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r51mb7/jack_dorsey_resigns_to_focus_on_his_beard/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:13:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[自從《華爾街日報》和《巴倫週刊》寫了關於現在是投資小盤股的最佳時機的文章後，羅素指數已經下跌200點。]]></title><description><![CDATA[11月12日
https://www.wsj.com/articles/inflation-bets-give-a-boost-to-small-cap-stocks-11636885800

"通脹押注給小盤股帶來推動力 較小的公司可以管理通脹
投資者說，較小的公司比較大的公司能更快地管理通貨膨脹的壓力。
他們說，小型公司比大型公司能更快地管理通貨膨脹的壓力，他們正在尋求價格的庇護...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r585l8/since_wsj_and_barrons_wrote_articles_on_now_being/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r585l8/since_wsj_and_barrons_wrote_articles_on_now_being/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:13:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;November 12th: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/inflation-bets-give-a-boost-to-small-cap-stocks-11636885800&quot;&gt;https://www.wsj.com/articles/inflation-bets-give-a-boost-to-small-cap-stocks-11636885800&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Inflation Bets Give a Boost to Small-Cap Stocks
Smaller companies can manage inflationary pressures more quickly than larger ones, say investors who are seeking refuge from price increases&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;November 12th: Barrons 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/cheap-small-company-stocks-51636763053&quot;&gt;https://www.barrons.com/articles/cheap-small-company-stocks-51636763053&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Small-Cap Stocks Are in Line to Be Big Winners in 2022&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look at the 1 month chart and it&amp;#39;s been a steady drop since these 2 articles happened. Very frustrating as I went all in on small caps and they are easily my biggest losers especially on a day like today with the market super up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the 12th, there has been only ONE day the Index went up (by a measly 5 points), every other day has gone down. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/search?client=safari&amp;amp;rls=en&amp;amp;q=Russell+index&amp;amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;amp;oe=UTF-8&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/search?client=safari&amp;amp;rls=en&amp;amp;q=Russell+index&amp;amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;amp;oe=UTF-8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$HIMX是一個不費吹灰之力的產品，在這個價格上是一個便宜貨，是你正在尋找的DD。]]></title><description><![CDATA[奇景科技有限公司是一家領先的供應商和無晶圓廠半導體制造商，總部位於臺灣台南市。
總部位於臺灣台南市，成立於2001年6月12日。

該公司IMHO在這個價格上被低估了，有很大的上升空間。
HIMX在過去4個季度有強勁的收入和盈利增長，但...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r522vr/himx_is_a_fukin_no_brainer_and_a_bargain_at_this/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r522vr/himx_is_a_fukin_no_brainer_and_a_bargain_at_this/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 23:46:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Himax Technologies, Inc. is a leading supplier and fabless semiconductor manufacturer headquartered in Tainan City, Taiwan founded on 12 June 2001.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company IMHO is so undervalued at this price and has much room to go up, HIMX had strong revenue and earnings growth in the last 4 quarters, but the stock price did not act accordingly, and I believe this growth will continue due to chip shortage, and the transformation in the global economy to electric cars, in 2030 most of the big cars brands are expected to stop producing diesel cars and produce only electric cars, this is regardless the already existed electric cars brands like Xpeng, Nio, Tesla etc. this will cause constant demand on chips and more production and revenue for HIMX and other semiconductor stocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/u5g0jy7vvk281.png?width=485&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=12c95a4227644109ca4be596b4ce38d3a91b3ff1&quot;&gt;HIMX Revenue and Earnings over the last 4 quarters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below a comparison between AMD and HIMX performance for the last 4 quarters:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;.HIMX Revenue growth ................  AMD Revenue growth&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q4 2020 $276M &lt;strong&gt;QoQ +15%&lt;/strong&gt; ----- Q4 2020 $3.24B &lt;strong&gt;QoQ +15%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q1 2021 $309M &lt;strong&gt;QoQ +12%&lt;/strong&gt; ------ Q1 2021 $3.45B &lt;strong&gt;QoQ +7%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q2 2021 $365M &lt;strong&gt;QoQ +18%&lt;/strong&gt; ------- Q2 2021 $3.85B &lt;strong&gt;QoQ +12%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q3 2021 $421M &lt;strong&gt;QoQ +15% -------&lt;/strong&gt; Q3 2021 $4.31B &lt;strong&gt;QoQ +12%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;....................HIMX...........AMD
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Price to Earnings ............ 5.35 .................... 49.23&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Price to Sales  ..................1.29  ....................12.76&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Book value per share .....$4.17!! 🤯  ...........$5.89!! 🤯&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Current ratio  ...................2.01 ...................... 2.24&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AMD is definitely bigger name than HIMX but I used this comparison just to show how HIMX is growing on the same pace as AMD, how it has healthy statistics, and how cheap its valuation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IMO HIMX is a solid play and a bargain at this price, the only thing that is holding back the stock price is the possible conflict between China and Taiwan, but if that happens, all the market will tank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My conservative prediction is that One year from now assuming normal market conditions HIMX price will be at least $20.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also 15% short interest add some spice to the stock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And my last word is, see you on the moon 🚀 🚀 🚀 🌙 🌙 🌙&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: this is not a financial advice, do your own DD before investing.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我必須要讀這個。現在你也知道了。https://t.co/7wwXuzu0uF]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465434225667153923</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465434225667153923</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 23:35:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以色列國內情報機構已經獲得臨時許可，可以訪問該國已確認的Omicron變體病例的人的電話數據，用於追蹤聯繫人。https://t.co/78ndtWqKvN]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465449663570583558</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465449663570583558</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 23:35:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這個男人、神話和傳奇人物將在美國東部時間今天下午6點加入我們的Twitter Spaces，談論他的最新專輯，他對比特幣的看法，以及更多的內容 ⚡️ https://t.co/6AypLg2HjR]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465441807374897152</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465441807374897152</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 23:35:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[網絡星期一即將來臨]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4oryc/cyber_monday_is_coming/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4oryc/cyber_monday_is_coming/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 21:35:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Covid公司的FUD並沒有欺騙任何人]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4wcpo/covid_fud_aint_fooling_nobody/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4wcpo/covid_fud_aint_fooling_nobody/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:57:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[縮放電話得到了回報。我可以正式說我賺了6位數。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4x1ec/zoom_calls_paid_off_i_can_officially_say_i_make_6/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4x1ec/zoom_calls_paid_off_i_can_officially_say_i_make_6/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:57:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我正在考慮賣掉我的富達賬戶中的所有東西，用先鋒基金代替。]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好，我是一個來自英國的新手投資者，24歲，我一直在投資。
我從2020年金融危機前就開始投資。

我一開始在vanguard（買入生命策略100%+sp500基金）。
然而，我覺得我的選擇有限，於是開了一個富達的賬戶。

我每個月都會存錢...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r52oqd/thinking_about_selling_everything_in_my_fidelity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r52oqd/thinking_about_selling_everything_in_my_fidelity/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:45:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi there, I&amp;#39;m a newbie investor from the UK here, 24 years old, I&amp;#39;ve been investing since just before covid 2020 crash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started off with vanguard (buying into life strategy 100% + sp500 fund), however I felt limited with my options and opened up a fidelity account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been depositing monthly into my fidelity account and into various different funds, Which I regret because I clearly have no idea what I&amp;#39;m doing... &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The funds have an average fee of 0.5% and I think this is quiet high (correct me if I am wrong). + the account fee + platform fee... this, over time, will eat into the value of my assets. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am writing today to get a second opinion and a bit of guidance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/jrhxnaieyk281.png?width=1920&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=f6ae3a1beda911396086e49e1aa8dd1dce48ca59&quot;&gt;30 fund portfolio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/0yy6ivbczk281.png?width=1482&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=1ffe3ea17a82b79b0cbdb88dbc3e1d2983a0e931&quot;&gt;vanguard portfolio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please help me... I am not too sure on what to do now... &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know this is a mess, all suggestions are welcome! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NSFW, my portfolio might give you anxiety. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在大流行病交易中賺取26億美元的對沖基金投資者表示，大流行病可能會對股市產生利好作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[對沖基金大亨比爾-阿克曼（Bill Ackman）週末表示，新的歐米茄變體的
導致COVID-19的冠狀病毒的新變種，如果它被證明會導致感染者出現輕度到中度的症狀，那麼可能會對股票產生利好。
感染者會出現輕度至中度症狀。該病毒的發現
該變種的發現導致了最糟糕的黑色星期五之一...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r517w5/hedgefund_investor_who_made_26_billion_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r517w5/hedgefund_investor_who_made_26_billion_on/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:32:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hedge-fund luminary Bill Ackman over the weekend said the new omicron variant of the coronavirus that causes COVID-19 could be bullish for stocks if it proves to result in mild to moderate symptoms for those who contract it. The discovery of the variant resulted in one of the worst Black Friday trading sessions in recent memory, with the Dow Jones Industrial Average DJIA, 0.98%, the S&amp;amp;P 500 index SPX, 1.62% and the Nasdaq Composite Index COMP, 2.08% all tumbling by at least 2%, but Ackman’s comments suggest that investors’ knee-jerk response may have been an overreaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bond yields on Friday also fell as prices for government debt saw a rush to the perceived safety of Treasurys on the back of fresh concerns about new restrictions that could result from a strain of COVID that the World Health Organization on Friday designated a variant of concern. However, stocks were bouncing back on Monday and the 10-year Treasury note yield TMUBMUSD10Y, 1.528% was up 8 basis points at 1.56%. Prices for Treasurys fall as yields rise. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ackman, who runs Pershing Square Capital, is known for his lucrative COVID wager. The Financial Times reported back in 2020 that the investor cashed out on bet that netted him a $2.6 billion profit on a $27 million at risk, on the premise that insurance premiums would soar during the height of the 2020 COVID pandemic as economies locked down. He also later in 2020 said that he placed bearish bets on corporate credit on the day that Pfizer PFE, -0.64%  and BioNTech BNTX, 3.65% released positive trial data on their COVID-19 vaccine, which triggered a whipsaw rally in stocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ackman was wagering that the vaccines would lead to mask-wearing complacency. However, that bet presumably turned out wrong as markets continued to surge in the aftermath of those vaccines. The danger posed by the omicron variant isn’t yet fully understood, even though governments in Europe, Asia, the Middle East and the Americas immediately restricted travel from southern Africa. Vaccine manufacturers have said that they are examining the variant closely and note that the current batch of remedies might still prove effective against the strain and new vaccines could be readied in early 2022 if needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/hedge-fund-investor-who-made-2-6-billion-on-pandemic-trades-says-omicron-could-be-bullish-for-stock-market-11638198173?mod=home-page&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/hedge-fund-investor-who-made-2-6-billion-on-pandemic-trades-says-omicron-could-be-bullish-for-stock-market-11638198173?mod=home-page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[年輕時承擔更大風險的謬誤]]></title><description><![CDATA[我經常聽到這樣的話。當你年輕的時候要承擔更大的風險。當你在
你20多歲的時候，重倉高風險/高回報的股票是可以的。但這是
有缺陷的推理。

事實上，在你年輕的時候冒大風險是更有風險的，因爲
機會成本。人們總是提到...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r533z7/the_fallacy_of_taking_bigger_risks_when_you_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r533z7/the_fallacy_of_taking_bigger_risks_when_you_are/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:32:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I hear this all the time. Take bigger risks when you are young. When you are in your 20’s its fine to go heavy in high risk/high reward stocks. But this is flawed reasoning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The truth is taking big risks when you are young is more risky because of opportunity costs. People always mention compounding interest over decades. But fail to apply this to investing in risky stocks when you are young. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lets say you are 20 years old and you have $10k to invest. Its common to hear people say you can be more risky since you are so young. And even if you do YOLO and lose it all you can easily recover. But think opportunity cost. What did you really lose doing a YOLO?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$10,000&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invest in an index fund that returns 8.5% annualized return &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Withdraw at 65 years old&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That $10k becomes $400k. So you basically lost $400k because you YOLOed on a risky stock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you hold till 70 you lost $600k. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At age 90 you can give your children and grandchildren $3.2 million. Or you could have fun and lose it all on a risky stock. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bottom line is a young persons greatest asset is TIME. Throwing investment time away by taking unnecessary risk is a massive mistake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not saying don’t buy stocks that are risky hyper growth companies. But also don’t gamble needlessly. Because you are gambling much more than that couple hundred or thousand you see next to the stock ticker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[遊戲店。Finviz報告112%的SI - 第二回合？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r503cb/gamestop_finviz_reporting_112_si_round_2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r503cb/gamestop_finviz_reporting_112_si_round_2/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 19:14:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[亞馬遜準備在2022年初超過UPS和聯邦快遞，成爲美國最大的快遞公司，執行官說]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/amazon-on-track-to-be-largest-us-delivery-service-by-2022-exec-says.html

亞馬遜全球消費者首席執行官戴夫-克拉克（Dave Clark）週一告訴CNBC，該公司有望成爲美國最大的快遞公司。
該公司有望在2021年底或2022年初成爲美國最大的快遞服務。
2021年底或2022年初成爲美國最大的快遞公司。

分析師們已經...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4zkvm/amazon_poised_to_pass_ups_and_fedex_to_become/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4zkvm/amazon_poised_to_pass_ups_and_fedex_to_become/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 18:16:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/amazon-on-track-to-be-largest-us-delivery-service-by-2022-exec-says.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/amazon-on-track-to-be-largest-us-delivery-service-by-2022-exec-says.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dave Clark, Amazon’s CEO of worldwide consumer, told CNBC on Monday that the company is on track to become the nation’s largest delivery service by the end of 2021 or early 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Analysts have long predicted Amazon would overtake carriers like UPS, FedEx and the U.S. Postal Service, thanks to its increasingly in-house network of planes, trucks, vans and ships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a positive development as Amazon dependence on other carriers will be lessen. The logistic and warehouse networks are in a optimal mode now as Amazon has been invested heavily to fight off the competition. This proves that the investment cycle has finally paid off as patience investors will be holding the amazon stocks and waiting for the next stock appreciation cycle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我剛剛在經紀公司存入7千美元，28歲，你會在這些股票中買入哪些股票做長線？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在上班前發這個帖子，所以請原諒我不是很詳細，將盡力而爲。
儘量使其與大家息息相關，而不僅僅是我對這3只股票的看法。
股票，我想知道對長期的意見。

特斯拉

蘋果

索菲

我擁有特斯拉是因爲.... 這就是特斯拉。在我看來，人們希望...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4wghb/i_just_deposited_7k_into_brokerage_age_28_which/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4wghb/i_just_deposited_7k_into_brokerage_age_28_which/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 18:16:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Posting this right before work so forgive me for not being super detailed, will try my best to make this relevant for everyone and not just me about these 3 stocks I want to know opinions on for long term: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sofi &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I own Tesla because.... It is Tesla. People in my honest opinion want to believe they will only be making vehicles in the future. Not the case if Elon Musk gets his way (check out the Tesla bot for example, not to mention space travel, etc). Before today held 2 shares of Tesla, plan on buying 2 more. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple is a good long term buy and hold because it is Apple of course. I do not believe the Apple car that should be releasing in the next 3 years has been priced in to the stock at all yet. I could see Apple being worth over $500/share say 3 years from now. Before today held 14 shares of Apple, plan on buying 10 more. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sofi is an underdog stock. I could see this stock going much further down, possibly to/below $10 a share again. Sofi is by definition loosing money, and it is the outlier compared to say a Tesla or an Apple stock... However I see it as being revolutionary when it comes to financial products for the everyday person. As a millennial most of my friends from around the United States seem to know more about Sofi than Goldman Sachs, Wells Fargo, etc. I would be shocked if Sofi is not worth $40 a share this time next year. Before today held 48 shares, will be buying 25 more today, and will wait for a potential dip below $12 - if that happens will buy as many shares as I can. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tell me if I am missing anything with these stocks, and for us readers in similar situations, maybe a few stocks to consider purchasing in lieu of any of the above 3?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[10月耐用品訂單下滑0.5%。]]></title><description><![CDATA[10月耐用品新訂單按季節性調整後減少了1美元。
經調整的12億美元或0.5%，至2601億美元，美國人口普查局公佈。
宣佈。 

這一下降是連續兩個月的下降，此前9月份經季節性調整後爲0.4%。
9月下降。不包括運輸業，新訂單...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r4z1e9/orders_for_durable_goods_slid_05_in_october/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r4z1e9/orders_for_durable_goods_slid_05_in_october/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:53:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;New orders for manufactured durable goods in October decreased A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $1.2  billion or 0.5% to $260.1 billion, the U.S. Census Bureau announced. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This decrease, down two consecutive months, followed a SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 0.4% September  decrease. Excluding transportation, new orders increased  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 0.5%.  Excluding defense, new orders increased  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 0.8%. Transportation equipment,  down three of the last four months, drove the SEASONALLY ADJUSTED decrease, 2.0 billion or  2.6% to $75.3 billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shipments of manufactured durable goods in October, up five of the  last six months, increased  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $4.0 billion or 1.5% to $261.5 billion. This  followed  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 0.6% September increase. Transportation equipment, up  following two consecutive monthly decreases, led the increase,  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $2.3  billion or 3.2% to $75.3 billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfilled orders for manufactured durable goods in October, up nine  consecutive months, increased  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $3.1 billion or 0.2% to $1,249.7 billion.  This followed  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 0.7% September increase. Machinery, up nineteen  consecutive months, led the increase, up  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED$1.4 billion or 1.2% to $113.7  billion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inventories of manufactured durable goods in October, up nine  consecutive months, increased  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $2.8 billion or 0.6% to $466.0 billion.  This followed  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED 1.0% September increase. Fabricated metal products, up  thirteen consecutive months, led the increase, up  A SEASONALLY ADJUSTED $0.9 billion or 1.4% to  $61.0 billion.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.floordaily.net/flooring-news/orders-for-durable-goods-slid-05-in-october&quot;&gt;https://www.floordaily.net/flooring-news/orders-for-durable-goods-slid-05-in-october&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一支你擁有相當比例的股票在瞬間上漲了數百萬美元

但這只是因爲你要卸任CEO了 https://t.co/GnA0DQORMb]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465330319331139596</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465330319331139596</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:40:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[由於通貨膨脹，COVID-19現在是COVID-20.178。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465372508228624401</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1465372508228624401</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:40:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[科維德的死亡率沒有上升。由於Omicron突變是 "超級溫和 "的變種，世衛組織和將限制和大規模歇斯底里換成了謹慎的樂觀態度。]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，夥計們，如果你們對市場的突然下滑感到擔憂，這裏有一個好消息
一些好消息

世界衛生組織和世界各地的冠狀病毒專家今天上午呼籲
各國放棄旅行限制，結束大規模的歇斯底里，轉而採取
謹慎樂觀的態度，因爲最初的報告顯示...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4z16b/covid_death_rate_not_rising_swap_restrictions_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4z16b/covid_death_rate_not_rising_swap_restrictions_and/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:15:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey guys, if you&amp;#39;re worried about the sudden downturn in the markets, here&amp;#39;s some great news &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The WHO and Coronavirus experts around the world are calling this morning for countries to drop travel restrictions and end the mass hysteria and instead be cautiously optimistic as initial reports out of South Africa suggest the new Omicron variant is not more lethal than the previous Delta variant. In fact, there have been no reports of hospitalisations or deaths as a result of anyone being diagnosed with Omicron. Most patients merely experience a severe headache, nausea, dizziness and a high pulse rate, according to hospitals and medics across Southern Africa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the news of the new variant, first reported in South Africa, led to mass hysteria around the world: markets thumbed and dozens of countries imposed travel restrictions and additional checks, including the UK, US, EU, Israel, Australia and Japan after the new mutation popped up in the UK, Germany, Italy, Czech Republic and Israel among other countries. Dr Angelique Coetzee, chair of the South African Medical Association, said this reaction was “medically seen, not justified.” A GP for over three decades, and chair of the South African Medical Association, she was the first African doctor to suggest to local authorities Covid had mutated into a new strain. Coetzee called the response from many European countries, including the UK, “just a hype.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Africa’s health minister Joe Phaahla also said the majority of cases of Omicron seen by doctors in his country have been “mild”. He added he has heard from GPs that the “majority of the people they’ve been seeing are mild.” “Our clinicians have not witnessed severe illness. Part of it may be because the majority of those who are positive are young people,” Dr Paahla added.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full story here &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cityam.com/covid-death-rate-not-rising-swap-travel-restrictions-and-mass-hysteria-for-cautious-optimism-as-omicron-mutation-is-super-mild-variant-who-and-coronavirus-experts-say/&quot;&gt;https://www.cityam.com/covid-death-rate-not-rising-swap-travel-restrictions-and-mass-hysteria-for-cautious-optimism-as-omicron-mutation-is-super-mild-variant-who-and-coronavirus-experts-say/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[多爾西從推特卸任]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.huffpost.com/entry/jack-dorsey-stepping-down-twitter-ceo_n_61a4e36fe4b025be1aec6591

Twitter的投資者似乎很喜歡這個，但有趣的是，SQ是平的。你會
你認爲這對SQ來說是好事，因爲他現在可以只關注該公司，而不是分散注意力。
而不是分散他的注意力。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4y3ma/dorsey_stepping_down_from_twitter/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4y3ma/dorsey_stepping_down_from_twitter/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:15:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.huffpost.com/entry/jack-dorsey-stepping-down-twitter-ceo_n_61a4e36fe4b025be1aec6591&quot;&gt;https://www.huffpost.com/entry/jack-dorsey-stepping-down-twitter-ceo_n_61a4e36fe4b025be1aec6591&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Twitter investors seem to like this, but interesting that SQ is flat. You&amp;#39;d think this would be good for SQ since he can now focus on just that company and not divide his attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我見過的最有趣的狗屎。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4xaoj/funniest_shit_ive_ever_seen/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4xaoj/funniest_shit_ive_ever_seen/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:15:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[市場在Tilray上犯了一個錯誤；至少有30%的上升空間]]></title><description><![CDATA[一直在關注大麻行業的人知道，Tilray最近的交易表現令人失望。
交易表現一直不盡如人意。在我看來，該公司交易業績的最大障礙是由於加拿大的成人娛樂活動。
該公司的交易表現的最大障礙是由於加拿大成人娛樂業的
行業的廣泛挑戰，以及與大麻相關的零售...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4urxr/market_made_a_mistake_on_tilray_at_least_30_upside/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4urxr/market_made_a_mistake_on_tilray_at_least_30_upside/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:15:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those who&amp;#39;ve been following the cannabis industry, knows that Tilray&amp;#39;s recent trading performance has been underwhelming. In my opinion, the biggest hurdle to the company&amp;#39;s trading performance is due to the Canadian adult recreational industry wide challenge along with covid-related retail headwinds. There&amp;#39;s been struggles for the Canadian cannabis LPs to generate growth organically within the adult recreational segment. For example, while Tilray, market leader in Canadian adult recreational, generated 26% topline growth from $405 million in 2020 to $513 million in 2021, much of that topline growth is derived from acquisitions. In other words, Tilray&amp;#39;s recent revenue growth were &amp;quot;bought&amp;quot; instead of generated organically as the market expands. Low growth within the segment along with some structural challenges and covid-related shut-downs further negatively impacted the industry&amp;#39;s outlook and profitability, resulting in depressing trading performances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As cannabis companies remain illegal in the United States at a federal level and debt capital raising are off the table as a result, Canadian cannabis LPs relies on equity issuance to fund acquisition opportunities to &amp;quot;grow&amp;quot; their toplines. Result of both stagnant growth and share dilution, Tilray traded down from $40 in February 2021 to $10 last close. Tilray&amp;#39;s TTM EV/Sales declined from 40x to 10x. For a growth company within a quickly expanding market that&amp;#39;s only 3 years old, 10x TTM sales EV is a good price in my opinion. What makes it even more attractive is that there&amp;#39;s a catalyst that the market has dismissed and forgotten that will completely derail the stagnant market growth narrative for Tilray.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Germany&amp;#39;s new coalition government has recently reached a deal that&amp;#39;s set to legalize recreational cannabis use. As a result, German pot stocks popped last week on Frankfurt exchange. For example, German cannabis company Synbiotic rose by 33% to $29 Euro, which implies a $100mm market cap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What the market has forgotten however is that Canadian cannabis LP Tilray is actually the market leader in the Germany&amp;#39;s cannabis market. But the stock didn&amp;#39;t move last week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do I know the market made a mistake instead of &amp;quot;everything has been priced in&amp;quot; narrative?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Easy. First, almost every German pot companies moved up last week. The fact that Tilray didn&amp;#39;t change at all suggests that whoever was making market genuinely forgot that Tilray is a market leader in the German cannabis market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, if we assume status quo on Tilray&amp;#39;s 10x EV/Sales multiple, which is a very conservative assumption because we&amp;#39;re completely dismissing the potential of a new, 3-days old, 83 million population addressable market. And if we proxy $90 million of additional revenue, which is another very conservative assumption as Tilray generated $90 million in revenue after Canada legalized their adult recreational cannabis market in 2018; Conservative because German population doubles of Canadian. With the conservative multiple assumption while holding other variables constant, just by adding the additional $90 million in revenue, we should expect Tilray trade up by at least 30%. The fact that it didn&amp;#39;t trade up at the slightest suggests whoever was making market was sleeping in his office after he had his turkey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Third, Tilray is production and distribution ready. Tilray operates two state-of-art facilities in Portugal and Germany with over 3 million square feet of production capacity. Tilray also owns and operates one of the largest market cap pharmaceutical company, CC Pharma, in Germany. Because of the company&amp;#39;s production and distribution capacity, institutional support, larger balance sheet, domestic moms &amp;amp; pops cannabis producers in Germany aren&amp;#39;t like to able to compete against Tilray in the immediate 24 months of legalization, allowing Tilray to secure market leadership. Again, this echoes with why assume only $90 million of revenue and 10x EV/Sales is a very conservative estimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Forth, there has been consistencies showing that the cannabis MTM is very inefficient. Most of you are aware that there were a squeeze with the Canadian cannabis LPs that took place in February. It was driven by Democrats winning the election, investors bet in favour that recreational cannabis use will be legalized in the U.S. It was similar to what&amp;#39;s happening today; similar but different. What&amp;#39;s similar is that both are political driven catalyst and market has gotten it completely wrong. Different was that last time Tilray were traded up for the wrong reason, Tilray has minimal operations in the United States, while they&amp;#39;re already a market leader in the German cannabis market with operations and infrastructures that are unmatched by their competitors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading, let me know if I got it wrong. Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Position: 500 shares long TLRY at C$13.32&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我想我做什麼 - 我做什麼]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4ugcq/what_i_think_i_do_what_i_do/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4ugcq/what_i_think_i_do_what_i_do/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 16:50:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[S&P500和恢復時間]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好! 在看到另一個子網站上關於S&P500和破淨的評論後，它讓我想到了
讓我想到了。如果我在最高價時投資於標準普爾500指數，然後價格下跌並不再投入資金，那麼最長的時間是多久？
跌，並且不再投入資金，那麼歷史上最長的時間是多久？
歷史上需要多長時間才能達到收支平衡？

希望這有意義？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4ibbc/sp500_and_recovery_time/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r4ibbc/sp500_and_recovery_time/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 16:07:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello! After seeing a comment on the s&amp;amp;p500 and breaking Even on another sub, it got me thinking.  If I invest into the s&amp;amp;p500 at the peak Price and the price falls and never put anymore money in, what’s the longest amount of time historically has it taken to breakeven? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully that makes sense? 😅 I’ll try to explain better if it’s not clear what I’m asking &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對購買共同基金股票感到困惑]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好，我一直想投資一些錢在FXAIX指數基金，但
我對這些股票是如何定價和交易的感到困惑。

從我讀到的內容來看，共同基金的股票價格是在每天收市後更新的，這也是股票交易的時間。
這也是股票交易的時間。這是否意味着我將不知道價格
的價格。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r4lz4c/confused_about_buying_mutual_fund_shares/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r4lz4c/confused_about_buying_mutual_fund_shares/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 15:30:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi there, I’ve been looking to invest some money in the FXAIX index fund, but I’m confused about how these shares are priced and traded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From what I read, mutual fund share prices are updated after market close each day, which is also when shares are traded. Does that mean I won’t know the price of the shares I’m buying until they are calculated after close, or am I buying them at the price they’re listed at during the day?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[彼得-林奇的《華爾街》一書摘要]]></title><description><![CDATA[領先於華爾街

 *股票最有可能被接受爲審慎的時刻，他們不是
 * 只投資你能承受的損失而不影響你的日常生活。
   只投資你能承受的損失，而不影響你的日常生活
 * 不要高估專業人士的技能和智慧
 * 利用你的優勢...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4oizg/peter_lynch_one_up_on_wall_street_book_summary/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r4oizg/peter_lynch_one_up_on_wall_street_book_summary/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 15:04:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;h1&gt;One Up on Wall Street&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stocks are most likely to be accepted as prudent at the moment they are not&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only invest what you could afford to lose without that loss having any effect on your daily life&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;#39;t overestimate the skill and wisdom of professionals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take advantage of what you already know&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look for opportunities that haven&amp;#39;t been discovered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Invest in a home first&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Invest in companies, not the stock market&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ignore short term movements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Predicting the economy is futile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Predicting the short term movement of the stock market is futile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Long term stocks have outperformed bonds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The average person is exposed to local companies years before wall street&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the stock market, one in the hand is worth 10 in the bush&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;Any idiot can run this business&amp;quot; is one characteristic of the perfect company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Invest in companies that make products people need to keep buying&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the company insiders are buying, you should too. Management normally sells 2.3 shares for every 1 share they buy. In 1987 after the crash, it was 4 buys for 1 sell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid the hottest stock in the hottest industry, any stock being touted as the next X&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A share of stock is NOT a lotto ticket. It is a part ownership of a business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;P/E ratio can be thought of as the number of years to earn back your original investment. IE = P/E of 10 would be 10 years assuming earnings stay constant. Ratios tend to be lower for slow growers and highest for the fast growers with cyclicals in between depending on the current cycle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look at average P/E ratios on the company you are researching and peers going back several years to determine if it is a good buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid stocks with HIGH P/E ratios. They must have incredible earnings growth to justify the price&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;P/E ratio that is half the growth rate (annual earnings) is very positive and one that is twice the growth rate is very negative. IE = P/E of 10 should be growing at 10%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formula = Growth rate plus dividend yield divided by P/E. IE = 12% growth + 3% yield/10 P/E = 1.5. Less than 1 is bad. 1.5 is ok and 2+ is great.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The stock market as a whole has its own collective P/E ratio, which is a good indicator of weather the market at large is over or under valued. If some stocks are selling at inflated prices relative to earnings, then it could be likely most stocks are selling at inflated prices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest rates have a large effect on p/e ratios as investors pay higher p/e when interest rates are lower and bonds less attractive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dividend paying stocks keep the stock price from falling as far as if there was no dividend&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You CAN&amp;#39;T predict future earnings. Wall Street has battalions of analysts trying to do this and they are wrong a lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cash Flow – amount of money a company takes in as a result of doing business. You want to buy companies that don&amp;#39;t need to spend a lot of money to make money IE = company spends 20 million to make 100 million is better than one that needs to spend 90 million to make 100 million. Formula = $20 stock with $2 per share annual cash flow has a 10-1 ratio which is standard (10%). $20 stock with $4 CF = 20% return on cash. Focus on free cash flow – what is left over after normal capital spending is taken out&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debt to equity ratio - normal is 25% debt to 75% equity but higher equity % is better&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[閃電般的下降楔形，是時候做空納斯達克了!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4ramn/descending_wedge_on_lightning_time_to_short_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r4ramn/descending_wedge_on_lightning_time_to_short_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 13:32:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>