<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:50:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通稱特斯拉欠銀行1.62億美元]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quy6j8/jpmorgan_says_tesla_owes_the_bank_162_million/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quy6j8/jpmorgan_says_tesla_owes_the_bank_162_million/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 14:47:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[預測市場崩潰的時間線（羅恩-保羅著）]]></title><description><![CDATA[2014年--市場必須修正，在它發生之前，誰會說這是一次崩潰？
發生之前，誰還會說是崩盤呢？我認爲，我們將迎來一次重大的修正。我認爲我們非常、非常
脆弱
[http://www.cnbc.com/2014/07/29/ron-paul-stocks-are-in-a-bubble-and-will-crash.html]

2015年--仍有很多不穩定因素存在......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv79af/timeline_of_predicting_a_market_crash_by_ron_paul/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv79af/timeline_of_predicting_a_market_crash_by_ron_paul/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 14:47:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnbc.com/2014/07/29/ron-paul-stocks-are-in-a-bubble-and-will-crash.html&quot;&gt;2014 -  The market has to correct, and who&amp;#39;s going to call it a crash until it  happens? We&amp;#39;re in for a major correction, I think. I think we&amp;#39;re very,  very vulnerable&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnbc.com/2015/06/19/ron-paul-stock-market-day-of-reckoning-is-near.html&quot;&gt;2015 -  There&amp;#39;s a lot of instability still out there, and this hasn&amp;#39;t been  corrected yet. I don&amp;#39;t think it&amp;#39;s going to correct easily, I don&amp;#39;t think  it&amp;#39;s going to be just a correction.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnbc.com/2017/07/02/ron-paul-not-a-shock-if-stocks-fall-25-percent-and-gold-soars-50-percent-by-oct.html&quot;&gt;2017 -  &amp;quot;If our markets are down 25 percent and gold is up 50 percent it wouldn&amp;#39;t be a total shock to me&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/14/ron-paul-market-meltdown-could-spark-depression-like-conditions.html&quot;&gt;2018 -  A 50% correction will spark depression-like conditions that may be ‘worse than 1929’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/the-dollar-is-going-to-self-destruct-talking-bitcoin-with-ron-paul&quot;&gt;2019 - The Dollar is going to self destruct&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_gbZlnyuQ6g&quot;&gt;2020 - The end result is an overinflated stock market that could see a “violent correction”, as well as a monetary system on the brink of collapse. I happen to believe it’s the biggest financial bubble in the history of monetary policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VCj-m08qPd4&quot;&gt;On the next economic crash in 2021&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[HSA賬戶，你有什麼想法？]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以，我想知道人們對HSA賬戶的看法。我讀了一篇文章
說這是一個很好的工具，可以把錢放進去，這樣將來當你
老年人時，你可以支付醫療費用。

它還可以降低你的應稅收入。

我唯一的問題是，我並不年輕...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qv5mv6/hsa_accounts_what_are_your_thoughts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qv5mv6/hsa_accounts_what_are_your_thoughts/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 14:35:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, I was trying to find out peoples thoughts on HSA accounts.  I read an article that said it is a great vehicle to put money into so that in the future when you are elderly you can pay for medical expenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also can lower your taxable income.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My only issue with this, is that I am not young anymore and have started having health problems.  A high deductible plan would suck out the cash from me.  I am guessing this is a good option for people in their early 20s since they are probably less likely to have health problems.  Not sure if the Boglehead community has thoughts on this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[還有誰在考慮做空Rivian？]]></title><description><![CDATA[不瞞你說，我甚至從未想過做空一家公司，但這是
太瘋狂了。前期市場高達157美元，沒有理由被估價爲1370億美元。
作爲參考，特斯拉，最著名的是被高估，但股價仍然上升
漲，其交易價格僅爲RIVN估值的7.3倍。然而，RIVN有0...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv44ti/who_else_is_thinking_of_shorting_rivian/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv44ti/who_else_is_thinking_of_shorting_rivian/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 13:31:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not going to lie, I’ve never even thought of shorting a company, but this is insane. Up to $157 in pre market with no reason to be valued at $137 billion. 
For reference, Tesla, most famous for being overvalued and the stock still goes up is trading at only 7.3x the valuation of RIVN. Yet RIVN has 0 sales, 0 revenue, 0 profit. 
This thing is going to fall hard. Just a matter of how long these buyers can hold the price this high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美國通脹預期的激增有增無減，上升到了有史以來的最高水平（5年的盈虧平衡點爲3.17%）。https://t.co/faPSer3Q4F]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460406986785411073</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460406986785411073</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 11:44:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[20M失業 - 我的父母給了我2000美元的投資，我做的這些選擇好嗎...？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我剛剛在Fidelity開了一個賬戶，準備買這些指數基金/債券。
但我只是想從你們那裏得到一些驗證，如果這些是我最好的
選擇。

 * 國內股票。FSKAX（總市場 - 0.015%）。

 *國際股票。FSPSX (國際 - 0.035%)

 *新興市場：...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qupyu7/20m_unemployed_i_have_been_given_2000_dollars_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qupyu7/20m_unemployed_i_have_been_given_2000_dollars_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 09:57:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just opened an account with fidelity and about to buy these index funds/bonds, but I just want some verification from you people whether if these are my best options.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;domestic stocks:            FSKAX (total market - 0.015%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;international stocks:     FSPSX (international - 0.035%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;emerging markets:         FPADX (emerging markets - 0.075%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. treasury bonds:      FUAMX (treasury bonds - 0.03%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. TIPS:                    FIPDX (inflation protected bonds - 0.05%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;real estate:                   FSRNX (real estate index fund - 0.07%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;and this will be the % split I am doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;30% domestic equity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% international equity &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;10% emerging market equity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% U.S. Treasury bonds&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% TIPS (inflation protected bonds)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% Real estate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不知道伊隆爸爸的最終目的是什麼，但他最近一直有一些超級大壞蛋的感覺。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quyhqs/not_sure_what_papa_elons_endgame_is_but_hes_been/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quyhqs/not_sure_what_papa_elons_endgame_is_but_hes_been/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 08:35:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tilray To the Moon DD裏面。]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和黨人南希-梅斯將在今天的大麻法案會議上提出她的大麻法案，時間是
美國東部時間下午2:00在國會山舉行。
https://twitter.com/RepNancyMace/status/1459565180585656325?s=20

德國新的聯合政府正在討論大麻合法化問題。Tilray
已經在德國銷售醫用大麻，並已...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qukdev/tilray_to_the_moon_dd_inside/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qukdev/tilray_to_the_moon_dd_inside/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 08:10:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican Nancy Mace is presenting her Marijuana bill conference today at 2:00pm EDT at Capitol Hill.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/RepNancyMace/status/1459565180585656325?s=20&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/RepNancyMace/status/1459565180585656325?s=20&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Germany&amp;#39;s new coalition government in talks of legalizing Marijuana. Tilray sells medical marijuana already in Germany and has license. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-10/germany-s-next-coalition-close-to-deal-on-legalizing-cannabis&quot;&gt;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-10/germany-s-next-coalition-close-to-deal-on-legalizing-cannabis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s go my precious little Diamond hands. Tilray currently up over 6%. This is not financial Advice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我25歲了，這是我的羅斯。我在這裏能做得更好嗎？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qungve/im_25_and_this_is_my_roth_what_can_i_do_better/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qungve/im_25_and_this_is_my_roth_what_can_i_do_better/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 07:50:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在富達的VTSAX相當於什麼？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qulqnk/what_is_the_vtsax_equivalent_at_fidelity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qulqnk/what_is_the_vtsax_equivalent_at_fidelity/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 06:49:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利發佈其2022年市場展望，並認爲會出現下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利認爲，在利率上升的背景下，美國股市未來一年將面臨更大的挑戰。
在利率上升、增長放緩和供應鏈中斷的背景下，美國股市將面臨更多挑戰。

這家華爾街公司最近將明年的標準普爾500指數目標定爲4,400點。
這意味着比目前的水平下降了5%。負面的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quo6jl/morgan_stanley_is_out_with_its_2022_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quo6jl/morgan_stanley_is_out_with_its_2022_market/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 05:22:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morgan Stanley sees a more challenging year ahead for U.S. equities against a backdrop of higher interest rates, slowing growth and supply chain disruptions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Wall Street firm recently set its S&amp;amp;P 500 target for next year at 4,400, implying a 5% decline from current levels. The negative projection followed a blockbuster year for stocks that has seen the &lt;a href=&quot;https://link.cnbc.com/click/25708849.282877/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuY25iYy5jb20vcXVvdGVzLy5TUFg_X19zb3VyY2U9bmV3c2xldHRlciU3Q21hcmtldGluZw/5ba060792ddf9c38dd023063Bd6668e6e&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;/a&gt; rallying 25% and raking in more than 60 record highs despite fears of persistent inflation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[從歷史上看，在收市時投資比在開市時投資要好得多，大多數收益是在一夜之間發生的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[早在2018年就有一篇有趣的文章說

> 如果你在每個工作日交易的最後一秒鐘買入SPY
> 自1993年以來，並在第二天開市時賣出 - 捕獲所有的淨
> 小時後的收益--你的累計價格收益將是571%。
> 
> 在另一方面...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quxd2t/historically_its_way_better_to_invest_at_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quxd2t/historically_its_way_better_to_invest_at_market/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 04:11:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is an interesting article back from 2018 that says&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you had bought the SPY at the last second of trading on each business day since 1993 and sold at the market open the next day — capturing all of the net after-hour gains — your cumulative price gain would be 571%  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, if you had done the reverse, buying the ETF at the first second of regular trading every morning at 9:30 a.m. and selling at the 4 p.m. close, you would be down 4.4%&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have backtested the same for 2020 and 2021, see the results below. Every day I was buying/selling just 1 share of $SPY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Buy at open, sell at close&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Buy at close, sell at open&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2020&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-$4.88&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$45.42&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2021&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-$38.05&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;$53.92&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: all calculations made using BreakingEquity&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是2021年11月15日星期一的市場回顧。請欣賞!]]></title><description><![CDATA[心理市場回顧--2021年11月15日，星期一

股市收盤時漲跌互現，道瓊斯指數（DIA）和科技股密集的納斯達克指數（QQQ）
收盤小幅下跌，因爲市場參與者消化了來自中國的樂觀經濟數據
市場參與者消化了來自中國的樂觀經濟數據，並等待着稍後的美國零售銷售的關鍵報告。
本週晚些時候美國零售銷售的關鍵報告。羅素指數...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qushen/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_nov_15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qushen/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_monday_nov_15/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:51:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Monday, November 15, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks finished mixed, with the Dow Jones (DIA) and tech-heavy Nasdaq (QQQ) closing modestly lower, as market participants digested upbeat economic data coming from China and await for a key report on retail sales in the US later this week. The Russell 2000 (IWM), which tracks the performance of small-caps, underperformed on the day, closing 0.44% lower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stronger than expected economic data coming out of China helped lift the sentiments of market participants following last week’s inflation report. The world&amp;#39;s second-largest economy saw both retail sales and industrial production unexpectedly rise in October in a year-over-year period, suggesting that China’s economy is holding up better than expected amid new stay-in-place restrictions and ongoing power shortages. However, prices of new homes dropped 0.25% in October versus September, marking the biggest drop in more than six years as the nation’s real estate market remains under pressure from the Evergrande situation. Here are the numbers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retail Sales: +4.9% YoY vs +3.5 expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Industrial Production: +3.5% YoY vs +3% expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow, market participants will receive the Commerce Department’s monthly Retail Sales report, which is expected to show a 1.3% year-over-year rise in retail sales, improving from September’s disappointing 0.7% rise. Moreover, major retailers like Walmart (WMT), Target (TGT), Home Depot (HD), and Lowe’s (LOW) are set to report Q3 earnings, which will offer additional data regarding the state of consumer demand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week, markets were spooked by the pace of inflation, with the recent Consumer Price Index (CPI) showing the fastest pace of increase in roughly 30 years. which showed prices soared 6.2% in a year-on-year period, accelerating from September’s 5.4% YoY rate, and higher than the 5.9% expected. The staying power and magnitude of inflationary pressures has, perhaps, become the central question for market participants, with companies across the board reporting rising input costs and price hikes passed on to the consumers to preserve margins. While Q3 earning results have robustly demonstrated that companies in the SPY were largely able to navigate these cost pressures, the possibility remains that if inflation runs hotter than expected for longer than expected, it could begin to hamper consumer demand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ian Shepherdson, Chief Economist at Pantheon Macroeconomics, wrote in a note to clients, “The surge in core inflation in October marks the start of a run of big gains, thanks to surging used auto prices, rebounding airline fares, and faster increases in housing costs. We think core inflation will peak at almost 7% in March, which will pose a serious challenge to the Fed&amp;#39;s benign medium-term view. Chair [Jerome] Powell will have to convince markets that the combination of rocketing payrolls and soaring inflation does not threaten the transitory story, to which he appears still to be committed. We remain of the view that the Fed will start to hike in September, but a June hike can&amp;#39;t be ruled out. If labor participation shows no sign of life by the March FOMC meeting, we expect the Fed to accelerate the taper and then hike in June. This would play badly across all asset markets.” As always, it is important to acknowledge and understand the risks present in the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Boeing (BA) surged after the company said it was “hopeful” China would resume order of the 737 Max two years after its grounding.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;U.S. crude oil output from the Permian Basin of West Texas and New Mexico is set to jump to a record 4.95 million barrels per day in December, a new government forecast showed on Monday. This would bring production in the key U.S. shale patch well above its pre-pandemic average from March 2020.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of oat-milk maker Oatly (OTLY) fell more than 20% after missing earnings expectations and cutting guidance. The stock is down roughly 50% since IPO back in late-May.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Snap (SNAP) were up after the company reached a deal with Sony Music Entertainment to allow the company to use its artist and sounds on the Snapchat App.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Twitter Inc said on Monday it will expand free access to the social networking site&amp;#39;s data to help software developers create tools and products that could promote safer online conversations or curate content. The move is part of Twitter&amp;#39;s growing effort over the past year to decentralize the company, a vision that aims to give users more control over what content they see in their Twitter feed or have new ways of sharing content on the site, Amir Shevat, Twitter&amp;#39;s head of product for the developer platform, said in an interview.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amazon.com Inc has reached a deal to sell virtual medical services to Hilton Hotels in the United States, one of the first major customers for the company’s burgeoning healthcare business. Amazon Care is an on-demand health offering that lets users message or video-chat clinicians and receive home visits in some cities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UK ministers are expected to order an in-depth investigation of Nvidia Corp&amp;#39;s planned $40 billion acquisition of British chip designer ARM over antitrust and national security concerns. As a huge NVDA bull, hope all goes well!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Finance Tech (SOFI) announced an offering of 50 million shares. The stock is down as a result. Not surprising for management to take advantage of this massive runup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of oat-meal maker Oatly (OTLY) gapped down -20% after missing earnings expectations and cutting guidance moving forward. After a promising start, the stock is now roughly -50% since its IPO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current stock price was written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AutoDesk (ADSK) target raised by Mizuho from $350 to $380 at Buy. Stock currently around $326&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Broadcom (AVGO) target raised by Argus from $560 to $620 at Buy. Stoick currently around $565&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coupang (CPNG) target raised by Mizuho from $32 to $40 at Overweight. Stock currently around $28&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salesforce (CRM) target raised by Mizuho from $320 to $360 at Buy. Stock currently around $305&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crowdstrike (CRWD) target raised by Mizuho from $330 to $360 at Buy. Stock was also downgraded by Morgan Stanley to $250, so there are competing perspectives here&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intuit (INTU) target raised by Morgan Stanley from $615 to $715 at Overweight. Stock currently around $626&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MasterCard (MA) target raised by Mizuho from $50 to $465 at Buy. Stock currently around $360&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Netflix (NFLX) target raised by KeyCorp from $690 to $725 at Overweight. Stock currently around $680&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NVIDIA (NVDA) with three target raises. Stock currently around $300

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Citigroup from $223 to $350 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robert W Baird from $240 to $360 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UBS Group from $230 to $350 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Palo Alto Networks (PANW) with three target raises. Stock currently around $518

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mizuho from $560 to $625 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deutsche Bank from $560 to $605 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Royal Bank of Canada from $560 to $590 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roblox (RBLX) target raised by BTIG Research from $98 to $133 at Buy. Stock currently around $108&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Signature Bank (SBNY) target raised by Raymond James from $360 at $400 at Outperform. Stock currently around $321&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snowflake (SNOW) target raised by Mizuho from  $340 to $450 at Buy. Stock currently around $393&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Finance Tech (SOFI) target raised by Mizuho from $28 to $30 at Buy. Stock currently around $22&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Valero Energy (VLO) target raised by Wells Fargo from $102 to $106 at Overweight. Stock currently around $77&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Don&amp;#39;t judge each day by the harvest you reap but by the seeds that you plant.&amp;quot; -Robert Louis Stevenson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Metaverse: 下一個最大的機會]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是90年代末的互聯網，2000年代的社交媒體，以及數字媒體。
2010年代的數字貨幣（加密貨幣）。Facebook的Metaverse可能是其中的一個。
2020年代最大的投資機會之一。如果你正在關注Facebook的
Connect 2021會議，你會意識到Facebook現在有多深...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quvg93/metaverse_next_biggest_opportunity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quvg93/metaverse_next_biggest_opportunity/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the internet in the late ’90s, social media in the 2000s, and digital currency (crypto) in the 2010s. Facebook’s Metaverse might be one of the greatest investment opportunities in the 2020s. If you are following Facebook’s Connect 2021 conference you will realize how much deep Facebook now Meta has invested in the platform. They own Oculus which is the first step towards VR/AR metaverse. The application of Metaverse based platforms is immense and beyond gaming and virtually every aspect of our lives. Here are some of the potential companies to benefit from:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unity Software: Virtually all applications will be developed either on Unity or Unreal Engine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Autodesk: They own 3D Max and Maya which again might be used to develop VR/AR applications. Plus they have various Building Information Modelling tools like Revit and Navisworks which might be useful in creating Metaverse beyond gaming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Matterport: 3D scanning &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trimble: Again they have Sketchup and various 3D scanning tools&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shopify and Amazon: They might be the first ones to create virtual stores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft: They own Minecraft and have developed ‘Hololens’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roblox: The platform already works with Oculus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me know if there are any other key players which I have missed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我令人沮喪的投資故事。今天我把大部分的東西都拿出來了，90天的禁令，我有一段時間不會回來了。Gg市場。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qul0k6/my_depressing_investment_story_today_i_took_most/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qul0k6/my_depressing_investment_story_today_i_took_most/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[火箭實驗室（RKLB）將收購行星系統公司。]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation

看起來火箭實驗室正在繼續嘗試縱向創新。這聽起來
對投資者來說是個好消息，特別是在他們已經購買了Advanced
解決方案公司之後...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qurofj/rocket_lab_rklb_to_acquire_planetary_systems_corp/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qurofj/rocket_lab_rklb_to_acquire_planetary_systems_corp/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation&quot;&gt;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like Rocket Lab is continuing to try to vertically innovate. This sounds like good news for investors especially after they already bought Advanced Solutions Inc earlier this year. These two acquisitions along with recent talks of selling rocket hardware to other companies look promising.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[管理是一個公司最重要的部分之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看到很多新的投資者都在關注FCF的內在價值、利潤或創新。
這些都很重要，但其中一個最重要的因素卻被忽略了。
往往被忽略了。

強大的管理將是你的大部分回報。如果首席執行官做出錯誤的決定
特別是在市場上......。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/queyas/management_is_one_of_the_most_important_parts_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/queyas/management_is_one_of_the_most_important_parts_of/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:38:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I see a lot of new investors looking at FCF intrisnic value, profits or innovation. which is all important but one of the most important factors is mostly overlooked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;strong management is going to be most of ur returns. If the CEO makes bad decisions u will become a bagholder. especialy in market downturns Reits or commodity&amp;#39;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best Example is Elon Musk is able to sell almost a million cars withour spending money on ads without Elon Musk tesla would be at 10/20% of their market cap max. If the company didnt go bankrupt. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ivanhoe has a legendairy CEO in mining and the company preforms well and has amazing assets. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes its better to sit on the sideline even if a stock is dirt cheap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;wereldhave has been cheap for years with an 10% dividend and even 20% for a while with a lot of intrisic value but did cut the dividend time and time again took huge losses and still holds bad assets. -80% of their peak and it use to be a large cap stock on the AEX/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intel was unable to preform with the rest of the market but when a new ceo comes he invest billions and claims the company holds a lot of tech which shows how weak management was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IBM used to be a leader but focussed on share buybacks insted of innovating. sold assets and tech cheap and the best parts. use to be one of the biggest tech companys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are countless examples of weak managment destroying share value in a small company 1 or 2 bad decisions can bankrupt the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;when looking at a stock look at management experience look at the board and insider ownership before u even touch the stock&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[挑選個別股票的理由]]></title><description><![CDATA[你挑選個人股票的理由是什麼？

除了試圖戰勝市場，還有其他原因嗎？

所有的研究表明，這真的很難做到，而那麼多人仍然選擇手工挑選股票。
選擇手工挑選股票，我真的想知道原因是什麼。

這是一個真實的問題，我並不是想...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quh9ag/reasons_to_pick_individual_stocks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quh9ag/reasons_to_pick_individual_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 02:08:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What are your reasons to pick individual stocks? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is there any other reason then to try to beat the market?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With all the research showing it’s really hard to do and so many people still choosing to hand pick stocks I was really wondering what are the reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a real question I am not trying to dismiss any market strategy. I am just curious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[火箭實驗室（RKLB）將收購行星系統公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation

看起來火箭實驗室正在繼續嘗試縱向創新。這聽起來
對投資者來說是個好消息，特別是在他們已經購買了Advanced
解決方案公司之後...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qurnf4/rocket_lab_rklb_to_acquire_planetary_systems/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qurnf4/rocket_lab_rklb_to_acquire_planetary_systems/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 02:08:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation&quot;&gt;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211115006228/en/Rocket-Lab-to-Acquire-Space-Hardware-Company-Planetary-Systems-Corporation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looks like Rocket Lab is continuing to try to vertically innovate. This sounds like good news for investors especially after they already bought Advanced Solutions Inc earlier this year. These two acquisitions along with recent talks of selling rocket hardware to other companies look promising.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[多少纔算夠？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qurk7o/how_much_is_enough/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qurk7o/how_much_is_enough/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 01:14:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我分析了$PLTR，所以你不必去分析。]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好，我一直看到很多人在談論$PLTR，所以今天我
決定分析一下$PLTR，也就是Palantir。我還分析了其他
公司，所以請隨時查看我的個人資料，瞭解其他的股票分析!

對於那些不知道的人來說，Palantir是一家軟件公司，...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quqjjj/i_analyzed_pltr_so_you_dont_have_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quqjjj/i_analyzed_pltr_so_you_dont_have_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 01:14:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone, I’ve been seeing a lot of people talk about $PLTR, so today I decided to analyze $PLTR otherwise known as Palantir. I’ve also analyzed other companies, so feel free to check out my profile for other stock analysis! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those that don’t know, Palantir is a software company that specializes in big data analytics. At the time of this post, they’re sitting at about $23.33. They reported earnings for Quarter 3 on November 9th, 2021. Revenue was reported to be $392 million, which is up 35.5% from the same quarter last year, beating expectations by $5.54 million. Furthemore, in Q3 they added 34 new customers and closed 54 deals worth at least $1 million, 33 of which were at least $5 million, and 18 of which were worth at least $10 Million. For Q4, Palantir is expecting $418 Million in revenue, consensus is $401.87 Million. The CEO of PLTR, Alex Karp, said that they expect revenue to grow at a rate of 30% or more for 2021 - 2025. Now let’s discuss their valuation...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Since Palantir had a larger number of customers and government deals in Q3, they reported stronger revenue growth, However, growth did lag in comparison to other competitors who are in the same space such as Datadog and Snowflake. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Palantir demonstrated the highest value for EBITDA margins compared to other companies in the space. Adjusted free cash flow for quarter 3 was $119 Million, which was a $172 million improvement year-over-year, representing a margin of about 30%. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Despite the fact that this company looks like it’s trading at a cheap price compared to its peers, it is trading at 17 to 20x revenue multiples which means that if they happen to have a bad quarter, the stock can drop hard. However, keep in mind that they do seem to be executing pretty well since they’ve been growing the amount of deals they’ve been making with organizations and firms, Have strong revenue growth, and also have good EBITDA margins. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of this being said, Palantir may be a buy only if you believe in the company long-term. In order for Palantir to succeed, they will need to grow their commercial product offering, since they already have a good presence on the government side. Things do seem to be going well on that end though because the commercial side growth has been going up as of recently. In my opinion, this company is still trading at too high of a price, your money would be better off invested in a different tech company. Thanks for reading everyone, if you have any questions feel free to comment down below or message me directly. I’d also love to hear your comments!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EBITDA = Earnings Before Interest, Taxes, Debt, Amortization&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lucid發佈第三季度業績，預訂量爲13,000個]]></title><description><![CDATA[第三季度的客戶預訂量上升至13,000個，反映出訂單量約爲1,000個。
約13億美元，此後又增加到17,000個以上。

 * Lucid Air今天贏得了2022年MotorTrend年度汽車大獎。

 *客戶車輛在第三季度開始在Lucid的先進製造工廠生產。
   客戶車輛的生產於第三季度在Lucid位於卡薩的先進製造廠（"AMP-1"）開始。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quqg52/lucid_releases_q3_results_with_13000_reservations/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quqg52/lucid_releases_q3_results_with_13000_reservations/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 01:14:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Customer reservations rose to 13,000 in Q3, reflecting an order book of approximately $1.3B, and have since increased beyond 17,000&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lucid Air today won the 2022 MotorTrend Car of the Year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Customer vehicle production started in Q3 at Lucid&amp;#39;s Advanced Manufacturing Plant (&amp;quot;AMP-1&amp;quot;) in Casa Grande, Arizona, and the second phase of construction broke ground to add 2.85 million square feet of space&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lucid bolstered its balance sheet to close Q3 with approximately $4.8B in cash&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lucid Group, Inc. successfully listed as a public company on Nasdaq in July under the ticker symbol LCID&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Third Quarter Financial Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the third quarter of 2021, Lucid significantly strengthened its balance sheet through the closing of the de-SPAC reverse merger + PIPE, bringing approximately $4.4B onto Lucid&amp;#39;s balance sheet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Continued to invest in the business, readying production and deliveries, globalization of our retail network and adding headcount across R&amp;amp;D and SG&amp;amp;A to continue growing our core operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initiated investment in property, plant, and equipment associated with Phase 2 expansion of manufacturing, continued investment in vehicle program development, and ongoing expansion of retail, delivery, and service capacities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Looking forward&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We remain confident in our ability to achieve 20,000 units in 2022. This target is not without risk given ongoing challenges facing the automotive industry, with global disruptions to supply chains and logistics. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lucid-announces-third-quarter-2021-210000175.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lucid-announces-third-quarter-2021-210000175.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼市場不會很快崩潰？]]></title><description><![CDATA[對這個子（以及類似的金融子）的悲觀情緒很嚴重。我甚至不記得
我甚至不記得在COVID崩潰期間或在過去5年多的任何時候，事情都是如此消極。
過去5年多的時間裏。

提高利率將扼殺增長型股票，中國的經濟衰退是一個大問題。
巨大的威脅，通貨膨脹將扼殺我們的現金，......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qurl3z/why_wont_the_market_crash_soon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qurl3z/why_wont_the_market_crash_soon/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 01:14:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pessimism on this sub (and similar financial subs) is rampant. I don&amp;#39;t even recall things being quite this negative during the COVID crash or anytime in the last 5+ years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Raising interest rates are going to kill growth stocks, China&amp;#39;s recession is a massive threat, inflation will kill our cash, real estate has overheated, the rug is really about to be pulled on almost all asset classes -- there&amp;#39;s really no way to financially survive the next year going off sentiment here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why won&amp;#39;t the markets tank? What&amp;#39;s going to send us to DOW 40,000+ that so many people are overlooking? I&amp;#39;d love to hear what anyone might be optimistic about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lucid確認2022年730億美元的公司只有可憐的2萬輛汽車]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lucid在數小時後證實，它將爲2022年生產2萬輛汽車。一個730億美元的
的公司!

一個小小的比較。大衆集團是市值的兩倍。它每天生產20,000輛汽車
天。不是一個星期，一個月，一年。是一天。

它有近十種BEV車型在全球銷售。截至第三季度，它的電動車銷量接近54萬輛。
到第三季度...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qus535/lucid_confirms_a_pathetic_20000_cars_for_2022_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qus535/lucid_confirms_a_pathetic_20000_cars_for_2022_for/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 23:46:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lucid confirmed after hours it would produce 20,000 cars for 2022.  A $73 billion company!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A little comparison.  VW Group is double the mkt cap.  It produces 20,000 cars a day.  Not a week, a month, a year.  A day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has nearly a dozen BEV models on sale worldwide.  It sold nearly 540K EV&amp;#39;s YTD to 3Q 2021.  In 2022 it will have over 20 EV models on sale and likely surpass Tesla in EV sales and be pushing 20,000 EV&amp;#39;s a day (Tesla will stil pip it in BEV&amp;#39;s by measure - and yes PHEV&amp;#39;s do matter making lots of moolah).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;20,000 EV&amp;#39;s a day...not a year, a day.  Yet just double the mkt cap.of Lucid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry to offend, but US investors are mostly utterly clueless when it comes to global EV mkts.  BYD in China knocked out 183K EV&amp;#39;s in their third quarter alone.  Again it trades for a lowly $130 billion vs Lucid&amp;#39;s absurd mkt cap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[接受 "無法戰勝市場 "的旅程--最後一步]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在尋找一個小的確認偏見，所以這個子似乎是最好的地方
開始......。

我一直聽說你無法戰勝市場，但我無法將其與我最初的假設相協調。
我最初的假設是，50%的人一定比另外50%的人做得更好。我是說，我是
聰明吧？至少比你們一半的人聰明！...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qumaht/journey_to_cant_beat_the_market_acceptance_final/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qumaht/journey_to_cant_beat_the_market_acceptance_final/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 23:17:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m in search of a little confirmation bias so this sub seemed the best place to start...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve always heard you can&amp;#39;t beat the market but couldn&amp;#39;t reconcile that with my initial assumption that 50% must be doing better than the other 50%. I mean, I&amp;#39;m smart right? At least smarter than half of you! Then I read Bogle and all the other data showing its single digit % of investors beat the market long term. To understand this I&amp;#39;ve come to a theory that &amp;quot;The Market&amp;quot; is an optimization, not an average. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The theory: as long as society maintains stability (bigger &amp;quot;if&amp;quot; these days), the economy will grow (for reasons) and thus companies and stocks along with it. There is always churn and noise but over the long term the duds get filtered out and the studs end up making a majority of the market. Even if you&amp;#39;re picking good stocks, so is the broader market. That makes it hard to beat when the market also has your winners every time. It also has mostly winners and very few losers so if you happen to pick one bad stock you can easily get crushed vs the index. The market is continually optimizing so the effort and reward for trying to beat it are not justified. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This concludes my surface level, non-economist, inexperienced justification for why I consolidated everything into SNDL...j/k, it starts with a V. Please destroy my optimization theory so I can learn about a hammer candle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[自2016年初以來，WeWork的淨虧損總額達134億美元。它今天的市值爲70億美元。$WE]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460261845818920970</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460261845818920970</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 22:41:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿里巴巴，軟趴趴的小弟弟模式要豎起來了！!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qupfzp/alibaba_limp_dick_pattern_bout_to_erect/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qupfzp/alibaba_limp_dick_pattern_bout_to_erect/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 22:41:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I 債券與高收益儲蓄賬戶的應急基金對比]]></title><description><![CDATA[我已經嘗試以分析的方式來處理以下決定，但我想看看其他人是否有類似的決定，或者是否可以幫助我。
別人是否有類似的決定，或者能否看到我的盲點。

我有一個相當高的儲蓄率，討厭讓我的錢在低效率的情況下工作。
效率低下。我的儲蓄越多，我就能越快地達到財務目標。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qula33/i_bonds_vs_high_yield_savings_account_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qula33/i_bonds_vs_high_yield_savings_account_for/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 22:25:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve tried approaching the following decision analytically but am checking if others have experienced similar decisions or can see any of my blind spots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a pretty high savings rate and hate to leave my dollars working inefficiently. The more I save, the quicker I can reach financial independence. In my 20’s I’ve stayed in 100% stocks and have not purchased any bonds. I have a pretty tough skin and risk tolerance and didn’t even consider selling during the short 2020 market crash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I also understand the importance of an emergency fund. I started with around $10,000 in an Ally savings account and have increased it up to $25,000 over the past few years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More recently, I’ve considered putting most of my emergency fund into I-bonds. I understand they are less liquid than a savings account but in the long run will be less affected by inflation. Looking at historic rates, they almost always are at least 1-2% higher than a high yield savings account.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/agSHRni&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/a/agSHRni&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pro to an online savings account is only liquidity and money available within a few days. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From what I can tell about I-bonds the pros and cons are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pros:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Higher Inflation Protected Interest Rates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Locked up for 1 year from time of purchase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forfeit 3 months interest if redeemed within 5 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Limited to $10,000 purchased per year &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;May take longer to redeem in an emergency &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I can deal with all of the cons in my current situation. If I purchase 10k this year and 10k towards the end of next year I could limit my exposure to liquidity issues. My plan would be to buy 10k this December, bring my emergency fund savings account back to 20k by next December, then buy 10k more. At that point I would have 20k in I-bonds and 10k in a savings account. Ideally for small emergencies I wouldn’t even have to touch the I-bonds. Even sacrificing 3 months of interest after 1 year I would still be ahead relative to a high yield savings account. 9 months at an I bond rate beats 12 months at current savings accounts rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the short term, 15k liquidity is plenty. I have a local safety net and could both cover a 6-month lease liability ($3750) and the maximum out of pocket for health insurance ($6500). Worst case I could also move back in with parents and just pay for partial utilities and food. My current industry also has a pretty high demand so it wouldn’t be difficult to get another similar paying job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my main concerns is how difficult it is in practice to redeem I-bonds. Could I put a large emergency expense on a credit card, cash in the same amount of electronic I-bonds the same day, and be able to pay off the credit card within 3 weeks?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Oatly股價在盈利後下跌20%，預計2022年收入減少。]]></title><description><![CDATA[第三季度的一些亮點。

 * 收入爲1.711億美元，比去年同期的1.147億美元增長49.2%。
   收入爲1.711億美元，比上年同期的1.147億美元增長49.2%。
 * 淨虧損總額爲4120萬美元，或每股7美分，此前虧損爲10.4美元
   去年虧損1040萬美元，或每股2美分。
 * 毛利潤爲4490萬美元，或每股1美分。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qukktc/oatly_shares_down_20_after_earnings_expecting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qukktc/oatly_shares_down_20_after_earnings_expecting/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 21:20:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some third quarter highlights:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue of $171.1 million, a 49.2% increase compared to $114.7 million in the prior year period&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Net losses totaled $41.2 million, or 7 cents per share, after a loss of $10.4 million, or 2 cents per share, last year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gross profit of $44.9 million, or a 26.2% gross profit margin, compared to $36.0 million, or a 31.3% gross profit margin, in the prior year period&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone looking at OTLY under $10? Honestly I&amp;#39;m not surprised by this, I already thought at $8B OTLY was pretty richly valued anyways but now it&amp;#39;s hit a new ATL of under $10. Is OTLY worth it around $5.65B valuation to anyone here? I think their oat milk sells well personally and I&amp;#39;ve seen them grow but I&amp;#39;m hesitant to invest in any vegan food companies long term. Might think about trading OTLY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What does anyone think of it at it&amp;#39;s new low? Is it heading towards $8?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[投資新手，這是個好策略嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我對投資知之甚少。我現在20歲出頭，由於有學習障礙
我懷疑我是否會成爲投資高手。然而，我聽說過
指數基金的好事情，因爲它的結果好，而且進入門檻低。這是否是一個
儘可能多地工作，並將大量資金投入指數基金，這是不是一個好主意？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qucy8u/new_to_investing_is_this_a_good_strategy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qucy8u/new_to_investing_is_this_a_good_strategy/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 20:31:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know very little about investing. I am in my early 20s and due to a learning disability I doubt I will ever become good at it. I have however heard good thing about index funds due to good results and low barrier of entry. Is it a good idea to work as much as I can and put a lot of it into an index fund and then just let it stay for 40-50 years or so? At least that has been my understanding of it so far on this subreddit. Is there something I am missing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如何對沖目前最壞的情況？]]></title><description><![CDATA[假設恆大違約，使中國陷入衰退。
衰退。美元要麼惡性通貨膨脹，要麼FED提高利率。
槓桿投資者出逃，市場崩潰，歐洲市場緊隨其後。

我不確定這是否可行，我的投資之旅纔剛剛開始......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qumlsi/how_to_hedge_against_the_current_worst_case/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qumlsi/how_to_hedge_against_the_current_worst_case/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 20:09:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s say that hypothetically, Evergrande defaults, putting China in a recession. The USD either hyperinflates or the FED increases interest rates, leveraged investors bail and the markets crash, European markets follow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not sure how feasible this is, i&amp;#39;ve only started my investment journey one year ago. But for argument sake let&amp;#39;s assume that whatever is the current worst projection becomes a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How does a retail investor react to this type of situation?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My portfolio consists mostly of a world index (MSCI World, &lt;a href=&quot;https://IWDA.AS&quot;&gt;IWDA.AS&lt;/a&gt;), small ammount of s&amp;amp;p500 Healthcare sector and a bit of crypto.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[是否有任何股票持有指數基金作爲其唯一的資產？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的國家（愛爾蘭）對所有ETF和其他一般基金每8年徵收41%的未實現收益稅。
其他一般的基金，這對我的複利有非常大的影響。
這對我計劃的持有期（70年）有非常大的影響，因此我正在尋找一種方法來購買
儘可能地與VWCE和QQQ密切相關的東西......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quen21/is_there_any_stock_that_holds_an_index_fund_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/quen21/is_there_any_stock_that_holds_an_index_fund_as/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 20:09:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My country (Ireland) taxes unrealized gains at 41% every 8 years on all ETFs and other funds in general, which has a very dramatic effect on compounding for my planned holding period (70 years), therefore I&amp;#39;m looking for a way to buy something as closely correlated as possible to VWCE and QQQ through stocks which would only be cost me 33% capital gains upon selling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m aware some companies like Berkshire are so diversified they are said to track total market ETfs fairly well (I think brk:b has a .66 correlation, but it depends on the time period obviously, with the correlation going quite negative at times) nevertheless I would rather a company that passively holds an index fund for several reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[通貨膨脹是否影響你的投資習慣？]]></title><description><![CDATA[很好奇人們是否在增加他們的投資金額或重新平衡向
債券，或採取其他什麼（如果有的話）緩解通貨膨脹的措施。
你正在採取的措施。

我在我的個人經紀中基本上是直接使用VT，在我的退休賬戶中使用目標日期。
退休賬戶。我只是在我的個人經紀業務中保持不變......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/quib2b/is_inflation_affecting_your_investing_habits/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/quib2b/is_inflation_affecting_your_investing_habits/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 19:50:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Curious if folks are increasing their investment amounts or rebalancing toward bonds with their contributions or what other (if any) inflation mitigating steps you&amp;#39;re taking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m basically straight VT in my personal brokerage and target-dates in my retirement accounts. Just staying the course in my retirement accounts. For my personal brokerage thus far I&amp;#39;ve stuck with just VT contributions but I&amp;#39;ve upped my monthly contributions significantly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still have about $30K surplus getting ate away at the bank set-aside for a car purchase, but with interest rates being what they are it seems smarter just to finance it (especially if money is losing value). Probably will end up dumping it all into VT but wondering what others are doing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉跌破1萬億美元市值]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-drops-below-1-trillion-market-cap-154047937.html

上週末，首席執行官埃隆-馬斯克說他可以出售更多的股票，在許多人看來
作爲對參議員伯尼-桑德斯(Bernie Sanders)一條推文的非彩色迴應。

馬斯克上週出售了約69億美元的股票，使股票...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qujwyc/tesla_drops_below_1_trillion_market_cap/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qujwyc/tesla_drops_below_1_trillion_market_cap/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 19:12:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-drops-below-1-trillion-market-cap-154047937.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-drops-below-1-trillion-market-cap-154047937.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the weekend CEO Elon Musk said he could sell more stock, in what many saw as an off-color response to a tweet from Senator Bernie Sanders. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Musk sold about $6.9 billion in shares last week, sending the stock price lower. Tesla shares are down more than 15% over the last five sessions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seem Elon will keep selling Telsa stocks this week to finish his 10% goal. Investors can start a small position this week under 1k as tesla is still the industry leader and very far ahead for many competitors. If the stock really drop back to $900, then it could consider to add more position.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[裏維安是世界上第三大汽車製造商（至少按市值計算）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://companiesmarketcap.com/automakers/largest-automakers-by-market-cap/

你可以爭論其中哪些是汽車製造商（特斯拉？
我不想在這裏再次討論這個問題。但這實在是太瘋狂了。這意味着什麼呢？
電動車泡沫？購買大衆汽車？賣掉所有的東西，遠離...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qukm4y/rivian_is_the_third_largest_automaker_in_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qukm4y/rivian_is_the_third_largest_automaker_in_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 18:53:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://companiesmarketcap.com/automakers/largest-automakers-by-market-cap/&quot;&gt;https://companiesmarketcap.com/automakers/largest-automakers-by-market-cap/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can argue which of these are automakers (Tesla?), and I don&amp;#39;t want to start a discussion about this here again. But this is just crazy. What does it mean? EV bubble? Buy Volkswagen? Sell everything and keep off the market?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full disclosure, I have shares of BYD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[股票大戰!]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，Reddit! 我和一個朋友正在進行一場 "股票大戰"，從聖誕節那天開始。
我們都在用100美元，要到學年結束時，有一個小問題。
我不知道我在做什麼，希望能得到任何幫助! 任何人都可以
自由加入，在今年年底我和我的朋友將...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtvis8/stock_battle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtvis8/stock_battle/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 18:53:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey Reddit! A friend and I are having a &amp;quot;stock battle&amp;quot; starting Christmas day, were both using 100$ and going to the end of the school year, one small problem, I have no idea what I&amp;#39;m doing and would love any help I can get! Anyone can feel free to join, at the end of the year my friend and I will be comparing our (hopefully) profits. whoever makes the most wins!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我想出了一個減緩通貨膨脹的解決方案。

我們都應該停止購買這麼多東西 https://t.co/pxq6EmUwAr]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460247607008182273</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460247607008182273</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 18:41:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[順便說一下，集裝箱費用剛剛從2500美元跳到25000美元。我們剛剛取消了今年餘下時間的所有訂單，這樣我們就不會賠錢。在那裏，我們的生活會變得很瘋狂。好運]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quh1r8/fyi_container_costs_just_jumped_from_2500_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quh1r8/fyi_container_costs_just_jumped_from_2500_to/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 17:29:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[簽出伊隆吧，拜託]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quida5/just_sign_out_elon_pls/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quida5/just_sign_out_elon_pls/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 17:29:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[隨船倒下]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quaw1q/down_with_the_ship/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/quaw1q/down_with_the_ship/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 16:21:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vanguard的年終基金分配初步估計將於今天（2021年11月15日）公佈]]></title><description><![CDATA[到今天早上檢查時還沒有，但今天會出來。見第三項
列表中的第三項。

初步的年終萬科基金分配估算
[https://advisors.vanguard.com/tax-center/tax-season-calendar/current-year]]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/quh2so/vanguards_preliminary_yearend_fund_distribution/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/quh2so/vanguards_preliminary_yearend_fund_distribution/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 15:53:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not yet available as of this morning&amp;#39;s check, but due out today.  See third item in list:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://advisors.vanguard.com/tax-center/tax-season-calendar/current-year&quot;&gt;Preliminary year-end Vanguard fund distribution estimates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[IDC報告稱，半導體行業將在2022年中期實現正常化和平衡，2023年有可能出現產能過剩。]]></title><description><![CDATA[國際數據公司預計，半導體市場在2021年將增長17.3%，而2020年爲10.8%。
2021年將增長17.3%，而2020年爲10.8%。據IDC稱，該行業將看到
到2022年中期，行業將實現正常化和平衡，並有可能出現
隨着大規模的產能擴張開始，2023年有可能出現產能過剩...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qu5pfc/semiconductor_industry_will_see_normalization_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qu5pfc/semiconductor_industry_will_see_normalization_and/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 13:20:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;International Data Corporation expects the semiconductor market to grow by 17.3% in 2021 versus 10.8% in 2020. According to IDC, the industry will see normalization and balance by the middle of 2022, with a potential for overcapacity in 2023 as larger scale capacity expansions begin to come online towards the end of 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=prAP48247621&quot;&gt;https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=prAP48247621&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼在需求增加的情況下，銅價仍然下跌？]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以最近銅價下跌，儘管人們對金屬的短缺感到擔憂。
金屬的短缺。儘管對它的需求很大，但價格仍在波動，整個情況非常混亂。
整個情況是相當混亂的。這讓我感到有些困惑，因爲我
我認爲，如果需求很高，而生產者正在努力爭取......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qudym9/why_do_copper_prices_still_go_down_despite_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qudym9/why_do_copper_prices_still_go_down_despite_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 13:20:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So recently copper prices went down despite the concerns about the shortage of the metal. Despite the great demand for it, prices are still volatile and the whole situation is pretty messy tbh. It’s somewhat confusing to me because I thought that if the demand is high and producers are struggling to comply, then the prices should go up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also thinking if my worries are warranted, especially since I have some copper stocks in my portfolio and I made investments recently too, placing some money in juniors. I know they’re a pretty risky investment, but I always remind myself to invest money I am willing t&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of them is Oroco Resources (ORRCF) which recently uncovered extensive copper deposits. The drilling activities that commenced in their&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.orocoresourcecorp.com/projects/santo-tomas/&quot;&gt; Santo Tomas Project&lt;/a&gt; confirmed the presence of polymetallic copper mineralization. They hold 100% interest in two contiguous mineral concessions in Guerrero, Mexico which are included in their project in Xochipala.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also placed some on&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.threevalleycopper.com/&quot;&gt; Three Valley Copper&lt;/a&gt; (TVC) since they’re pretty much on a roll recently. They will start mining next month or in early 2022 and are expected to have an annual production between 13,000 and 16,000 tonnes of copper cathode by 2023. The company recently announced an upsize with a recent deal financing to $16 million due to investor demand. Also just last month they released their second quarter results where they were able to mine 178,105 tonnes of ore at a grade of 0.50%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now I’m going to hold back from investing despite the price dip because I’m pretty anxious because of the whole situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[請爸爸不要再傷害我了]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtwxkm/plz_papa_dont_hurt_me_no_more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtwxkm/plz_papa_dont_hurt_me_no_more/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 11:39:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我終於添加了債券!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我設立了一個賬戶，購買了1000美元的I類債券。這甚至不是我財富的百分之一
財富的百分之一，它主要是爲了最終成爲應急基金。我覺得這是個
一個好的生活選擇。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qu6uo8/i_finally_added_bonds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qu6uo8/i_finally_added_bonds/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 11:26:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I set up a account and purchased $1000 in I bonds.
It isn&amp;#39;t even a percent of my wealth and it&amp;#39;s mainly to eventually become an emergency fund. I feel like it&amp;#39;s a good life choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[雜草可能是下一個競選對象]]></title><description><![CDATA[似乎我們一直在進行的輪換的最後階段，從價值股開始，到SPAC的巨型抽水機結束。
價值型股票，最後是SPACs的巨型泵，收入爲零的公司*cough
裏維安*，以及雜草叢生。

催化劑

有傳言說，南卡羅來納州的梅斯議員（R）正在提出一項法案，以使大麻在聯邦範圍內合法化。
大麻在聯邦的合法化...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qu13sv/weed_could_run_next/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qu13sv/weed_could_run_next/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 10:38:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seems towards the end of the rotations we&amp;#39;ve been having starting with value stocks and ending with mega pumps from SPACs, companies with zero revenue *cough Rivian*, and weed stonks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Catalyst&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rumor has it, that Rep. Mace (R) from SC is proposing a bill to legalize Marijuana at the Federal level. &amp;quot;Those who’ve &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-12/republicans-pot-bill-to-propose-lower-taxes-more-state-control&quot;&gt;seen&lt;/a&gt; Mace’s draft say it would regulate cannabis more like alcohol&amp;quot;. This bill coming from the republican side may garner more support than Sen. Schumer&amp;#39;s already proposed bill. &amp;quot; Mace’s proposed excise tax is 3.75%, according to Cobb -- a fraction of the 25.5% that Schumer’s legislation would put on marijuana products.&amp;quot; Personally, I&amp;#39;ve heard this bill could be brought forward as early as Monday 11/15. But, that&amp;#39;s just chatter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Well, which dank stock should I buy?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve looked at various companies and honestly diversifying into a few may be worth it. However, I have the greatest conviction in &lt;strong&gt;$TLRY&lt;/strong&gt; the largest market share in Canada, Germany, and ties to the US with Sweetwater brewing. Those with the greatest dependence on the US may outperform. But, screw the fundamentals because that&amp;#39;s not how this market works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*for simplicity I&amp;#39;ll just illustrate $TLRY to represent the Marijuana sector since it has the largest market cap*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Institutions buying $420M+?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In general, Institutions have been buying these Cannabis companies as they blew off earlier in the year. Heaviest buying has been in $TLRY with the heaviest selling in $SNDL. Interestingly most of the buys come during Q2 which means most of these institutional apes are holding some serious bags. They could be down anywhere from -4% to -33% depending on when they bought in Q2. So, don&amp;#39;t be surprised if this gets pumped and ultimately dumped to lighten their bags.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/n0904d0bzmz71.png?width=2386&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=fb69d29fe355abc07e40a01cc412993d9f8b3b3b&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/n0904d0bzmz71.png?width=2386&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=fb69d29fe355abc07e40a01cc412993d9f8b3b3b&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leaders in the Sector?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$ACB&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;$SNDL&lt;/strong&gt; currently lead the move upward as they are right at their 200-day moving average. Does that mean they&amp;#39;ll continue leading the way? I don&amp;#39;t know. Does that mean the others have more to run? I can&amp;#39;t see the future, you twit. As a result, diversifying in this sector might be the way to go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Crayons&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It appears &lt;strong&gt;$TLRY&lt;/strong&gt; has started to round out and will try to push hire. The green lines are historical supply/demand lines at candle closes. I&amp;#39;m setting my stop near the recent low of $9.98 and will continue to sell out starting at $15.50 to $30.00 for a gain close to between 20% and 130%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/cssq7ipczmz71.png?width=2712&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=80aa4805f62ae8a139a233ae266c836122544bd9&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/cssq7ipczmz71.png?width=2712&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=80aa4805f62ae8a139a233ae266c836122544bd9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social Traction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another reason I am choosing to look at &lt;strong&gt;$TLRY&lt;/strong&gt; is because of all the weed stocks, &lt;strong&gt;$TLRY&lt;/strong&gt; gains the most attention on google trends and is the 2nd most mentioned on WSB behind &lt;strong&gt;$SNDL.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Positions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I literally have none and plan on buying Monday with any of you that like the stock(s). I&amp;#39;ll update after buys are in. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*This is literally my uneducated, unlicensed opinion. Don&amp;#39;t listen to me. You&amp;#39;ll Lose money\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果人們在經紀人停止購買GME時感到憤怒，那麼，如果股票市場崩潰，普通投資者無法賣出，會發生什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我剛剛聽了一個投資顧問的播客，他說他和他的客戶都是做多股票的。
他說他和他的客戶都是做多股票的，而且他們都有止損單，以防崩盤。
以防出現崩潰。隨着市場的上漲，他們會提高止損價格。

然而，我想知道，如果市場關閉，這將如何運作，或...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qu188u/if_people_were_angry_when_brokers_halted_gme_buys/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qu188u/if_people_were_angry_when_brokers_halted_gme_buys/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 06:31:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was just listening to a podcast with an investment advisor who said that he and his clients are all long equities and they have stop loss orders placed in case of a crash. As the market goes up they raise their stop price. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I was wondering how this would work if the market is closed, or if the circuit breakers kick in, and when the market re-opens the prices are all well below their limit/stop price. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, lets say the Dow closes at 36,000 and some terrible news event occurs overnight there might be no way people would be able to exit their positions at 36,000. They wlll have to sell after the market opens right? And the market wil open much lower than 36,000.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, if word gets out that certain investors were able to sell, while retail investors were unable to get their orders filled this could lead to a full scale revolt. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is this concern legitimate, or are their controls in place to prevent retail investors from getting hosed while the well connected all exit their long positions?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[等待恆大崩盤。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qu77t9/waiting_for_the_evergrande_collapse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qu77t9/waiting_for_the_evergrande_collapse/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 06:00:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能爲80萬億美元的市值創造機會。凱西-伍德是在扯皮嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA["我們假設在未來10年內，人工智能將在企業軟件領域帶來30億美元的市值機會。
在企業軟件領域提供30美元的市值機會。
萬億美元，"這位明星股民在上個月的米爾肯研究所會議上說。
他在上個月的米爾肯研究所會議上說。"我們的新數字是80美元...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtxork/ai_to_create_opportunity_for_an_80_trillion/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtxork/ai_to_create_opportunity_for_an_80_trillion/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 04:59:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We were assuming that in the next 10 years, artificial intelligence would deliver, in the enterprise software space, a market cap opportunity of $30 trillion,” the star stockpicker said at a Milken Institute conference last month. “Our new number is $80 trillion.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-wood-just-called-technology-140000074.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-wood-just-called-technology-140000074.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is an interesting use of terminology.  “Market cap” is the market value of a publicly-traded company&amp;#39;s outstanding shares.  Therefore, I’m to take it that AI is an opportunity for a single company to be worth 80T. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alphabet is one of the leaders in the AI space; at an almost $2T market cap, they would need to grow 45% YoY over the next 10 years to hit 80T.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost any other company in the world would need significantly more growth to get to $80T. No one would have thought APPL would be a $2.5T company 10 years ago when they were $335b, but to get there was a 20% YoY growth from 2011 -&amp;gt; 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where is she pulling this info from? How can she justify these claims?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are your thoughts? Do you see the possibility of an $80T company in 10 years? Will it come from AI?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在DCA-ing進入高度分散的ETF時，是否有每月的市場週期模式可以使用？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我每個月都要到VWRA（如果你在美國，就想VT）進行DCA-ing，我想知道是否有特定的日子，可以在那裏進行Standing。
我想知道是否有一個特定的日子，據統計，那裏的價格是最低的？
最低？

我在問自己，如果有很多人在同一天進行DCA，是否會對價格產生影響？
對價格的影響。我可以想象有一些模式，並且是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qtphhb/are_there_monthly_market_cycle_patterns_that_i/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qtphhb/are_there_monthly_market_cycle_patterns_that_i/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 04:59:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am DCA-ing into VWRA (think VT if you are in the US) every month and am wondering if there is a specific day where statistically the price is the lowest?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was asking myself if a lot of people DCA-ing at the same day would have an impact on price. I can imagine there being some patterns and was wondering if anyone has ever done this analysis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe it&amp;#39;s the last days of the month because people have to sell to cover bills etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or it&amp;#39;s on any of Mondays in a month because ... everyone hates Mondays and that affects buying pressure ...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>