<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 22:39:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[下一個 "雲計算 "是什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[5-10年前投資於雲計算會讓你成爲多個包子。

我的意思不是說下一步什麼會取代雲計算，而是在你看來
觀點，下一個像這樣的利基領域將在未來5-10年內爆發出來
5-10年內爆發？

電動汽車顯然是熱門話題，對...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw71tf/what_is_the_next_cloud_computing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw71tf/what_is_the_next_cloud_computing/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 21:29:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investing in cloud computing 5-10 years ago would&amp;#39;ve made you multiple baggers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t literally mean what will replace cloud computing next, but in your opinion, what is the next niche area like this that will explode over the next 5-10 years?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Electric vehicles are obviously the hot topic right now but I am just not in on that bandwagon, so I&amp;#39;m curious to hear what y&amp;#39;all think could be next?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not even looking to hear about specific stocks just the industry but feel free to share those as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天賣掉了AMC--這很傷人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這其實更像是一種咆哮/感嘆，所以如果你不想聽，請隨意。
繼續滾動。

總之，我在2020年向AMC投入500美元，希望在1-2年內獲得6-7倍的回報。
幸運的是，這成爲了紀念性的股票之一，並飆升至70美元。
我很高興能成爲運動的一部分，我...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qw5q85/sold_amc_today_this_hurts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qw5q85/sold_amc_today_this_hurts/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 21:13:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is really more of a rant/lament, so if you don&amp;#39;t want to hear it, feel free to keep scrolling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyhow, I put $500 into AMC back in 2020 hoping for a 6-7x return in 1 - 2 yrs. As luck would have it, this became one of the meme stocks and it shot up to $70. Excited to be part of the movement, I hung on, joined the AMC stock forum and stayed in as it dipped back down and down. But it&amp;#39;s just gotten to a point where it doesn&amp;#39;t make responsible sense for me to keep it anymore in hopes of another price surge up to $60 and beyond, when the last few months&amp;#39; price surges only go up ~$40 and I&amp;#39;m sitting on ~14x and have real life bills to pay, including a major medical bill. So, I bit today&amp;#39;s price surge past $40 and sold, I know it was the responsible thing to do - but damn this hurts. Really wanted to be a part of the next a-p-e nation win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: so i posted here bc i figured the other forums would hate on me for selling.  I know this was the responsible thing to do, but it would&amp;#39;ve been nice to hang in there with the rest of a-p-e nation - but don&amp;#39;t have the extra $$ to be doing that right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit 2: want to add, despite my decision to sell, i think this whole memestock phenomenon is so cool and when i&amp;#39;m old with grandkids, it&amp;#39;ll be cool to look back and say that I was a part of it even for a little bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Covid投資者的湧入將如何影響下一次大的市場衰退？]]></title><description><![CDATA[自從Covid開始以來，散戶投資者的數量已經大大增加，這已經不是什麼祕密了。
當每個人都想坐上印鈔機的火車時，Covid開始了。現在的問題是
現在的問題是，所有這些投資者（他們只在有史以來最偉大的牛市中出現過）將如何？
這些投資者（他們只在歷史上最偉大的牛市之一出現過）會如何反應？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw3asn/how_will_the_influx_of_covid_investors_affect_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw3asn/how_will_the_influx_of_covid_investors_affect_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 20:53:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s no secret that the number of retail investors has increased immensely since the start of Covid, when everyone wanted on the money printing train. The question now becomes, how will all of these investors (who have only ever been around during one of the greatest bull markets in history) react to the next major downturn?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It could be tomorrow, it could be in 5 years, but I believe there&amp;#39;s going to be substantially more panic than usual when it arrives. Could be an excellent opportunity for more seasoned, rational investors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[希望他們能在市場關閉前給我答覆。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw5eog/hopefully_they_get_back_to_me_before_the_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw5eog/hopefully_they_get_back_to_me_before_the_market/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 20:40:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特在Rivian的股份，沒有銷售任何汽車，現在價值175億美元，而它自己的市值爲790億美元，儘管它到2021年第三季度銷售了140萬輛汽車。]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，在收盤時，福特的市值只有790億美元，儘管它在2021年前三季度賣出140萬輛
2021年前三個季度的汽車。它還擁有超過150,000份2022年F150 Lightening的預訂單
其2022年的F150 Lightening的預訂單，並且在10月底已經售出21,700輛Mach-E汽車。
10月份。

福特擁有1.02億股股票（它應該賣掉它們...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvybd6/fords_shares_in_rivian_thats_sells_no_cars_now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvybd6/fords_shares_in_rivian_thats_sells_no_cars_now/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 20:25:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So at close Ford&amp;#39;s mkt cap was only $79 billion, despite it selling 1.4 million cars in the first three quarters of 2021.  It also has over 150,000 pre-orders for its F150 Lightening for 2022 and had sold 21,700 Mach-E&amp;#39;s at the end of October.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ford owns 102 million shares (it should sell them sharpish at this price) worth an incredible $17.5 billion in Rivian that has sold a couple of hundred cars to employees to date. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s not absurd at all. I mean Rivian had a massive 13,000 orders at end of 3Q (giggle).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I seriously wonder how many Rivian investors know that Ford has a massive stake.  I hope it sells it very soon as a Ford shareholder.  Those funds can quickly be put to use massively outselling Rivian in BEV&amp;#39;s by even larger multiples in 2022, 2023, 2024....(basically forever).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The US stock market has genuinely lost its marbles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nvidia今天公佈盈利情況。以下是期待的內容]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nvidia將在週三收盤後公佈第三季度財報。
週三。隨着股價在歷史高點附近徘徊，它將需要一個巨大的報告來感動投資者。
巨大的報告才能打動投資者的心。Nvidia股價在週二的交易中上漲0.6%至
週二交易中的302.03美元。本月早些時候股價飆升，因爲...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvw3t4/nvidia_reports_earnings_today_heres_what_to_expect/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvw3t4/nvidia_reports_earnings_today_heres_what_to_expect/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 20:25:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nvidia is set to report third-quarter earnings results after the market closes on Wednesday. With shares hovering around record highs, it will take a blockbuster report to move the needle for investors. Nvidia stock rose 0.6% to $302.03 in Tuesday trading. Shares surged earlier this month as investors bought in on hype surrounding Nvidia’s financial prospects amid billions in investment, most notably from Facebook ‘s newly rebranded parent Meta Platforms (FB), to build a theorized next phase of the internet called the metaverse. Not even renewed scrutiny in the U.K. related to its proposed acquisition of chip designer Arm could stop the graphics card stock’s 131% year-to-date run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the third quarter, analysts polled by FactSet forecast adjusted earnings of $1.11 a share and sales of $6.82 billion. The earnings report or outlook may need to be a blowout for the stock to continue rising. Though 34 of the 43 analysts listed by FactSet have Buy or equivalent ratings, the stock’s mean price target is $280.70. Bullish analysts will either need to raise their targets or downgrade the stock if shares hold above their targets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/articles/nvidia-stock-earnings-preview-51637101805?mod=mw_latestnews&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/articles/nvidia-stock-earnings-preview-51637101805?mod=mw_latestnews&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡努和傳聞中的沃爾瑪交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[Canoo（$GOEV）今天上午上漲了23%，因爲有傳言說它已經找到了沃爾瑪作爲
的合作伙伴。這一傳言的起因是卡努公司將其總部遷至
本頓維爾，也就是沃爾瑪總部所在地。卡奴還在其收益電話會議上預告
財報電話會議上，它將爲一個不知名的公司建造一些原型。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvy3j9/canoo_and_rumored_walmart_deal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvy3j9/canoo_and_rumored_walmart_deal/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 19:44:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canoo ($GOEV) is up 23% this morning due to rumors that it has landed Walmart as a partner. This rumor started because Canoo moved its headquarter to Bentonville, the home of Walmart headquarters. Canoo also teased during its earnings call that it will be building some prototypes for an unnamed partner, which of course the internet jumped on the idea that it must be Walmart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m a little skeptical of this, since Walmart already has other car partners like Ford and Gatik. Does it make sense to add Canoo?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My thesis is that Canoo is a decent speculative stock even if it doesn&amp;#39;t have this Walmart deal. There&amp;#39;s lots of other tailwinds such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The infrastructure bill.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Canoo fills a niche that&amp;#39;s not directly competitive against Rivian or Tesla (and definitely not Lucid). For example Canoo would be great for local governments and schools which will be forced to go green and would like vehicles with low maintenance costs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The market is hungry for EV stock right now. And at sub $20 this is something people can feel good throwing a few bucks in and hold for years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Possible cons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worried that Canoo doesn&amp;#39;t manufacture it&amp;#39;s own vehicles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Canoo already had one hyped up story with the acquisition talks with Apple. If this Walmart thing go south investors will &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; hate Canoo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Possible discussion topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are there &lt;em&gt;other&lt;/em&gt; possible reasons to move to Bentonville? Perhaps that city offer huge incentives not seen elsewhere, or maybe it&amp;#39;s actually a great hub of manufacturing. Anyone in that area know?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;How does Canoo stack up against other EV &amp;quot;hype&amp;quot; stocks right now?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclosure: I bought some Canoo this morning, and I kinda like their aesthetic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Metaverse ?]]></title><description><![CDATA[整個行業是否嚴重高估了人們在視頻遊戲中花費X
時間的慾望？

我實際上看了facebook關於元的整個演示。我還參加了
其他公司目前所稱的 "元"，如Roblox。
第二人生等等。



我是不是錯過了...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvta30/metaverse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvta30/metaverse/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 18:46:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is the industry at large grossly overestimating people&amp;#39;s appetite to spend X amount of time in a video game?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I actually watched facebook&amp;#39;s entire presentation on meta. I&amp;#39;ve also been in what other companies are referring to as &amp;quot;metaverses&amp;quot; currently such as Roblox, second life etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Am I missing something here? I used to be an avid gamer myself. But my current age I dont have the mental or physical will power to play a game when I get home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m just tired as hell. Its been a drag for my significant other, since we were both avid gamers together.  But its just the reality.. I&amp;#39;m way too tired to play anything on the weekends. Luckily, I just spectate whatever she&amp;#39;s playing and I guess I get my gaming fix there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question remains though. I know my anecdotal experience isnt going to be very useful but I&amp;#39;m just wondering how everybody else feels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I saw the FB meta video, all +1 hour of it, and I just thought.. wow. Who would want to be logged into a video game with that shit on your face for multiple hours??&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it just me? Am I just an old fart?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also vaguely reminds me of the 3d movies phase as well. Everybody thought we&amp;#39;d be lining up to see these 3d movies forever but people quickly got tired of that too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[亞馬遜將停止接受在英國發行的Visa信用卡，理由是費用高昂]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 關鍵點
> 
> 亞馬遜已經告訴一些客戶，從1月19日起，該公司將不再接受
> 不再接受在英國發行的Visa信用卡。
> 
> 該電子商務巨頭以支付處理商收取的高額費用爲由。
> 
> 維薩公司表示，它 "對亞馬遜威脅要在英國使用維薩信用卡感到非常失望"。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw4ca8/amazon_to_stop_accepting_visa_credit_cards_issued/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qw4ca8/amazon_to_stop_accepting_visa_credit_cards_issued/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 18:33:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KEY POINTS&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon has told some customers that, from Jan. 19 onward, the company will no longer accept Visa credit cards issued in Britain.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The e-commerce giant cited high fees charged by the payment processor.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visa said it was “very disappointed that Amazon is threatening to restrict consumer choice in the future.”&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LONDON — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AMZN&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; plans to stop accepting payments made via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/V&quot;&gt;Visa&lt;/a&gt; credit cards issued in the U.K. starting next year.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The e-commerce giant has told some customers that, from Jan. 19 onward, the company will no longer accept Visa credit cards issued in Britain ” due to the high fees Visa charges for processing credit card transactions.”&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Visa shares fell 2.5% in U.S. premarket trading.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visa earlier this year hiked the interchange fees it charges merchants for processing digital transactions between the U.K. and the European Union.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After Brexit, an EU cap on interchange fees no longer applies in the U.K., allowing card networks to raise their charges.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/MA&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mastercard&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;has also increased its U.K.-EU interchange fees.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon customers were told they will still be able to use debit cards — including those issued by Visa — and non-Visa credit cards like Mastercard and&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AXP&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;American Express&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;. Users are being encouraged to update their default payment method ahead of the changes.&lt;/strong&gt; The news was first reported by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-17/amazon-will-stop-accepting-visa-credit-cards-issued-in-the-u-k?srnd=technology-vp&quot;&gt;Bloomberg&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Visa said it was “very disappointed that Amazon is threatening to restrict consumer choice in the future.”  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“U.K. shoppers can use their Visa debit and credit cards at Amazon U.K. today and throughout the holiday season,” a Visa spokesperson told CNBC.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We have a long-standing relationship with Amazon, and we continue to work toward a resolution, so our cardholders can use their preferred Visa credit cards at Amazon U.K. without Amazon-imposed restrictions come January 2022.”  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon blasted Visa for its high card charges. “The cost of accepting card payments continues to be an obstacle for businesses striving to provide the best prices for customers,” a spokesperson for the company told CNBC.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“These costs should be going down over time with technological advancements, but instead they continue to stay high or even rise.”&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The move could be viewed as a way for Amazon to get some bargaining power over Visa to lower its fees. The payments firm also charges businesses scheme fees to become part of its network.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While smaller retailers aren’t in a position to negotiate, Amazon — given its size — may have better luck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/amazon-to-stop-accepting-visa-credit-cards-issued-in-the-uk.html&quot;&gt;CNBC&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/finance/quote/V:NYSE&quot;&gt;Visa is down about 5%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[仍然是一顆寶石]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw1iz3/still_a_gem/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qw1iz3/still_a_gem/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 17:54:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[目前處於歷史高位。

-股票市場
-國內生產總值
-家庭淨資產
-住房價格
-零售業銷售
-可用的工作機會

然而，消費者的情緒正在崩潰

奇怪的時代

https://t.co/CCSzf8DXG3]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460752388617289731</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460752388617289731</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 17:42:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[中國恆大創始人出售豪宅和私人飛機以抵償債務]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvx70d/china_evergrande_founder_sells_mansions_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvx70d/china_evergrande_founder_sells_mansions_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 17:42:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你是否買入跌停板？

$BTC $ETH $SOL

👇]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460602142985760774</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460602142985760774</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 16:35:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我要告訴我的老闆，"去死吧，我擁有Lucid！"]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvykva/going_to_tell_my_boss_to_go_fuck_yourself_i_own/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvykva/going_to_tell_my_boss_to_go_fuck_yourself_i_own/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 16:33:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我們所處的狂野時代]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvzney/wild_times_we_live_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvzney/wild_times_we_live_in/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 16:33:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[第一次用電話。完全不知道我在做什麼，我做得對嗎？另外，我怎樣才能從中賺錢？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvo1pr/first_time_with_calls_absolutely_zero_idea_what/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvo1pr/first_time_with_calls_absolutely_zero_idea_what/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 15:26:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lucid Motors 40k股份]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvprvj/lucid_motors_40k_shares/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvprvj/lucid_motors_40k_shares/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 15:26:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有什麼比泡沫更糟糕？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvy6j5/whats_worse_than_a_bubble/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvy6j5/whats_worse_than_a_bubble/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:59:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[亞馬遜將停止接受在英國發行的Visa信用卡]]></title><description><![CDATA[亞馬遜（AMZN）將從明年起停止接受英國發行的Visa（V）信用卡的付款。
據透露，從明年開始，亞馬遜將停止接受英國發行的Visa（V）信用卡付款。

這家在線零售巨頭將這一決定歸咎於Visa收取的高額交易費用。
處理交易。

彭博社稱，這些變化最早將於2022年1月19日生效。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvyppt/amazon_to_stop_accepting_visa_credit_cards_issued/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvyppt/amazon_to_stop_accepting_visa_credit_cards_issued/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:20:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon (AMZN) is to cease accepting payments made by UK-issued Visa (V) credit cards from next year, it has been revealed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The online retail giant blamed the decision on high fees charged by Visa to process transactions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The changes will come into effect as early as 19 January 2022, Bloomberg first reported, citing information that Amazon had shared with its customers this week, after they had purchased items.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$V down approx 3.25% in the pre-market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[維度公司爲美國小型股價值ETF和國際小型股價值ETF提交文件]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是否有可能解決流行的AVUV對小盤股價值傾斜的一些限制（我可能不知道）？
這是否有可能解決流行的AVUV小盤股價值傾斜的一些限制（我可能不知道）？我意識到小盤股的傾斜
並不是博格瑞德最擅長的動作，但是我看到它最近在這個子項目中比較流行，我自己也對它很感興趣。
在這個子裏的受歡迎程度，而且我自己也對它相當感興趣。我很想...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvxzxa/dimensional_files_for_us_small_cap_value_etf_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvxzxa/dimensional_files_for_us_small_cap_value_etf_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:20:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Could this have the potential to solve some limitation (that I may not know about) in the popular AVUV for small cap value tilts? I realize an SCV tilt isn&amp;#39;t the most Boglehead move, however I have seen its relatively recent popularity in this sub and am quite interested in it myself. Would love to hear what you guys think!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://us.dimensional.com/about-us/media-center/dimensional-lists-four-fixed-income-etfs-and-announces-further-expansion-of-etf-offering&quot;&gt;https://us.dimensional.com/about-us/media-center/dimensional-lists-four-fixed-income-etfs-and-announces-further-expansion-of-etf-offering&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆仍有超過50%的特斯拉股份可供出售 從推特上看]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你考慮到他在9月份向美國證券交易委員會提交的近10億美元的股票，可以說接近60%。
在他發推文之前，美國證券交易委員會（SEC）9月份的文件已經規定他要賣掉近10億美元的股票。

https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.marketwatch.com/amp/story/another-day-another-tesla-stock-sale-for-elon-musk-8-8-billion-over-past-7-days...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvxlci/elon_still_has_more_than_50_of_shares_to_sell_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvxlci/elon_still_has_more_than_50_of_shares_to_sell_in/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:20:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arguably closer to 60% if you allow for the near $1 billion stock that he was already due to sell from September SEC filings, that preceded his tweet:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.marketwatch.com/amp/story/another-day-another-tesla-stock-sale-for-elon-musk-8-8-billion-over-past-7-days-11637116058&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.marketwatch.com/amp/story/another-day-another-tesla-stock-sale-for-elon-musk-8-8-billion-over-past-7-days-11637116058&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course if Sanders would just respond to his damned tweets, he could be a great scapegoat for offloading far more shares on the highs.  And who would blame Musk if he did.  He did afterall think Tesla &amp;#39;insanely&amp;#39; over valued at $50 billion:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.vanityfair.com/news/2017/05/even-elon-musk-thinks-teslas-stock-is-insanely-overvalued/amp&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.vanityfair.com/news/2017/05/even-elon-musk-thinks-teslas-stock-is-insanely-overvalued/amp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[塔吉特公司盈利超出預期，但股價下跌，因爲零售商專注於保持客戶價格低廉]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/target-tgt-q3-2021earnings.html

每股收益。調整後爲3.03美元，預期爲2.83美元

收入：256.5億美元 vs. 247.8億美元

塔吉特公司第三財季的收益名列前茅，因爲萬聖節和返校等季節性因素促進了銷售。
萬聖節和返校日等季節性因素促進了銷售。

該零售商...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvydgi/target_tops_earnings_estimates_but_shares_fall_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvydgi/target_tops_earnings_estimates_but_shares_fall_as/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:20:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/target-tgt-q3-2021earnings.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/target-tgt-q3-2021earnings.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earnings per share: $3.03 adjusted vs. $2.83, expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revenue: $25.65 billion vs. $24.78 billion&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Target topped earnings for the fiscal third quarter, as seasonal moments like Halloween and back-to-school boosted sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The retailer raised its forecast, saying that comparable sales could rise at between a high-single digit and low double-digit pace in the holiday period. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CEO Brian Cornell said the company is focused on value as prices of food, gas and more rise and consumers face sticker shock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is another non tech stock that always outperform. The e-commerce operations have been improved and getting competitive advantages against Walmart and Amazon. The management teams are dealing with inflations perfectly and will be able to pass those to customers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[許家印變賣個人資產，向恆大投入超過70億元人民幣的救命資金]]></title><description><![CDATA[中國恆大集團董事局主席許家印承諾
許家印承諾確保投資者的利益，並承諾復工和保證交付建設。
的董事長許家印，正在出售他的個人資產以拯救恆大。
恆大。自7月1日以來，爲了維持恆大的流動資金...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvomsc/xu_jiayin_sold_personal_assets_and_invest_over/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvomsc/xu_jiayin_sold_personal_assets_and_invest_over/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:43:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xu Jiayin, chairman of the board of directors of China Evergrande, who promised to ensure the interests of investors and promise the resumption of work and guarantee the delivery of buildings, &lt;strong&gt;is selling his personal assets to save Evergrande&lt;/strong&gt;. Since July 1st, in order to maintain the liquidity of the group, Xu has raised funds through the &lt;strong&gt;sale of personal assets&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;pledged equity&lt;/strong&gt; and has invested more than &lt;strong&gt;RMB7 billion&lt;/strong&gt; in the group to maintain the basic operations of the huge Evergrande empire. During this period, Evergrande did not have financing and sales suspension, but it must ensure the monthly payment of &lt;strong&gt;10%&lt;/strong&gt;, the salary of headquarters employees, and the payment of interest on domestic and foreign bonds, so as to promote the resumption of work and production of projects across the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you think this action can save Evergrande?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在淘金熱中，出售鐵鍬]]></title><description><![CDATA[在芯片熱潮中（由於電動車、採礦、元數據），相關的芯片供應商有哪些？
供應商公司？

我知道TSM是一個大公司，但他們是一家臺灣公司。我正在尋找一家美國公司。
我知道英特爾和Qorvo有他們自己的內部工廠，作爲一個IC設計師，我的設計是在Qorvo進行的。
我的設計是在Qorvo和Global...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvspcz/during_a_gold_rush_sell_shovels/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvspcz/during_a_gold_rush_sell_shovels/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:30:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;During a chip rush (due to EV, mining, metaverse), what are the relevant chip suppliers companies?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know TSM is a big one but they are a Taiwan company. I&amp;#39;m looking for a US one. I know Intel and Qorvo have their own in house fab and as an IC designer I had my designs fab at Qorvo and Global Foundries too. But which companies are the main suppliers for this chip rush?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特公司在最近的高價位19.79美元，是否仍有上升的空間]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道福特公司在Rivian有很大的投資。如果福特公司持有裏維安公司的股份，那麼他們的收益將是什麼呢？
如果他們持有這項投資或決定將其清算，對福特來說會有什麼好處？我個人認爲
我個人認爲，妹妹的車輛仍有很大的增長潛力，特別是他們的
EV150有巨大的未來訂單。你是否認爲...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvp7du/ford_at_a_recent_high_price_of_1979_does_it_still/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvp7du/ford_at_a_recent_high_price_of_1979_does_it_still/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:30:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know that Ford has a big investment in Rivian.  What will the upside be for Ford if they hold onto that investment or decide to liquidate it. Personally I think there’s still a lot of growth potential sister vehicles especially their EV 150 has a tremendous amount of future orders. Do you think will see a move up towards $30 per share during 2022?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[投資初級礦業股票是否值得？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我從今年年初開始投資，雖然我把一些錢放在了FCX和BHP等大型股票上。
較大的股票，如FCX和BHP，我也計劃投資於一些小型企業。I
但我不打算在這些股票上投入大量資金，因爲我知道投資的風險。
因爲我知道投資這些股票的風險。

我正在研究三隻股票...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvx11z/is_investing_in_junior_mining_stocks_worth_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvx11z/is_investing_in_junior_mining_stocks_worth_it/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:30:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been investing since early this year and while I have placed some money on bigger stocks like FCX and BHP, I am planning to invest in some juniors too. I don’t plan on placing a lot on them though, since I am aware of the risks that come with investing in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am looking into three stocks which includes &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fortitudegold.com/&quot;&gt;Fortitude Gold&lt;/a&gt; (FTCO). They are a small producer but a good thing about them is that they have no debts. They recently increased their dividend by 14%, and reported positive results in their Golden Mile property.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I included &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.threevalleycopper.com/&quot;&gt;Three Valley Copper&lt;/a&gt; (TVC) since they’re showing great potential too. They announced a financing with a deal brought about by investor demand, financing the company with $16 million dollars. They are expected to start mining early 2022 and will potentially produce 13-16 thousand tonnes of copper cathodes in a few years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m still looking into other juniors to add to my bigger mining stocks but some peers have been encouraging me to hold physical metals as well. I’m not really sure about this though. It would help me a lot if you guys share your thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[明天的NVDA...你的想法是什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我現在不在NVDA中，我可能只是從旁觀看
我可能只是從旁觀者的角度看一下收益，但看看NVDA的表現肯定會很有趣。
明天白天的股價表現，然後顯然是盤後的情況。
發生在盤後。

通常情況下，我認爲任何事情，即使是遠程...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvo2a3/nvda_tomorrow_your_thoughts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvo2a3/nvda_tomorrow_your_thoughts/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:03:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not currently in NVDA right now, and I&amp;#39;m probably just going to watch earnings from the sidelines, but it&amp;#39;ll certainly be interesting to see how the stock performs during the day tomorrow, and then obviously what&amp;#39;s going to happen in afterhours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Normally, I&amp;#39;d think that anything even remotely good has already been priced into this stock, so I don&amp;#39;t see how it could possibly explode to the upside after earnings. I&amp;#39;m sure they&amp;#39;re hurting in getting parts from their suppliers like anybody else. So, I&amp;#39;d think the forward guidance would be very cautious. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course anything is possible. The thing could hit $350 in AH or maybe $270&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian的市值目前爲1450億。在未來的幾年裏，有哪些市值低於1500億的好股票是你比較看好的？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直聽說Rivian在過去幾天裏已經超過了幾家公司的市值。
我想知道什麼是最好的進入。

你覺得在未來的幾個月和幾年裏，什麼是最好的？
你覺得在未來的幾個月和幾年裏，哪些是最好的，也是市值在1500億以下的？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjzf7/rivians_market_cap_is_currently_at_145b_what_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjzf7/rivians_market_cap_is_currently_at_145b_what_are/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 12:33:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I keep hearing Rivian has surpassed several companies market caps over the last few days and wondering what would the best ones to go into.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you feel are the best ones over the coming months and years to be holding onto that are also sub 150B market caps?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["我們不會因爲擔心可能出現的通貨膨脹而先發制人地提高利率。我們將等待實際通貨膨脹或其他不平衡的證據。" - J. 鮑威爾

過去一年的通貨膨脹...
出口價格。+18.1%
進口價格。+10.7%
生產者價格指數: +8.6%
消費物價指數: +6.2%
PCE: +4.4%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460828560797667330</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460828560797667330</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:43:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你們這些人讓我感到噁心，Rivian在這些水平上顯然被低估了，你們沒有看到整個畫面。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我很震驚，人們還不明白這一點。rivian出售的T恤衫
[https://rivian.com/gear-shop]。我買了一件35美元的Rivian T恤。
我買了一件35美元的T恤，它的材料真的很好，這有助於證明+1400億美元的
市值，如果我是誠實的。這艘船纔剛剛開始，它...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvo2v1/you_people_make_me_sick_rivian_is_clearly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvo2v1/you_people_make_me_sick_rivian_is_clearly/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:43:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m shocked that people don&amp;#39;t still understand this yet. &lt;a href=&quot;https://rivian.com/gear-shop&quot;&gt;RIVIAN SELLS T-SHIRTS&lt;/a&gt;. I bought one of those $35 dollar T-shirts Rivian sells, it&amp;#39;s really good material which IMO helps justify the +$140 billion market cap if I&amp;#39;m being honest. This ship has only started &amp;amp; it won&amp;#39;t be long until more people buy these t-shirts. Rivian is not just a car company, it&amp;#39;s a clothing company too.(&lt;del&gt;Tsla is not just a car company, it&amp;#39;s a technology company too&lt;/del&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$RIVN的市值比他媽的大衆汽車還要高。絕對不是泡沫。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvfn8c/rivn_has_a_higher_market_cap_than_fucking/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvfn8c/rivn_has_a_higher_market_cap_than_fucking/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:31:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[電動汽車股票有什麼特別之處？]]></title><description><![CDATA[今天和過去幾個月以及2020年和2021年的大部分時間裏，電動車股票一直是
在股價升值方面的領先行業。

我們有LCID，他今天上漲了23%。

RVN今天上漲了15%，其市值幾乎達到1500億美元。

其他如GOEV、FSR、XPEV、PTRA，他們的表現都很出色......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvilhs/what_is_so_special_about_ev_stocks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvilhs/what_is_so_special_about_ev_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:31:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today and for the past few months and most of 2020 and 2021, EV stocks have been the leading sectors in terms of stock price appreciation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have LCID who is up 23% today. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RVN who is up 15% today and with a market cap of almost $150B. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Others like GOEV, FSR, XPEV, PTRA who have been outperforming most of the market recently. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shit, TSLA is at $1T valuation and won’t stop there most likely. Yes, yes, I know Tesla is NoT jUsT aN EV cOmPaNy. But still. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Point is, what is the hype with EV stocks? I understand that it is a rapidly growing industry since mandates and adoption will allow EVs to replace ICE vehicles in the coming years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, automaker margins are freaking terrible. I just don’t see the appeal of auto maker stocks going up just because they are going EV. There will be lots of competitors (obviously), beit the new companies like Lucid, Rivian, and Tesla and the legacy makers like Volkswagen, Toyota, etc. Also, it’s not like EV is some niche field where duopolies or monopolies will thrive either. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s also not mention that EVs will cost more to make when compared to ICE. So it’s not like auto makers are going to cut major costs like when Ford introduced the assembly line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just want to start a discussion and hear people’s thoughts. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And no, I’m not shorting or buying puts. Just genuinely surprised that this EV bubble or rally - whatever you want to call it - is still going strong. Especially in times of inflation fears.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[週五鮑威爾的決定會對市場產生多大程度的影響？]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登剛剛宣佈美聯儲將在4天內作出決定......因此，這要麼是週五晚些時候
星期五晚上或星期六。因此，當市場在週末關閉時，這使得
我擔心他正在更換負責人並取代鮑威爾。

比起利率、糖價飆升、通貨膨脹......我最大的擔憂是迄今爲止的變化
在...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qviwx9/how_badly_will_the_market_be_affected_by_powell/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qviwx9/how_badly_will_the_market_be_affected_by_powell/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:18:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Biden just announced fed decision will be in 4 days… so that’s either late Friday night or Saturday. So when the market is closed on a weekend which makes me concerned he is changing the head and replacing Powell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More than rates, covid spike, inflation… my biggest concern was by far a change in Powell because the market hates change and unexpected news. I could totally see this resulting in what should have probably already happened with a correction especially with big market cap stocks. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the new chair would be Brainard who has a major supporter in Senator Warren, who opposes the FAANG stock dominance. I am very concerned and hopefully he just sticks with Powell. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The market is going so well this would really be the biggest negative that would sink things for end of year&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["我兩邊都在玩，這樣我總能出頭。"]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvqhsk/im_playing_both_sides_so_that_i_always_come_out/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvqhsk/im_playing_both_sides_so_that_i_always_come_out/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:18:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[電動汽車初創公司Lucid的市值超過福特，股價暴漲，超過890億美元]]></title><description><![CDATA["我對我們的股票價格感覺很好，"豪斯在聯合採訪中告訴CNBC。
採訪時說。"我們已經有的上升，它今天的位置，以及增長的軌跡，坦率地說，這在我們面前。
坦率地說，在我們面前的是增長的軌跡。我看到我們被認爲是一家擁有平臺的技術公司。
我看到我們被認爲是一家技術公司，它的平臺可以擴展到很多領域。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjuok/ev_startup_lucids_market_value_blows_past_ford_at/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjuok/ev_startup_lucids_market_value_blows_past_ford_at/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 10:44:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;I feel great about our stock price,&amp;quot; House told CNBC during the joint interview. &amp;quot;The runup that we&amp;#39;ve had, where it is today and also the growth trajectory, frankly, that&amp;#39;s in front of us. I see that we&amp;#39;re being regarded as a technology company with a platform that&amp;#39;s extensible across lots of vehicle variants and sustainable tech.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1980年至2021年標準普爾500指數的月度平均回報率：年底前的強勁表現？]]></title><description><![CDATA[以下是自1980年以來的平均回報率（%）。

數據是到2021年9月。資料來源。標準普爾和哈弗分析。

1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 +1.2 -0.1 +0.5 +1.5 -0.1 +0.8
+1.6 +0.7 -1.0 +0.4 +0.9 +1.3

你對2021年12月的賭注是什麼？你是如何準備的？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjvni/average_monthly_sp_500_returns_from_1980_to_2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjvni/average_monthly_sp_500_returns_from_1980_to_2021/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 08:11:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below are the average return in % since 1980.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Data are through September 2021.  Source: Standard &amp;amp; Poor’s and Haver Analytics. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Jan&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Feb&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Mar&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Apr&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;May&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Jun&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Jul&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Aug&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Sep&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Oct&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Nov&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Dec&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+1.2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-0.1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+0.5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+1.5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-0.1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+0.8&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+1.6&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+0.7&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-1.0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+0.4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+0.9&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+1.3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What your bet for Dec 2021? How are you preparing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$PFE https://t.co/fQaigrZgaM]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460766555801886722</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460766555801886722</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 06:49:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登公佈美聯儲新任主席的意外人選]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvm3sv/biden_unveils_surprise_pick_for_new_fed_chair/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvm3sv/biden_unveils_surprise_pick_for_new_fed_chair/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 06:49:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[電動汽車公司Polestar（有銷售）將通過SPAC上市 - $GGPI]]></title><description><![CDATA[被忽視的SPAC交易，Polestar，一家位於瑞典的以電動爲重點的汽車公司正在與GGPI合併。
瑞典的電動汽車公司正在與GGPI美元合併。

他們已經在銷售他們的Polestar 1（一種混合動力車）和Polestar 2。
全電動汽車。他們還發布了Polestar "Precept "的願景。

財務狀況

他們做了6.45億美元的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvmzuu/ev_company_polestar_with_sales_going_public_via/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvmzuu/ev_company_polestar_with_sales_going_public_via/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 05:56:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overlooked SPAC deal, Polestar, an electric-focused automotive company based in Sweden is merging with $GGPI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are already selling their Polestar 1, a hybrid, and the Polestar 2, fully-electric car. They are also released a vision for the Polestar &amp;quot;Precept.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Financials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They did $645M in revenue in 2020, and are projecting $1.6B in 2021. Right now, the SPAC is valued at just $1.55B.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/3jmd9c5ulvz71.png?width=624&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=54caf7be4f0b42872a22d4a633e3f28aa78b836c&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/3jmd9c5ulvz71.png?width=624&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=54caf7be4f0b42872a22d4a633e3f28aa78b836c&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;compared to other EV/automotive companies. $645M* revenue&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are also backed by Volvo, Geely, and Leonardo DiCaprio? IMO most undervalued EV company after GM and F.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[新文章。

股票市場不是經濟...

https://t.co/HTQvTJLLHf https://t.co/mg6NMfQ2NF]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460723942314938372</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460723942314938372</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 05:43:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不是在開玩笑。內衣/內褲公司Naked Brand與電動汽車製造商Cenntro Automotive合併後飆升]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是一個多星期前的事。這些公司並不像Lucid或Rivian那樣非常有名。
Rivian，但我認爲電動車公司的市場佔有率最高。

 *Naked Brands的股票在週二飆升至30%，因爲該公司
   該公司宣佈與Cenntro Automotive合併。
 * 這家內衣製造商正在轉向電動汽車。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvocts/not_kidding_lingerieunderwear_company_naked_brand/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvocts/not_kidding_lingerieunderwear_company_naked_brand/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 05:43:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was over a week ago. The companies are not very well known like Lucid or Rivian but I&amp;#39;m calling market top for EV companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Naked Brands stock soared as much as 30% on Tuesday after the company announced a merger with Cenntro Automotive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The lingerie maker is pivoting to electric vehicles as investors look to find the next Tesla.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cenntro develops electrified commercial vehicles and has sold more than 3,000 units to date.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://africa.businessinsider.com/finance/a-lingerie-makers-stock-is-soaring-on-a-deal-to-merge-with-an-ev-manufacturer/040c5jh&quot;&gt;https://africa.businessinsider.com/finance/a-lingerie-makers-stock-is-soaring-on-a-deal-to-merge-with-an-ev-manufacturer/040c5jh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對迪士尼（DIS）的看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[我已經觀察迪斯尼幾個月了，認爲它是一個很好的股票，適合我長期持有。
我的長期持股。自從它跌到160美元以下，我最近開始增加股票。
大家對這隻股票有什麼看法？對它的評價是否過多地集中在
迪斯尼+而不是整個公司？

它已經有了一個新的增長點。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvk3q2/thoughts_on_disney_dis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvk3q2/thoughts_on_disney_dis/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 05:43:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been watching Disney for a few months now and think it’s a great stock for my long term holdings. I began adding shares recently since it dropped sub $160. What are everyone’s thoughts on the stock? Is it being judged too much on Disney+ and not the company as a whole?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s had an underwhelming year and is now 20% below ATH. Has anyone held throughout this recent slump?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone discourse would be appreciated :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[購買比特幣的Bogleheads？]]></title><description><![CDATA[對於在這個子裏做他們的5%有趣的錢和購買比特幣的Bogleheads，哪個
你是用哪個應用程序或供應商來購買比特幣的？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvh6s9/bogleheads_who_buy_bitcoin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvh6s9/bogleheads_who_buy_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 04:32:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the Bogleheads in this sub who do their 5% fun money and buy Bitcoin, which app or provider are you using to buy Bitcoin?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[裏維安的收入爲0美元，現在是地球上第三大價值的汽車製造商]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvinva/rivian_has_0_in_revenue_and_is_now_the_third_most/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvinva/rivian_has_0_in_revenue_and_is_now_the_third_most/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 03:46:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Metaverse以及爲什麼你應該關注 - 基本分類]]></title><description><![CDATA[介紹和什麼是Metaverse？

你們現在可能都知道，流行的社交媒體公司，即以前稱爲
臉書已將其名稱改爲Meta。這引發了關於
這引發了關於Metaverse及其對社會未來影響的討論，這也是理所當然的。雖然我已經
看到許多帖子...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvc6fr/the_metaverse_and_why_you_should_pay_attention/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvc6fr/the_metaverse_and_why_you_should_pay_attention/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 03:32:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction and what is the Metaverse?:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you all probably know by now the popular social media company formerly known as Facebook has changed its name to Meta. This has sparked discussions about the Metaverse and its future effect on society, and rightfully so. Although I have seen many posts online and especially on Reddit which don’t quite seem to grasp what the Metaverse is and why it&amp;#39;s the future, please note if you are one of these people don’t worry - it’s complicated for sure! This post will explain simply what the Metaverse is and why you should get on board now. I will do my best to explain but if you have any questions please feel free to ask in the comments and I will be sure to reply.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Metaverse put simply is the combination of multiple elements of technology, but put more complexly is where virtual reality, blockchain and web3 meet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best way of explaining web3 is to first understand web1 and web2. Web1 is what many may consider the first stage of the internet, if you look at what the first iterations of the internet were, it was just code on a screen. It was complex to use and only really used for sharing scientific work. Web2 is what we now know as the internet. This includes Youtube, Reddit etc. The main downside of web2 is for the longest time other than a domain name you couldn’t own anything online. You could make a video and post it on Youtube, even though you feel you own the video and control it, Youtube at any point can remove the video and even your channel. At any point in time everything online can be controlled by someone else. This is where web3 comes in. Web3 is the next evolution of the internet. Web3 may as well be called the decentralised internet. It allows users to freely use the internet run on blockchain, so anyone can participate without having your personal data involved or monetized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a big reason crypto based items such as coins and NFT’s have taken off as they are based on web3 technology. For the first time normal everyday people are able to own their own little part of the internet, and no one, including the government, can tell you what to do. It&amp;#39;s the next step for total freedom online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Metaverse isn’t a place, the Metaverse isn’t something you can touch. A big mistake I see is people think that there is going to be some sort of invention or overnight change where suddenly the Metaverse is mainstream and that&amp;#39;s our lives, no. It will be a gradual change which has already started and will continue to the point that our virtual life is worth more to us than our physical lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why is the Metaverse the next big thing?:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the best place to start on why the Metaverse will be the next big thing will be to look back at previous technology. 99% of human attention used to be on our physical environment. TV’s dropped that to 85%. Computers dropped that to 70%. Phones dropped that to 50%. It&amp;#39;s clear that as technology advances it absorbs more and more of our time and energy. At some point something new will drop that to lower and lower numbers to the point where we are using technology 100% of the time, this may take decades but it&amp;#39;s entirely possible. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t have to be something mind-blowing but just imagine some type of augmented reality device which either connects to your brain or you see it through contact lenses, imagine it just helped with basic everyday things like arrows on a road so you don&amp;#39;t have to distract yourself with a GPS, or walking into a McDonalds and being able to see the calories of each food item on the menu. These are just basic examples of what the first iteration of augmented reality can do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Metaverse will be the next big thing because &lt;strong&gt;it will be everything.&lt;/strong&gt; Anything you could imagine will be in the Metaverse. It can range from anything from gaming to concerts to seeing family members from the other side of the world. There is no beginning, middle and end, it&amp;#39;s just infinite code waiting to be filled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real life application and potential benefits:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the potential benefits I want to start with isn’t about what will be good inside the Metaverse but outside it. A comment I’m seeing a lot online is people saying “I want to work on fixing the real world, not create a fake one”. But I think people are missing the point that this will make the real world better. Imagine the millions of cars we can get off the road and reduce pollution if people no longer had to drive to work and school, and instead would stay at home and work in the Metaverse. Of course this may vary depending on the industry but even if we could get 50% of cars off the road it would be a massive achievement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I write this more and more benefits keep popping in my head, I will just briefly write some ideas but it&amp;#39;s really going to be endless. Surgeons can practice their work virtually. Architects can design and walk around buildings before construction. Home buyers can visit a home from their own home. People on lower incomes can travel the world from their living room. Schools can visit any museum. Entrepreneurs and businesses can save money on office space. Lovers of history can travel to any time desired (DINOSAURS!). The list really is endless, so I will stop there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Potential negatives and why it won’t matter:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with any new technology there are always downsides. When the microwave first came out people were terrified of it, same with TV, radio, social media and now the Metaverse. I will note that is a good thing. As a society we should always look to protect ourselves and do what&amp;#39;s best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Metaverse won’t be perfect. Even nowadays cyber bullying is a major issue and it may not be any better in the Metaverse. We will distance ourselves further from the real world. Spending less and less physical time with our friends and family and more virtual time with them. The thing is though, the negatives don’t matter. Whether it&amp;#39;s good or bad technology has always advanced on and those who don’t get on board are left behind. Many said at the birth of the internet that it would be bad but it is undoubtedly the best thing to happen to humanity in the past century, and this will have the same effect. I greatly encourage those to at least have an open mind when it comes to the Metaverse, we are on the dawn of something great and those who capitalise on it will be rewarded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How long until the Metaverse is ready and becomes mainstream?:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this is a very hard question. Actually, I think this is an impossible question. You could try and rephrase it to ‘How long until the internet is ready and becomes mainstream?’ At no point does anyone announce the internet is ready and at no point is it officially called mainstream. At some point it just became what it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Metaverse creation will be gradual, it will most likely take a decade minimum but my guess is as good as yours. I think the point at which we accept as a society that the Metaverse is ready is when our digital selves are worth more than our physical selves. You even start to see it now. Kids care more about how they look on Fortnite than in real life. Teens care more about how many followers they have on Instagram than in real life. The world has and always will be  changing with technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to buy and how to make profit:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could list any number of companies which could make you great gains in the near future, including FB, MSFT, U, RBLX, AMZN, ADSK etc. and I would be completely wrong! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though I and many others may know a lot about the Metaverse, the truth is we won’t be able to predict even 1% of what the final product will be. If you asked a million people before the internet what the most popular websites would be you wouldn’t get a single right answer. No one knows so anyone telling you what to buy don’t actually have a clue. Yes you can make money in the short term but that’s it. Remember the dot com bubble? Watch out for a Metaverse bubble.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final thoughts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My thoughts are to tell people now to worry. This isn’t some doomsday device, it’s better to just see it as an extension of your phone. The truth is we are years off of anything serious and no one is going to be forced to use it. I also don’t see any chance of it being stopped by the government as I see some people online say. Sugar and cigarettes are bad but they are legal too. I would recommend anyone to at least try and allocate a small percentage of their portfolio to one of the bigger stock names linked to the Metaverse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[市場被低估了]]></title><description><![CDATA[還記得你們10年前的生活嗎？是的。你們有比以前更多的狗屎。
你有更多的選擇。更多他媽的技術。

現在更加專業化了。

所以未來10年？這將是一個他媽的彩虹。創新並沒有停止。
創新的速度加快了，這是最高的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvo3kl/the_market_is_undervalued/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvo3kl/the_market_is_undervalued/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 03:32:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember your lives 10 years ago? Yeah. You have way more shit than ever before. You have way more options. Way more fucking technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is more specialized now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the next 10 years? It&amp;#39;ll be a fucking rainbow. Innovation has not stopped. Innovation picked up the speed that is the highest that it ever has been.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s an amazing ride. Enjoy it. It&amp;#39;s never been better to be alive than now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Metaverse might actually happen. Maybe it&amp;#39;s not if but when?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla is overvalued. Is it though? No idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Facebook and Coinbase are ridiculously undervalued.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$10T market cap? Will we ever see it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn&amp;#39;t matter. Hug people you care about. We are all going to die. It does not matter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在目前的市場條件下，是否有可能出現調整？]]></title><description><![CDATA[真正的問題。在目前的市場條件下，廣泛的、交叉的指數修正是否可能？
的市場條件下，是否有可能出現廣泛的、交叉的指數調整？老實說，我認爲不可能。我認爲由於QE和美聯儲的支持
有如此多的現金到處亂晃，尋找一個家，以至於任何有回報前景的東西都被立即投資。
哪怕是回報前景渺茫的東西，都會被立即投資進去。

聽着...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvgi4h/is_a_correction_even_possible_under_current/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvgi4h/is_a_correction_even_possible_under_current/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 02:51:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Genuine question. Is a broad, cross-index correction possible given the current market conditions? I honestly think not. I think due to QE and Fed bolstering there is so much cash sloshing around looking for a home that anything with an even remote prospect of return is instantly invested in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hear me out. I really think this is a new paradigm, not as in oh market goes up forever and this time is different, and more as in this amount of QE and stimulus mixed with bare bones low interest rate has never been achieved before. We have never had a market with the combination of those 2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here&amp;#39;s how I see things going forward:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dumb money is here to stay. There&amp;#39;s just too damn much of it flooding the market looking for a home. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Retail investor sentiment has changed. No one is risk-adverse on a broad scale anymore. Investors are willing to hold through dips and plunge more cash into them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interest rates are rock bottom, and there&amp;#39;s the possibility they stay that way or go negative due to debt implications if they&amp;#39;re raised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s going to change? Is retail suddenly going to become risk adverse? Is the amount of capital flooding the system going to be reigned in? Are interest rates going to drastically rise, if at all?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t think so. I quite literally think that given market conditions and sentiment a correction is not even possible. Do all the remind me&amp;#39;s you want. The market is unable to correct.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉有價值的唯一原因是超級充電網絡，而Rivian和Lucid沒有這個網絡。]]></title><description><![CDATA[兩年前，我以開玩笑的方式試駕了一輛特斯拉3型車，結果當天就買了一輛。
同一天。它們實際上是非常酷的車，而且快得要命......但你知道爲什麼我和其他有錢的正常人（又不是你們這些沒錢的弱智）都要買。
但你知道爲什麼我和其他有錢的正常人（又稱不是你們這些在RH賬戶裏有500美元的破產弱智）會買這些車。
500美元在你的RH賬戶）買它們？

超級充電器網絡....]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvelvp/the_only_reason_tesla_is_worth_anything_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvelvp/the_only_reason_tesla_is_worth_anything_is/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 02:29:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I test drove a Tesla model 3 two years ago as a joke and ended up buying one that same day. They&amp;#39;re actually really cool cars and fast as shit... but you know why I, and other normal people with money (aka not you broke retards with $500 in your RH accounts) buy them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE SUPER CHARGER NETWORK. This is basically a system of electric gas stations that charge your car in 30-40 minutes, and allows you to drive ANYWHERE in America and Canada. You can drive from San Diego to NYC with this network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know what you can&amp;#39;t do with a Rivian or Lucid? Drive anywhere you don&amp;#39;t normally drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you try to charge your car at a charge port or whatever, it&amp;#39;ll take you 8 hours for a full charge. The only reason Tesla is worth anything is because of their phenomenal super charger network. How the fuck are lucid and rivian going to compete with that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;edit: looks like the truth has triggered some fuckin’ noobs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[財政部長珍妮特-耶倫警告說，拜登的基礎設施法案中的要求可能加速美國的債務違約。]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 財政部長珍妮特-耶倫週二警告國會領導層說
> 如果聯邦政府不採取行動，它可能在下個月出現債務違約。
> 採取行動提高債務上限。
> 
> 耶倫女士在給高層立法者的一封信中預計，在12月15日之後，將有
> 有一些情況在...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvlndx/treasury_secretary_janet_yellen_warns_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvlndx/treasury_secretary_janet_yellen_warns_that/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 02:29:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen warned congressional leadership Tuesday that the federal government could default on its debt next month if they don’t take action to raise the debt ceiling.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a letter to top lawmakers, Ms. Yellen projected that after Dec. 15, there are scenarios in which the Treasury could have “insufficient resources to continue to finance the operation of the U.S. government.”  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ms. Yellen added that she has “a high degree of confidence” in the Treasury’s ability to make debt payments through Dec. 15. That’s two weeks longer than her initial forecast of Dec. 3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More money coming in? More pump?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[還有人討厭新的Vanguard應用程序嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我討厭那些試圖成爲超時尚和極簡主義的應用程序。我不知道什麼是
哪些地方，而且感覺功能都被拿走了。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvj98f/anybody_else_hate_the_new_vanguard_app/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvj98f/anybody_else_hate_the_new_vanguard_app/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 01:53:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I hate apps that try to be ultra sleek and minimalist. I don&amp;#39;t know where anything is, and it feels like features have been taken away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>