<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 20:14:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[紐約宣佈因新的Covid變體而進入緊急狀態]]></title><description><![CDATA[你認爲市場在週一會有什麼反應？
紐約宣佈進入緊急狀態，旨在增加醫院的容量和解決醫務人員的
紐約宣佈進入緊急狀態，旨在增加醫院的能力並解決醫務人員短缺的問題，因爲全國都在準備應對冠狀病毒的新歐米茄變體。

新協議將於12月3日生效，該命令將...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3jg1m/new_york_declares_state_of_emergency_due_to_new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3jg1m/new_york_declares_state_of_emergency_due_to_new/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 19:36:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;How do you think the market will react on Monday?New York declared a state of emergency aimed at increasing hospital capacity and addressing medical staffing shortages as the nation braces for the new omicron variant of the coronavirus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new protocols will take effect Dec. 3 and the order will remain in place at least until Jan. 15, when it will be reassessed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The emergency declaration will allow the state Department of Health to limit nonessential and nonurgent hospital procedures in situations where a hospital has less than 10% staffed bed capacity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.yahoo.com/news/york-declares-state-emergency-hike-074026369.html&quot;&gt;https://www.yahoo.com/news/york-declares-state-emergency-hike-074026369.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在家庭飯桌上談論一個華爾街博彩公司的交易員]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3fh4o/talking_about_a_wallstreetbets_trader_at_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3fh4o/talking_about_a_wallstreetbets_trader_at_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 19:23:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你對市場調整的遊戲計劃是什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[現在，這個子項目最不需要的就是對市場是否會崩潰/向下修正的更多無意義的猜測。
市場是否會崩潰/向下修正。我們沒有人可以預測
我們都聽說過，選擇市場時機是徒勞的。讓我們把這種
炒作到最低限度。

對於那些擔心這個問題的人...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3fl3r/whats_your_game_plan_for_a_market_correction/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3fl3r/whats_your_game_plan_for_a_market_correction/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 18:52:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, the last thing this sub needs is more pointless speculation on whether or not the market&amp;#39;s going to crash/correct downward. None of us can predict the future and we&amp;#39;ve all heard that timing the market is futile. Let&amp;#39;s keep that speculation to a minimum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who are worried about this though, what positions are you taking? Do you have a small percentage of your portfolio in some type of hedge? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OTM SPY puts? VIX calls? A larger than usual cash position? What are you using and how much is it costing you? What&amp;#39;s the potential pay off?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to stay invested, but I also know that the market is historically overvalued, and I want peace of mind at night with some form of hedge. Any suggestions are welcomed. Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[原油價格昨天下跌13.1%，是有史以來第九大單日跌幅。$WTIC https://t.co/YKYxzbXBCM]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464612670590664706</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464612670590664706</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 18:38:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WSB之美]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r39952/the_beauty_of_wsb/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r39952/the_beauty_of_wsb/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 18:38:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你對晨星的看法如何？]]></title><description><![CDATA[問候。有沒有人試過晨星保險費，你對它有什麼看法？
你對它有什麼看法？

如果你使用過或目前正在使用，你覺得他們的投資組合跟蹤如何？
功能如何？諸如 *容易加載和更新頭寸 *自定義視圖
部門、市場、資產細分等屬性的自定義視圖

我看到...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3fy7k/whats_your_opinion_of_morningstar/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r3fy7k/whats_your_opinion_of_morningstar/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 18:15:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greetings. Have anyone tried the Morningstar premium, and what’s your opinion on it? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you used it or currently use it, how do you like their portfolio tracking functions? Things like 
* ease of loading and updating positions 
* custom view on attributes like sector, market, assets breakdowns&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I saw some fundamentals attributes in the free service, does it provide more robust data on premium?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also what do you all use for portfolio tracking? (I also got personal capital, it’s great for my main portfolio…but hard to set up secondary and mock accounts)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks all!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼會有這麼多新的電動汽車公司？]]></title><description><![CDATA[首先，自己造一輛車已經很困難了，而且還得有事情發生。
當你在路上遇到顛簸時就會散架。其次，製造汽車是一項
巨大的事業和資本支出。如果我想開一家新公司，電動汽車將是最後的選擇。
電動汽車將是名單上的最後一件事，也許這就是原因？I...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3eer7/why_are_there_so_many_new_electric_vehicle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3eer7/why_are_there_so_many_new_electric_vehicle/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 18:15:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;First of all, it’s hard enough to build a car on it’s own without things falling apart when you hit a bump in the road. Second, to manufacture them is a humongous undertaking and capital expense. If I wanted to start a new company, EV’s would be the very last thing on the list, maybe that’s why? I don’t get it&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是一個完全陌生的人，正在考慮投資PayPal ?]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想過只買1股PayPal的股票，然後從那裏開始。我覺得不好
我在23歲的時候纔開始，而且可以投資的資金很少，我只有8千塊錢
我的整個名字，這很糟糕。我可能會投資300美元，這是我所願意失去的。
願意失去的，再多就不負責任了。

任何...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3epsv/im_completely_new_and_thinking_about_investing_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r3epsv/im_completely_new_and_thinking_about_investing_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 16:54:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thought about buying just 1 share of PayPal and starting from there. I feel bad that I’m starting late at 23 and with so little to even invest, I’ve only got 8k to my entire name which sucks lol. I’d invest maybe $300, that’s what I’m willing to lose, anything more would be irresponsible. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any advice? Is this a good start? Anything I should know as a complete newbie? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Words words words hopefully my post isn’t taken down for low effort this time&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GGPI (Polestar) vs LCID (Lucid) ???? 有什麼想法嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直在考慮在我的月度投資清單中增加一個這樣的項目。我是一個
長期投資者，我有一個每月投資的股票清單。

我的第一個問題..... GGPI股票是否只代表Polestar公司？

另外，我想知道你對這兩家電動汽車製造商的看法。I...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r38awo/ggpi_polestar_vs_lcid_lucid_any_thoughts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r38awo/ggpi_polestar_vs_lcid_lucid_any_thoughts/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 15:51:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have been thinking of adding one of these to my monthly investing list. I am a long term investor and I have a list of stocks that I invest in every month. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first question..... Does GGPI stock represent Polestar only? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, I  want to know your views on these 2 Electric cars manufacturers. I am thinking of investing regularly in GGPI (Polestar) since they have successfully sold a significant number of cars. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not able to see any strong points favouring Lucid. Please fill me in if I am missing something important about them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know that scaling an electric car business is very difficult as stated by Elon Musk in multiple interviews. Keeping that in consideration I think Polestar has already solved its scaling issue since its parent company is Volve. I can&amp;#39;t say the same for Lucid though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$VIX週五飆升了54%，是歷史上第四大單日漲幅（注：$VIX數據可追溯至1990年）。https://t.co/TmZcja9Otd]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464597978778382347</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464597978778382347</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 15:38:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你是如何爲你的房子存錢的？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一個23歲的年輕人，有興趣在我們20多歲到30多歲有孩子之前和我的另一半買房子。
我們在20多歲到30多歲時有了孩子（理想情況下）。有什麼建議嗎？
這個目標的建議？我聽說你可以從你的Roth中拿出錢來支付首付。
這是真的嗎？我現在有一筆微薄的儲蓄，但正在把...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r37wyd/how_did_you_save_for_your_house/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r37wyd/how_did_you_save_for_your_house/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 15:38:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m a 23 year old interested in buying a house with my significant other before we have kids in our late 20s to early 30s (ideally). Any advice on how to save for this goal? I heard you can take money out of your Roth for a down payment is that true? I have a meager savings right now but am putting away what I can when I can. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在我看來，Vanguard應用程序的更新拿走了Vanguard應用程序最酷的一個功能。只是發泄一下。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我把這個貼在這裏是因爲Bogle經常與Vanguard交織在一起。
希望你能看到這一切是適用的。這似乎是一個 "爲了改變而改變
變化 "的更新，他們被賣了。Vanguard應用程序本週更新。

上一個應用程序的最佳功能是你可以點擊你的賬戶，...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r39ew4/the_vanguard_app_update_took_away_the_coolest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r39ew4/the_vanguard_app_update_took_away_the_coolest/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 14:42:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m posting this here because Bogle is often intertwined with Vanguard, hopefully you see it all as applicable. This seems like a “change for the sake of change” update they were sold on. The Vanguard app updated this week. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best feature of the last app was you could click your account, or performance, and hover/slide with your thumb over the months and see how much has changed in that one month. It was such a simple to use, nice features to see while looking at a chart. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new update? It’s gone. It’s almost as if they hired people who don’t use the app to update it. I’m sure that days is somewhere in the app, but not as cleanly and easily accessible as it was with the thumb/hold/slide feature of the last app. Bummer. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s all&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Omicron的恐慌。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3b8sc/omicron_panic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r3b8sc/omicron_panic/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 13:53:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[週一80,000美元的SPY Puts，因爲你們這些弱智在今天收盤時都買了看漲期權]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2u2a0/80000_spy_puts_for_monday_bc_all_you_retards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2u2a0/80000_spy_puts_for_monday_bc_all_you_retards/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 10:54:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對在這次大流行中投資航空公司的想法？]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好，感謝大家的閱讀。
世界已經發展成爲一個許多事情都在網上完成的地方，而我已經
我決定加入進來，從投資股票開始。所以，對於主要的
問題。在100美元的起始預算下，我應該投資什麼。當然，我並不是想通過投資賺取1000美元。
當然，我並不是想通過投資來賺取1000美元...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2wv59/thoughts_on_investing_in_airlines_during_this/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2wv59/thoughts_on_investing_in_airlines_during_this/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 10:54:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey all, and thanks for reading.&lt;br/&gt;
The world has grown to be a place   where so many things are done online, and I&amp;#39;ve decided to join in by  starting with investing in stocks. So, to the main question: What do I  invest in, with a starting budget of $100. I am, of  course, not looking  to make $1000 off of this $100 initial budget, but  seeing any profit  would motivate oneself to invest more in the future. I  was thinking of  investing in popular airlines I could get my hands on,  as with the new COVID variant, these businesses are likely to be worth  much less. So, thoughts on this? And, any other information anyone could  share on the  matter with how to start off?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[注意空頭交易者]]></title><description><![CDATA[說到賺錢，我是最不走運的人，我所能做的就是在任何事情上輸掉。
任何事情。我接觸的所有東西在我購買的瞬間就自動變成了狗屎
100%準確。很明顯，我有熊市的能力。

我也有能力瞬間讓任何人生氣，只是我的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r38uub/attention_short_position_traders/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r38uub/attention_short_position_traders/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 10:42:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am the unluckiest man when it comes to making money, all I can do is lose with anything. Everything I touch automatically turns to shit the instant I buy it with 100% accuracy. It is clear I have the power to bear markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also have the ability to instantly make anyone pissed off just by my mere presence alone. I am a true form of perfect negative energy in the universe, and thus I can be weaponized for hire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use my powers to short anything. Pay me up front, tell me what to buy one share of, and short your way to billions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[無論是否有COVID，哪些股票是強勢股？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在這一點上，我只是預計每隔幾個月就會有新的變種出現，所以
航空公司和一些行業，如郵輪留置權，對我來說風險太大，不能賭
的風險太大，我不想爲了很少的回報而進行賭博。

另一方面，不管有沒有COVID的消息，什麼股票是好戲？
我個人喜歡Costco，它是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r36gk8/what_stocks_are_strong_plays_with_or_without_covid/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r36gk8/what_stocks_are_strong_plays_with_or_without_covid/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 09:57:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this point, I just anticipate new variants popping up every few months so airlines and some sectors like cruise liens are just too risky for me to gamble on for very little reward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, what stocks are good plays to get with or without COVID news? I personally like Costco which is defensive but also a trade that has sailed from earnings even post &amp;quot;delta&amp;quot;, Roblox which is another great stock in case of shutdowns but also had phenomenal earnings despite things reopening and kids going back to school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What else?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[零售業股票在黑色星期五的強勁銷售中下挫。歸咎於對Covid變體的恐懼]]></title><description><![CDATA[週五上午，零售股與大盤一起下跌，因爲人們擔心
新的Covid-19變體在可能強勁的黑色星期五銷售中衝擊着市場。
週五的銷售。美元樹(Dollar Tree)(DLTR)的股價，其大部分產品--包括玩具、家庭裝飾品、廚房用品--都是在黑色星期五出售的。
該公司的大部分產品--包括玩具、家居裝飾品、廚房用品和季節性產品--都是由Dollar Tree公司銷售的。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2saq2/retail_stocks_sink_amid_strong_black_friday_sales/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2saq2/retail_stocks_sink_amid_strong_black_friday_sales/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 09:44:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Retail stocks, along with the broader market, were down Friday morning as fears of a new Covid-19 variant hammered the market amid potentially strong Black Friday sales. Shares of Dollar Tree (DLTR), which sells the majority of its products—including toys, home decor, kitchenware, and seasonal goods—was down nearly 4% to $140.81. Nordstrom (JWN) was down 7% at $21.04. Macy’s (M) was off 7.2%. Retailers that struggled to keep up with supply-chain crunches—as noted in their third-quarter earnings—including Kohls (KSS) and Gap (GPS) were down 2.1% to $54.09, and 3.4% to $17.25, respectively. Shares of Abercrombie &amp;amp; Fitch (ANF) were down 3.3% to $37.98.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the most part though, retail stocks have been gaining amid high demand this year. The SPDR S&amp;amp;P Retail exchange-traded fund (XRT) is up 50.05% this year as of Friday morning, still on pace for its best year since 2009, when it rose 74.8%. The ETF is down 2.8% in Friday trading. The Invesco S&amp;amp;P 500 Equal Weight Consumer Discretionary ETF (RCD) is up nearly 25% this year, a sign that despite the previous Delta variant, shoppers are ready to spend their cash and investors recognize the demand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Data from Friday morning showed U.S. consumers are expected to spend $12.9 billion in online sales and have already spent $6.9 billion online during Thanksgiving Day, up 1.1% from last year, according to data from Salesforce. The National Retail Federation estimates 58.1 million people will shop on Small Business Saturday, and 62.8 million will shop online on Cyber Monday. The trade organization projects consumers will spend an average of $997.73, with total spending up as much as 10.5% to $859 billion this season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;U.S. online sales for the first three weeks of November are up 10% year-over-year, $74 billion already spent, as consumers continue to fit in holiday shopping as early as possible over concerns regarding shipping delays and supply chain issues, according to Salesforce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Dow was on track for its worst Black Friday on record, with the S&amp;amp;P 500 and Nasdaq on pace for their worst Black Friday since 2009.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/articles/retail-stocks-sink-amid-strong-black-friday-sales-blame-covid-variant-fears-51637946074?mod=mw_latestnews&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/articles/retail-stocks-sink-amid-strong-black-friday-sales-blame-covid-variant-fears-51637946074?mod=mw_latestnews&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[白癡朋友們，你們是怎麼做的？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2xi84/how_do_you_do_fellow_idiots/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2xi84/how_do_you_do_fellow_idiots/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 07:27:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[QQQ與SPY的對比？]]></title><description><![CDATA[考慮投資QQQ或SPY，但不能確定哪個是
適當的一個。或者我應該同時投資於這兩種股票嗎？

我的DD顯示。

- QQQ跟蹤納斯達克100指數，而SPY跟蹤標準普爾500指數 - QQQ是
少數行業中的100只股票，主要集中在科技領域。SPY是500
股票，分佈在...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2snig/qqq_vs_spy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2snig/qqq_vs_spy/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 07:07:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Considering investing in either QQQ or SPY but can’t determine which is the right one.  Or should I invest in both? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My DD shows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;— QQQ tracks the NASDAQ 100 Index, while SPY tracks the S&amp;amp;P 500 Index
— QQQ is 100 stocks in a handful of sectors, largely concentrated in tech. SPY is 500 stocks spread across all sectors
— looks like QQQ is already inside SPY while SPY is over 1/4 tech.l
— expense fees for QQQ is higher (at 0.20%) meanwhile SPY is cheaper (at 0.09%)
— NASDAQ 100 has beaten the S&amp;amp;P 500 over the past 10 years, generating an average annual return of 20.27% vs 14.26%
— QQQ assets has $201.39B while SPY has $417.28B&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is everyone else’s thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT:  leaning towards VOO (due to low expense ratio) and QQQ.  Since SPY and VOO are so similar I think lower expense ratio is the deciding factor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[血腥的一天，但添加了BA,OKE, CVX,UPS,FDX, VZ]]></title><description><![CDATA[長期看，但利用今天的下跌機會買入一些高質量的
公司。

波音公司。$197.45. (已在238美元處建倉 😕)

奧諾克 61.00美元

雪佛龍112.50美元

聯合包裹系統 204.85美元

聯邦快遞 $237.50

Verizon $51.60

不管是好是壞，我們都會看到結果。

如果你...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2u0pn/bloody_day_but_added_baoke_cvxupsfdx_vz/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2u0pn/bloody_day_but_added_baoke_cvxupsfdx_vz/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 06:29:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking long-term but use today’s selloff opportunities to buy some quality companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boeing.  $197.45. (Already has a position at $238 😕)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oneok         $61.00&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chevron  $112.50&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;United parcel system $204.85&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Federal Express.   $237.50&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verizon        $51.60&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For better or worse we will see what happens. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you purchased some shares today what did you buy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What did you want to buy that you did not buy?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[更多!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2qt2m/more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2qt2m/more/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 05:47:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[馬斯克反對補貼，特斯拉決定不爲德國電池廠提供國家援助]]></title><description><![CDATA[ * 特斯拉撤回對國家資金的申請
 * 馬斯克在推特上說，所有的補貼都應該被取消
 * 汽車廠建設進展順利--經濟部
 * 區域資金申請仍在進行中

柏林，11月26日（路透社）--特斯拉（TSLA.O）週五表示，它已經撤回了其
撤回申請...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2xgg0/tesla_decides_against_state_aid_for_german/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2xgg0/tesla_decides_against_state_aid_for_german/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 03:52:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tesla withdraws application for state funding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All subsidies should be eliminated, Musk tweets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Car plant construction progressing well - economy ministry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regional funding application still underway&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BERLIN, Nov 26 (Reuters) - Tesla (TSLA.O) said on Friday it has withdrawn its application for state aid for its planned battery factory near Berlin as CEO Elon Musk declared the electric vehicle maker opposed all subsidies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The European Union in January approved a plan that included giving state aid to Tesla, BMW (BMWG.DE) and others to support production of electric vehicle batteries and help the bloc to reduce imports from industry leader China.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla was expected to receive 1.14 billion euros ($1.28 billion) in EU funding for its battery plant in Gruenheide, Brandenburg under the plan, with a final decision likely by the end of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Tesla has informed the Federal Ministry of Economics and the Brandenburg Ministry of Economics... it is withdrawing its IPCEI application for state funding for the battery factory in Grünheide,&amp;quot; a Tesla spokesperson said, referring to European subsidies allocated to so-called &amp;#39;Important Projects of Common European Interest&amp;#39;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Construction plans for the plant would not be affected by the decision, the spokesperson said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;It has always been Tesla’s view that all subsidies should be eliminated,&amp;quot; Musk posted on Twitter in response to a tweet by another user after Tesla said it had withdrawn its funding application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;But that must include the massive subsidies for oil &amp;amp; gas. For some reason, governments don’t want to do that...,&amp;quot; Musk added, deviating from the subject of the factory grant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla itself is investing 5 billion euros in the battery plant, according to German economy ministry estimates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, construction of a car production site alongside the battery plant, which Tesla has begun building under pre-approval permits while it awaits final approval from the regional government, has made good progress in the last few weeks, a spokesperson for the federal economy ministry said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The electric vehicle maker also applied in November 2020 for regional funding from Brandenburg, according to the regional government&amp;#39;s website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Brandenburg economy ministry spokesperson said this application had not been withdrawn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The amount Tesla applied for is undisclosed, but investments worth over 100 million euros are generally given 6.8% of their value, the website says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The latest round of online consultations for the public to express environmental and other concerns about the car factory and battery plant closed last week and Tesla CEO Elon Musk has said he hopes to formally begin production by the end of the year and then ramp up as quickly as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Musk has made his irritation for German laws and processes known, saying in a letter to authorities in April that the country&amp;#39;s complex planning requirements were at odds with the urgency needed to fight climate change. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-withdrew-state-funding-application-german-battery-plant-economy-ministry-2021-11-26/&quot;&gt;https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-withdrew-state-funding-application-german-battery-plant-economy-ministry-2021-11-26/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[https://t.co/WYYPr7IR71]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464429941706182667</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464429941706182667</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 03:40:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[凱西-伍德在最新的CNBC採訪中把ARKK的目標價格更新爲~440]]></title><description><![CDATA[以前的目標，~310，5年內每年15%。

新目標，~440，5年內達到4倍，或5年內每年達到33%。

或以表格形式顯示

今天 2022 2023 2024 2025 2026 15% 155 178 205 236 271 312 33% 108 144 191 254
338 449]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2gt66/cathie_wood_updates_price_target_for_arkk_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2gt66/cathie_wood_updates_price_target_for_arkk_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 03:23:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous target, ~310, 15% per year for 5 years&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New Target, ~440, 4x in 5 years or 33% per year for 5 years&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or in table format&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Today&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2022&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2023&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2024&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2025&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;2026&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;15%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;155&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;178&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;205&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;236&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;271&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;312&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;33%&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;108&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;144&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;191&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;254&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;338&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;449&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bogleheads的方法只是針對富人的嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我對長期投資感興趣，並最終來到這裏，但我只是看到
人們投入40多萬，最後得到100萬。我沒有那麼多錢可以
我沒有那麼多錢投資，我有機會用小錢試試嗎？比如說更少。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r30qt2/is_bogleheads_method_just_for_rich_people/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r30qt2/is_bogleheads_method_just_for_rich_people/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 02:56:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m interested in investing money for long term and end up here, but I just see people who put 400k+ and end with a million. I don&amp;#39;t have that much money to invest, do I have a chance to try with little money? Like more little.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$PSFE Paysafe最近下跌了50%。反彈交易的好機會？]]></title><description><![CDATA[跌幅如此之大，似乎是因爲他們調整後的指引？這似乎是一個
跌幅極大，而且低於分析師目標價的下限。它正在
在日線圖上也出現了看漲的rsi背離。

誰能告訴我股價在這裏發生了什麼？看起來像
a...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2r9dk/psfe_paysafe_down_50_recently_good_opportunity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2r9dk/psfe_paysafe_down_50_recently_good_opportunity/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 02:40:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Down so dramatically seemingly because of their adjusted guidance? Seems like an extreme drop and it&amp;#39;s below the lower band of analyst price targets. It&amp;#39;s putting in a bullish rsi divergence on the daily chart too. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can someone fill me in on what&amp;#39;s going on with the stock price here? Looks like a good buying opportunity to me but I haven&amp;#39;t done much research yet. Hoping one of you has been looking into this and can shed some light. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[因此，市場在一天內下跌了2%以上。我們能從中預測到什麼嗎？答案可能不會讓你喫驚（是 "不能"）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，今天S&P500指數下跌了約2點左右，最終低於其ATH值約3%。
當然，市場比其ATH值低3%並不值得一提，但是
但它在一天內下降了兩個百分點的事實似乎引起了一些關注。
引起了一些關注。

因此，我想知道：市場上有多普遍的情況是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2xegl/so_the_market_dropped_by_more_than_2_in_a_day_can/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2xegl/so_the_market_dropped_by_more_than_2_in_a_day_can/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 02:40:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So today S&amp;amp;P500 dropped about 2 point something%, ending about 3% below its ATH. Of course, the market being 3% under its ATH is nothing to write home about, but the fact that it dropped by two percentage points in a single day seemed to raise some concerns.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I wondered: how common is it for the market to drop by two percentage points or more in a single day, and does this tell us anything about its likely return after, say, 100 days (this is likely much shorter than the time horizon of many of us here, but longer periods would likely make the effect - if any - of the drop harder to notice)? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I downloaded from yahoo finance  the daily S&amp;amp;P500 data for the 1994-2021 period and played around a little with it trying to see if any correlation could be found. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This graph shows the percentage change from the previous day versus the percentage return after 100 days: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/FzScbjp&quot;&gt;One day fluctuations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not seeing much of a correlation between one-day fluctuations and 100-days returns here. Also worth noting is that the days which saw a drop of 2% or more from the previous day were uncommon but not &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; uncommon (I found 299 of them in 6998 days, that is, about one every 23 days). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I tried anyway to try to see if I could find a correlation, just for completeness&amp;#39; sake, and the result is what you would expect from that graph: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/0Lt9SRt&quot;&gt;No correlation&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If anything, it would seem that the change from the previous day might be slightly &lt;em&gt;negatively&lt;/em&gt; correlated to the 100-days return - i.e., great days might lead to poorer returns after 100 days - but the correlation coefficient is so low and the standard error so high that the only reasonable conclusion is that one-day changes are of no predictive value for 100-days returns. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what about extremes? What if we consider only the &amp;quot;bad&amp;quot; days in which the market dropped by more than 2%? Here is what we get:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/6Pd1kN8&quot;&gt;Bad days&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let us compare this with the (235 out of 6998) days in which the market rose by more than 2%: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/q1Cl1eR&quot;&gt;Good days&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About the same mean, slightly lower standard deviation but that&amp;#39;s too close to say anything meaningful. For completeness&amp;#39;s sake, I also looked at the &amp;quot;meh days&amp;quot; in which the market did not change by more than 2% in either direction from the previous day: for those days, the average return after 100 days was by 4% - more or less in line with the others - and the standard deviation was by by 0.09 -- lower than the others, but not enough that I&amp;#39;d be confident making any conclusions out of this. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion: the fact that the market dropped by more than 2% today tells us nothing meaningful about what it will do in the next 100 days. Is it possible that the market will crash soon? Sure, that is always possible; but today&amp;#39;s drop, in itself, tells us nothing about its chances.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有沒有在新西蘭的Bogleheads？]]></title><description><![CDATA[與美國相比，新西蘭的投資和稅收情況略有不同。

如果有人感興趣，我很想比較一下最好的方法。

對於資產配置，我目前是這樣的。

 * 85%的AMP ACWI（60%美國/40%世界其他地區） - 69%對沖爲新西蘭元；以及

 * 15%的家庭偏見（簡單...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2xg0t/any_bogleheads_in_new_zealand/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2xg0t/any_bogleheads_in_new_zealand/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 01:04:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a slightly different investing and tax landscape in NZ compared to the US. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d be keen to compare notes on the best approach if anyone is interested.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For asset allocation, I’m currently:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;85% AMP ACWI (60% US / 40% rest of the world) - 69% hedged to NZD; and &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;15% home bias (Simplicity NZ Share a fund)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we approach retirement I’m looking to move toward 60% shares / 40% fixed interest.   Weighing up the pros/cons of moving out of PIE funds and investing direct.  Although I don’t like the currency risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Covid：是時候爲非洲服務了]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2v5f7/covid_its_time_for_africa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2v5f7/covid_its_time_for_africa/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 01:04:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼銀行對新的Covid變體新聞大跌眼鏡？]]></title><description><![CDATA[標題是不言自明的，但銀行和新的covid變體的嚴重下降趨勢背後的原因是什麼？
銀行和新的covid變體背後的原因是什麼？在我看來，如果通貨膨脹持續，銀行將從最有可能的加息中受益。
如果通貨膨脹持續下去，銀行將從最可能的加息中受益。有誰能說明一下
談談這個問題？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2q5zd/why_banks_go_down_heavily_on_new_covid_variant/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2q5zd/why_banks_go_down_heavily_on_new_covid_variant/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 23:55:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Title is self-explanatory, but what&amp;#39;s the reasoning behind the heavy downtrend of banks and the new covid variant?
The way I see it banks will benefit from the most than likely interest hike if inflation persists. 
Anyone can shed some light on this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[市場上的F**Cockatoo回來了！!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2r088/market_fck_cockatoo_is_back/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2r088/market_fck_cockatoo_is_back/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 23:29:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天的股票市場就像]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2xdc2/the_stock_market_today_be_like/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2xdc2/the_stock_market_today_be_like/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 23:29:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[中國因擔心安全問題要求滴滴出行從美國退市]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://archive.md/20211126053013/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-26/china-is-said-to-ask-didi-to-delist-from-u-s-on-security-fears

中國監管機構已要求滴滴全球公司的高管們制定一個計劃，以從美國退市。
熟悉此事的人士稱，滴滴全球公司的高管已經要求他們制定一個從美國證券市場退市的計劃，...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2m6n2/china_asks_didi_to_delist_from_us_on_security/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/r2m6n2/china_asks_didi_to_delist_from_us_on_security/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 23:07:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.md/20211126053013/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-26/china-is-said-to-ask-didi-to-delist-from-u-s-on-security-fears&quot;&gt;https://archive.md/20211126053013/https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-26/china-is-said-to-ask-didi-to-delist-from-u-s-on-security-fears&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chinese regulators have asked Didi Global Inc.’s top executives to devise a plan to delist from U.S. bourses, people familiar with the matter said, an unprecedented request that’s likely to revive fears about Beijing’s intentions for its giant tech industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The country’s tech watchdog wants management to take the company off the New York Stock Exchange because of concerns about leakage of sensitive data, the people said, asking not to be identified discussing a sensitive matter. The Cyberspace Administration of China, the agency responsible for data security in the country, has directed Didi to work out precise details, subject to government approval, they said.  Proposals under consideration include a straight-up privatization or a share float in Hong Kong followed by a delisting from the U.S., the people added. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the privatization proceeds, the proposal will likely be at least the $14 IPO price since a lower offer so soon after the June initial public offering could prompt lawsuits or shareholder resistance, the people said. If there is a secondary listing in Hong Kong, the IPO price would probably be a discount to the share price in the U.S., $8.11 as of Wednesday’s close. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shares in SoftBank Group Corp., Didi’s biggest minority shareholder, slid more than 5% in Tokyo. Deliberations continue and it’s possible regulators will backtrack on their request, the people said. Either option would deal a severe blow to a ride-hailing giant that pulled off the largest U.S. IPO by a Chinese firm since Alibaba Group Holding Ltd.’s in 2014. Representatives for Didi and the CAC didn’t respond to requests for comment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi sparked the ire of Beijing when it proceeded with its New York stock offering this summer, despite regulatory requests that it ensure the security of its data before the IPO. Chinese regulators quickly launched multiple investigations into the company and have considered a range of unprecedented penalties, Bloomberg News reported in July. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s possible that the delisting would be part of a package of punishments for Didi. Beijing’s municipal government has proposed an investment in the company that would give state-run firms effective control, Bloomberg News reported in September. Such an investment could help Didi finance the repurchase of its U.S.-traded shares. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi is currently controlled by the management team of co-founder Cheng Wei and President Jean Liu, which received aggregate voting power of 58% after the company’s U.S. initial public offering. SoftBank and Uber Technologies Inc. are Didi’s biggest minority shareholders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if Didi shifts its listing to Hong Kong, it will have to address the data security concerns that have drawn regulatory scrutiny. The company may have to give up control of its data to a third-party -- again undercutting its price tag.
Read more about Didi’s brushes with Beijing regulators&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regulators have weighed a delisting for Didi since the summer, after the world’s largest ride-hailing company infuriated officials by ploughing ahead with its U.S. IPO, Bloomberg News has reported. A withdrawal from U.S. bourses could stoke fears of an exodus of Chinese firms as Washington and Beijing quarrel about access to listed firms’ books. On Thursday, a senior Chinese regulatory official said such delistings would be a setback for relations with the U.S., while offering broad support for Hong Kong as an alternative venue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Didi -- once feted for defeating Uber in China -- has now become a test case for a broader Chinese government effort to curb the power of internet titans. Xi Jinping’s administration, keen to promote his vision of sharing the wealth or “common prosperity,” has targeted an internet sector that’s accumulated vast wealth by operating on the periphery of the law, minted an unprecedented number of billionaires and enriched local and foreign investors in the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A state-directed privatization would be unprecedented for a private firm of Didi’s stature, affirming that the Chinese government remains bent on curtailing the power of the country’s internet firms and unlocking the data and wealth hoarded during a decade of heady expansion. It would send a chilling signal to American investors, long accustomed to investing freely in China’s largest corporations from Alibaba to Baidu Inc. and JD.com Inc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beijing’s moves against Didi have been particularly harsh, even after a crackdown that has penalized giants like Alibaba and Tencent Holdings Ltd. The Cyberspace Administration of China saw Didi’s IPO decision as a challenge to the central government’s authority, which led to the CAC, the Ministry of Public Security, the Ministry of State Security and several other agencies initiating on-site inspections at Didi’s offices in July.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s since been ensnared by probes into data security and the way it treats its millions of drivers. Many of the options Beijing is weighing involve re-asserting state control over a company that’s traditionally operated in a legal gray zone, Bloomberg News has reported.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[醒來查看我的SPY看漲期權值多少錢]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2pbv0/waking_up_to_check_how_much_money_my_spy_calls/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2pbv0/waking_up_to_check_how_much_money_my_spy_calls/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 22:37:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[書籍推薦]]></title><description><![CDATA[除了《Boglehead投資指南》，你還會推薦哪些關於投資的書籍？
投資指南之外，還有哪些關於投資的書籍？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2q1y4/book_recommendations/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2q1y4/book_recommendations/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 21:43:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What books would you recommend on investing beyond the Boglehead guide to investing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天的交易策略在12秒內完成]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2ni8n/todays_trading_strategy_in_12_seconds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2ni8n/todays_trading_strategy_in_12_seconds/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 21:43:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天有誰在進行稅收損失收割？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的新資金一直在進入債券和國際市場，所以我今天在美國ETF上沒有任何損失。
今天在美國ETF上的損失。我在國際市場上已經超過了TLH的門檻。

今天有誰在收穫稅收損失嗎？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2qzda/anyone_tax_loss_harvesting_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/r2qzda/anyone_tax_loss_harvesting_today/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 21:14:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My new money has been going into bonds and international, so I don’t have any losses on US ETFs today. I am over a TLH threshold for international. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anybody tax loss harvesting today?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[r/Stocks 每日討論與基本面 2021年11月26日星期五]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是每日討論，所以任何與股票有關的東西都可以，但今天的主題是基本面。
今天的主題是基本面，但如果基本面不是你的事，那麼就
忽略這個主題和/或發表你反對基本面的論點......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2kb5u/rstocks_daily_discussion_fundamentals_friday_nov/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2kb5u/rstocks_daily_discussion_fundamentals_friday_nov/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 20:53:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the daily discussion, so anything stocks related is fine, but the theme for today is on fundamentals, but if fundamentals aren&amp;#39;t your thing then just ignore the theme and/or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+%22r%2Fstocks+semiannual+arguments+against+TA%22&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;post your arguments against fundamentals here&lt;/a&gt; and not in the current post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some helpful day to day links, including news:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finviz.com/quote.ashx?t=spy&quot;&gt;Finviz&lt;/a&gt; for charts, fundamentals, and aggregated news on individual stocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/markets&quot;&gt;Bloomberg market news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;StreetInsider news:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Market+Check&quot;&gt;Market Check&lt;/a&gt; - Possibly why the market is doing what it&amp;#39;s doing including sudden spikes/dips&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Reuters&quot;&gt;Reuters aggregated&lt;/a&gt; - Global news&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most fundamentals are updated every 3 months due to the fact that corporations release earnings reports every quarter, so traders are always speculating at what those earnings will say, and investors may change the size of their holdings based on those reports.  Expect a lot of volatility around earnings, but it usually doesn&amp;#39;t matter if you&amp;#39;re holding long term, but keep in mind the importance of earnings reports because a trend of declining earnings or a decline in some other fundamental will drive the stock down over the long term as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the following word cloud and click through for the wiki:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/wiki/fundamentals-themed-post&quot;&gt;Market Cap - Shares Outstanding - Volume - Dividend - EPS - P/E Ratio - EPS Q/Q - PEG - Sales Q/Q - Return on Assets (ROA) - Return on Equity (ROE) - BETA - SMA - quarterly earnings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a basic question, for example &amp;quot;what is EBITDA,&amp;quot; then google &amp;quot;investopedia EBITDA&amp;quot; and click the Investopedia article on it; do this for everything until you have a more in depth question or just want to share what you learned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Useful links:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/fundamental-analysis-4689757/&quot;&gt;Investopedia page&lt;/a&gt; on fundamental analysis including &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/university/dcf/&quot;&gt;Discounted Cash Flow&lt;/a&gt; analysis; see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/d/dcf.asp&quot;&gt;definition here&lt;/a&gt; and read &lt;a href=&quot;http://i.investopedia.com/inv/pdf/tutorials/fundamentalanalysis_intro.pdf&quot;&gt;their PDF on the topic.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finviz.com/quote.ashx?t=aapl&quot;&gt;FINVIZ&lt;/a&gt; for fundamental data, charts, and aggregated news&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.earningswhispers.com/stocks/aapl&quot;&gt;Earnings Whisper&lt;/a&gt; for earnings details&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See our past &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+%22r%2Fstocks+daily+discussion%22&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;daily discussions here.&lt;/a&gt;  Also links for:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Atechnicals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Technicals&lt;/a&gt; Tuesday, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Aoptions&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Options Trading&lt;/a&gt; Thursday, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Afundamentals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Fundamentals&lt;/a&gt; Friday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美國禁止南非、博茨瓦納、津巴布韋、納米比亞、萊索托、埃斯瓦蒂尼、莫桑比克和馬拉維的旅行。

聽起來像種族主義者]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464309113484107784</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464309113484107784</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 20:41:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不得不把經典帶回來]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2s89n/had_to_bring_back_the_classic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2s89n/had_to_bring_back_the_classic/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 20:25:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你是否同意，B.1.1.529 "可怕的 "殺手病毒株（50個尖峯蛋白突變）現在將成爲任何做空備忘錄股票的人的保證金調用催化劑？]]></title><description><![CDATA[該病毒突變還有其他10個基因突變。世衛組織召開緊急
會議。航空公司關閉旅行。市場跌宕起伏。截至本報告撰寫時爲止。
道瓊斯指數期貨下跌850點，羅素2000指數期貨下跌4.5%。

我和我的朋友們進行了一些討論，說單是這一點就可以...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2iejk/do_you_agree_that_the_b11529_horrific_killer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2iejk/do_you_agree_that_the_b11529_horrific_killer/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:59:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The virus mutation also has 10 other genetic mutations.  WHO convening emergency meeting.  Airlines shutting down travel.  Markets tumbling.  As of this writing, DOW futures are down 850 points, and russel 2000 index futures are down 4.5%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some talks with my friends going on about how this alone could serve as a GME, AMC &amp;#39;MOASS&amp;#39; catalyst, since collateral and margin maintenance requirements.  With markets crashing like this, the NSCC algos do indeed raise capital requirements.  What are your thoughts on the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GME, AMC, and other meme stocks have a negative beta and therefore serve as a hedge against falling markets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;These stocks remain heavily shorted, and therefore, funds that are stuck in egregious short positions have to buy to cover to get out, and potentially very quickly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.1.1.529 &amp;#39;horrific&amp;#39; killer virus strain could induce this market catalyst (as unfortunate as that is to say that it came to this in order to have free and fair markets).  Thoughts?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[南部非洲出現一個嚴重變異的Covid變體

扯淡]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464136788583329792</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1464136788583329792</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:35:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[投資與交易。什麼是最簡單的財富積累方式？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我從今年2月開始投資，在股市中存入了26,000美元。
股票市場，目前我已經達到33,014美元，所以到目前爲止我賺了25%的利潤。我的
我的投資組合目前由九隻股票組成。我一直在研究期權
交易，這涉及高風險，但可以帶來高回報......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r24bqb/investing_vs_trading_what_is_the_easiest_way_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r24bqb/investing_vs_trading_what_is_the_easiest_way_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:34:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been investing since February of this year with $26,000 deposited in the stock market and I’m currently up to $33,014 so I made a 25% profit so far. My portfolio currently consists of nine stocks. I’ve been looking into options trading recently which involves high risk but can give high returns if I know what I’m doing. However, investing in established companies is obviously safer but takes longer to build wealth unless I have at least $200,000 in the market, and I can’t afford to deposit anywhere near that amount right now. Between investing in a diverse set of stocks, investing in two or three startup company stocks that may blow up one day, or doing options trading, which of these strategies do you think would be the easiest for building significant wealth within ten years?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[謝謝你的保險金]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2pexn/thanks_for_the_insurance_money/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2pexn/thanks_for_the_insurance_money/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:34:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有誰在DCA-ing進入迪士尼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[迪斯尼是官方的，遠遠低於我的平均成本154美元。
現在已經跌到了148美元。我一直在穩定地購買更多的股票
但不想落入落井下石的怪圈。

還有人買入更多的迪士尼嗎？有什麼我應該注意的嗎，或者這只是
覬覦者...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2qwft/anyone_dcaing_into_disney/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2qwft/anyone_dcaing_into_disney/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 18:49:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disney is official well below my average cost of $154. It was at $200 at one point and now has crashed down to $148. I’ve been steadily buying more shares but don’t want to fall into the falling knife thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone else buying more of Disney? Anything I should be aware of or is this just a covid scare?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[來自越南弱智的黑色星期五快樂! 我應該賣出還是持有我的MRNA看漲期權？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2orio/happy_blackfriday_from_a_vietnamese_retard_should/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2orio/happy_blackfriday_from_a_vietnamese_retard_should/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 18:49:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我就發這個帖子，希望市場能轉綠。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2oe7s/ima_just_post_this_in_hopes_of_the_market_turning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2oe7s/ima_just_post_this_in_hopes_of_the_market_turning/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 17:48:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特爾重返GPU市場對Nvidia的影響是否被低估了？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我注意到，這裏的大多數人都非常看好Nvidia，即使在其目前的估值下也是如此。
但我沒有看到很多關於英特爾重返GPU市場將如何影響Nvidia的估值和未來增長的討論。
但我沒有看到很多關於英特爾重返GPU市場將如何影響Nvidia的估值和未來增長的討論。

英特爾擁有資金和人才，尤其是在拉賈-科杜裏的領導下。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2l9n8/is_the_impact_of_intel_returning_to_the_gpu/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/r2l9n8/is_the_impact_of_intel_returning_to_the_gpu/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 17:48:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have noticed that most people on here are very bullish towards Nvidia even at its current valuation but I haven&amp;#39;t seen much talk about how Intel&amp;#39;s return to the GPU market will affect Nvidia&amp;#39;s valuation and future growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intel has the money and talent especially with Raja Koduri leading the Graphics department to become highly competitive with Nvidia if not a leader in the market. Intel will also have the advantage of using their new fabs in the future to produce their GPU&amp;#39;s whereas Nvidia will be reliant on TSMC/Samsung.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With AMD also becoming more competitive and both Intel and AMD not being as limited to just the GPU market unlike Nvidia, should people be worried that Nvidia may have to lower profit margins and suffer from lower growth that could make their current price look extremely high?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For disclosure I do own some INTC and would be interested in NVDA if the valuation was more reasonable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NVDA電話已經準備好了，今天要跟我幹架了]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2iqrz/nvda_calls_are_ready_to_fck_me_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/r2iqrz/nvda_calls_are_ready_to_fck_me_today/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 17:34:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>