<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 22:46:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[How much do you allocate for Large/Mid/Small caps?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Normally I’d just “VT and Chill” but I have a limited fund selection in my 401K.
The plan then would be something like this, but I worry the Smallcap allocation
is a bit too high looking at target date funds for reference:

70% FID 500 Index (FXAIX)

20% FID MID CAP IDX (FSMDX)

10% FID SM CAP IDX…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrox4q/how_much_do_you_allocate_for_largemidsmall_caps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrox4q/how_much_do_you_allocate_for_largemidsmall_caps/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 22:24:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Normally I’d just &lt;em&gt;“VT and Chill”&lt;/em&gt; but I have a limited fund selection in my 401K. The plan then would be something like this, but I worry the Smallcap allocation is a bit too high looking at target date funds for reference:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;70% FID 500 Index (FXAIX)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;20% FID MID CAP IDX (FSMDX)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;10% FID SM CAP IDX (FSSNX)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently I’m just doing a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TRowePrice Target Date Fund&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (TRPLX — it’s the only TDF available to me in the 401K), but the Expense Ratio on that is nearly half a percent (0.46) so I’m weighing just switching it over to the Fidelity SP500 + Fidelity Mid / Fidelity Small cap (significantly lower expense ratios).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly there aren’t any good options for International or Bond Funds in my 401K (options are all actively managed with laughable expense ratios) so I’d have to get those in my Taxable/Roth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I’ve done is look at Target Date Funds and it looks like Schwab for example allocates about 20% to mid cap and about 6% to Small cap. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I analyzed $SOFI so you don't have to]]></title><description><![CDATA[SOFI Technologies, Inc. is an online personal finance company. They provide a
range of lending and wealth management services. At the time of this post, they
are trading at about $23.65. They released earnings for Q3 on November 10. They
reported Revenue of $272.01 million for the 3rd quarter of…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qru1ch/i_analyzed_sofi_so_you_dont_have_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qru1ch/i_analyzed_sofi_so_you_dont_have_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 22:24:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOFI Technologies, Inc. is an online personal finance company. They provide a range of lending and wealth management services. At the time of this post, they are trading at about $23.65. They released earnings for Q3 on November 10. They reported Revenue of $272.01 million for the 3rd quarter of 2021 which is a 35.5% increase from the same prior-year period. SoFi beat estimates by $16.38M. Furthermore, they added 377,000 new members which is the second-highest quarterly increase in the company&amp;#39;s history. That being said, SoFi looks to be a potential buy. Not convinced yet? Here are some other reasons why I believe SoFi is a good company to buy into. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SoFi’s total members grew 96% Year-over-Year. Part of the reason why this occurred is because the products they offer have doubled Year-over-Year. The company beat Revenue Expectations, Earnings Per Share, almost doubled their member growth Year-over-Year and began offering way more products. Most people can find a product that suits them through SoFi’s financial services. In Quarter 3, they did a great job at  demonstrating their ability to capture market share. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SoFi has increased the amount of marketing they’ve been doing. They’ve been working with influencers across Twitter, Instagram, Youtube, and Tik Tok. Which has driven an additional 400 Million impressions and 775K engagements with SoFi content. SoFi has been investing a lot in their marketing strategy and attempts to acquire customers which has obviously translated into very great results. By the looks of it, SoFi has started to get creative in adopting additional customers. These new strategies could help boost the company by a lot. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In relation to their valuation, SoFi experienced strong growth which was driven by the growth of users they had experienced and the products they offer, especially in the personal loans sector. Right now, the company looks like it’s trading at a decent price in comparison with other companies in this sector. If the company can somehow increase their Earnings before interest, taxes, depreciation, and amortization over the years coming, they could see it’s multiples inflate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve made it this far into this post you’re probably asking yourself, Are there any risks involved with investing in this company? Like any investment, there is always a risk. Despite the fact that SoFi reported a strong quarter, they need to show that they can keep up their strength. The stock continuing to go up will be contingent on continued success and an increase in profitability over the future quarters. That being said, I wouldn’t say this is a strong buy, but a potential one. It could be a great buy if it dips again. However, This company is currently trading at reasonable multiples. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading everyone! If you have any questions let me know in the comments below or feel free to message me! I hope this helped you figure out whether or not to buy into SoFi. Also, feel free to check out my profile and see the analysis I did on Digital Turbine AKA $APPS. You will definitely learn something from it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Understanding and Profiting from our Current Inflationary Environment]]></title><description><![CDATA[Inflation is a persistent issue coming out of the COVID lockdown economy and
continues to create a great amount of confusion for the retail investor space.
Many retail traders don't know what it means or how to respond. More
specifically, many are having trouble with tailoring their portfolios to…]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrtkox/understanding_and_profiting_from_our_current/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrtkox/understanding_and_profiting_from_our_current/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 22:24:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inflation is a persistent issue coming out of the COVID lockdown economy and continues to create a great amount of confusion for the retail investor space. Many retail traders don&amp;#39;t know what it means or how to respond. More specifically, many are having trouble with tailoring their portfolios to either avoid risk or take advantage of inflationary circumstances. I aim to somewhat remedy this. I hope the pointers below will help you better understand the inflationary environment and identify economically favorable industries/sectors. This is not the end all or be all and I welcome your observations and comments on what I could have missed. Enjoy this and lets make some money taking advantage of these once in a lifetime economic circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inflations is Measured by a Change in Rate:&lt;/strong&gt; Inflation doesn&amp;#39;t usually go down. The RATE of inflation goes up or down, but inflation itself is persistent. This is by design. Could you imagine what would happen to the economy if you knew that your dollar would be worth more tomorrow than it is today? Spending on goods other than necessities would come to a very dramatic reduction (&lt;em&gt;Note: You might be rethinking crypto right now huh?&lt;/em&gt;). So it is important to understand that what we are looking at is the CHANGE IN RATE of inflation. There is no deflation!! Deflation is 1000x worse for the economy than inflation. So do not expect deflation. The Fed simply will not allow it. Nor should they!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Current Inflation is Largely a Result of too Much Demand:&lt;/strong&gt; During the COVID lock downs many businesses were forced to grind their operations to a halt. Remember food, toilet paper, &amp;amp; other essentials flying off the shelves? Indeed many grocery stores were limiting the amount of water you could buy. It only stands to reason that when you force businesses to close down you create a situation where the goods that people demand are not being replaced by a steady supply. So what happens as the economy opens back up? Suddenly those same businesses have reduced inventories, they need to hire back workers, they need to order new supplies, &amp;amp; they need to meet an increased demand as a result of some competitors closing their doors for good. Now the quantity of goods demanded well exceeds the quantity of goods supplied ... on all fronts. Reopening firms are competing against other reopening firms for the same raw materials, supplies, resources, shipping, etc. They are also competing for the same labor pool. Remember that goods &amp;amp; services in times of extreme scarcity go to the highest bidder.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secondary &amp;amp; Tertiary Effects of too Much Demand (Or too Little Supply):&lt;/strong&gt; Below you will find the inflationary issues we find ourselves in as a result of increased demand and limited supply. Below each topic you will also find some examples of how to profit from each. You will also receive some examples of secondary and tertiary effects of each.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Supply Chain Bottlenecks:&lt;/strong&gt; First and foremost in the news are the supply chain bottlenecks. We&amp;#39;ve all seen the ships floating off the Port of Los Angeles, or the very long line of trucks waiting to pick up freight from the ports. The United States &amp;amp; Europe have but a limited number of ports and they&amp;#39;re taking on all the supplies that firms ordered as the economy opened back up. Making things worse ... its holiday shopping season. So cost of shipping dry bulk overseas is not just rising as a result of increased demand, but as a result of the fact that it costs money to have all these carriers waiting weeks to offload their goods. Making matters worse many of the imported goods are perishables which can spoil and reduce the supply of foodstuffs amid an already high demand. As a result many firms are opting for alternative methods of shipping like the much more expensive option of air freight.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: Moderately bullish on sea freight carriers, rail, trucking, logistics, logistics outsourcing, and air freight&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Supply Chain Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; As if the bottlenecks weren&amp;#39;t bad enough, there are but a limited number of domestic shipping firms. Firms that not only transport materials to businesses, or, finished goods to retailers, but also delivering orders to retail shoppers. Here we are once again talking about rail, trucking, mail delivery, air freight, logistics firms, logistics outsourcing, etc. So yet again we have an increased demand for shipping and logistics with but a limited supply. And while this demand will keep up for some time, many firms know it will eventually come back down to normal, and therefore, are very hesitant to expand too fast too quickly for fear that they will one day have too much fleet for future business.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: Moderately bullish on rail, trucking, logistics, logistics outsourcing, and air freight&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Semiconductor Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; Everything these days has a semiconductor. Whether its semiconductors, passive semiconductors, diodes, you name it, chances are if it was an electronic made in the last 5 years, it needs a semiconductor to properly operate. Indeed before the supply chain shortages hit critical mass, we were dealing with semiconductor shortages. Now we will not likely fix the semiconductor issue until we fix the supply chain issue. Once again as the economy opened back up &amp;amp; demand skyrocketed, semiconductors too experienced a complementary spike in demand. Semiconductors alone are preventing the automakers from producing at full capacity. There are not enough semiconductors to make vehicles. And with the holidays on the horizon semiconductors are in higher demand than ever. Even Sony had to reduce the number of PlayStations they could manufacture and ship due to component shortages and logistics issues. So expect the price of any new electronic device that has a semiconductor to increase in price.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: Bullish on electronics &amp;amp; semiconductors&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vehicle Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; As noted with the semiconductors, vehicles are in short supply. As a result the quantity of vehicles demanded exceed the quantity of vehicles supplied. Therefore we not only have a shortage of vehicles but the price o vehicles have skyrocketed. Have you seen the empty lots at your local dealership? There&amp;#39;s nothing to sell! People are ordering direct from factory. As a result people turned toward used vehicles which now are also in short supply. As a result people who could not afford the increased price of used vehicles resulted to maintaining their current vehicles. And as a result of people maintaining their current vehicles, the demand for auto parts &amp;amp; auto mechanics have skyrocketed. And I don&amp;#39;t know many large firms that do not need a frequent supply of vehicles to maintain operations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Note:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Moderately bullish to bullish on used car firms, auto parts, and car repair&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;**)**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Raw Material Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; Raw materials were the first to explode out of COVID. Wood, steel, ore, oil, &amp;amp; minerals ... you name it, its all going up. The quantity of supply demanded exceed the current supply ... and for many reasons.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Note:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Moderately bullish on miners, steel, mining equipment suppliers, and oil/gas producers ... see energy shortage below for more detail on oil/gas&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;**)**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Increased Demand for Housing:&lt;/strong&gt; Largely as a result of low interest rates incentivizing lending, we experienced a housing and construction boom in the middle of a Pandemic. Houses and industrial builds in many areas have skyrocketed in value. But this was not only as a result of low interest rates. When the federal government instituted a ban on evictions from rental properties, many took advantage by simply not paying their rent. The forgone payments to the landlord forced the renter to pass on the costs on to new tenants, which increased the cost of rental properties beyond that just owning a home in many areas. So people bought homes instead. Moreover many people moved out of urban areas to escape burdensome COVID restrictions which furthermore increased the demand of housing. Furthermore lifetime renting millennials saw the low interest rates as a great time to buy their first home. Finally, mortgage forbearance reduced a lot of foreclosures during COVID. Less foreclosures means less supply, less supply amid high demand results in higher prices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Note:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Not very bullish on housing &amp;amp; real estate at this time but still moderately bullish on construction, furniture, paint, fixtures, and infrastructure&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;**).**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Energy Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; As we began to put the COVID economy behind us, more people are travelling to work, to school, and going on vacation. More recently international travel is opening back up.  Moreover firms are expanding rapidly to meet demand and shippers are using more energy than ever. This all of course increases the price of oil, natural gas, jet fuel, and the fuel you pay at the pump. Making matters worse, no matter what your politics are, the current administration in the White House is the most ardently unfriendly domestic coal and fossil fuel administrations we&amp;#39;ve had in 5 years. OPEC, perhaps realizing that such demand will be but temporary for the next 1-2 years, refuses to entertain the Biden administrations request to ramp up oil supply. Oddly enough big oil hasn&amp;#39;t been in this good of a position for the last 4 years where the increase of supply made it seriously hard for oil firms to profit. Energy is used for producing everything. When energy goes up the cost of everything goes up. When energy goes up, people spend more on energy and less on other things. So the increase in energy costs are a result of both increased post COVID demand and politics. Of all the issues we are experiencing with inflated prices, energy is among the easiest to fix.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Note: B&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;ullish on oil, natural gas, oil and natural gas equipment maintainers and suppliers, and perhaps oil exploration if the Biden administration would quit putting up road blocks&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;**)**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Worker Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;quot;Worker Shortages&amp;quot; is misleading. When people think of a &amp;quot;worker shortage&amp;quot; they generally think that we don&amp;#39;t have enough workers to meet demand. They would be correct. But we should phrase it as &amp;quot;firms do not have enough workers to meet CURRENT demand.&amp;quot; Lets face it we are rear view looking creatures. Simply because a firm doesn&amp;#39;t have enough workers does not indicate that they cant beat previous profit/revenue, but rather they can not only beat previous revenue projections, but also be in a position where they cannot meet CURRENT demand. And just like anything else, when the quantity of labor demanded exceeds the quantity of labor supplied, we run into increased labor costs ... namely wages. And wages are overwhelmingly the highest cost for most firms. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Note:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bullish on staffing and outsourcing firms&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;**)**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secondary &amp;amp; Tertiary Effects of too Much Demand ... Conclusion:&lt;/strong&gt; Lets keep this simple. You want to buy a car. That car is made from raw materials such as aluminum &amp;amp; steel. The car requires electronics. Those electronics require semiconductors. You need a labor force to put that car together. You need energy to manufacture that car. You need truckers &amp;amp; freighters to ship those cars or bring manufacturers the materials to make cars. You need equipment to make cars. In short 100% of the price of all components of that car, or the components used to make that car, have gone up. Still, you have a high demand market where people and businesses require vehicles, but the manufacturer cant meet that demand due to the lack of supplies available. Nevertheless the vehicle manufacturer still needs to pay for overhead costs to keep the doors open. And as so many people are demanding such a short supply of cars, the manufacturers simply increase the price of that car to meet the demand of the highest paying bidders. And this phenomenon is happening in each step of the chain to make that car from the folks who supply the materials, to the folks who produce the energy, to the folks who ship the finished product. When the quantity of goods demanded exceed the quantity of goods supplied, prices necessarily must go up.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monetary Drivers of Inflation:&lt;/strong&gt;  As a result of the dramatic initial downward shift in demand amid COVID lockdowns, the Federal Reserve made money cheap, essentially lowering interests rates to both incentivize borrowing and make borrowing more affordable. The result? Massive influxes of borrowing and lending which in turn flooded the economy with cash. At first this excess cash was used to make it through the pandemic. Later this cash was used by firms to expand rapidly to meet demand. People also used cheap money via extremely low interest rates to purchase homes, which increased the demand for housing. Eventually the Fed is going to need to raise interest rates to disincentive lending and cool off a hot economy. If allowed to persist for too long the influx of cash will lead to investments by firms looking to to stave off losing the value of money via inflation and thereby creating a massive bubble. There are already indicators of this happening by virtue of equity valuations in the market. (&lt;em&gt;Note: the Fed has also been incentivizing investment in the stock market by buying treasury bonds on the secondary market which resulted in keeping the yields artificially low. As a result people were less inclined to buy treasury bonds and more incentivized to invest in other equity&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Government Drivers of Inflation:&lt;/strong&gt; The rapid inflation we are experiencing has not deterred President Biden for advocating for trillions in spending measures. The U.S. Government is a customer just like anyone else, and the government competes for the same goods and services you and I do. Increased spending will to some extent result in crowding out the private sector that competes for the same goods and services. Remember that an increase in demand with limited supply generally results increased prices. If the government spends too much, it can seriously hurt consumers in the form of increased prices. Moreover the Biden administration isn&amp;#39;t the most friendly administration when it comes to mining for coal, oil, minerals, etc.. This inevitably leads to increased costs of energy and raw materials. (&lt;em&gt;Note: This comment used a political figure as an example of a negative economic consequence. Do me a favor, take the example for what its worth to you, and realize I am not going to entertain heated political discussion. There is a cost and benefit to everything, and I don&amp;#39;t have the time to entertain the talking points you pulled from a political webpage or favorable news site and tell you why you&amp;#39;re wrong, when no matter how much the evidence is stacked against you, you&amp;#39;re not going to change your mind anyway. Ergo a massive waste of time that benefits no one&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inflation is Excellent for Debt!:&lt;/strong&gt; I will keep this one quick. Lets say you took out a 30 year fixed mortgage in 1990. You paid $90,000 for your home and have a mortgage of $400 per month. In the year 2019 your home is now worth $200,000 in market value but you&amp;#39;re still paying $400 per month at a fixed rate. Through inflation your wages have eventually increased while your fixed rate mortgage remained stagnant. In short, you may have been scrimping for pennies when you took out the mortgage, but years later you can make your payment while working at a fast food restaurant. Neat huh? Inflation is excellent for debt ridden companies. As their profit margins increase over time through inflation they will find it much easier to pay off their long term debt. (&lt;em&gt;Note: Perhaps this put some of the companies you were looking at into better perspective, and if debt was a major factor for not investing, then you may or may not want to revisit your decision.&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bullish Sectors You Can Profit From that I did not Mention Above:&lt;/strong&gt; Industrial Chemicals, Industrial Equipment, Fertilizers, Farm Equipment/Construction, and Pesticides. As firms ramp up production they will increase the demand for industrial chemicals. Moreover, as food prices continue to increase the more land farmers will be incentivized to clear for additional farming which requires more farming construction, farming equipment, chemicals/pesticides, and fertilizers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Canary in the Inflation Coal Mine:&lt;/strong&gt; If the change in prices rise beyond the change in incomes to the point where people need to start economizing their necessities and forgoing their wants, we could be looking at a very serious correction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/strong&gt; I hope the pointers above have helped you better understand the inflationary environment and identify economically favorable industries/sectors. Please understand that I will be reading this over and over again to identify typos &amp;amp; unclear sentences. I may even edit it as people bring ideas to my attention. Anyway I hope you enjoyed it and can turn this into long term investment opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[科技股、半導體股是否考慮到了中國可能入侵臺灣？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在很多人不情願的情況下，我以我認爲很便宜的價格買了臺積電。最初的不情願來自於一個簡單的擔心：中國可能會破壞臺積電的發展。
最初的不情願來自於一種簡單的恐懼：中國可能會擾亂中國的經濟。
地區。

現在，我不想談政治。我對地緣政治沒有太大的興趣，而且
我傾向於在購買時忽略這些影響因素。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrlnmy/do_tech_semicondutor_stocks_take_in_consideration/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrlnmy/do_tech_semicondutor_stocks_take_in_consideration/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 21:59:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a lot of reluctance I bought TSMC for what I consider a bargain price. The initial reluctance comes from a simple fear: China’s possible disruption of the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I don’t wanna get political. I have not much interest over geopolitics, and I tend to ignore such influences when buying a business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eventually I came to a conclusion: If TSMC is under threat, so is Apple, AMD, and many other industries for that matter. In fact, every single company on this planet has some exposure if China invades Taiwan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But at the end of the day we cannot paralyze ourselves and wait for a possible tragedy that may or may not happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the stock market does not compute the macro bc the macro is impossible to be predicated. So What you guys think?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我被邀請加入我公司的401k委員會。有什麼建議，我應該提出什麼問題或建議？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們有一個10人的401k審查委員會，在我們的CFO發現我對投資的熱情後，我被邀請加入。
CFO發現了我對投資的外在熱情。有什麼建議可以告訴我
應該注意什麼？

背景。我們使用富達公司。我在公司已經工作了4年，對
我已經在公司工作了4年，對公司的情況有了相當好的瞭解...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrqced/i_was_invited_to_join_my_companys_401k_committee/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrqced/i_was_invited_to_join_my_companys_401k_committee/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 21:47:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have a 10-person 401k review committee and I&amp;#39;ve been asked to join after our CFO caught onto my outwardly enthusiasm for investing. Any tips as to what I should be paying attention to? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Background: We use Fidelity. I&amp;#39;ve been at the company for 4 years and have a pretty good understanding of the basics when it comes to retirement accounts. I already contribute the IRS max but am curious about contributing more via mega backdoor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這就是美國 
https://t.co/5hO930dHv0]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458856640598487049</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458856640598487049</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 21:35:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[滾蛋的素食主義者]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrs7oa/fuck_off_vegans/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrs7oa/fuck_off_vegans/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 21:34:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$SFT Shift Technologies要印刷了]]></title><description><![CDATA[在過去的三年裏，Shift公司積累了大量的二手車庫存。
導致了二手車價格的空前飆升。他們的時機（主要是
他們的時機（主要是運氣）不可能更完美。更重要的是，他們
具體而言，他們積累了大量的庫存，這些庫存以前是10...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrodnr/sft_shift_technologies_is_going_to_print/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrodnr/sft_shift_technologies_is_going_to_print/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 21:19:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shift has amassed a HUGE amount of pre-owned inventory in the past three years leading up to this unprecedented surge in used car prices. Their timing (mostly by sheer luck) could not have been more perfect. More importantly, they specifically have amassed a huge inventory of what were previously 10-20k cars to appeal to the lower/middle income demographic. This range has appreciated more than any range of used vehicle. We’re talking 50-60% from a couple years ago in many cases. Best part is, used car prices continue to skyrocket as supply shortages and inflation show no signs of retreat. At some point the carousel will stop but until then I think Shift will experience rapid growth and profitability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anecdotally, I have heard more and more people talk about buying from Shift, and it’s relative ease compared to Carvana.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shift is rapidly stealing market share from Carvana, yet is valued at only 600mil to Carvana’s 49Bil valuation. For whatever it’s worth, last I checked it’s short interest was about 22%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shift reports earnings today after market close. I think it’s a nice opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;100 1/2023 $10C&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[父母退休後有100%的股票IRA。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我和退休的父母聊天時，他們告訴我，今年他們在IRA的總價值爲37.5萬至40萬的資金中增加了7萬。
IRA總價值爲37.5萬-40萬，但倉位是100%的大盤基金。

父母已經退休，正在領取已故配偶的養老金。退休後
財務狀況是我不熟悉的，但我的理解是......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrsr4o/parent_has_100_stocks_ira_post_retirement/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrsr4o/parent_has_100_stocks_ira_post_retirement/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 20:56:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Was chatting with my retired parent who told me they were up 70k this year in IRA worth a total of 375k - 400k but position is 100% Large Cap fund.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Parent is retired and receiving deceased spouses pension. Post-retirement financials are something I am not familiar with, but my understanding is she should transition to a large percentage of bonds at this point to significantly lessen her risk tolerance (60/40 or 50/50?). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a little overwhelmed of what to recommend. I think she should speak to a fiduciary possibly?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for any guidance or if a suggestion of a different subreddit that would be more appropriate. I have learned a lot here about my own retirement savings so wanted to ask here first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[羅賓漢是垃圾]]></title><description><![CDATA[今天，我又一次被Robinhood的另一個故障所擊倒。對於那些
的人，或者沒有受到影響的人，我今天醒來時
上午（在我4天週末的第一天）。檢查了我的投資組合後看到
我最大的頭寸上漲了5.2%。一種偉大的感覺! 我登錄了...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrtijr/robinhood_is_garbage/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrtijr/robinhood_is_garbage/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 20:31:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once again, I was let down today by YET ANOTHER glitch in Robinhood. For those of you who don’t already know, or who were not affected by it, I woke up this morning (on my first day of a 4 day weekend). Checked my portfolio after seeing my biggest position was up 5.2%. A great feeling! I logged in and saw all my options moved from out of to in the money, and I was up a couple hundred on my shares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robinhood did not update my portfolio balance and I figured it was bad WiFi. I switched to LTE. Same thing. Then I was hit with an unexpected error message, so I restarted the app. Then, I get told I could not log in. With the recent hacks, I became nervous. I did a web search and found that “several users were experiencing problems with login preventing them from logging into their account”. One hour later, I log back in to see that the moment I was checking my account I was up $2,000 and was now up $500. I love the Robinhood interface and commission free trades but damn. That was the last straw&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[願望袋持有者現在是這個分論壇的傳銷獵手。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrl1c1/wish_bagholders_are_the_mlm_huns_of_this/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrl1c1/wish_bagholders_are_the_mlm_huns_of_this/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 19:50:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[中央銀行對大流行病的對策總結]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrf5jb/a_summary_of_the_measured_response_by_central/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrf5jb/a_summary_of_the_measured_response_by_central/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 19:37:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[恆大確認違約後，香港和上海指數上漲超過1%。這對市場來說是一個好的還是壞的跡象？]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，是的，這將如何影響市場的發展。所有中國
指數收盤上漲約1%，但恆大剛剛證實他們
正在拖欠貸款。這對整個市場是好事還是壞事？
這是否會導致即將發生的崩潰？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrh2z3/hong_kong_and_shanghai_index_are_up_over_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrh2z3/hong_kong_and_shanghai_index_are_up_over_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 18:52:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So yeah pretty much how will this effect the market moving forward. All Chinese indexes closed up about a percent yet Evergrande has just confirmed that they are defaulting on their loans. Is this good or bad things for the overall market and will this cause an upcoming crash?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[肉類之外，淨收入...
2021年YTD（Q1-3）：-1.02億美元
2020年：-5300萬
2019年: -1200萬美元
2018年: -3000萬美元
2017: -3,000萬美元
2016年: -2500萬美元
$BYND]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458792238515953665</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458792238515953665</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 18:35:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對半導體的現狀有什麼看法？]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，我認爲非常清楚半導體有多重要，並將在未來很長一段時間內繼續如此。
在很長一段時間內將繼續如此。然而，在過去的1到2年裏，由於供應量的增加，半導體行業出現了巨大的繁榮。
我想知道，你們是否認爲
會有一個修正嗎？我確實想長期投資於此。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrj20t/thoughts_on_the_current_state_of_semiconductors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrj20t/thoughts_on_the_current_state_of_semiconductors/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 18:09:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I think it&amp;#39;s pretty clear just how important semiconductors are, and will continue to be for a long time. However, they boomed massively in the last 1 to 2 years because of the supply shortages and I&amp;#39;m wondering, do you guys think there will be a correction? I do want to get into it for the long term, and am considering the VanEck Semiconductors ETF but am curious if I should wait. Naturally, since I&amp;#39;m in it for a long term it doesn&amp;#39;t matter that much if there is a correction, however a correction does mean I could get more shares in it. I&amp;#39;m not sure if I&amp;#39;m falling for the classic &amp;quot;it&amp;#39;s too late already&amp;quot; bias here or not. Does anyone have some more insight on the current state of them?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[投資金額與儲蓄金額]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好

我的妻子和我3個月前決定開始我們的bogleheads之旅。我們都是
全職工作，並且還在計算我們可以爲我們的Vanguard指數基金分配多少資金。
Vanguard指數基金。

我們每月向我們的儲蓄賬戶捐款（應急基金、度假
錢等等。我們每月向我們的儲蓄賬戶（應急基金，度假資金等）和我們的指數基金供款。我的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrkbfi/investment_amount_vs_savings_amount/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrkbfi/investment_amount_vs_savings_amount/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 17:37:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife and I decided to start our bogleheads journey 3 months ago. We are both working fulltime and are still figuring out how much we can allocate to our Vanguard index fond. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We do monthly contributions to our savings account (emergency fund, vacation money etc. ) and to our index fond. My question is do you guys reach a certain point after you eliminate the monthly contributions to your savings account? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are still discussing about this because if we stop contributing to our savings account we could of course invest way more into vanguard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently we contribute 2k into Vanguard and 2k into savings account each month - we have around 30k in Vanguard and 100k in savings account. Together we make about 180k per year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[什麼是經過驗證的、合理的、可靠的、與boglehead方法相關的使用槓桿的方式？]]></title><description><![CDATA[許多書（如《生命週期投資》）認爲，使用槓桿實際上是
對於低資本的年輕人來說是更聰明的方法。

誰能分享一下你自己應用的一些策略？

我不是在說 "買入TQQQ "並永遠持有，而是在尋找
我不是在說 "買入TQQQ "並永遠持有，而是在尋找使用歷史數據的策略。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrj5bz/whats_is_a_proven_reasonable_and_reliable_way_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrj5bz/whats_is_a_proven_reasonable_and_reliable_way_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 17:37:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many books (e.g. Lifecycle investing) argue that using leverage is actually the smarter approach for young people with low capital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can anyone share some strategies that you apply for yourself?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not talking about &amp;quot;buy TQQQ&amp;quot; and hold forever but actually looking for strategies using historical data and reason&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[(30M)我在達到65萬西北部的旅程中創建並使用了這些，我希望這些也能幫助你。鏈接在正文中]]></title><description><![CDATA[徹底的預算編制模板。
https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1Do-Efenrh0net1DBy6PFvOARNaG6QQutcqh33g4Mvok/edit?usp=sharing
(右上方有一些資源的鏈接)

淨值跟蹤器。
https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1N-WkOAIAoaSu-fpt_itJTOTtcy-Lze63p6F4nn_W6Tk/edit?usp=sharing

時間...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrn3e5/30m_i_created_and_used_these_on_my_journey_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrn3e5/30m_i_created_and_used_these_on_my_journey_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 17:09:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thorough budgeting Template: &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1Do-Efenrh0net1DBy6PFvOARNaG6QQutcqh33g4Mvok/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1Do-Efenrh0net1DBy6PFvOARNaG6QQutcqh33g4Mvok/edit?usp=sharing&lt;/a&gt; (has links in top right to some resources)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Net Worth Tracker: &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1N-WkOAIAoaSu-fpt_itJTOTtcy-Lze63p6F4nn_W6Tk/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1N-WkOAIAoaSu-fpt_itJTOTtcy-Lze63p6F4nn_W6Tk/edit?usp=sharing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time Value - stocks vs cash: &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1qS411RjSOpilZTw9poLfQ3783pbb1CpoH_JEsjZ4tTU/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1qS411RjSOpilZTw9poLfQ3783pbb1CpoH_JEsjZ4tTU/edit?usp=sharing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$WISH解僱了其首席執行官，因爲核心收入暴跌55%，公司燒掉了25%的剩餘現金餘額...]]></title><description><![CDATA[鏈接到公關。
https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211110006210/en/Wish-Reports-Third-Quarter-2021-Financial-Results-and-Provides-Business-Update

 1. 公司在沒有指定繼任者的情況下解僱了其CEO

 2. 核心市場收入下降55%。

 3. 第四季度的收入預計將比第三季度更差...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrd11e/wish_fires_its_ceo_as_core_revenue_plummets_55/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrd11e/wish_fires_its_ceo_as_core_revenue_plummets_55/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 16:42:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Link to the PR: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211110006210/en/Wish-Reports-Third-Quarter-2021-Financial-Results-and-Provides-Business-Update&quot;&gt;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20211110006210/en/Wish-Reports-Third-Quarter-2021-Financial-Results-and-Provides-Business-Update&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Company fires its CEO without a named successor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Core marketplace revenue down 55%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Q4 revenue expected to be even worse than Q3 despite the holidays… unheard of.  The company had already completely shut off marketing in Q3, so this means customers are ditching Wish left and right&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most importantly, Free Cash Flow was -$344M this quarter.  The company is burning roughly $300M/quarter this year (despite shutting off sales and marketing) and has $1.1B left… At this rate, the company will be insolvent by next summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not saying short the stock, but if you think the stock has “bottomed”, I think there’s a good chance the bottom is at $0/share and it’ll get there as soon as next summer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[預先訂購電動SUV和卡車的Rivian客戶能夠購買pre-ipo股票，並從IPO中賺取數百萬美元的收益]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/rivian-pre-order-customers-made-over-240-million-in-profit-on-ipo-pop.html

德克薩斯州奧斯汀市的環境顧問拉吉夫-帕特爾(Rajiv Patel)今年早些時候爲一輛Rivian電動SUV支付了1000美元的定金。
定金，買了一輛Rivian電動SUV。他不知道自己何時能
得到他的車輛，稱爲R1S，但...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrkqtb/rivian_customers_who_preordered_electric_suvs_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrkqtb/rivian_customers_who_preordered_electric_suvs_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 15:48:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/rivian-pre-order-customers-made-over-240-million-in-profit-on-ipo-pop.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/rivian-pre-order-customers-made-over-240-million-in-profit-on-ipo-pop.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rajiv Patel, an environmental consultant in Austin, Texas, put down a $1,000 deposit on a Rivian electric SUV earlier this year. He has no idea when he’ll get his vehicle, called the R1S, but his down payment is paying off in a very different way. As a pre-order customer, Patel was able to buy into Rivian’s IPO on Tuesday night as part of the company’s directed share program. He purchased the maximum 175 shares for $13,650 at the $78 IPO price. After the stock popped 29% on Wednesday, Patel’s stake is now worth $17,628. “When I invest in these companies, I’m always a long hold guy,” said Patel, 45, adding that he invested in Tesla not long after its 2010 IPO and also bought shares in Lucid Motors, which went public in July. “I’m definitely not a meme stock guy. With these three, I feel good about the tech.” The tech is all Patel can currently bet on. Following its Nasdaq debut on Wednesday, Rivian has a market cap of $86 billion, higher than Ford and about equal to General Motors, even though the company is projecting revenue of between zero and $1 million for the third quarter. Rivian reserved up to 7% of the IPO shares for DSP participants, as the company laid out in its prospectus. Eligible investors fell into two categories: People who reserved either an R1S or an R1T electric truck as of Sept. 30, and company officers, directors and their affiliates. The deposits are refundable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The program follows similar moves by Airbnb, Uber and Doximity, which set aside shares in their offerings for hosts, drivers and doctors, respectively. What sets Rivian’s DSP apart is that the EV company doesn’t have actual customers yet, despite a backlog of 55,400 pre-orders, as of Oct. 31. Assuming the DSP allocated all its available shares, participants collectively invested about $835 million into Rivian’s stock. As of Wednesday’s close, those shares are worth a total of close to $1.08 billion, representing a paper gain of around $245 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joshua White, a finance professor at Vanderbilt University, said it’s a great deal for those who can participate because hot IPO stocks almost always enjoy a first-day pop, and retail investors usually get shut out. DSP investors can also sell immediately if they choose because they’re not subject to a post-IPO lock-up period. “You kind of know going in this is going to be a pretty good sweetheart deal for customers who sign up,” said White, who previously served as an economist for the Securities and Exchange Commission. “Not having a product, it’s a way to extend some goodwill upfront so they can lock in those returns right away.” Patel received his first email about Rivian’s DSP last month and was told he needed to pre-register by Oct. 25. The program was being run by Morgan Stanley, the lead underwriter on the IPO. After the stock priced at $78 late Tuesday, Patel was able to go into his Morgan Stanley account and select how many shares he wanted, up to 175. He selected the max and transferred the money.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪士尼的計劃是去Metaverse]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 在今天的全年收益電話會議上，迪斯尼首席執行官Bob Chapek首次向股東提出了
> 第一次向股東們提出了 "元空間 "的概念。他首先指出
> 迪斯尼 "作爲一個早期採用技術的公司的長期記錄"。
> 以增強娛樂體驗"，並提供了一些例子。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr88fh/disneys_plans_to_go_to_metaverse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr88fh/disneys_plans_to_go_to_metaverse/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 15:30:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In its full-year earnings call today, Disney CEO Bob Chapek brought up the idea of the metaverse to shareholders for the first time. He began by pointing out Disney&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;long track record as an early adopter in the use of technology to enhance the entertainment experience,&amp;quot; offering examples such as Steamboat Willie (one of the first cartoons to be produced with synchronized sound), its historical use of animatronics, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ign.com/movies/thor-love-and-thunder&quot;&gt;and&lt;/a&gt; broadly the technological work of Pixar in its animations.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He went on: &amp;quot;Suffice it to say, our efforts today are merely a prologue to a time when we&amp;#39;ll be able to connect the physical and digital worlds even more closely, allowing for storytelling without boundaries in our own Disney metaverse. We look forward to creating unparalelled opportunities for consumers to experience everything Disney has to offer across our product and platforms wherever the consumer may be.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;As we look ahead to this next frontier, given our unique combination of brands, franchises, physical and digital experiences, and global reach, we see limitless potential, and that makes us as excited as ever about the Walt Disney Company&amp;#39;s next 100 years.&amp;quot;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you feel like we&amp;#39;ve been hearing about the metaverse a lot lately, it&amp;#39;s because in the last year a lot of massive tech companies have been getting in on the idea. We&amp;#39;ve been hearing about it for a while now, with companies in gaming like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ign.com/articles/what-is-epic-games-metaverse-and-is-it-worth-billions&quot;&gt;Epic Games&lt;/a&gt; seemingly interested in creating a persistent, virtual space that bridges the gap between virtual and the real world, and where people can interact with one another in real time. As more gaming companies brought it up, some have suggested that games such as Roblox, Minecraft, and Second Life already exist as a sort of proto-metaverse. But that hasn&amp;#39;t stopped companies like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ign.com/articles/microsoft-metaverse-announcement&quot;&gt;Microsoft&lt;/a&gt; and Facebook (which just &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ign.com/articles/facebook-new-name-meta&quot;&gt;rebranded to Meta&lt;/a&gt; for exactly this reason) for also trying to take control of whatever this virtual future looks like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ign.com/articles/disney-metaverse&quot;&gt;Now Disney&amp;#39;s Going in on the Metaverse, Too - IGN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[強生公司的單劑量疫苗在6個月內對COVID的保護率從86%驟降到只有13% ***。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458716009645420546</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458716009645420546</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 13:35:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我們是否正在走向衰敗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[這裏有一個真正的問題。我知道這裏的每個人都只是一個賭徒，沒有人知道
狗屎，包括我自己。但有沒有人覺得，或者最好是有任何
證據表明我們已經完蛋了？我的意思是，我們是否正在走向一個比08年更糟糕的市場
崩潰，比08年還嚴重？

從目前發生的情況來看，通貨膨脹率將達到30...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr9ri8/are_we_heading_down_the_shitter/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr9ri8/are_we_heading_down_the_shitter/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 13:17:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Genuine question here. 
I know everyone here is just a gambler and no one knows shit, including myself. But does anyone feel like or better yet have any evidence that we are fucked? By that I mean that are we headed for a market collapse worse than 08?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From what is happening, inflation going to 30 year record, Chinese housing market collapsing, supply shortages, labor shortages, govt that seems to be sitting on a very large dildo, it seems like all of this is not going to end well. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is all of this going to lead to an I am Legend scenario without the zombies or is the fed just going to keep lying and is everyone just going to not care at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From my position it seems that all the shit happening cannot last forever and it has to come crumbling down some time. But I am also very stupid. Any input welcome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I would like to also add that everyone always thought “oh I live in America where everything is made of sunshine and rainbows” but recently people have woken up to the fact that we are vulnerable to the same shit the third world countries have been dealing with for years. So if you think you are protected just because you live in a nice neighborhood, you are wrong. And you can primarily blame the government for that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit 2: of all the people saying “oh people have been saying this for years” or “just another gay bear.” None of those people have offered any evidence that I’m wrong, which I find interesting. And you dorks just saying “we had 12 green days in a row” that literally proves my point. That the market is stupid and not based on anything close to resembling fundamentals and that this market is simply unsustainable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[幾個月前買了 "願望 "牌浸劑]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrie43/bought_the_wish_dip_months_ago/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrie43/bought_the_wish_dip_months_ago/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 13:17:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是一個進口商，在我看來，通貨膨脹的真正成本不是錢太多了，而是因爲......。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是因爲現在的物流是一場噩夢。

我從中國進口東西。像我這樣的公司有成千上萬家。我們是
我們把東西賣給分銷商，分銷商把東西賣給
商店。我們也是直接在亞馬遜和其他電子商務網站上銷售的公司。
網站。

在COVID之前，...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qriwag/im_a_importer_in_my_point_of_view_the_true_cost/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qriwag/im_a_importer_in_my_point_of_view_the_true_cost/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 13:17:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s because the logistic is a nightmare right now. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I import things from China. There are thousands of companies like mine. We are the one that sells shit to ur the distributors, the distributors sells to stores. We are also the one directly sells on Amazon and other e-commerce website. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pre COVID, a 40ft high cube costs me only $4000 from China to Long Beach. Currently it costs me god damn $20000, and that doesn’t include land transport. If I want to sent a container of goods to Ohio, the total cost on shipping alone is like $40000, excluding import duties. Back in the day shipping make up abt 30% of my cost, it makes up 60-70% now. Pre COVID a container of nice double layer fleece lining hoodies cost me 60k includes shipping. It costs me 100k this year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are 110 some container ships stuck outside of Long Beach. You probably have no idea how many that is..ima use the nice fleece lining hoodies as example again. Each 40ft high cube carry’s 6000 this hoodie (so 20ft carry abt 3000). Each ship carry 20000 TEU (20ft equivalent units). there are also some 2 million TEU still in the port waiting to be hauled.. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s do the math&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3000&lt;em&gt;20000=60 million hoodies 
110&lt;/em&gt;20000=2.2million containers on ship stuck outside still. 
2.2million+2million=4.2 millions on containers total. 
4200000*60000000=252000000000000&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;US population is 333000000 
That’s 756 thousand hoodies for each person just stuck there waiting to be distributed! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s say my number is off by 50%, it’s still 378 thousands hoodies just stuck there! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can’t unload at Houston or New York cuz it will cost us even more… &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem Is not the demand, it’s supply. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not that there are too many monies were printed, who cares if we print more money, we can print unlimited useless pieces of paper and buy real goods from China ( export our Inflation)!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, if u see on the news that the supply chain has been fixed, or the port of Long Beach has been cleared, or you know inflation is about to stapled.. until that , whatever the fed say is bs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Side note Biden should declare national emergency and have nat guard come in and help haul these sticker goods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[只是對一些開始讓我對近中期市場感到擔憂的事情的一些想法]]></title><description><![CDATA[只是想對我一直關注的幾個指標給予一些關注。



 * 標準普爾的CAPE席勒市盈率10正接近歷史高點
   (CAPE=39.29)。在預測經濟衰退方面，它不像其他一些分析方法那樣出色。
   分析方法，但是，有兩個關鍵點是非常突出的。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr5eb1/just_some_thoughts_on_some_things_starting_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr5eb1/just_some_thoughts_on_some_things_starting_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 11:51:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just wanted to give some attention to a few metrics I&amp;#39;ve been keeping an eye on. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The CAPE Schiller P/E 10 ratio for the S&amp;amp;P is nearing all time highs (CAPE=39.29).  It hasn&amp;#39;t been as great at predicting recessions as some other analysis methods, but, two key points that stand out on the historical chart did precede crashes.  We exceeded one of those levels and are approaching the other. The last time the Schiller ratio was near 40 was right before the dotcom bubble burst in 2000.  Prior to that, the last time it spiked to these levels it preceded the great depression (CAPE = 32) in 1929. The economist who developed this ratio was given the Nobel prize for using this ratio to predict the dot com bubble, so this measurement does carry some weight.&lt;br/&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://data.nasdaq.com/data/MULTPL/SHILLER_PE_RATIO_MONTH-shiller-pe-ratio-by-month&quot;&gt;https://data.nasdaq.com/data/MULTPL/SHILLER_PE_RATIO_MONTH-shiller-pe-ratio-by-month&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rumors are surfacing that Evergrande has defaulted on one of it&amp;#39;s payments.  This is hearsay at this point, but it seems very suspicious that some banks and bond holders are not commenting on if they are receiving payment from Evergrande.  It also stands to reason, the company is fighting to keep their heads above water to make these payments but they are over $300b in debt.  In reality they are just kicking the can down the road.  It&amp;#39;s a house of cards at this point and the bottom is being pulled out, it&amp;#39;s only a matter of time.

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-await-evergrandes-overdue-148-mln-payment-amid-contagion-fears-2021-11-09/&quot;&gt;https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-await-evergrandes-overdue-148-mln-payment-amid-contagion-fears-2021-11-09/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Treasury yield curves are flattening.  This is a potentially huge indicator of the uncertainty within the market.  It has reliably predicted the last 7 recessions up to and within 18 months of an inverted yield curve.  The curve is not currently inverted but is starting to flatten. 

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;Strategists are watching the move in the Treasury curve which is showing a narrowing between long end yields, like the 30-year and the shorter end, like the 5-year.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The flattening of the curve reflects more hawkish fed assumptions, also reflected in the fed funds futures market,” said Jeffery. He said the spread between the 5-year and 30-year is narrower, at 68 basis points, or 0.68 percentage points. That is the flattest since the early weeks of the pandemic in March, 2020.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;A flattening yield curve can indicate that investors are worried about a weakening economy.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/the-first-fed-rate-hike-is-now-expected-as-early-as-july-following-the-hot-cpi-data.html?&amp;amp;qsearchterm=flatten%20yield%20curve&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/the-first-fed-rate-hike-is-now-expected-as-early-as-july-following-the-hot-cpi-data.html?&amp;amp;qsearchterm=flatten%20yield%20curve&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021年第三季度 😂 https://t.co/G4KW6IvN0i]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458751697518481408</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458751697518481408</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 11:38:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[等等，還有更多。本週至今，埃隆-馬斯克已售出50億美元的特斯拉股票https://t.co/S19eRPcvSB]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458646216925921281</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458646216925921281</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 11:38:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[凱西-伍德旗艦店出現有史以來最高的季度流出量]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrcrcy/cathie_wood_flagship_sees_highest_quarterly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrcrcy/cathie_wood_flagship_sees_highest_quarterly/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 09:41:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[大空頭》投資者Michael Burry稱特斯拉股價可能暴跌90%--並指出埃隆-馬斯克去年說它的價格過高，爲160美元。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr994g/the_big_short_investor_michael_burry_says_tesla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr994g/the_big_short_investor_michael_burry_says_tesla/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 09:24:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[誰能解釋一下里維安、福特和特斯拉的股票價格差異？]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特：19美元 市值773.7億，市盈率27.47

特斯拉：1067，市值1.06T，市盈率346.55

裏維安：100，市值859億。

發生了什麼事？這對Rivian來說有什麼意義，他們甚至還沒有賣出一輛車？
他們連一輛車都沒賣出去，這對Rivian來說有什麼意義？我很難決定這是否是可以進入的東西
入還是不入....]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrb5b7/can_someone_explain_the_difference_in_stock_price/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrb5b7/can_someone_explain_the_difference_in_stock_price/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 08:29:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ford: $19 market cap 77.37B, P/E 27.47&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla: 1,067. market cap $1.06T, P/E 346.55&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rivian: 100, Market cap 85.9 billion, &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s going on? How does this make any sense for Rivian when they haven&amp;#39;t even sold a single car yet? I&amp;#39;m having trouble deciding if this is something to get into or not. Compared to a Tesla which is most often compared to, 100 actually doesn&amp;#39;t seem too bad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我應該在孩子們的Roth IRA中購買什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我剛剛爲我的孩子開了一個Roth IRA。她今年16歲。我是監護人賬戶持有人
直到她年滿21歲。

我應該用6000美元買什麼？在NFLX、蘋果、谷歌、亞馬遜之間平分。
微軟和特斯拉？ 還是隻買特斯拉？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr4tam/what_should_i_buy_in_kids_roth_ira/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr4tam/what_should_i_buy_in_kids_roth_ira/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 08:29:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just opened a Roth IRA for my kid. She is 16. I am a custodian account holder until she reaches 21. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What should I buy with $6000? Equally split between NFLX, Apple, Google, Amazon, Microsoft &amp;amp; tesla? or Just Tesla?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WSB明天]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr9kno/wsb_tomorrow/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr9kno/wsb_tomorrow/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 07:35:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[本週到目前爲止，埃隆-馬斯克已經出售了大約50億美元的特斯拉股票，而且可能還沒有結束。
https://t.co/e4nweaIsSQ]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458649047649107971</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458649047649107971</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 06:43:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在過去的一年裏。

通貨膨脹率+6.2
S&amp;P 500指數 +32.6
黃金 -1.1
債券 -0.6

在通脹率上升的環境中，債券比黃金更好地對沖了。

WTF https://t.co/KjUvUSDS8W]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458542296291479556</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458542296291479556</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 06:43:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[馬斯克追加出售359萬股特斯拉股票，價值約40億美元]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458671734215827459</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458671734215827459</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 06:43:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Beyond Meat股價因虧損而崩潰，公司預計未來美國銷售增長乏力]]></title><description><![CDATA[Beyond Meat公司週三報告說，由於美國對其肉類替代品的需求萎縮，其第三季度的虧損有所擴大。
由於美國對其肉類替代品的需求萎縮，以及成本上升侵蝕了其利潤。

該公司的第四季度展望也令投資者失望。
該公司表示，預計銷售不會立即恢復，....。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrba22/beyond_meat_shares_crater_as_losses_mount_company/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrba22/beyond_meat_shares_crater_as_losses_mount_company/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 05:29:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond Meat on Wednesday reported a widening loss in its third quarter as U.S. demand for its meat substitutes shrank and higher costs ate into its profits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company also disappointed investors with its fourth-quarter outlook, indicating that sales aren’t expected to snap back immediately. Shares of the company tumbled 18% in extended trading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s what the company reported compared with what Wall Street was expecting, based on a survey of analysts by Refinitiv:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Loss per share: 87 cents vs. 39 cents expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revenue: $106.4 million vs. $109.2 million expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond reported fiscal third-quarter net loss of $54.8 million, or 87 cents per share, wider than a net loss of $19.3 million, or 31 cents per share, a year earlier. Analysts surveyed by Refinitiv expected a loss of 39 cents per share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company said it faced higher transportation and warehousing costs and increased its inventory write-offs, which hurt its profits. About $9 million was written off due to water damage at one of its plants, which mostly affected packaging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Net sales rose 12.7% to $106.4 million, missing expectations of $109.2 million. Compared with the second quarter, its revenue fell, bucking typical seasonal trends for the company’s products. Customers usually buy more Beyond Burgers during the summer to grill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company reported strong growth outside the United States, with international grocery and restaurant divisions each seeing sales more than double during the quarter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, U.S. revenue fell 13.9% compared with a year ago, mostly due to weaker grocery demand. CEO Ethan Brown told analysts that grocery sales didn’t help make up for shrinking food service orders, unlike in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company also said softer demand and operational challenges, like severe weather, hurt its domestic sales. Brown said new competitors in the market are putting pressure on its market share, but data doesn’t reveal that the lower demand is due to other companies stealing its customers. New products, like its meatless chicken, slightly offset U.S. sales declines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In October, the company warned investors that it would be reporting weaker sales than it had previously predicted, citing a wide range of factors, including the delta variant and distribution problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the company’s forecast doesn’t indicate a sunnier fourth quarter. Beyond is predicting net sales of $85 million to $110 million for those three months. Wall Street was expecting revenue of $131.6 million during the quarter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond said it’s expecting some of the operational challenges from the third quarter to drag down its fourth-quarter results as well. It also cited restaurants’ labor challenges and hesitant ordering behavior due to uncertainty tied to the pandemic as other factors embedded in the outlook. The company noted that the period contains 5 fewer shipping days than a year prior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Near-term market and operating conditions notwithstanding, we remain committed to our long-term strategy,” Brown said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He told analysts he is feeling optimistic about 2022. He hinted at new product launches coming next year, saying that some of those items could reach price parity with meat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/beyond-meat-bynd-q3-2021-earnings.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/beyond-meat-bynd-q3-2021-earnings.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[r/Stocks Daily Discussion Wednesday - Nov 10, 2021]]></title><description><![CDATA[這些日常討論從週一到週五進行，包括在我們的主題性
帖子。

一些有用的鏈接。

 * Finviz [https://finviz.com/quote.ashx?t=spy] 提供圖表、基本面和個人新聞的彙總。
   個別股票的彙總新聞
 * 彭博市場新聞[https://www.bloomberg.com/markets]
 *...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqrg59/rstocks_daily_discussion_wednesday_nov_10_2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qqrg59/rstocks_daily_discussion_wednesday_nov_10_2021/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 05:29:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;These daily discussions run from Monday to Friday including during our themed posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some helpful links:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finviz.com/quote.ashx?t=spy&quot;&gt;Finviz&lt;/a&gt; for charts, fundamentals, and aggregated news on individual stocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/markets&quot;&gt;Bloomberg market news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;StreetInsider news:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Market+Check&quot;&gt;Market Check&lt;/a&gt; - Possibly why the market is doing what it&amp;#39;s doing including sudden spikes/dips&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.streetinsider.com/Reuters&quot;&gt;Reuters aggregated&lt;/a&gt; - Global news&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a basic question, for example &amp;quot;what is EPS,&amp;quot; then google &amp;quot;investopedia EPS&amp;quot; and click the investopedia article on it; do this for everything until you have a more in depth question or just want to share what you learned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please discuss your portfolios in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?sort=new&amp;amp;q=Rate+My+Portfolio+-+r%2FStocks+Quarterly+Thread&amp;amp;t=all&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&quot;&gt;Rate My Portfolio sticky.&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See our past &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+%22r%2Fstocks+daily+discussion%22&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;daily discussions here.&lt;/a&gt;  Also links for:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Atechnicals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Technicals&lt;/a&gt; Tuesday, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Aoptions&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Options Trading&lt;/a&gt; Thursday, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/search?q=author%3Aautomoderator+title%3Afundamentals&amp;amp;restrict_sr=on&amp;amp;include_over_18=on&amp;amp;sort=new&amp;amp;t=all&quot;&gt;Fundamentals&lt;/a&gt; Friday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[總體淨值應如何影響你的資產配置計劃？(內部澄清)]]></title><description><![CDATA[好消息是，我（32歲）說服我的妻子（33歲）閱讀了《Bogleheads的投資指南》。
投資指南》，現在她正式成爲我們中的一員了! 壞消息 "是
她現在是個人理財專家，認爲我們的資產配置
(85%的股票和15%的固定收入，以及12個月以上的應急基金）...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qr0eq0/how_should_overall_net_worth_affect_your_asset/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qr0eq0/how_should_overall_net_worth_affect_your_asset/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 05:11:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news is that I (32) convinced my wife (33) to read The Bogleheads&amp;#39; Guide to Investing, and now she&amp;#39;s officially one of us! The &amp;quot;bad news&amp;quot; is that she&amp;#39;s now an expert on personal finance and thinks that our asset allocation (85% equities and 15% fixed income, with a 12+ month emergency fund) is too aggressive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She likes the idea of &amp;quot;your age in bonds,&amp;quot; though she is willing to compromise on 80% equities and 20% fixed income.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are fortunate enough to be able to max out our 401(k) and Roth IRA and have a bit left over for investments in a taxable account. &lt;strong&gt;With that in mind, my question is... would your asset allocation plan change if you had $5,000 / yr to invest vs. what we currently do?&lt;/strong&gt; In other words, all things being equal, can you afford to be more aggressive as the value of your portfolio increases?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: We compromised on 80% equities / 20% bonds as long as I get to invest a bit more of our emergency fund in I bonds. Case closed :) Thanks for the help!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[幾年前對NVDA或AMD進行高額買入的人--你的過程是什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們經常在這裏聽到人們如何在10美元時進入AMD或NVDA的故事。那是
但我想知道的是。

> 你是如何找到這些偉大的買點的，我們可以複製你的過程嗎？

還有

> 用同樣的方法，目前有哪些股票看起來像下一個AMD或NVDA
> （在它們...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qra2t4/people_who_made_highconviction_buys_into_nvda_or/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qra2t4/people_who_made_highconviction_buys_into_nvda_or/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 05:11:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;We often hear stories here about how people got into AMD or NVDA at $10. That&amp;#39;s fantastic but I would like to know:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How did you find these great buys and can we duplicate your process?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Using that same method, what current stocks look like the next AMD or NVDA (before they mooned)?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;re especially interested in stories that describe a great research method that hopefully we can duplicate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A couple of caveats:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can share other stories that&amp;#39;s not AMD or NVDA, but try to keep it in the tech growth sector if possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Try to avoid stories of &amp;quot;Well it was so cheap so I just Yolo&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;I heard it on Reddit.&amp;quot; That&amp;#39;s great for you but it&amp;#39;s not a process we can duplicate. Remember, it must be a &amp;quot;high conviction&amp;quot; buy for you, not just a random dart throw.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021年第三季度 😂 https://t.co/G4KW6IvN0i]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458647521262243843</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458647521262243843</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 04:52:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不，謝謝，Laurie! 我還是堅持吸吮陰莖吧，謝謝!]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr8tc3/no_thanks_laurie_ill_stick_to_sucking_dicks_thanks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr8tc3/no_thanks_laurie_ill_stick_to_sucking_dicks_thanks/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 04:52:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[通貨膨脹率達到21年來的新高......實際工資增長-1%......初次申請失業救濟金人數增加......但石頭只會上升......。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqx3xa/inflation_at_21_year_high_real_wage_growth_1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qqx3xa/inflation_at_21_year_high_real_wage_growth_1/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 03:25:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[EPIC損失色情。-46k Today.  😭]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr2zko/epic_loss_porn_46k_today_upvotes_needed_for_moral/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr2zko/epic_loss_porn_46k_today_upvotes_needed_for_moral/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 02:58:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[儘管他週末在推特上進行了民意調查，但埃隆-馬斯克還是在9月14日做出了出售特斯拉股票的計劃，目的是爲了納稅。
https://t.co/z5N2MbyEQX]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458618892566286341</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458618892566286341</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 02:46:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是今天（星期三）的市場回顧，2021年11月10日]]></title><description><![CDATA[心理市場回顧 - 2021年11月10日，星期三

股市令人眼花繚亂的漲勢在下列情況下戛然而止
發佈了一份關鍵的通貨膨脹報告，該報告顯示，儘管新申請的失業救濟金人數達到了大流行的水平，但消費者價格的跳升幅度超過了預期。
儘管新申請的失業救濟金人數達到了大流行時期的低點，但股市令人目眩的漲勢還是戛然而止。證券時報
標準普爾500指數...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr6lxi/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_wednseday_nov_10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr6lxi/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_wednseday_nov_10/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 02:18:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Wednesday, November 10, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dizzying rally in the stock market came to a screeching halt following the release of a key inflation report that showed a greater than expected jump in consumer prices despite new jobless claims coming in at a pandemic-era low. The S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) closed 0.8% lower, the tech-heavy Nasdaq (QQQ) closed 1.47% in its third consecutive red day while the Dow Jones (DIA) closed 0.61% lower. The Russell 2000 (IWM), which tracks the performance of small-caps, closed 1.58% lower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning, the Labor Department released the monthly Consumer Price Index, which showed prices soared 6.2% in a year-on-year period, accelerating from September’s 5.4% YoY rate, and higher than the 5.9% expected. This represents that fastest pace of inflationary expansion since 1990, though one has to take into account easy comparisons to last year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The staying power and magnitude of inflationary pressures has, perhaps, become the central question for market participants, with companies across the board reporting rising input costs and price hikes passed on to the consumers to preserve margins. While Q3 earning results have robustly demonstrated that companies in the SPY were largely able to navigate these cost pressures, the possibility remains that if inflation runs hotter than expected for longer than expected, it could begin to hamper consumer demand. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though the Fed has commenced a tapering in the pace of quantitative easing, members of the Fed have so far maintained that supply-chain disruptions and labor market imbalances caused by the pandemic have prevented producers from keeping up with demand, particularly as we head into the busiest time of the year, the holiday season. I broadly agree with this narrative, even the Fed has conceded that inflation could last longer “than they currently assume”. The latest Fed meeting minutes said, “Most participants saw inflation risks as weighted to the upside because of concerns that supply disruptions and labor shortages might last longer and might have larger or more persistent effects on prices and wages than they currently assumed.” We’ll have to see what happens in the coming months, if inflation doesn’t begin moderating in the next 5-6 months, the Fed will likely be forced to step in and raise interest rates in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With roughly 89% of companies in the S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) having already reported earnings, 81% of those have so far posted better than expected earnings per share and 75% of those reported better than expected revenue. FactSet projects that the year-on-year earnings growth rate for the index stands at 40%, though this number has continued creeping higher as earnings season unfolds. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_110521.pdf&quot;&gt;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_110521.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No highlights today sorry, will be back tomorrow&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt; -Eleanor Roosevelt&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[市場時機日記：像你這樣的普通人如何預測了過去1次崩盤中的9次]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們定期在這裏收到對市場有疑問的人的帖子。
今天，在恆大、加密貨幣和天知道其他什麼之間，有很多的
不確定性的原因。確切地說，我沒有投資日記，但我有一個
但我對自己的投資者情緒有很好的記錄，因爲我開始......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qr7hcg/market_timing_diary_how_a_regular_guy_like_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qr7hcg/market_timing_diary_how_a_regular_guy_like_you/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 01:45:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Periodically, we get posts on here of people with doubts about the market. Today, between Evergrande, crypto, and lord knows what else, there are plenty of reasons for uncertainty. I don&amp;#39;t have an investing diary, exactly, but I have a pretty good account of my own investor sentiment since I started investing in 2013. My approach was Bogle-inspired, although as I note, I shifted a bit (often for bad reasons). I thought I might share them, as a good representation of timing the market, as well as illustrating other cognitive biases one might have (e.g. the way we can become overcommitted to a strategy once we have emotionally invested in it). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;January 2015: I started to get worried when the Shiller forward P/E went above 25, the level it was before the 2008 financial crisis. I have generally fretted about this, and the Buffet indicator (market cap: GDP) since then. I did shift my portfolio from being 100% domestic to include international index funds at this point (not that it did any good).  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;November 2016: I thought Trump winning the 2016 election would tank the markets (actually it did briefly upset overnight futures markets). It didn&amp;#39;t, of course. Rather, the market boomed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;October 2017: I still remember the cover of The Economist. &amp;quot;The bull market in everything&amp;quot;. I was sure that there was something afoot. There would be a few subsequent moments that felt like &amp;quot;now it&amp;#39;s about to start&amp;quot;. In February 2018 the VIX surged as the trade war accelerated and the Fed raised rates above 1%. There &lt;em&gt;was&lt;/em&gt; (and this points to the difficulty of timing) a sharp correction in December 2018, but the market almost immediately recovered.    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;August 2019: the yield curve inverted, and once again I began to thought that the end was nigh. There was going to be a recession and that was it. The rise of the S&amp;amp;P 500 into early 2020 felt suspicious to me. Arguably, this is the one time my gut might have been right. &lt;em&gt;But&lt;/em&gt; I was right for the wrong reasons. The crash of 2020 was caused by the pandemic, which I obviously hadn&amp;#39;t considered in August 2019 (nor even in January 2020). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;March 9, 2020: now, those were crazy times my friend. Some days were up double-digits and some were down by the same. It was circuit breaker city, man. Critically though, the signs of a financial crisis were there - repo markets were drying up and even treasuries were dropping.On March 9th I came damn close to shifting large amounts of my portfolio into bonds. I still have the trade confirmation, though I stopped it at the last second. The S&amp;amp;P 500 had fallen to something like 2800.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;April 9, 2020: I held through the bottom, when a strange thing started happening. The market recovered very rapidly. In a few days the S&amp;amp;P 500 was up from a low of something in the 2200s to almost 2800. I thought there was no way it could keep going like this. I remember looking at graphs (which people were posting widely at the time) showing the market through the Great Depression. One of the striking takeaways was that it hadn&amp;#39;t just been down down down followed by recovery. There were so many bear traps. Could this be one of them? It was at this point that I broke from Bogle advice. As the market recovered, I shifted modest amounts into bonds reasoning that when the real bottom appeared I would buy everything cheap. A completely irrational factor in my move: relatives bragging that they saw the crash coming and pulled everything out just in time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;June 6, 2020: as my fear of bear traps receded, I reverted back to my long-term optimal portfolio. One day later, the market saw the biggest crash since the heady days of March. A-ha! I thought. It turns out I was right all along. And &lt;em&gt;of course&lt;/em&gt; I was - unemployment had just hit the highest levels since the Great Depression, some states were prematurely reopening from the pandemic, etc. I didn&amp;#39;t sell everything, but I maintained an overly bond-heavy portfolio for my age (mid-30s). As the market rose further in July and August, I continued to shift assets to bonds (I also shifted my bond holdings to TIPS which did work out... so far). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;September 2020: through August I had read the story about Softbank&amp;#39;s sometimes insane bets on tech, and was again sure that a crash was nigh. I felt bearish - one day I went running in the woods and literally saw a family of black bears crossing the road. And indeed, the S&amp;amp;P 500 started to correct (the Nasdaq somewhat more). And yet... pretty soon after, it was back to normal. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;January 22, 2021: this story involves my active trading account, which represents a very small proportion of my investments. When GME started to surge to $65 (vs. $4 in August 2020) following the beginnings of the campaign on Wall Street Bets, I was sure that the stock would fall. I bought OTM puts. When it rose more, I bought more OTM puts - and I even was able to time the peak correctly the second time. Obviously, the first set of puts became worthless, but interestingly, so did the second because I had bought them when volatility was so high that the stock would have to hit ridiculously low levels for my puts to print.      &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m sure that there are other folks out there who are better investors than I. Maybe they have the time to do research and find diamonds in the rough. Maybe they have the discipline to avoid going double or nothing (and to resist confirmation bias) when their theses prove false. And hey, maybe they are smarter and possessed of some abilities that I lack. But I would have to say that the smartest thing I&amp;#39;ve ever done is to ignore my instincts, saved, diversified, and waited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian Gain Porn. 16分鐘和18,456美元 🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr0gsr/rivian_gain_porn_16_min_and_18456/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr0gsr/rivian_gain_porn_16_min_and_18456/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 01:45:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[好了......重新設置計數器]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr5jeo/welpresetting_the_counter/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qr5jeo/welpresetting_the_counter/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 01:45:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼貝寶的價格這麼低？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在230美元的時候購買了一些PayPal的股票，因爲有人告訴我這是一個很好的買點，而且我也經常使用PayPal，而且它的業績也不是很好。
因爲我也經常使用PayPal，而且它已經有一段時間沒有這麼低了。
但是它就這樣一直跌到了204美元？有沒有人知道，如果
這是否有什麼原因？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr4603/why_is_paypal_so_low/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qr4603/why_is_paypal_so_low/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 01:45:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I purchased some PayPal shares at 230$ because I was told it was a good buy, and because I frequently use PayPal as well and it had not been that low in a while. But it has just continued to drop all the way down to 204$?? Does anyone know if there is a reason for this&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>