<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 16:25:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Vanguard的年終基金分配初步估計將於今天（2021年11月15日）公佈]]></title><description><![CDATA[到今天早上檢查時還沒有，但今天會出來。見第三項
列表中的第三項。

初步的年終萬科基金分配估算
[https://advisors.vanguard.com/tax-center/tax-season-calendar/current-year]]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/quh2so/vanguards_preliminary_yearend_fund_distribution/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/quh2so/vanguards_preliminary_yearend_fund_distribution/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 15:53:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not yet available as of this morning&amp;#39;s check, but due out today.  See third item in list:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://advisors.vanguard.com/tax-center/tax-season-calendar/current-year&quot;&gt;Preliminary year-end Vanguard fund distribution estimates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[IDC報告稱，半導體行業將在2022年中期實現正常化和平衡，2023年有可能出現產能過剩。]]></title><description><![CDATA[國際數據公司預計，半導體市場在2021年將增長17.3%，而2020年爲10.8%。
2021年將增長17.3%，而2020年爲10.8%。據IDC稱，該行業將看到
到2022年中期，行業將實現正常化和平衡，並有可能出現
隨着大規模的產能擴張開始，2023年有可能出現產能過剩...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qu5pfc/semiconductor_industry_will_see_normalization_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qu5pfc/semiconductor_industry_will_see_normalization_and/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 13:20:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;International Data Corporation expects the semiconductor market to grow by 17.3% in 2021 versus 10.8% in 2020. According to IDC, the industry will see normalization and balance by the middle of 2022, with a potential for overcapacity in 2023 as larger scale capacity expansions begin to come online towards the end of 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=prAP48247621&quot;&gt;https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=prAP48247621&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼在需求增加的情況下，銅價仍然下跌？]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以最近銅價下跌，儘管人們對金屬的短缺感到擔憂。
金屬的短缺。儘管對它的需求很大，但價格仍在波動，整個情況非常混亂。
整個情況是相當混亂的。這讓我感到有些困惑，因爲我
我認爲，如果需求很高，而生產者正在努力爭取......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qudym9/why_do_copper_prices_still_go_down_despite_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qudym9/why_do_copper_prices_still_go_down_despite_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 13:20:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So recently copper prices went down despite the concerns about the shortage of the metal. Despite the great demand for it, prices are still volatile and the whole situation is pretty messy tbh. It’s somewhat confusing to me because I thought that if the demand is high and producers are struggling to comply, then the prices should go up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also thinking if my worries are warranted, especially since I have some copper stocks in my portfolio and I made investments recently too, placing some money in juniors. I know they’re a pretty risky investment, but I always remind myself to invest money I am willing t&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of them is Oroco Resources (ORRCF) which recently uncovered extensive copper deposits. The drilling activities that commenced in their&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.orocoresourcecorp.com/projects/santo-tomas/&quot;&gt; Santo Tomas Project&lt;/a&gt; confirmed the presence of polymetallic copper mineralization. They hold 100% interest in two contiguous mineral concessions in Guerrero, Mexico which are included in their project in Xochipala.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also placed some on&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.threevalleycopper.com/&quot;&gt; Three Valley Copper&lt;/a&gt; (TVC) since they’re pretty much on a roll recently. They will start mining next month or in early 2022 and are expected to have an annual production between 13,000 and 16,000 tonnes of copper cathode by 2023. The company recently announced an upsize with a recent deal financing to $16 million due to investor demand. Also just last month they released their second quarter results where they were able to mine 178,105 tonnes of ore at a grade of 0.50%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now I’m going to hold back from investing despite the price dip because I’m pretty anxious because of the whole situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[請爸爸不要再傷害我了]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtwxkm/plz_papa_dont_hurt_me_no_more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtwxkm/plz_papa_dont_hurt_me_no_more/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 11:39:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我終於添加了債券!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我設立了一個賬戶，購買了1000美元的I類債券。這甚至不是我財富的百分之一
財富的百分之一，它主要是爲了最終成爲應急基金。我覺得這是個
一個好的生活選擇。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qu6uo8/i_finally_added_bonds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qu6uo8/i_finally_added_bonds/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 11:26:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I set up a account and purchased $1000 in I bonds.
It isn&amp;#39;t even a percent of my wealth and it&amp;#39;s mainly to eventually become an emergency fund. I feel like it&amp;#39;s a good life choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[雜草可能是下一個競選對象]]></title><description><![CDATA[似乎我們一直在進行的輪換的最後階段，從價值股開始，到SPAC的巨型抽水機結束。
價值型股票，最後是SPACs的巨型泵，收入爲零的公司*cough
裏維安*，以及雜草叢生。

催化劑

有傳言說，南卡羅來納州的梅斯議員（R）正在提出一項法案，以使大麻在聯邦範圍內合法化。
大麻在聯邦的合法化...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qu13sv/weed_could_run_next/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qu13sv/weed_could_run_next/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 10:38:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seems towards the end of the rotations we&amp;#39;ve been having starting with value stocks and ending with mega pumps from SPACs, companies with zero revenue *cough Rivian*, and weed stonks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Catalyst&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rumor has it, that Rep. Mace (R) from SC is proposing a bill to legalize Marijuana at the Federal level. &amp;quot;Those who’ve &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-12/republicans-pot-bill-to-propose-lower-taxes-more-state-control&quot;&gt;seen&lt;/a&gt; Mace’s draft say it would regulate cannabis more like alcohol&amp;quot;. This bill coming from the republican side may garner more support than Sen. Schumer&amp;#39;s already proposed bill. &amp;quot; Mace’s proposed excise tax is 3.75%, according to Cobb -- a fraction of the 25.5% that Schumer’s legislation would put on marijuana products.&amp;quot; Personally, I&amp;#39;ve heard this bill could be brought forward as early as Monday 11/15. But, that&amp;#39;s just chatter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Well, which dank stock should I buy?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve looked at various companies and honestly diversifying into a few may be worth it. However, I have the greatest conviction in &lt;strong&gt;$TLRY&lt;/strong&gt; the largest market share in Canada, Germany, and ties to the US with Sweetwater brewing. Those with the greatest dependence on the US may outperform. But, screw the fundamentals because that&amp;#39;s not how this market works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*for simplicity I&amp;#39;ll just illustrate $TLRY to represent the Marijuana sector since it has the largest market cap*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Institutions buying $420M+?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In general, Institutions have been buying these Cannabis companies as they blew off earlier in the year. Heaviest buying has been in $TLRY with the heaviest selling in $SNDL. Interestingly most of the buys come during Q2 which means most of these institutional apes are holding some serious bags. They could be down anywhere from -4% to -33% depending on when they bought in Q2. So, don&amp;#39;t be surprised if this gets pumped and ultimately dumped to lighten their bags.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/n0904d0bzmz71.png?width=2386&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=fb69d29fe355abc07e40a01cc412993d9f8b3b3b&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/n0904d0bzmz71.png?width=2386&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=fb69d29fe355abc07e40a01cc412993d9f8b3b3b&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leaders in the Sector?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$ACB&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;$SNDL&lt;/strong&gt; currently lead the move upward as they are right at their 200-day moving average. Does that mean they&amp;#39;ll continue leading the way? I don&amp;#39;t know. Does that mean the others have more to run? I can&amp;#39;t see the future, you twit. As a result, diversifying in this sector might be the way to go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Crayons&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It appears &lt;strong&gt;$TLRY&lt;/strong&gt; has started to round out and will try to push hire. The green lines are historical supply/demand lines at candle closes. I&amp;#39;m setting my stop near the recent low of $9.98 and will continue to sell out starting at $15.50 to $30.00 for a gain close to between 20% and 130%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/cssq7ipczmz71.png?width=2712&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=80aa4805f62ae8a139a233ae266c836122544bd9&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/cssq7ipczmz71.png?width=2712&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=80aa4805f62ae8a139a233ae266c836122544bd9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social Traction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another reason I am choosing to look at &lt;strong&gt;$TLRY&lt;/strong&gt; is because of all the weed stocks, &lt;strong&gt;$TLRY&lt;/strong&gt; gains the most attention on google trends and is the 2nd most mentioned on WSB behind &lt;strong&gt;$SNDL.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Positions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I literally have none and plan on buying Monday with any of you that like the stock(s). I&amp;#39;ll update after buys are in. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*This is literally my uneducated, unlicensed opinion. Don&amp;#39;t listen to me. You&amp;#39;ll Lose money\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果人們在經紀人停止購買GME時感到憤怒，那麼，如果股票市場崩潰，普通投資者無法賣出，會發生什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我剛剛聽了一個投資顧問的播客，他說他和他的客戶都是做多股票的。
他說他和他的客戶都是做多股票的，而且他們都有止損單，以防崩盤。
以防出現崩潰。隨着市場的上漲，他們會提高止損價格。

然而，我想知道，如果市場關閉，這將如何運作，或...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qu188u/if_people_were_angry_when_brokers_halted_gme_buys/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qu188u/if_people_were_angry_when_brokers_halted_gme_buys/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 06:31:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was just listening to a podcast with an investment advisor who said that he and his clients are all long equities and they have stop loss orders placed in case of a crash. As the market goes up they raise their stop price. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I was wondering how this would work if the market is closed, or if the circuit breakers kick in, and when the market re-opens the prices are all well below their limit/stop price. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, lets say the Dow closes at 36,000 and some terrible news event occurs overnight there might be no way people would be able to exit their positions at 36,000. They wlll have to sell after the market opens right? And the market wil open much lower than 36,000.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, if word gets out that certain investors were able to sell, while retail investors were unable to get their orders filled this could lead to a full scale revolt. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is this concern legitimate, or are their controls in place to prevent retail investors from getting hosed while the well connected all exit their long positions?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[等待恆大崩盤。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qu77t9/waiting_for_the_evergrande_collapse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qu77t9/waiting_for_the_evergrande_collapse/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 06:00:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能爲80萬億美元的市值創造機會。凱西-伍德是在扯皮嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA["我們假設在未來10年內，人工智能將在企業軟件領域帶來30億美元的市值機會。
在企業軟件領域提供30美元的市值機會。
萬億美元，"這位明星股民在上個月的米爾肯研究所會議上說。
他在上個月的米爾肯研究所會議上說。"我們的新數字是80美元...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtxork/ai_to_create_opportunity_for_an_80_trillion/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtxork/ai_to_create_opportunity_for_an_80_trillion/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 04:59:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We were assuming that in the next 10 years, artificial intelligence would deliver, in the enterprise software space, a market cap opportunity of $30 trillion,” the star stockpicker said at a Milken Institute conference last month. “Our new number is $80 trillion.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-wood-just-called-technology-140000074.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/cathie-wood-just-called-technology-140000074.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is an interesting use of terminology.  “Market cap” is the market value of a publicly-traded company&amp;#39;s outstanding shares.  Therefore, I’m to take it that AI is an opportunity for a single company to be worth 80T. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alphabet is one of the leaders in the AI space; at an almost $2T market cap, they would need to grow 45% YoY over the next 10 years to hit 80T.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost any other company in the world would need significantly more growth to get to $80T. No one would have thought APPL would be a $2.5T company 10 years ago when they were $335b, but to get there was a 20% YoY growth from 2011 -&amp;gt; 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where is she pulling this info from? How can she justify these claims?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are your thoughts? Do you see the possibility of an $80T company in 10 years? Will it come from AI?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在DCA-ing進入高度分散的ETF時，是否有每月的市場週期模式可以使用？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我每個月都要到VWRA（如果你在美國，就想VT）進行DCA-ing，我想知道是否有特定的日子，可以在那裏進行Standing。
我想知道是否有一個特定的日子，據統計，那裏的價格是最低的？
最低？

我在問自己，如果有很多人在同一天進行DCA，是否會對價格產生影響？
對價格的影響。我可以想象有一些模式，並且是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qtphhb/are_there_monthly_market_cycle_patterns_that_i/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qtphhb/are_there_monthly_market_cycle_patterns_that_i/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 04:59:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am DCA-ing into VWRA (think VT if you are in the US) every month and am wondering if there is a specific day where statistically the price is the lowest?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was asking myself if a lot of people DCA-ing at the same day would have an impact on price. I can imagine there being some patterns and was wondering if anyone has ever done this analysis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe it&amp;#39;s the last days of the month because people have to sell to cover bills etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or it&amp;#39;s on any of Mondays in a month because ... everyone hates Mondays and that affects buying pressure ...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[VAX UP!
 https://t.co/1a6iyAfVD2]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460083117172080643</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460083117172080643</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 04:43:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[更多美國人比以往任何時候都有100萬美元的退休儲蓄]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 富達公司的數據顯示有數十萬人擁有百萬美元的
> 退休賬戶，我爲他們歡呼。他們的黃金歲月看起來
> 好。
> 
> 總的來說，擁有100萬美元或更多的賬戶數量增長了74.5%，但不清楚這代表了多少人。
> 不清楚這代表了多少個人，...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qu6vu5/more_americans_have_1_million_saved_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qu6vu5/more_americans_have_1_million_saved_for/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 04:11:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fidelity’s data show hundreds of thousands of people with million-dollar retirement accounts, and I say hurray for them. Their golden years are looking good.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Together, the number of accounts with $1 million or more grew 74.5%, but it’s not clear how many individuals this represents, since investors can have multiple accounts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you grown you retirement account to any decent numbers? What&amp;#39;s the approach that you are taking?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[90,000美元的大麻股票 - 這是一個壞主意嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好。

我（31M）有90,000美元的大麻股票。隨着即將離開
我覺得這一定是一個安全的賭注，對嗎？我的錢相當
均勻地分佈在大約13只美國的大麻股票和ETF上。我不是
一個非常有經驗的投資者。我在寫...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qu4fer/90000_in_cannabis_stocks_is_this_a_bad_idea/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qu4fer/90000_in_cannabis_stocks_is_this_a_bad_idea/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 03:38:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi all,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I (31M) have 90,000 dollars in marijuana stocks. With the impending departure from prohibition, I feel this must be a safe bet, right? I have the money fairly evenly distributed across about 13 USA based marijuana stocks and ETFs. I am not an extremely experienced investor. I am writing this post to get a few pieces of information: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;1.  Is this a good idea? Either way, please back up your response with credible information. 
2.  If you’re invested in pot stocks, what’s your strategy? How much do you have in? I am curious to know how many other people out there are like me.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉（TSLA）現在的市場情況非常好。馬斯克正在出售他持有的10%的股份。我發現每天都有重複的模式，是不是擁有]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，我現在有一個交易特斯拉的特殊機會


它是如何開始的。

https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1457064697782489088

根據這條推文，他宣佈出售10%的股票，這在當時是
他的推文的時候。1.726億股普通股

他於11月8日星期一開始......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtzgu6/extraordinary_market_situation_for_tesla_tsla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtzgu6/extraordinary_market_situation_for_tesla_tsla/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 02:39:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok so I there is an extraordinary opportunity to trade Tesla right now&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;How it started:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1457064697782489088&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1457064697782489088&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As per this tweet he announced to sell 10% of his stocks, which was at the time of his tweet: 172,6m ordinary shares&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He started on monday 8th november and started selling. We know exactly how much he sells each day since he needs to file those numbers to the SEC. You can find them here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://ir.tesla.com/sec-filings&quot;&gt;click&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the proof he is really selling as announced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may check this article to see its legit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/elon-musk-sells-tesla-stock-in-plan-set-before-twitter-poll-sec-filing-shows-11636591389&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/elon-musk-sells-tesla-stock-in-plan-set-before-twitter-poll-sec-filing-shows-11636591389&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;How it is going:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found this graphic on Twitter which visualizes his sales in relation to the performance of the Tesla share price: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/RawBooty2/status/1459121681549733893&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This shows that Elons sales continously move the price downwards. Please note that the graphic wasnt updated for fridays sales yet. I will update it as soon as its available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Now the interesting part We know how many shares he still has to sell !&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is 17,3m shares (10% of 172,6m) minus what has been sold already.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So that is 11,4m shares left for sale&lt;/strong&gt; since we know from SEC files he sold 4,9m shares until friday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I copied all the SEC files in one Excel document and calculated the sales volumes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we assume he will continue to sell 500 - 639k shares a day as he did the last three days that means &lt;strong&gt;he will be selling for another 18-23 trading days&lt;/strong&gt;. Which would be 8th dec - 15th dec&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So how do we use this knowledge ?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well I assume and the chart proves it that the buyers will not be willing to jump in front of the bus while Elon dumps his shares. So there is a really good chance we see lower prices until he is done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately i cant include pictures in this post. I will give you guys a link to a post with pictures in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a rise in SP on Wednesday but he filed his first SEC report on Wednesday evening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So ever since it is public knowledge that he &lt;strong&gt;really&lt;/strong&gt; started selling and how much he sells it was going down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;How to play it:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see several possibilities to take profit from this knowledge&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold puts until Elon is almost done&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sell a part of holding now and buy it back later at lower prices (some say thats what EMusk might intend to do)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold puts until Elon is done and reinvest your gains in calls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look at the daily patterns, caused by Elons broker dumping shares&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, i cant post pictures here. I will include the link to the pictured post in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might notice that each day from Wednesday to Friday starts with a dip and then a mini rally which peaks between 10:30 AM and 11:00 AM. Followed by descending prices through the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently i am holding puts which i bought last monday and wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am no financial advisor and please dont regard this as any form of advice or recommendation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please do your own due dilligence!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I Bonds大型主題（I Bond Heads Rejoice!）]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qtzrc6/i_bonds_mega_thread_i_bond_heads_rejoice/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qtzrc6/i_bonds_mega_thread_i_bond_heads_rejoice/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 02:05:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我在30分鐘$SPY圖表上做了一些TA。情況對我們來說並不樂觀。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtsr2y/i_did_some_ta_on_the_30min_spy_chart_things_dont/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtsr2y/i_did_some_ta_on_the_30min_spy_chart_things_dont/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 02:05:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這裏沒有自閉症患者擁有如此深刻的知識。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtxkda/no_autist_here_posses_such_deep_knowl/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtxkda/no_autist_here_posses_such_deep_knowl/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 02:05:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[隨着88%的公司發佈報告，S&amp;P 500指數的收益有望連續第三個季度創下新高。GAAP收益同比增長52%，而運營收益增長37%。$SPX https://t.co/ytdqtVPyFR]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459977017500352518</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459977017500352518</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 01:04:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我怎樣才能瞭解研究買什麼股票？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我相信這個問題被問得很多，但如果我是誠實的，我沒有絲毫的
知道如何對股票進行市場研究。我希望我的投資組合能夠增長
投資組合，以利於長期投資，因爲我想在以後的生活中能夠
在我的生活中積累股息收入。

當然，要想知道...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtx1kk/how_can_i_learn_about_researching_what_stocks_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtx1kk/how_can_i_learn_about_researching_what_stocks_to/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 01:04:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m sure this gets asked a lot, but if I’m being honest I haven’t the slightest clue how to do market research into stocks. I want to be able to grow my portfolio to be good for long term investing, as I’d like to be able to accumulate dividend income later in my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, trying to figure out what stocks could potentially blow up are fun as well, but I’ve grown to feel that’s just a bit unrealistic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now I have about $950 invested in individual stocks on Robinhood and another $720 on Acorns. I currently own shares in APPL, ACB, RKT, CNK, and BLV. None of these 5 have done as much as I would have expected them to at this point in the year but it’s fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyhow, hope this question makes sense, just want to learn how to make quality investments. What kind of research I need to do beforehand would be helpful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[恆大。短篇小說]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qttn15/evergrande_a_short_story/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qttn15/evergrande_a_short_story/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 23:43:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我的妻子在掙錢方面令人難以置信，每年帶來50萬美元的收入。但她在商場裏掉了1500美元，正在危及我們的退休生活。

理財師，我應該怎麼做？https://t.co/uYQ3Jg9Ta7]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459495597241769993</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459495597241769993</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 22:37:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[暫時性的......🤔🤔🤔🤔。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtrokr/transitory_right/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtrokr/transitory_right/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 21:56:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[第三季度收入增長，同比變化%...
NVIDIA $NVDA: +68%
特斯拉 $TSLA: +57%.
AMD $AMD: +54%
Shopify $SHOP: +46
谷歌 $GOOGL: +41
Facebook $FB: +35%
蘋果 $AAPL: +29
Salesforce $CRM: +23%
Adobe $ADBE: +22
微軟 $MSFT: +22%
Netflix $NFLX: +16%
亞馬遜 $AMZN: +15%
S&amp;P 500 $SPY: +14%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459984128829534219</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459984128829534219</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 21:43:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-馬斯克和他的財務顧問是誰，都認爲他的股票被高估了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[當首席執行官自己給出的跡象表明他們認爲自己的股票價格過高時。
我認爲是時候開始注意了。如果有人能感覺到什麼時候
如果有人知道非理性何時會結束，那可能就是他和他的顧問。

關於埃隆試圖兌現一些股票以支付稅款的整個事情，作爲一個好人
的人，...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qtyl1f/elon_musk_and_whoever_are_his_financial_advisers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qtyl1f/elon_musk_and_whoever_are_his_financial_advisers/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 21:31:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the CEO himself is giving signs that they think their stock is overpriced, I think it&amp;#39;s time to start taking note. If anyone has a sense on when the irrationality will end, it&amp;#39;s probably him and his advisors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This whole thing about Elon trying to cash out some stock to pay taxes as a nice guy, was an obvious BS excuse. Then the media comes out saying his REAL intention is to pay taxes that are due. Brilliant, double play to cover for his personal cash out. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If Elon had faith that his stock still had room to grow, there is no chance in hell he&amp;#39;d be selling. He&amp;#39;d just be getting a loan to cover his tax liabilities, while his equity value increases. The fact that he&amp;#39;s trying to cash out shows he thinks it&amp;#39;s near peak and about to go down. All the media drama is just an attempt to retain value for as long as possible to distract and justify his cash out. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s crazy how I see NO ONE talking about this... And instead it&amp;#39;s all about &amp;quot;clever redditors&amp;quot; seeing his real intentions are to cover his tax liability. No it&amp;#39;s not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[專業提示：在月末購買I型債券。]]></title><description><![CDATA[財政部直接把它當作你整個月的投資。這
有效地將12個月的鎖定期縮短爲11個月零一天。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qtxwt3/pro_tip_buy_i_bonds_at_the_end_of_the_month/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qtxwt3/pro_tip_buy_i_bonds_at_the_end_of_the_month/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 21:15:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Treasury Direct treats it as if you’ve been invested for the whole month. This effectively shortens the 12 month lock up period to 11 months and a day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[投資VOO和SPY的意義何在？]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近，我看到人們在社交媒體上以餅狀圖的形式發佈他們的投資組合。
社會媒體。作爲一個新的投資者，我在想，爲什麼人們要投資於多個
基金，持有相同的資產。爲什麼不乾脆全部採用VOO，並利用較低的費用率？
低費用率的優勢？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qtr9d8/what_is_the_point_of_investing_in_voo_and_spy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qtr9d8/what_is_the_point_of_investing_in_voo_and_spy/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 20:27:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently I’ve seen people posting their portfolios in pie chart format all over social media. As a new investor I was wondering why people invest in multiple funds with the same holdings. Why not just go all VOO and take advantage of the lower expense ratio?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[凱爾-巴斯談中國、習近平風險和保持通脹領先]]></title><description><![CDATA[不確定播客是否經常在這裏發佈，但這絕對是一個不能錯過的
特雷-洛克比和凱爾-巴斯之間的訪談。簡而言之，如果你
如果你沒有調查過中國的審計實踐，中國公司的美國存託憑證的可變利益實體
中國公司的美國存託憑證的結構（不是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qtrnbt/kyle_bass_on_china_xi_jinping_risk_and_staying/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qtrnbt/kyle_bass_on_china_xi_jinping_risk_and_staying/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 19:23:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not sure podcasts are frequently posted here, but this is definitely a can&amp;#39;t miss interview between Trey Lockerbie and Kyle Bass. To be concise, if you haven&amp;#39;t investigated Chinese auditing practices, variable interest entity structures for American depository receipts of Chinese companies (not discussed explicitly here but follows the same theme),  the game theory associated with using  China&amp;#39;s digital currency as a geopolitical power grab, and party rhetoric towards reclaiming Taiwan, you really do not know what you own in individual Chinese stocks or even in your 401k emerging market ETFs with 30% China exposure. For transparency, I have not yet fully disinvested from China (I&amp;#39;m only 22 and my funds at risk are minimal), but going forward it is something I&amp;#39;m increasingly aware of. Would recommend an hour of your time to listen. Even if you aren&amp;#39;t as bearish on China, it still is a thoughtful and honest approach to analyzing under the radar risks from an investor profiled in the Big Short for foreseeing the housing  crisis&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/episode/4epYMzRSq7q3818IMXduKp?si=c025205ba3814484&quot;&gt;https://open.spotify.com/episode/4epYMzRSq7q3818IMXduKp?si=c025205ba3814484&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[限制接觸大科技的ETF？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在一家大型科技公司工作，我未來收入的很大一部分是通過RSU捆綁在公司股票上。
在公司的股票中，通過RSU。

對於我的退休賬戶，我想從大型科技公司中分散投資。我是否
VTI/VXUS的多樣化程度是否足以限制對FAANG的暴露，或者是否有其他低成本的投資選擇？
還是有其他低成本的投資選擇，我應該...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qtry8q/etfs_that_limit_exposure_to_big_tech/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qtry8q/etfs_that_limit_exposure_to_big_tech/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 18:37:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I work at a big tech company and a very large part of my future income is tied up in company stock via RSUs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For my retirement accounts, I&amp;#39;m looking to diversify away from big tech. Is VTI/VXUS diversified enough to limit exposure to FAANG or are there other low cost investment options I should consider?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼股票下跌時，（長）國債會上漲（至少最近是這樣）？]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是否因爲。

a) 人們正在向安全地帶逃離（選擇國債而不是現金
的原因），或者

b) 每個人都認爲其他人都會購買國債，所以他們想提前進入
所以他們想早點進入，享受需求增加帶來的價格上漲，或者

c) 他們期待美聯儲降息，只有這樣......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qtpqyc/why_do_long_treasuries_go_up_when_stocks_go_down/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qtpqyc/why_do_long_treasuries_go_up_when_stocks_go_down/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 17:52:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is it because:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a) People are engaging in a flight to safety (and choose treasuries over cash for some reason), or&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;b) Everyone thinks everyone else will buy treasuries, so they want to get in early and enjoy the price boost as demand increases, or&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;c) They expect the Fed to cut rates and only then do they buy the treasuries, or&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;d) Some combination of the above?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t quite understand the argument for (a) because I doubt most investors decide to drop VTI or MSFT and buy and hold TLT for 18 years or whatever it&amp;#39;s average duration is, so it must only be a short term play (are they really expecting the down-turn to last the duration of TLT?), but why would it be safer than just holding cash or short/ultra-short bonds?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And if they really thought the currency was going to collapse, why not switch to another currency rather than locking into the USD with bonds that will get killed by inflation as the dollar collapses, so I don&amp;#39;t see how they are a flight to safety there either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it a reflex, IPS/corporate investment rules-based, is it not wanting to keep large amounts of cash in bank accounts, or is it some combination of (b) and (c), i.e. a profit motive?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果埃隆賣出更多的特斯拉股票，就怪罪於伯尼吧。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtswnt/blame_bernie_if_elon_sells_more_tesla_stock_lol/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtswnt/blame_bernie_if_elon_sells_more_tesla_stock_lol/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 17:20:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在您看來，現在哪隻股票的價值最被低估？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我希望在這個問題上能得到一堆回覆，然後無論哪隻股票最終成爲
在前五條回覆中，我今天會對它們進行自己的研究，然後
希望能在今晚之前公佈我的發現。

進入投資領域是我的新年決議，我已經開始真正地
進入...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtrh2g/in_your_opinion_which_stock_is_most_undervalued/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtrh2g/in_your_opinion_which_stock_is_most_undervalued/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 17:20:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m hoping to get a bunch of replies on this and then whichever stocks end up being in the top five replies, I’ll do my own research on them today and then hopefully post my findings by the end of the night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting into investing was my New Years resolution and I’ve been getting really into researching stocks since the start of the year. I’ve read and learned a lot about how to analyze different stocks but have never really posted on here about my own research.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d like to hopefully do that tonight for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a couple rules though:
1. You can only pick one company, don’t post like 5 of them, it wont count
2. Company’s valuation needs to be at least $3 billion dollars. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a few hours I’ll update this post with which five I’ve picked and then begin my research with the goal of hopefully posting what I’ve found tonight&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDIT:&lt;/strong&gt; Since I’m already getting replies, I’ll put a deadline for 1pm EST. Whichever five replies are the top rated at that time are the one’s I’ll look into&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲了月亮，我的朋友們！! 🚀镸週日塗鴉 ✍️]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtoq4h/to_the_moon_my_friends_sunday_scribble/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtoq4h/to_the_moon_my_friends_sunday_scribble/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 16:54:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[本週誰在做空Rivian？]]></title><description><![CDATA[現在大家都知道，Rivian將以與特斯拉18個月前相同的估值衝擊市場。
價值與特斯拉18個月前的價值相同。在我看來，Rivian是
將被嚴重打壓。Rivian公司的評估是基於特斯拉的表現。特斯拉有沒有
Rivian開發了一條生產線或電池，或芯片或人工智能或...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qthc16/whos_shorting_rivian_this_week/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qthc16/whos_shorting_rivian_this_week/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 16:54:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s now well know that Rivian is going to hit the Market with the same valuation as Tesla was at 18 months ago. It seems plain to me the Rivian is going to flop hard. Rivian&amp;#39;s evaluation is based on what Tesla has done. Has Rivian developed a production line or batteries, or chips or AI or logistics. Do they attract the world&amp;#39;s best engineers? Do they have an energy company? Do they have an insurance company? Also  do they have an Elon? If you can answers these questions properly you can see me point. What are your thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[過去一個月的市場情況如何]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtq4lx/how_the_market_has_been_over_the_past_month/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtq4lx/how_the_market_has_been_over_the_past_month/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 16:16:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[估值和基本面還重要嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我真的很想知道這一點。在每個人都認爲我是一個好的潮人，或者認爲我是一個價值投資者，把我的全部淨資產都投入到BABA，我不是。
投資人將我的全部淨資產投入BABA，我不是。我是在問一個
理論層面的問題。

在過去，估值和基本面都很重要，因爲大機構和普通散戶投資者都認爲。
機構和普通散戶投資者認爲...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qtn82y/do_valuations_and_fundamentals_matter_anymore/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qtn82y/do_valuations_and_fundamentals_matter_anymore/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 15:38:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I genuinely wonder this. Before everyone thinks ok boomer or that I&amp;#39;m some value investor dumping my entire net worth into BABA I&amp;#39;m not. I&amp;#39;m asking on a theoretical level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past, valuations and fundamentals have mattered because the big institutions and the average retail investor thought they mattered. Even algos, which on some level were active at the onset of the 80&amp;#39;s were programmed and directed to sell off stock when the valuation became too absurd. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But when I look at the Rivians and Nikolas of the world I start to think maybe they&amp;#39;re just a symptom of the larger mentality of the market, including institutions, including the algos that are programmed by humans that have normal human biases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Theoretically, if the larger consensus of the market.. from institutions to retail to the programmers making algos, was that only future potential growth mattered and nothing else, wouldn&amp;#39;t that theoretically mean that only growth and hype stocks would have growth and interest forever? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean on a purely theoretical level, if we reached a point where it was a consensus by the vast majority of investors from all levels and backgrounds was that speculation and growth wins the day, wouldn&amp;#39;t the market reflect that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I mean to say is the market can be a reflection of the risk appetite of the broad spectrum of humans investing and trading in it, and if that were to slowly shift would it be possible that value stocks or old blue chips are largely forgotten forever, or have a bad return versus hype/speculation/growth moving forward?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If no one is a Warren Buffett anymore, why would Warren Buffett-esque stocks have any market beating returns? No one would invest in them (on a level compared to hype/speculation stocks). They&amp;#39;d just theoretically sit there at low valuations forever paying out dividends and what not, with their only real growth being from stock buy backs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just a musing I had.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[未發佈的片段。週末的美聯儲]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtjfbl/unreleased_footage_fed_reserve_during_weekend/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtjfbl/unreleased_footage_fed_reserve_during_weekend/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 15:38:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[每天]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtmoki/everyday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtmoki/everyday/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 14:43:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一年內從3萬8千美元到11萬7千美元。由AMD提供 ❤️🚀🤑]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qt3wdm/38k_to_117k_in_a_year_courtesy_of_amd/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qt3wdm/38k_to_117k_in_a_year_courtesy_of_amd/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 14:30:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我今年19歲，在過去4個星期裏在股市中賺了2萬8千美元，現在我怎麼才能不失去這些呢？]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以我上個月基本上以1.5千美元起家，在使用槓桿的同時我
在22美元的時候買了Lucid，現在我已經賺了很多錢。

問題是我不能繼續使用我一直在使用的相同策略，因爲我
我覺得我很快就會失去它。所以我的問題是，我可以使用什麼策略，以便
即使我的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtmxsk/im_19_years_old_and_made_28_k_in_the_stock_market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtmxsk/im_19_years_old_and_made_28_k_in_the_stock_market/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 13:01:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I basically started off with 1.5 k last month and while using leverage I bought lucid at 22$ now I’ve made a bunch of money . &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem is I can’t keep using the same strategy I’ve been using because I feel like I’ll lose it very fast . So my question is what strategy can I use so even if my trades fail I don’t lose big chunks of my portfolio .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你究竟如何在股票和債券之間取得平衡？]]></title><description><![CDATA[是否有一個確切的公式可以遵循？還是隻是生理上的問題？究竟如何
你如何評估 "風險"？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qtf4i6/how_exactly_do_you_balance_between_stocks_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qtf4i6/how_exactly_do_you_balance_between_stocks_and/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 11:18:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is there an exact formula to follow? Or is it just physiological? How exactly do you assess &amp;quot;risk&amp;quot;?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這週會很有趣]]></title><description><![CDATA[本週的收益包括一些Reddit最提及的公司，它們包括
包括。

- Nvidia

- 阿里巴巴

- JD

- 百度

- Jmia

- 海底撈

其他有收益的公司包括零售店，如Target、Walmart。
羅斯、科爾士等]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qt3a50/this_week_will_be_interesting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qt3a50/this_week_will_be_interesting/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 10:04:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week earnings include some of Reddit&amp;#39;s most mentioned companies and they include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Nvidia&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Alibaba&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• JD&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Baidu&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Jmia&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Sea Limited&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other companies with earnings include retail stores such as Target, Walmart, Ross, Kohl&amp;#39;s, etc&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你對一隻股票最熱衷的看法是什麼，是看漲還是看跌？]]></title><description><![CDATA[你對任何一個股票行情的最有爭議的看法是什麼？無論它是一個
是大家都喜歡但你不喜歡的公司？
大家都看跌但你卻看漲它的未來？

我記得不久前的2017年，看漲特斯拉是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qthgfr/what_is_your_hottest_take_about_a_single_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qthgfr/what_is_your_hottest_take_about_a_single_stock/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 10:04:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What’s your most controversial take on any one stock ticker? Whether it’s a company that everyone tends to love but you don’t or if it is a company that everyone is bearish on but you are bullish on its future? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember not too long ago in 2017, being bullish on Tesla was considered controversial. These sort of takes tens to get the best returns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[EVERGRANDE在 "幾天內 "走向破產，匿名消息人士稱付款是 "錯誤 "的。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtcr3h/evergrande_is_heading_toward_bankruptcy_in_days/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtcr3h/evergrande_is_heading_toward_bankruptcy_in_days/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 08:25:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[通貨膨脹與印鈔之間的關係]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好。

我有一個經濟學教授告訴我的同學，從長遠來看，他認爲
通貨膨脹和貨幣供應量的增長將是一致的。許多人傾向於同意
這個經典理論，所以我花了幾個小時去研究它。

我發現，m2貨幣供應量，自1961年以來已經...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qt7foh/the_relationship_between_inflation_and_money/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qt7foh/the_relationship_between_inflation_and_money/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 06:39:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey Everyone, &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have an econ prof who told my class that in the long run, he believed that inflation and money supply growth would match up. Many people tend to agree with this classical theory, so I took a few hours and looked into it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I found was that m2 money supply, since 1961 has compounded annually at about 7.1% while CPI inflation has compounded annually at about 3.2%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, based on the above facts I&amp;#39;d argue that, over the past 60 years inflation and money supply haven&amp;#39;t shown a relationship approximating the classical economic theory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do you think M2 and inflation aren&amp;#39;t as correlated as economists tend to believe?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[裏維安與特斯拉的理智檢查：信封式計算]]></title><description><![CDATA[這將是簡短而溫馨的，因爲我現在得了covid（疲勞是一個b***c）。

讓我們假設TSLA不是像許多人所說的那樣是有史以來被高估的巨型股票之一。
爭論，我同意它被高估了很多。我不是TSLA的超級粉絲...

但....，我們假設TSLA的價值是公平的。

目前的市場...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtal6i/rivian_vs_tesla_sanity_check_back_of_the_envelope/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtal6i/rivian_vs_tesla_sanity_check_back_of_the_envelope/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 05:08:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This will be short and sweet as I am down with covid now (Fatigue is a b***c).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s assume that $TSLA is NOT one of the most overvalued mega cap ever as many argue and &lt;strong&gt;I agree it is overvalued by a lot&lt;/strong&gt;. Not a huge TSLA fan here...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But ....let&amp;#39;s assume TSLA is fairly valued.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Current market cap:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$TSLA: 1T&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$RIVN: 127B&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ratio of market cap: 7.8&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not going to judge RIVN on current (near zero) revenue. Let&amp;#39;s look at 2 years out and 9 years out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A conservative forecast is that $TSLA can add &lt;a href=&quot;https://cleantechnica.com/2021/11/09/tesla-growth-in-the-next-two-years-2022-2023/&quot;&gt;1.21M&lt;/a&gt; vehicles to its yearly production. This is based on actual plants in/soon-to-be in production. Assuming 2021Q4 will grow at 15% over 2021Q3 (same growth from Q2 to Q3), TSLA would have produced 900M vehicles this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TSLA 2021: 900M&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TSLA 2023: 2.11M&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TSLA 2030: Elon projects 20M&lt;/strong&gt;. This can be super optimistic, I will get back to it soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Demand for TSLA? TSLA does not have a demand issue as Elon. For example, currently TSLA is the second largest EV in *CHINA*.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s Look at RIVIAN ($RIVN) production forecast according to its own CEO, however ambitious and optimistic:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RIVN 2023: &lt;a href=&quot;https://insideevs.com/news/546885/rivian-production-capacity-target-1million/&quot;&gt;CEO projects 200K&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RIVN 2030:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://insideevs.com/news/546885/rivian-production-capacity-target-1million/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CEO projects at least 1M&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Car production:&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whether in 2023 or 2030, TSLA will produce at least 10X as RIVN. I say at least because TSLA can prove based on current plans capacity it can deliver 2.1M in 2023, RIVN CEO cannot really prove that, but let&amp;#39;s take his work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Demand&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Much hype has been made about RIVN because F and AMZN invested in it. And AMZN has committed to purchase 100K vehicles over the next 5 years. Let&amp;#39;s put things into perspective: &lt;strong&gt;TSLA has proved its popularity in CHINA, EUROPE, and US vs. RIVN has a contract with AMZN.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some misunderstanding by retail investors about RIVN:&lt;/strong&gt; Just because F and AMZN backed RIVN does not mean they will be giving RIVN free money OK?  IF that guarantees that RIVN can finance with future rounds (good thing), this will dilute your shares&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other production&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unlike TSLA, RIVN is ONLY a car company. TSLA produces solar, batteries, software, soon Lithium, + has proven it can navigate through shortages&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Management:&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I think we all agree - even TSLA haters - that Elon is one of the smartest most innovative, most ambitious visionary with a long track record of success after success. We know nothing about Scaringe. He is definitely a smart guy, but it would be extremely extremely optimistic to think he can one up Elon on innovation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Finally we can talk about returns on your investment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RIVN remains largely pre-revenue, it has not proven itself yet. Therefore investors RIVN which is more risky play, needs to deliver higher returns than TSLA. &lt;strong&gt;No one would invest in a pre-revenue company if its expected return on investment does not exceed  more mature companies.&lt;/strong&gt; Would you invest in TSLA if the returns on its stock is not going to exceed that of KO?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2030 TSLA/RIVN Car production only &lt;strong&gt;= 20x.&lt;/strong&gt; Let&amp;#39;s say Elon is too optimistic about 2030 and Scaringe is conservative, &lt;strong&gt;let&amp;#39;s say it is 15X&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Currently the market cap is only 7.8 X half of production ratio.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This means that even if TSLA&amp;#39;s non-car production (solar, software, chips, etc) does not materialize and is equal to zero (against all evidence) ...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TLDR/CONCLUSION:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At fair valuation in 2030 &lt;strong&gt;with extremely generous assumption to RIVN&lt;/strong&gt; compared to TSLA &lt;strong&gt;the returns on your RIVN investment will be HALF of that of TSLA&lt;/strong&gt;.. (1+x)=2*(1+y)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If the return on your TSLA stock is 100% ===&amp;gt; $RVN will be 0%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If the return on your TSLA stock is 50% ===&amp;gt; $RVN will be -25%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If the return on your TSLA stock is 0% ===&amp;gt; $RVN will be -50%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IF TSLA crashes by 30% as some TSLA skeptics such as me believe it is possible, RIVN will have to crash by 65%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, this is under the assumption that TSLA (like RIVN) is only a car company and that RIVN will meet and exceed its goals in comparison to TSLA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Would you invest in a pre-revenue company with lower returns than a mature company?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more analysis like this you can follow me on twitter: at TCPresearch ... I will be soon revealing a couple of companies that are garbage which are under the radar. I also retweet the most actionable investment insights I see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy investing everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以植物爲基礎的飲食已超過10年。Beyond Meat/Impossible是一項可怕的投資。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我尊重他們的產品，但他們的整個業務完全是一個垃圾場。
超越公司是投資者對利潤的壓力的受害者，而不是發展研究和
長期增長。

 1. 你爲什麼要與大的連鎖店合作，向顧客介紹一些
    新的和有競爭力的東西，而不是像......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtee3g/plant_based_diet_for_over_10_years_beyond/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qtee3g/plant_based_diet_for_over_10_years_beyond/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 03:55:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I respect their product, but their entire business is a complete dumpster fire. Beyond is victim of investor pressure for profits over developing research and long-term growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why would you partner with big chains to introduce customers to something new and competitive to as something as powerful as meat? Meat consumers have context behind their diet and have eaten it in a number of ways and occasions. WHY WOULD FAST FOOD QUALITY PRODUCTION CONVINCE PEOPLE? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oatly understand consumer behavior and capitalized on the right trend. It had decades of research and recipe mastery before growing into public consciouness. It&amp;#39;s currently questioning willingness to pay due to shortage and inflationary pressures, and it knows how to disrupt larger players.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I hate tattooed chef but at this point I would agree that it&amp;#39;s a better plant based investment than Beyond Meat. At the very least, Tattooed chef knows who to focus on and where to be discovered so that a customer COMES BACK FOR MORE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond Meat will fail as a company. To me it was clear after they failed to deliver on chicken substitutes, which should have been easier to land and expand with but they didn&amp;#39;t. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea doesn&amp;#39;t suck. The company does.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你現在對你的應急基金/現金做了什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[很好奇其他Bogleheads現在對他們的應急基金做了什麼？
現金--我曾經把它放在一套滾動的CD中，但CD一直很糟糕，我不再這樣做，而是把它留在MM中。
但CD一直很糟糕，我不再這樣做，而是把它留在MM中，但我在想是否有更好的
選擇。我們要考慮到未來幾年的大學開支。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qt93n5/what_are_you_doing_with_your_emergency_fundcash/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qt93n5/what_are_you_doing_with_your_emergency_fundcash/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 02:47:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Curious what other Bogleheads are doing right now with their emergency fund / cash - I used to keep it in a set of rolling CDs, but CDs have been so crappy I stopped doing that and have left it in MM, but I&amp;#39;m wondering if there are better options.  We have college expenses to think of in the next few years, so we need a decent amount in something guaranteed and accessible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[什麼是da meta寶貝？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtakyk/whats_da_meta_baby/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qtakyk/whats_da_meta_baby/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 02:47:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[他是我們中的一員]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qta29w/hes_one_of_us/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qta29w/hes_one_of_us/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 02:19:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我從來沒有讀過一本不推薦至少20%債券的投資書。]]></title><description><![CDATA[然而，有那麼多的人似乎相信，所有既定的
作家和專業人士都是不正確的，而他們這些小的散戶投資者是
是正確的。這裏似乎有些不對勁。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qtbvy1/ive_never_read_a_single_book_on_investing_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qtbvy1/ive_never_read_a_single_book_on_investing_that/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 02:19:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet there are so many out there who seem convinced that all the established writers and professionals are incorrect, and they, the small retail investor are correct.  Something seems off here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>