<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 03:22:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[⚠️🇺🇸#Update: Suspects now described as either Black OR Arab.

- 兩名嫌疑人仍然在逃
- 警方建議Waukesha的居民鎖好所有門窗
- CBS新聞現在報道有 "多個死亡 "https://t.co/vHAcNFrYEK]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462607860878254082</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462607860878254082</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 02:41:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[20個國家的亞馬遜員工將在黑色星期五罷工以爭取更好的工作條件]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 20個國家的亞馬遜員工正準備在黑色星期五進行罷工，作爲
> "讓亞馬遜付錢 "運動的一部分。 
> 
> 該運動包括一個由70個組織組成的聯盟，包括綠色和平組織。
> 樂施會，和亞馬遜工人國際。
> 
> 抗議活動是在越來越多的人反對的情況下進行的。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qza112/amazon_employees_in_20_countries_will_strike_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qza112/amazon_employees_in_20_countries_will_strike_on/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 02:41:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon employees in 20 countries are preparing to strike on Black Friday as part of the &amp;quot;Make Amazon Pay&amp;quot; campaign.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The campaign includes a coalition of 70 organizations, including Greenpeace, Oxfam, and Amazon Workers International.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The protests come amid mounting dissent from Amazon employees over working condition and union busting. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This seems like a one more strike that is going to have no effect on working conditions, stock or anything really. Share what you think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對沖基金目前擁有的前10只股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[對沖基金目前正在擊敗大盤，他們的綜合購買力
的力量可以輕易地推動股票上漲。花旗銀行剛剛發佈了一份名單，列出了截至年底最大的50家對沖基金持有的前10只
截至第三季度末，最大的50家對沖基金持有的10只股票。我不能說這個名單
名單是令人驚訝的，但它是有趣的，可以看到。



股票名稱...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz1jhq/the_top_10_stocks_owned_by_hedge_funds_right_now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz1jhq/the_top_10_stocks_owned_by_hedge_funds_right_now/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 02:41:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hedge funds are beating the broader market right now and their combined buying power can easily drive stocks higher. Citi just put out a list of the top 10 stocks held by the biggest 50 hedge funds as of the end of Q3. I can&amp;#39;t say the list is surprising, but it is interesting to see. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Ticker&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Name&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Number of funds holding as top 10 position in size&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;MSFT&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Microsoft&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;26&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;GOOGL&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;17&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;AMZN&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Amazon&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;17&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;FB&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;AAPL&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Apple&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;NFLX&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Netflix&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;CRM&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Salesforce&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;BKNG&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Booking Holdings&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;DASH&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Doordash&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;MA&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Mastercard&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s noteworthy that just because hedge funds own these stock, that doesn&amp;#39;t mean they are completely bullish on them in the near term. It&amp;#39;s very possible they are running shorts in the various forms (covered calls, puts, etc) against their own holdings to hedge themselves. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The only thing that stuck out to me here is BKNG&lt;/strong&gt;, which seems  overvalued, given it is trading at a price that is well above pre-pandemic levels and a P/E for this year over 55. Earnings are projected to grow at 130% next year.  That means the company would have about $100 per share in earnings. BKNG has traded very richly for some time, so applying a healthy 25X multiple on earnings, that would project a stock price of $2500 next year. In this market, a p/e of 25 looks pretty low, especially if the company continues to grow revenues quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sales for Q3 came in just under $4.7B&lt;/strong&gt;, which puts it on pace to exceed 2019 revenues of $15B in 2022 IF the trajectory continues. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BKNG sold off big after its last earnings report, despite the fact they delivered a healthy beat of expectations. The drop is presumably because expectations had grown too high in advance of earnings, on concerns that COVID would impact travel, and on profit taking.  It&amp;#39;s now down over 300 points from its high. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s interesting to see the trend reversal that just occurred in the travel sector. AirBnB, BKNG, and Expedia, were all up double digits from mid-August and in the past 10 days, all 3 are down. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Attractive entry point for BKNG?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It could be, but I&amp;#39;m betting the stock will retreat further as COVID cases rise due to holiday travels.  I&amp;#39;ll be looking to buy the stock if it dips back to 2,100 again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我的投資組合應該至少與標準普爾500指數一樣好嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，夥計們，我最近找到了一份工作，今年我成功地在ROTH IRA中獲得了6000美元，並開始了401k。
ROTH IRA並開始了401k。標準普爾500指數自9月以來上漲了20%（當我開始
我的倉位）。但我的回報卻少得多。我是否應該只投資於
標準普爾500指數？對不起，我是投資新手]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz5thz/should_my_portfolio_be_at_least_as_good_as_sp_500/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz5thz/should_my_portfolio_be_at_least_as_good_as_sp_500/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 02:07:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey guys, I recently got a job and this year I managed to both get 6000 in a ROTH IRA and start a 401k. The S&amp;amp;P 500 is up 20% since September (when I started my positions). But my returns are much less. Should I just be investing in the S&amp;amp;P 500? Sorry i am noob investor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在Waukesha假日遊行中，一輛汽車剛剛衝破警戒線，衝過行人，向窗外發射子彈。我和家人都很安全。事件發生在我們前面20英尺處。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462560182857310208</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462560182857310208</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 23:43:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如何以較小的風險獲得3倍於標準普爾指數的年複合增長率 | 長期的槓桿作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2741701

對於那些想知道現在到底該怎麼辦的人，我向你們介紹一個新的
無名英雄Michael Gayed。邁克爾找到了一種方法，可以系統性地超越
在承擔較少風險的情況下，系統地超越標準普爾500指數3倍以上，這是一個極其重要的方法。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qz07zp/how_to_3x_the_sp_cagr_with_less_risk_leverage_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qz07zp/how_to_3x_the_sp_cagr_with_less_risk_leverage_for/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 23:43:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2741701&quot;&gt;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2741701&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of your wondering what the hell to do now, I introduce you to a new unsung hero Michael Gayed. Michael has found a way to systemically outperform the S&amp;amp;P 500 by over 3x while taking on less risk and it&amp;#39;s an extremely simple investment strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone says that triple leveraged ETFs have volatility decay and are not meant for long-term holding. Well guess what, those people are idiots. Let&amp;#39;s look at the data: If you invested in UPRO using this guy&amp;#39;s simple strategy, backtested all the way back to 1928, you would have returned 27% CAGR while the S&amp;amp;P did 9% and by taking on half as much risk (0.6 Sharpe ratio for this strategy vs. 0.3 for buy &amp;amp; hold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rules are simple, if the underlying index closes below the 200 day moving average, you sell. Once it crosses back above the 200 MA, then reenter. That is it. &lt;strong&gt;Investing $10k in 1928 with this strategy would have returned $28 TRILLION (with a T) while the S&amp;amp;P would have returned $39 million.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason this works is because of the lack of volatility above the 200 MA, and higher volatility below the 200 MA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the sweet taste of compounding returns my friends because this is a ticket to an early retirement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR: Read the damn paper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼我現在要投資，因爲崩潰可能會到來......]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qz63mh/why_should_i_invest_now_when_a_crash_might_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qz63mh/why_should_i_invest_now_when_a_crash_might_be/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 23:43:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[新文章。

7張圖的星期天...

https://t.co/uZLzNqvOAy https://t.co/QJJsFAgJgh]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462535662641590287</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462535662641590287</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 22:38:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[無名氏的問題。爲什麼是國際？]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以我們的投資冒險剛剛開始。我們已經見了幾個
顧問和Vanguard PAS。每個人和維基都說你應該把一些
國際股票VTIAX的3/4基金組合。PAS建議高達
在75/25的股票債券組合中，30%的國際股票。我們有一個AUM的人說...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyyhnt/noob_question_why_international/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyyhnt/noob_question_why_international/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 22:22:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So we&amp;#39;re just starting out on our investing adventure. We&amp;#39;ve met with a couple advisors and Vanguard PAS. Everyone and the wiki says you should some international stock VTIAX in a 3/4 fund portfolio. PAS recommended as high as 30% international in a 75/25 stock bond portfolio. We had a AUM guy say 8% international. Just trying to wrap my mind around this. I have no business running backtests, but when I do = portfolios with higher % international don&amp;#39;t perform as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[將價值5萬美元的指數交易到英偉達？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道，KNOW NVIDIA是改變未來的脊髓。I
我認爲在10年內，它的價值至少在1000-1500美元/股。我真的
我真的相信它，而且作爲一名計算機工程師，我很瞭解它。

我已經知道omniverse的公告有一段時間了，所以買了227股...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0x1l/trade_50k_worth_index_into_nvidia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0x1l/trade_50k_worth_index_into_nvidia/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 22:22:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know, KNOW NVIDIA is the spinal cord that&amp;#39;s going to be changing the future. I think in 10 years it&amp;#39;ll be worth at least $1000-$1500 per share. I really believe in it, and being a computer engineer I understand it well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve known about the omniverse announcement for awhile, so bought 227 shares at $220 ($49,940) two months ago. But &lt;a href=&quot;/r/bogleheads&quot;&gt;/r/bogleheads&lt;/a&gt; convinced me it was gambling so I took it out and I&amp;#39;m pissed I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, in order to get that $50k I&amp;#39;d be having to sell 50k worth of VTSAX, meaning forfeiting early capital gains. I&amp;#39;ve only been investing for like 2 years, so it&amp;#39;s not that much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or.... should I just leave the VTSAX alone, invest $500 per week in that, then another $500 per week in QQQ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMD的未來？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在AMD有一個小倉位。50股。我已經在上面賺了一點錢。
但我想知道該公司的未來到底會怎樣？我知道
他們即將與xilinx合併，並與Meta公司合作，但是否有更多的增長？
但該股是否有可能有更多的增長？我不能完全看到...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0sab/the_future_of_amd/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0sab/the_future_of_amd/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 21:44:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have a small position in AMD. 50 Shares. I&amp;#39;ve made a little bit of money on them but I&amp;#39;m wondering what exactly the future holds for the company? I know they have an upcoming merger with xilinx and they&amp;#39;ve partnered with Meta, but is more growth for the stock possible? I can&amp;#39;t exactly see Semiconductors going anywhere, so I feel like the sky&amp;#39;s the limit. What are everyone&amp;#39;s thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你什麼時候知道自己是股票投資者或股票交易員？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直在網上閱讀一堆關於我目前感興趣的不同公司的隨機帖子。
我意識到，我很高興我是一個投資者，而且我永遠都是。
永遠都是。

我不明白人們怎麼能以交易員的心態存在。這似乎是
你需要學習大量的準科學，在...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyw688/when_did_you_know_you_were_stock_investor_or_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyw688/when_did_you_know_you_were_stock_investor_or_a/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 21:44:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been reading a bunch of random posts online about different companies I&amp;#39;m currently interested in, and I realize I&amp;#39;m happy that I&amp;#39;m an investor and I always will be. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t understand how people can exist with a trader mindset. It&amp;#39;s seems like you need to study alot of quasi science, be on social media constantly, do alot of cocaine, and it really just seems stressful. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The neat thing about reddit is I can look and see when people post their &amp;quot;analysis&amp;quot; of a stock. Which for 99% of reddit, is just a trader saying voodoo witch craft nonsense about enter and exit points, resistance this and that, cutting losses, and special orders. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then you ask for their portfolio and they have none or its top secret or something. It&amp;#39;s not illegal to share your portfolio you great traders. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m an average Joe, and I&amp;#39;m not that smart. so I feel really good when I read posts from people who buy a stock like MU, three years ago, at 40-43 a share, and sell it saying they see no future in it. It&amp;#39;s trading at like $83 now. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love it when I read people saying they bought Uber near ipo at 40 and sold at 32 and say it&amp;#39;s doomed to fail. But Uber is still around, in fact it hit a height of $60 last spring and now it&amp;#39;s $44. You haven&amp;#39;t even given it a chance to grow or become something yet. Like the company is a verb, give it a few years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think traders are like fake friends in high school. They&amp;#39;re only around you if you&amp;#39;re cool. Once you&amp;#39;re not cool anymore they abandon you. But traders are onlu a small portion of money for a company a company makes stuff to sell to people and that&amp;#39;s what really draws in revenue to grow. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see alot of people talk about the &amp;quot;opportunity cost&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;oppurtuniy lost, &amp;quot; something like that when you&amp;#39;re not trading. Like if I buy something that isn&amp;#39;t moving fast, or something is in the red, it&amp;#39;s better to &amp;quot;cut my losses.&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But that&amp;#39;s like... Buying high and selling low. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That sounds like the exact opposite of what you&amp;#39;re supposed to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honestly, I&amp;#39;d rather sink with my ship if you&amp;#39;re telling me to always sell the moment my stock goes red. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;if I was so foolish as to pick a bad company, I&amp;#39;d rather just take the full loss, rather then death by a thousand cuts. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I pick companies that make more revenue every year, have increasing dividends, and are medium to large size growth companies. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m boring. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just look at the best performing companies, read their 10k and just invest. My first two companies I bought were Apple and Starbucks, I then bought Nvidia and Realty Income. I bought Pennymac and Weyerhaeuser afterward. I just sorta sit on them. I just hold them and buy more. If I somehow become broke instantly from these decisions then damn. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m investing in known companies with easy business models. I like safety and simplicity. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t believe I&amp;#39;m gonna become a multi millionaire with several cars and boats. I just want to make enough money to be the first millionaire in my family, and have my children live of my dividends so they don&amp;#39;t have to work so hard. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It just seems like people don&amp;#39;t have patience on the internet. And when you take the time to read people who argue about a particular stock, and then for those same people to be proven wrong by time. It feels good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[是否有充分的理由從富達或施瓦布轉到Vanguard？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道他們本質上可以做同樣的事情，但我喜歡Vanguard的整個精神。
但我喜歡Vanguard的整個精神，並經常想，我是否應該轉換。這只是一種偏好
還是使用Vanguard有明顯的優勢？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyy6h0/is_there_a_strong_reason_to_switch_to_vanguard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyy6h0/is_there_a_strong_reason_to_switch_to_vanguard/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 21:16:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know they essentially can do the same things, but I like the whole ethos of Vanguard and have often wondered if I should switch. Is it just a preference thing or are there clear advantages from using Vanguard?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是否應該開設羅斯退休基金？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我有一個401k，我把工資的20%放在一個星期內。我每月把大約500美元左右的資金存入
每月在應稅賬戶中存入約500美元。目前我的應稅賬戶佔我總儲蓄的23%。
退休。

我是否也應該開一個羅斯賬戶？它們聽起來非常有吸引力，有幾個原因。

我把應稅賬戶作爲一個安全網...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyu75h/should_i_open_a_roth_ira/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyu75h/should_i_open_a_roth_ira/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 20:42:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have a 401k that I&amp;#39;m putting 20% of pay in a week. I put about $500 or so a month in a taxable account. Currently my taxable is 23% of my total savings for retirement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should I open a Roth as well? They sound very attractive for several reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was using a taxable account as a safety net should I need to access some of the money. Also I was hoping to retire at 55 and use this account to bridge me over to my 401k.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But from my understanding I could open a Roth and take some or all of the principle out at anytime without penalty.  Also this money grows tax free and can be withdrawn tax free at 59.5. So essentially I could start taking the principle out early if I want to retire early.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe its best to have a combination of all 3 401k, Roth, Taxable?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有了納斯達克，爲什麼還要買SP500？]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好，我在市場上投資已經3-4年了。我只是DCA
像你們中的大多數人一樣。我知道的不多。

起初，我買了WORLD追蹤器，然後我意識到大部分的%來自於
美國（我住在歐洲），所以我換成了標準普爾500，現在我意識到大部分的
％來自...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyv4a9/why_sp500_when_there_is_nasdaq/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyv4a9/why_sp500_when_there_is_nasdaq/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 20:27:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello there, it has been 3-4 years since I&amp;#39;m investing in the market. I just DCA like most of you. I don&amp;#39;t know much tbh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At first, I bought WORLD Tracker, then I realized most of the % comes from the US (I live in Europe btw), so I switched to S&amp;amp;P500 and now I realize most of the % comes from NASDAQ100. (Yeah I&amp;#39;m not a quick learner).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, why wouldn&amp;#39;t I want to put everything in NASDAQ100? I know the drawdown is higher but the profit is as well. And inflation is just starting imo...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[關於俄羅斯準備在1月下旬攻擊烏克蘭的消息。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這裏的新聞文章
https://www.militarytimes.com/flashpoints/2021/11/20/russia-preparing-to-attack-ukraine-by-late-january-ukraine-defense-intelligence-agency-chief/

我想知道這是否值得關注？ 通常情況下，這些事情不會影響到美國的經濟。
美國股市，因爲它通常是由兩個小的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0kx4/news_about_russia_preparing_to_attack_ukraine_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qz0kx4/news_about_russia_preparing_to_attack_ukraine_in/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 20:27:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;news article here &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.militarytimes.com/flashpoints/2021/11/20/russia-preparing-to-attack-ukraine-by-late-january-ukraine-defense-intelligence-agency-chief/&quot;&gt;https://www.militarytimes.com/flashpoints/2021/11/20/russia-preparing-to-attack-ukraine-by-late-january-ukraine-defense-intelligence-agency-chief/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was wondering is this of any concern? normally these thinsg wouldnt affect the US stock market because it usually from 2 small countries. but this seems like a different situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vanguard在等待時間，我在1:17放棄了]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyw6vc/vanguard_on_hold_times_i_gave_up_at_117/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyw6vc/vanguard_on_hold_times_i_gave_up_at_117/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 17:53:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我們的人民https://t.co/UUuzClMemw]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461790163177295884</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1461790163177295884</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 17:41:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在2月份的歷史高點購買了所有這些股票，在市場創下歷史高點時，它們仍然全部下跌。現在削減損失嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道，在市場上的時間比在市場上的時間更重要，這就是爲什麼我在所有時間的高點買入。
在所有時間的高點買入。但當納斯達克和標準普爾指數每隔一天都在上漲時
但當納斯達克指數和標準普爾指數每隔一天都在上漲時，要想在這些股票持續交易時平均下來是很困難的。
橫盤/下跌。一個人如何克服不想要的心態呢？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyx5s1/purchased_all_these_stocks_in_feb_at_all_time/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyx5s1/purchased_all_these_stocks_in_feb_at_all_time/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 17:22:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know the saying time in the market beats timing the market, which is why I bought during all time highs. But when the nasdaq and s&amp;amp;p keep going up every other day it’s tough to want to average down when these stocks keep trading sideways/ down. How does one get over the mindset of not wanting to sell for a loss?
Arkf -16%
Arkg -37%
Arkw -17%
Moon -32%
Expi -40%
Prnt -24%&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這就是你的投資方式。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyth8s/this_is_how_you_invest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyth8s/this_is_how_you_invest/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 15:40:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[第一次上萬科的網站....，真的這麼簡單嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[有人可以只開一個賬戶，購買VTI，每年拿到稅單，就可以了。
就這樣簡單了？

幾乎看起來太容易了？

挑選賬戶容易嗎？Roth/經紀公司等？我一直在想，這裏面一定有
一些棘手的地方]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyuykq/first_time_on_the_vanguard_siteis_it_really_this/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyuykq/first_time_on_the_vanguard_siteis_it_really_this/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 15:21:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Someone can just make an account, buy VTI and get the tax paper each year and that’s it in a nutshell? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost seems too easy? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is picking the account easy? Roth/brokerage etc? I keep thinking there has to be something tricky somewhere&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[將你的時間和精力過度分配給投資組合優化是次優的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不知道這種情況有多普遍，但這是我意識到的一個戰略錯誤。
我認爲這可能值得思考。

對投資組合進行研究和回溯測試等等是很有趣的，我知道。
我知道，我當然同意，花時間設計投資組合是很重要的。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyry5y/overallocating_your_time_and_effort_to_portfolio/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyry5y/overallocating_your_time_and_effort_to_portfolio/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 13:03:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not sure how common this is, but this is a strategic mistake I realized I&amp;#39;m making and I think that it might be worth thinking about. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Geeking out about portfolios and studying and backtesting and so on is fun, I know, and I certainly agree that it is important to take the time to design a portfolio that is compatible with one&amp;#39;s objectives and risk tolerance; but, as with many other things, extra effort has diminishing returns and there soon comes a time when your time (heh) and work would be better spent elsewhere. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Case in point: lately I have been obsessing about whether to increase my bond allocation by 5% now or 2/3 years from now as per my initial plan (this has nothing to do with the market being &amp;quot;high&amp;quot;, I&amp;#39;m just concerned that I might be overestimating a little my risk tolerance), and I spent way more time thinking about this than putting extra work towards a certification that could increase my wages by about &lt;strong&gt;10%&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I... don&amp;#39;t think I have to spell out why this is not the best use of my time and effort. So yeah, it might be worth it to keep in mind that it is suboptimal to overallocate one&amp;#39;s resources towards portfolio optimization. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now if I know myself, the danger is that I&amp;#39;ll spend the next four months designing and refining the perfect allocation of my time and mental efforts towards my various work and life objectives rather than doing what I am supposed to do... :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[週末，當我不持有看漲期權時，特斯拉與我持有看漲期權時，特斯拉。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qykw6v/tesla_over_the_weekend_when_i_dont_own_calls_vs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qykw6v/tesla_over_the_weekend_when_i_dont_own_calls_vs/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 13:03:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我在WSB上的第一個帖子--我應該持有還是賣出？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyedi1/my_first_post_on_wsb_should_i_hold_or_sell/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyedi1/my_first_post_on_wsb_should_i_hold_or_sell/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 12:36:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ZIM看起來還好嗎？17%的股息？]]></title><description><![CDATA[該死的，我在45點賣掉了我在ZIM的小倉位，現在又回到了57點！我還注意到他們現在有17%的股息。

我還注意到他們現在有17%的股息。這有聽起來那麼好嗎？

不管怎樣，我想週一在ZIM上投1500美元。新的目標價格是80美元
我想航運終於開始有點緩解了？

任何關於...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qykjyh/is_zim_looking_ok_17_dividend/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qykjyh/is_zim_looking_ok_17_dividend/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 11:33:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Darn I sold my small position in ZIM at 45 and now it&amp;#39;s back to 57!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also noticed they have a 17% dividend now.  Is that as good as it sounds?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways I&amp;#39;m thinking of throwing $1500 in ZIM Monday.  New price target is $80 and I guess shipping is finally starting to ease a bit?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any info on shipping? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is ZIM a good move now?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Empower對我的401k轉帳徵稅？]]></title><description><![CDATA[幫助! 我正在向IRA和Roth IRA轉帳（從401k和Roth 401k）。
我在電話中與Empower公司的代表進行了非常徹底的溝通。
我在電話中與Empower公司的代表進行了非常徹底的溝通（將其保留在IRA中，並轉爲他們的IRA經紀賬戶
產品），並將所有的東西都以實物形式滾動起來。應該不會有什麼問題。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyb85h/empower_taxed_my_401k_rollover/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyb85h/empower_taxed_my_401k_rollover/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 10:59:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Help! I’m in the middle of a rollover to an IRA and Roth IRA (from a 401k and Roth 401k) I went through everything pretty thoroughly on the phone with the rep from Empower (Keeping it with Empower in an IRA, to their IRA brokerage acct product) and rolling everything over in kind. There should be no taxes associated with the transaction, but it’s showing I’m paying state and fed taxes on this. It seems like Empower screwed something up here, hopefully they aren’t screwing me in the process. I’ve rolled over 401ks before and this has always been a pretty uneventful process, has anyone seen this happen?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[薩爾瓦多將創建 "比特幣城"，用計劃中的10億美元債券發行中的5億美元購買更多的比特幣]]></title><description><![CDATA[薩爾瓦多是唯一一個將比特幣作爲法定貨幣的國家，它將會
總統Nayib Bukele在週六晚上的薩爾瓦多比特幣週上說，他將在最大的加密貨幣基礎上建立一個完整的城市。
在週六晚上薩爾瓦多比特幣周的一次演講中說。

"比特幣城 "將位於豐塞卡灣沿岸，靠近一個...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyp4ry/el_salvador_to_create_bitcoin_city_use_500m_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyp4ry/el_salvador_to_create_bitcoin_city_use_500m_of/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 10:47:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;El Salvador, the only country in which bitcoin is a legal tender, is going to build an entire city based on the largest cryptocurrency, President Nayib Bukele said in a Saturday night presentation at Bitcoin Week in El Salvador.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Bitcoin City” will be located along the Gulf of Fonseca near a volcano. The government plans on locating a power plant by the volcano to provide energy for both the city and bitcoin mining, the president said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Bukele, Bitcoin City will be a full-fledged metropolis with residential and commercial areas, restaurants, an airport as well as a port and rail service. The city will be laid out in a circle (like a coin) and in the city center will be a plaza that will be host to a huge bitcoin symbol. The city will have no income, property, capital gains or payroll taxes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bukele also said El Salvador plans on issuing $1 billion US “bitcoin bond,” a tokenized financial instrument developed by Blockstream, on the Liquid Network. Of that amount, $500 million will be used to help construct needed energy and bitcoin mining infrastructure and $500 million to buy even more bitcoin. At the cryptocurrency’s recent trading price of about $59,000, that would bring the country’s treasury stash to just under 2,000 bitcoins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coindesk.com/business/2021/11/21/el-salvador-to-create-bitcoin-city-use-500m-of-planned-1b-bond-offering-to-buy-more-crypto/&quot;&gt;https://www.coindesk.com/business/2021/11/21/el-salvador-to-create-bitcoin-city-use-500m-of-planned-1b-bond-offering-to-buy-more-crypto/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[什麼是基本的退休Boglehead組合？]]></title><description><![CDATA[60/40股票/債券 - 假設20%的外國股票 - 使用VTI/VXUS/BND/BNDX

像這樣嗎？

VTI 48% VXUS 12% 32% BND 8% BNDX

就這樣嗎，並使用4%的規則？Bogglehead認可嗎？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyf4h9/what_is_the_basic_at_retirement_boglehead/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyf4h9/what_is_the_basic_at_retirement_boglehead/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 10:47:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;60/40 Stocks/Bonds - Assuming 20% Foreign - Using VTI/VXUS/BND/BNDX&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VTI 48% VXUS 12% 32% BND 8% BNDX&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s it? and use the 4% rule? Bogglehead approved?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這是我今晚的幸運餅乾。不過他們把位置拼錯了。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyl6pd/this_was_my_fortune_cookie_tonight_they/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyl6pd/this_was_my_fortune_cookie_tonight_they/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 10:11:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在我妻子的分娩宮縮日線圖上有非常看漲的指標。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qymmak/very_bullish_indicator_on_my_wifes_labor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qymmak/very_bullish_indicator_on_my_wifes_labor/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 09:22:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ARK投資公司的凱西-伍德說："只要我們不陷入衰退，"我們就處於一個長期的牛市，https://t.co/OE9BPCgVjO。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462118090112737291</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462118090112737291</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 08:45:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這些是我手上的袋子。你認爲哪些是我應該退休的，哪些是我應該放棄的？]]></title><description><![CDATA[這些是我所持有的最近受到很大沖擊的股票，而且
跌幅在10%或以上的股票

tpic, -44%, -5.313k$

bfly, -38%, -2.871k

CRSR，-29%，-1.98萬

Tdoc, -26%, -13.9K

EXI, -22%, -1.3K

美聯儲, -19%, -1.6k

巴巴, -16%, -3.96K

BIDU, -16%, -12.7K

PYSF, -12%, -0.25K

哪些人做...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyf4oo/these_are_the_bags_that_i_am_holding_which_ones/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyf4oo/these_are_the_bags_that_i_am_holding_which_ones/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 08:45:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are the stocks that I hold that have been hit quite hard recently and where I am10% or more down&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TPIC, -44%, -5.313K$&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BFLY, -38%, -2.871K&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CRSR, -29%, -1.98k&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TDOC, -26%, -13.9K&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EXPI, -22%, -1.3K&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MGNI, -19%, -1.6K&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BABA, -16%, -3.96K&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BIDU, -16%, -12.7K&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PYSF, -12%, -0.25K&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which ones do you think are gonna take the longest to break even (if at all) and which ones are hopeless? BABA, BIDU and TDOC, I am long, but the others I am not sure..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS: I have been very bad in my timing with EXPI, MGNI and TDOC (EXPI was up about 10% at the end of October, MGNI was up 100% in march and break even beginning of Sep, TDOC I was break even in July)...missed all these exit or position reduction points..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[蒙特利爾銀行認爲標普500指數明年將達到5,300點，增幅爲12%。]]></title><description><![CDATA[> BMO認爲，明年股市將繼續上漲，儘管幅度較小。
> 標準普爾500指數今年迄今已飆升25%，2020年爲16%，2019年爲30%。
>在2019年。
> 
> 該銀行的首席投資策略師布萊恩-貝爾斯基(Brian Belski)預測，該指數將在2022年達到5300點。
> 在2022年達到5,300點。這將代表一個收益...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qy62wa/bmo_sees_sp_500_hitting_5300_next_year_a_12_gain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qy62wa/bmo_sees_sp_500_hitting_5300_next_year_a_12_gain/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 07:17:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BMO believes the stock market will continue to ascend next year, though less vigorously, after the S&amp;amp;P 500 has soared 25% year to date, 16% in 2020 and 30% in 2019.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bank’s Chief Investment Strategist Brian Belski predicts the index will hit 5,300 in 2022. That would represent a gain of 13% from the Friday’s recent level of 4,699.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you ready for more pump? What&amp;#39;s your top pick?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[關於指數基金的逆向視角。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我總是喜歡聽到逆向的觀點。這個人有一個觀點，即
投資於SPY、IVV、VOO和其他標準普爾500指數ETF可能並不那麼明智或
他的觀點是，投資於SPY、IVV、VOO和其他標普500指數的ETF可能並不像標準投資建議所顯示的那樣明智或多樣化。

他的觀點是，很大比例的投資者只是購買SPY或類似的
ETFs....]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyjoxz/a_contrarian_perspective_on_index_funds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyjoxz/a_contrarian_perspective_on_index_funds/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 06:54:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I always love hearing contrarian perspectives. This guy has a perspective that investing in SPY, IVV, VOO And Other S&amp;amp;P 500 ETFs may not be as wise or diversified as standard investment advice would make it seem. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His perspective is that a large percentage of investors just buy SPY or similar ETFs. Such a sizable amount that the diversity argument for them is effected. Diversity only works well if there&amp;#39;s enough buyers and sellers of the individual stocks that make up the index. But if mostly everyone is buying the index, diversity doesn&amp;#39;t matter: as instead of the index &amp;quot;tracking&amp;quot; these stocks the index is influencing their price instead; thus you start to have similar liquidity issues as you would it you only bought stock in one or two companies. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words, the more people invest in index funds, the less effective the diversity of the index fund is, and the more liquidity risk you are exposed to. Basically it&amp;#39;s better to handle diversification more actively rather than rely on indexes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Article was written in 2017, so he may not have foreseen the liquidity injections of 2020 and 2021. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not quite sold on his thesis. What do you all think?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hvst.com/posts/4-reasons-you-should-run-away-from-spy-ivv-voo-and-other-s-p-500-etfs-E2ATWDnB&quot;&gt;https://www.hvst.com/posts/4-reasons-you-should-run-away-from-spy-ivv-voo-and-other-s-p-500-etfs-E2ATWDnB&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不能停止交易股票/期權？你可能已經上癮了]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 成癮是指無法停止消費一種化學品或追求一種
> 活動，儘管會造成傷害。

交易的人也會發生非常多的情況。我們能否將交易成癮定義爲
我們是否可以將交易成癮定義爲：在對投資充滿熱情和失去投資熱情之間越過一條線
喪失停止交易的能力。

>的。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyms02/cant_stop_trading_stockoptions_you_may_be_addicted/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyms02/cant_stop_trading_stockoptions_you_may_be_addicted/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 05:53:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Addiction is the inability to stop consuming a chemical or pursuing an activity despite causing harm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very much the same happens to people who trade. Can we define trading addiction as a crossing a line between being passionate about investing and losing the ability to stop trading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The problem focuses on the brain and understanding how its reward systems can train you to trade compulsively and dangerously.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some signs of addiction&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You spend far too much of your free time trading.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are trading stocks at work (and it isn’t your job)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The “high” of trying to find the next “moonshot” is the focus of attention.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have feelings for frustration, aggression or attempt to suppress other personal problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Losing money on a position makes you depressed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can’t stop trading.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continually looking at your phone to check the latest value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You lie to others about what you are doing on your phone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The bulk of your investing advice comes from social media “experts.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You borrowed money on a credit card, home equity line, or a personal loan to invest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your emotional state is directly tied to the outcome of the stock market.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is a lack of self-control or ability to stay away from your trading app.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sounds like many people that I know are addicted...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[邁克爾-伯裏的最新持股（山頓資產管理公司）]]></title><description><![CDATA[科隆資產管理有限公司

http://www.scionasset.com - Saratoga, ca

## scion資產管理公司位於Saratoga，由Dr. MICHAEL J.
BURRY經營。科隆資產管理公司是一家對沖基金，有5個客戶，全權管理的
管理的資產（AUM）爲638,901,404美元（2021-03年的表格預付款）。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qy9nxu/michael_burrys_latest_holdings_scion_asset/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qy9nxu/michael_burrys_latest_holdings_scion_asset/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 03:43:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;h1&gt;SCION ASSET MANAGEMENT, LLC&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;HTTP://WWW.SCIONASSET.COM&quot;&gt;HTTP://WWW.SCIONASSET.COM&lt;/a&gt; • SARATOGA, CA&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;## Scion Asset Management is based out of Saratoga and is run by Dr. Michael J. Burry. Scion Asset Management is a hedge fund with 5 clients and discretionary assets under management (AUM) of $638,901,404 (Form ADV from 2021-03-31). Their last reported 13F filing for Q3 2021 included $41,719,000 in managed 13F securities and a top 10 holdings concentration of 100.0%. Scion Asset Management’s largest holding is CVS Health Corp. (Melville Shoe) with shares held of 200,000. Whalewisdom has at least 16 13F filings, and 7 13D filings.&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Click link for current holdings with detail:&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/HpdNN83.jpg&quot;&gt;https://i.imgur.com/HpdNN83.jpg&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Original link to 13F&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://whalewisdom.com/filer/scion-asset-management-llc#tabholdings_tab_link&quot;&gt;https://whalewisdom.com/filer/scion-asset-management-llc#tabholdings_tab_link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CVS  40.68% of Portfolio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LMT  24.82%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GEO 20.75%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CXW 8.79%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DNOW 2.75%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SCYX 2.21%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a lot to unpack here, but have at it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Few notes. Massive reduction in securities:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Q2 ‘21 USD 147,257,000.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Q3 ‘21 USD  41,719,000.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TSLA PUTS comprised the largest portion of his portfolio in previous quarters and now make up 0%. Unknown what the actual loss was, but assume it was substantial. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Q2 ‘21 35% -&amp;gt; Q3 ‘21 0%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Current lineup looks a hedge to some great coming apocalypse. This will end badly for Burry. I’d be surprised if SCION doesn’t shut down within a year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美國的通貨膨脹趨勢真的那麼可怕嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美國10月份的通貨膨脹率按年計算爲6.2%，這是一個超高的數字。
考慮到近期低於3%的利率的歷史。

也就是說，我來自一個地方，在那裏，當他們得到6%的通貨膨脹率時，人們會擊掌相慶。
6%的通脹率。雙位數是那裏的常態。當我還是個孩子的時候
我們生活在...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyjgng/is_the_inflation_trend_in_the_us_really_that_scary/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qyjgng/is_the_inflation_trend_in_the_us_really_that_scary/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 03:00:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The October inflation in the US was 6.2% on an annual basis, which is super high given the recent history of sub-3% rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That said, I come from a place where people were high-fiving when they get anywhere 6% inflation. Double digits were the norm back there. When I was a kid we lived under hyperinflation which is a complete shit show, people get their paychecks and immediately go buy their groceries for the month. This is not a figure of speech, they really did go IMMEDIATLY because the prices were readjusted 1 or 2 times IN THE SAME DAY. Concept of savings was non-existent. Either you buy as much US Dollars as possible or put in some asset that has intrinsic value like real estate. The house I grew up was huge, and I learned that was not because my father was in a good financial situation, but rather it was the only option to dump all his savings before it lose half of its value in matter of weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Long story short, my bar is a bit out of place here... so should I be concerned with the 6.2% rate? My take on this: likely FED will increase rates, which will devalue bonds and stock prices. But then this should be already embedded in the current asset prices, so I don&amp;#39;t think I should be doing anything with my portfolio here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[傻瓜式的市場泡沫解釋]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyhjq0/market_bubble_explained_for_dummies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qyhjq0/market_bubble_explained_for_dummies/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 01:46:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[更正：MarketWatch刪除了早些時候的一條推文，該推文不準確地暗示每加侖5美元的汽油、90美元的葡萄酒和200美元的音樂會門票是普通美國人近期的典型購買行爲。該報道已被更正。

https://t.co/Y8kBdRHPKI https://t.co/n48rruC9h7]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462160448665665544</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462160448665665544</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 23:39:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不要相信金融市場風險模型。現實總是太複雜，無法準確建模。]]></title><description><![CDATA[2010年，投資者和Baupost集團的創始人Seth Klarman描述了金融危機的主要教訓。
金融危機中的關鍵教訓，這些教訓要麼從未被吸取，要麼被大多數市場參與者立即遺忘。
被大多數市場參與者立即遺忘。由他掌舵的
Baupost集團的平均收益率爲18%左右，而且自1982年以來------。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyaa0c/do_not_trust_financial_market_risk_models_reality/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qyaa0c/do_not_trust_financial_market_risk_models_reality/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 22:46:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2010  investor and founder of the Baupost Group Seth Klarman described key lessons from the financial crisis which were either never learned or else immediately forgotten by most market participants. With him at the helm the Baupost Group has averaged around 18% and that since 1982 - a spectacular return. Some of these lessons are very relevant today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do not trust financial market risk models. Reality is always too complex to be accurately modeled. Attention to risk must be a 24/7/365 obsession, with people – not computers – assessing and reassessing the risk environment in real time. Despite the predilection of some analysts to model the financial markets using sophisticated mathematics, the markets are governed by behavioral science, not physical science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s your take on where the stock market going in 2022?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[把大部分應急資金放在I型債券上是個好主意]]></title><description><![CDATA[鑑於通貨膨脹和目前的I型債券利率，我正在考慮開始將
將我的應急基金的一大部分轉移到I型債券。當然，我將在若干年內
在若干年內，這樣我就不會處於這樣的境地，即我在持有一年前就需要動用這筆錢......
需要在持有1年之前動用這筆錢......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyck93/good_idea_to_put_most_of_emergency_funds_in_i/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qyck93/good_idea_to_put_most_of_emergency_funds_in_i/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 22:34:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given inflation and current I bond interest rate, I’m considering starting to move a big chunk of my emergency fund into I bonds. Of course I would space this out over a number of years so that I wouldn’t be in a position where I would need to access that money before the 1 year holding period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interest to hear thoughts - do people think this is a good idea? How quickly can I bond funds be transferred to a bank account (after the 1 year hold period of course). My thinking is that in a major emergency, I could use a credit card to hold us over for a few weeks while we transfer the I bond money. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just hate to have a decent amount of money sitting in an online savings account making 0.4% when it could be making 7.12% in an I bond.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在《家有兒女》中，父母坐在頭等艙，讓孩子們坐在長途汽車上，這是潮人的終極舉措。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462119945270177796</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462119945270177796</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 20:40:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ETF如何在幕後運作，重新平衡和防止資本收益]]></title><description><![CDATA[想象一下VOO。人們（如我）購買和出售VOO ETF，在幕後
Vanguard採取步驟，定期對指數進行再平衡。這是我的
我的理解是，這種重新平衡發生在提前知道的日期。作爲所有者
作爲ETF的所有者，我們希望不要看到這些調整引發的資本收益。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qy7q2x/how_etfs_work_behind_the_scenes_rebalancing_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qy7q2x/how_etfs_work_behind_the_scenes_rebalancing_and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 18:50:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine VOO.   Folks (like me) buy and sell the VOO ETF and behind the scenes Vanguard  takes the steps to periodically rebalance the index.  It&amp;#39;s my understanding that this rebalancing happens on dates known in advance.   As owners of the ETF, we hope not to see capital gains triggered by these rebalancing events because that means taxes.   My question is, how this rebalancing happens and is there some aspect around the ETF construct which allows vanguard to (say) sell a stock at a profit (as part of the rebalancing) yet somehow not pass that capital gain back to folks holding the ETF?   Or is vanguard leveraging tax loss harvesting as a means to counter capital gains and thus not pass gains to folks holding VOO?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If vanguard is leveraging tax loss harvesting to counter gains in order to prevent capital gains from being passed on to VOO holders, can vanguard shuffle, behind the scenes, those tax losses between different ETFs or must those losses remain associated with the stocks tied to VOO?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just trying to understand the details here...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是弱智]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qy8vmy/im_retarded/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qy8vmy/im_retarded/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 18:34:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特爾作爲ASML的衍生品交易。英特爾終於趕上了摩爾定律的步伐]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩爾定律指出，芯片上的晶體管數量每兩年增加一倍
但生產成本卻下降了一半。這一概念是由戈登
摩爾創造的，他是英特爾的聯合創始人，實際上已經堅持了幾十年。

ASML公司設計和製造EUV光刻機，它是...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qy7sk6/intel_as_a_derivative_trade_on_asml_intel_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qy7sk6/intel_as_a_derivative_trade_on_asml_intel_is/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 18:34:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moore&amp;#39;s Law states the amount of transistors on a chip doubles every two years but the cost of production drops by half. This concept was created by Gordon Moore, the co-founder of Intel and has actually held up for decades.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ASML designs and manufactures EUV lithography machines, which are extremely high precision machines that put complex designs on incredibly small chips. ASML is the only EUV lithography design and manufacturer in the world. Look up their stock performance and financials if you question these claims.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intel used to be a top class chip manufacturer but they&amp;#39;ve struggled with the 7nm chips and their stock has been punished. The simple reason for Intel&amp;#39;s shortcomings is they&amp;#39;ve not been using EUV lithography machines from ASML.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plain and simple, without EUV lithography, Intel has been handicapping itself for years now and is a big reason they have fallen behind. The last link below notes how their 7nm chip design is now using EUV lithography at the 2 new fab plants they are building for $20B in Arizona. Intel is going to start to catch up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR: ASML provides the technology to keep Moore&amp;#39;s Law alive and Intel hasn&amp;#39;t been using it until now. Their depressed, low P/E stock valuation will begin to correct with outperformance as their technology begins to catch-up after major mistakes not using EUV lithography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/asml-extreme-ultraviolet-lithography-chips-moores-law/&quot;&gt;ASML Keeping Moore&amp;#39;s Law Alive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://semiwiki.com/semiconductor-services/semiconductor-advisors/302806-asml-is-the-key-to-intels-resurrection-just-like-asml-helped-tsmc-beat-intel/&quot;&gt;ASML is the Key to Intel&amp;#39;s Resurrection Just like TSMC beat Intel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.intel.com/content/www/us/en/newsroom/news/idm-manufacturing-innovation-product-leadership.html#gs.h19m75&quot;&gt;Intel 7nm Chip Design to Now Use EUV Lithography&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[沒有稅收 😎]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qy72b5/no_taxes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qy72b5/no_taxes/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 17:16:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[普通美國人購買一張音樂會門票的費用高達100至200美元，一瓶葡萄酒90美元，每加侖汽油5美元。 

https://t.co/rTciIVOEfn]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462062684103450624</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1462062684103450624</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 16:52:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在YouTube上觀看的Bogleheads]]></title><description><![CDATA[只是在尋找一些建議，看看在YouTube上跟隨和觀看誰來學習。
的建議。無論是談論boglehead方式、經濟、金融建議。
股票市場或任何類似的東西。舉個例子，我關注Rob Berger
而且他幾乎總是有內容豐富的視頻。謝謝...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxyqll/bogleheads_on_youtube_to_watch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxyqll/bogleheads_on_youtube_to_watch/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 16:52:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just looking for some suggestions on who to follow and watch on YouTube to learn from. Whether it be talking about the boglehead way, economy, financial advice, stock market or anything along those lines.  As an example, I follow Rob Berger and he almost always has informative videos.  Thanks for suggestions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[華爾街日報的新文章。4%的退休規則受到質疑。你的 "鳥巢 "能持續嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[這裏沒有什麼驚天動地或令人驚訝的事情。也許除了50%的股票和
50%的債券組合不可能支持一個典型的30年退休的4%的SWR。
未來幾年的退休生活。

這篇文章的鏈接。

https://www-wsj-com.cdn.ampproject.org/c/s/www.wsj.com/amp/articles/the-4...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxvgu9/new_wsj_article_the_4_retirement_rule_is_in_doubt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qxvgu9/new_wsj_article_the_4_retirement_rule_is_in_doubt/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 16:12:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nothing earth shattering or surprising here. Except maybe that 50% stocks and 50% bonds portolio isn&amp;#39;t likely to be able to support a 4% SWR for a typical 30 year retirement over the next few years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link to the article:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www-wsj-com.cdn.ampproject.org/c/s/www.wsj.com/amp/articles/the-4-retirement-rule-is-in-doubt-will-your-nest-egg-last-11636713035&quot;&gt;https://www-wsj-com.cdn.ampproject.org/c/s/www.wsj.com/amp/articles/the-4-retirement-rule-is-in-doubt-will-your-nest-egg-last-11636713035&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[恆大將被從恆生中國企業指數中剔除]]></title><description><![CDATA["香港，11月19日（路透社）--陷入困境的開發商中國恆大集團
(3333.HK) [https://www.reuters.com/companies/3333.HK]將從香港恆生中國企業指數(HSCE)中剔除。
香港的恆生中國企業指數（HSCE）中刪除。
[https://www.reuters.com/quote/.HSCE]，該基準供應商周五表示
在其...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxn8ji/evergrande_to_be_removed_from_hang_seng_china/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qxn8ji/evergrande_to_be_removed_from_hang_seng_china/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 15:50:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;HONG KONG, Nov 19 (Reuters) - Embattled developer China Evergrande Group &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/companies/3333.HK&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(3333.HK)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; will be removed from Hong Kong&amp;#39;s Hang Seng China Enterprises Index &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/quote/.HSCE&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(.HSCE)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the benchmark provider said on Friday following its regular quarterly review.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Hang Seng Indexes Company does not typically give reasons for changes to its indexes, and did not in Friday&amp;#39;s statement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Hang Seng China Enterprises Index is designed to reflect the performance of mainland Chinese companies listed in Hong Kong, and includes the top 50 eligible stocks by a measure of their market value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evergrande&amp;#39;s shares have fallen over 80% year to date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Separately, Hang Seng Indexes said they had added technology firms JD.com &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/companies/9618.HK&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(9618.HK)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and Netease &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/companies/9999.HK&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(9999.HK)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to the benchmark Hang Seng Index &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/quote/.HSI&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(.HSI)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hang Seng Indexes is trying to include more securities in the benchmark to make it more reflective of the companies listed in Hong Kong.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;($1 = 7.7917 Hong Kong dollars)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/evergrande-be-removed-hang-seng-china-enterprises-index-2021-11-19/?utm_source=reddit.com&amp;amp;utm_source=reddit.com&quot;&gt;https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/evergrande-be-removed-hang-seng-china-enterprises-index-2021-11-19/?utm_source=reddit.com&amp;amp;utm_source=reddit.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>