<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 23:19:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Pssst，需要一些綠色的東西嗎，先生？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsdeyo/pssst_need_some_greens_sir/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsdeyo/pssst_need_some_greens_sir/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 22:46:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲你的應急基金投資]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好! 前幾天我在聽《千禧年投資》播客的一集。
有一天。在這一集裏，主持人採訪了克里斯-卡瓦亞。克里斯提出的
爭論說，最好是投資你的應急基金，而不是將其作爲
現金。他建議將88%的資金投資於債券，另外12%的資金投資於銀行賬戶。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsha3j/investing_your_emergency_fund/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsha3j/investing_your_emergency_fund/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 22:34:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello! I was listening to an episode of The Millenial Investing podcast the other day. In this episode, the host interviews Chris Kawaja. Chris makes the argument that it is better to invest your emergency fund rather than keep it as cash. He proposes investing 88% in bonds and the other 12% in a S&amp;amp;P 500 index fund. Historically, this combination has kept up or beaten inflation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you guys think? Anyone take this approach?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[關於迪士尼股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，我在兩週前套現了，現在正坐在一大筆現金上等待合適的機會。
等待合適的機會。現在，隨着迪斯尼在過去5天內大幅下跌15美元
過去5天裏，你們認爲將所有的2萬塊錢投資到DIS上怎麼樣？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsgldu/about_disney_stocks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsgldu/about_disney_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 22:14:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I cashed out about 2 weeks ago and a sitting on a large sum of cash waiting for the right opportunity. Right now with the huge 15$ drop of Disney in the past 5 days, what do you guys think about investing all 20k into DIS?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這個牛市與其他任何牛市一樣......或者說是這樣？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我從幾年前就開始投資，所以我不知道2008年以前的投資感覺如何。
2008年以前的投資。我看到很多 "PE不再重要"，"這個週期是
不同 "之類的評論，我首先想到的是把它們當作 "不重要 "來拋棄。
我的第一個想法是把它們當作沒有經驗的想法，這些人和我一樣，不知道什麼是......。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsbs5s/this_bull_market_is_like_any_other_or_is_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsbs5s/this_bull_market_is_like_any_other_or_is_it/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 22:14:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been investing since a few years, so I have no idea of how it felt to invest pre 2008. I see a lot of &amp;#39;PE doesn&amp;#39;t matter anymore&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;this cycle is different&amp;#39; and that kind of comments, and my first thought is to discard them as inexperienced thoughts from people who, like me, don&amp;#39;t know what a serious bear market feels like. But I can&amp;#39;t pass on one thought: the information has changed. Before 2008, regular folks had access to a completely different kind of information than today. I don&amp;#39;t know how the landscape changed for institutions sinc ethen, maybe they already had access to the info we use nowadays to base our decisions, maybe they even had algo trading already, but the internet was so different that it must have made a tremendous impact for them as well. It seems a relevant discussion to be had, so I&amp;#39;m asking you: do you believe this time is different? If you don&amp;#39;t, what&amp;#39;s your counter argument?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[東芝將一分爲三]]></title><description><![CDATA[本週，企業集團正在解體，就像無人問津一樣。首先是通用電氣
現在是通用電氣的直接競爭對手東芝，其根源可以追溯到1875年。此外
此外，我們還有強生公司的分拆。我們幾乎應該期待
西門子也會採取同樣的做法
途徑。https://www.wsj.com/articles/toshiba...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsd3uu/toshiba_to_split_into_three/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qsd3uu/toshiba_to_split_into_three/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 21:53:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conglomerates are breaking up like it&amp;#39;s nobody&amp;#39;s business this week. First GE and now a direct GE-competitor, Toshiba, whose roots date back to 1875. In addition we have the Johnson and Johnson s split. We should almost expect Siemens to follow the same path.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/toshiba-like-ge-plans-to-split-into-three-parts-11636700609?mod=hp_lead_pos3&quot;&gt;https://www.wsj.com/articles/toshiba-like-ge-plans-to-split-into-three-parts-11636700609?mod=hp_lead_pos3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這只是交易員基本技能的一部分]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsc3lg/its_just_a_part_of_basic_trader_skillset/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsc3lg/its_just_a_part_of_basic_trader_skillset/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 20:23:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[什麼是最省稅的Vanguard經紀基金？]]></title><description><![CDATA[就目前而言，我的現金有點太多了。目前我的IRA
和401k。什麼是最有效的Vanguard非稅收優惠基金？我在想
我在想一個簡單的80/20的VTI/VXUS。債券現在不做任何事情，所以沒有
入這些基金也沒有用。

我有一個迫在眉睫的擔憂，傑克...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs9id6/what_are_the_most_tax_efficient_vanguard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs9id6/what_are_the_most_tax_efficient_vanguard/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 18:00:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of right now, I have a little too much in cash.  Currently maxing out my IRA and 401k.  What are the most efficient Vanguard non-tax advantaged funds? I was thinking a simple 80/20 VTI/VXUS.  Bonds aren&amp;#39;t doing anything right now, so no use getting into those.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One looming concern I have, and Jack Bogle talks about this in his book, is &amp;quot;reversion of the mean&amp;quot;.  He even said in an interview that sometimes you do have to time the market.  But that&amp;#39;s just my personal choice, and I am going to choose to wait until the reversion of the mean to invest in a non-tax advantaged account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So thoughts on taxable ETFs? Reinvest dividends? Use dividends to pay taxes?  Are VTI and VXUS good choices?  Is skipping bonds completely a bad choice?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你是如何說服自己賣掉你最後的個人股票贏家，去完成3個基金的投資組合？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我幾乎完全是一個擁有4個基金（VOO、VXUS、VGIT、TIP）的Bogelhead。但我
仍然堅持着過去的幾個贏家。amzn, aapl, msft, zen, prgfx。
你是如何證明釦動扳機的？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsdb10/how_did_you_convince_yourself_to_sell_your_last/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qsdb10/how_did_you_convince_yourself_to_sell_your_last/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 17:33:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am almost completely a Bogelhead with a 4-fund (VOO, VXUS, VGIT, TIP). But I still hang on to a couple winners from the past: AMZN, AAPL, MSFT, ZEN, PRGFX. How did you justify pulling the trigger?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[自閉症的賭注]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs96pb/autism_bets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs96pb/autism_bets/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 17:04:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[天價通脹不是因爲 "供應鏈瓶頸"，而是因爲印了太多的錢]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看到這些天有很多文章和帖子都在談論供應鏈問題。
不管是關於購買一個集裝箱有多貴，還是說
或航運港口沒有足夠的空間，或沒有足夠的
卡車司機，等等。

然而，這些都是微觀層面的症狀。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsdxg3/sky_high_inflation_isnt_due_to_supply_chain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsdxg3/sky_high_inflation_isnt_due_to_supply_chain/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 17:04:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I see a lot of articles and posts these days talking about supply chain issues: whether it&amp;#39;s about how expensive it is to buy a shipping container, or that there isn&amp;#39;t enough space at shipping ports, or that there aren&amp;#39;t enough truckers, etc. etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, these are all micro-level symptoms of a macro-level problem. Don&amp;#39;t miss the forest for the trees. Journalists need to write something new every day (or every hour it seems), even if there isn&amp;#39;t anything new to say. Which leads to a lot of noise that clouds your mind from making sense of what is really happening in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my view, the problem is clear: governments overdid it with stimulus. Unlike the 2008 Global Financial Crisis where policymakers did too little and acted too slow, this time around governments decided to err on the side of doing too much too quickly. If you look at consumer spending on FRED, it didn&amp;#39;t just fully recovery from the 2020 shock, it&amp;#39;s arguably on a stronger trajectory than it otherwise would be without the pandemic! At the same time, unemployment is still high and labor force participation is dreadfully low! The Fed created such a tremendous wealth effect, people are earning multiple years worth of stock market returns in the span of months. I&amp;#39;m not surprised many people are taking career breaks or retiring early. So why do we have red hot inflation? Because we&amp;#39;re printing more money and making less things, it&amp;#39;s that simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The inflation problem highlights how difficult it is to be a policymaker. On one hand, you don&amp;#39;t want to under spend and risk seeing long-term economic scarring, but if you stimulate too much, you risk fueling inflation as well as asset price bubbles. The other factor at play is the politicization of economic policy. You&amp;#39;re everyone&amp;#39;s favorite politician when you&amp;#39;re fueling spending, but it&amp;#39;s hard to get reelected when you advocate for cutbacks. Prudent policymaking requires spending when times are bad, and building reserves when times are good - politicians have forgot about the latter half of that equation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在目前的價格下，你會在V、MA和PYPL之間選擇哪個？]]></title><description><![CDATA[支付寶的PE爲48.6

萬事達卡爲43.6

Visa爲37.4

雖然單純從PE的角度來看，Paypal是最昂貴的，但我更傾向於他們，因爲他們在過去的歷史中一直是最受歡迎的。
我更傾向於他們，因爲他們在歷史上有更高的收入增長。
與其他兩家相比，他們有更高的收入增長，而且他們是多元化的，或正試圖多元化的
到諸如...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs4tiv/at_current_prices_which_would_you_choose_between/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs4tiv/at_current_prices_which_would_you_choose_between/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:59:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paypal at PE of 48.6&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mastercard at 43.6&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Visa at 37.4&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Paypal is the most expensive purely from PE point of view, I&amp;#39;m leaning more towards them because they&amp;#39;ve historically had higher revenue growth compared to the other two and they&amp;#39;re diversified or are trying to diversity into things like crypto, stock broker, etc. Also Paypal is around 33% off from its 52 week high, which is far lower than V or MA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you had to pick one out of these 3? Which would you buy at today&amp;#39;s prices?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[收入（TTM）...
裏維安：0美元
通用汽車：1310億美元
福特：1350億美元

淨收入（TTM）...
裏維安：-16億美元
通用汽車：111億美元
福特：29億美元

市值...
裏維安：1050億美元
通用汽車：900億美元
福特：780億美元

$RIVN $GM $F

數據來自@ycharts https://t.co/xlR1mX989K]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459153703320043523</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1459153703320043523</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:47:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[賣出Vanguard ETFs(VTI)並轉移到Vanguard共同基金(VTSAX)]]></title><description><![CDATA[我開了一個非稅收優惠的Vanguard賬戶，與我的退休賬戶分開。
賬戶。我的Vanguard賬戶只是用於個人投資。

我不想爲我的3個基金投資組合分配足夠的資金以滿足3千美元的最低限額，以購買海軍司令部的股份。
3個基金組合。

隨着時間的推移或更多的錢變得可用，我是否應該被...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs99dt/sell_vanguard_etfs_vti_and_move_to_vanguard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs99dt/sell_vanguard_etfs_vti_and_move_to_vanguard/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:47:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I opened a non tax advantaged Vanguard account separate from my retirement accounts. My Vanguard account is just for personal investing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t want to allot enough to meet the $3k minimums for admiral shares for my 3 fund portfolio. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As time goes on or more money becomes available should I being selling the ETFs and use the proceeds to move my 3 fund portfolio to Vanguard mutual funds instead of ETFs?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有道理。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsbj9q/makes_sense/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qsbj9q/makes_sense/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你的妻子，你妻子的男友，你的股票爆炸後的你]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs599y/your_wife_your_wifes_bf_you_after_your_stocks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs599y/your_wife_your_wifes_bf_you_after_your_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你希望在你開始投資之前有人告訴你什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一個初級投資者，目前正在學習所有的基礎知識，並盡力教育自己。
我想知道：你們認爲有哪些重要的概念/方法/工具導致了你的成功？
導致你們成功的一些重要概念/方法/工具？最重要的是。
什麼導致了你最大的失敗，你是如何恢復的？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsavil/what_do_you_wish_someone_told_you_before_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qsavil/what_do_you_wish_someone_told_you_before_you/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 14:47:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m a beginner investor learning all the basics currently and educating myself as best as I can to be successful and was wondering: what do you guys think are some vital concepts/methods/tools that led to your successes? Most importantly, what led to your biggest failures and how did you recover? Failure is truly a teacher and I want to hear about yours! I figure that I could go into the market and fail again myself (down 46% already lmao), or I could utilize the failures from the three million investors on here!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[強生公司計劃分拆爲兩家公司，分離消費者健康業務]]></title><description><![CDATA[強生公司的股價在盤前交易中跳漲，此前該公司的醫療保健巨頭宣佈
在醫療保健巨頭宣佈將自己拆分爲兩家上市公司後，強生公司的股價在盤前交易中跳升。

新公司將包括一個專注於消費產品的公司，如
Band-Aid繃帶和嬰兒爽身粉，另一家則專注於...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs9ko5/johnson_johnson_plans_to_split_into_two_companies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs9ko5/johnson_johnson_plans_to_split_into_two_companies/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 14:35:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares of Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson jumped in premarket trading after the healthcare giant announced that it is splitting itself into two publicly traded companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new companies will consist of one focused on consumer products, such as Band-Aid bandages and baby powder, and another focused on prescription drugs and medical devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson was already undergoing a major transition, as CEO Alex Gorsky has previously announced that he will step down in January. Joaquin Duato, who was tapped as Gorsky’s successor, will lead the new J&amp;amp;J following the spinoff, the company said Friday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the company said it planned to keep its total dividend “at least at the same level” following the change. J&amp;amp;J currently sports a divided yield of about 2.6%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson plans to split into two companies, separating consumer health business &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/jj-shares-jump-after-ceo-says-health-giant-plans-to-break-up-in-wsj-report.html?__source=iosappshare%7Ccom.apple.UIKit.activity.CopyToPasteboard&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/jj-shares-jump-after-ceo-says-health-giant-plans-to-break-up-in-wsj-report.html?__source=iosappshare%7Ccom.apple.UIKit.activity.CopyToPasteboard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[仍然不明白期權/期貨以及它們是如何運作的，或者它們的意義何在？]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以我看了關於期權和期貨的視頻，我知道它們都是
不同，但保持着類似的原則，就像你得到了在未來買入/賣出某物的權利。
但從根本上講，這對我來說沒有任何意義。
我不明白。

比如你爲什麼不直接購買或持有某樣東西？什麼...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs3vvg/still_dont_get_optionsfutures_and_how_they_work/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs3vvg/still_dont_get_optionsfutures_and_how_they_work/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 14:35:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;#39;ve watched the videos on options and futures and I get that they&amp;#39;re both different but maintain a similar principle that like you get the right to buy/sell something in the future but fundamentally it doesn&amp;#39;t make any sense to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like why wouldn&amp;#39;t you just buy or hold something? What advantage do options or futures give you over just traditional investing? I get things like margin or leverage as in riskily buying more than you can afford but I just don&amp;#39;t get what the point or how options or futures work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, options sounds like ok I&amp;#39;ll buy the right to buy a stock at this price, if it goes down I just won&amp;#39;t fulfill the obligation because I don&amp;#39;t have to and if it goes up then sure I&amp;#39;ll fulfill the contract. Again, that&amp;#39;s definitely not right because that would just be an infinite money glitch because you would always never take the option if it&amp;#39;s going down and always take it if it goes up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Futures makes a little more sense because you have to oblige the contract. But then why wouldn&amp;#39;t you just buy something normally? What&amp;#39;s the benefit of buying at a set time?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL:DR, genuinely have no idea how options/futures work and what their point is, and I probably sound really dumb but if someone can explain in a way that makes sense I would really appreciate that, thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Paysafe - 是買入還是轉出？]]></title><description><![CDATA[Paysafe（PSFE）的股票今天下跌了40%，因爲第三季度的收益報告令人沮喪。
該公司收入比2020年第三季度下降了1%。

到目前爲止，分析師對Paysafe的評價相當高，特別是隨着在線賭博市場的增長，以及該公司收購了幾個較小規模的公司。
特別是隨着在線賭博市場的增長，以及它收購了幾個較小的
歐洲金融科技...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qru6rq/paysafe_buy_the_dip_or_gtfo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qru6rq/paysafe_buy_the_dip_or_gtfo/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 14:20:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paysafe (PSFE) stock dropped 40% today following a soberiing Q3 earnings report where company revenue dropped 1% from Q3 2020. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Up until now, analysts had been quite high on Paysafe, particularly as the market for online gambling has grown, and as it acquired several smaller European fintech companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have about 2% of my portfolio in Paysafe, and until today was already at a -12% ROI, but that&amp;#39;s in part bexause I was already buying it&amp;#39;s not 10 month dip. The plan was to hold for no fewer than five years. Is it time to double down and take advantage of the freefall, or cut losses and bail?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[強生公司計劃分拆爲兩個獨立的公司!]]></title><description><![CDATA[將把它的消費者部門與它的製藥和醫療設備部門分開。
器械部門。大家對這個新方向有什麼看法？強生公司
強生公司是世界上銷售額最大的健康產品公司，但認爲
這兩個部門的方向和增長正在迅速分化....。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs9jsv/johnson_and_johnson_planning_on_splitting_into/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs9jsv/johnson_and_johnson_planning_on_splitting_into/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 13:56:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will be separating it&amp;#39;s consumer division from it&amp;#39;s pharmaceutical and medical device division. What&amp;#39;s everyone&amp;#39;s take on this new direction?   Johnson and Johnson is the world&amp;#39;s largest health products companies by sales but believes that the two divisions directions and growth are diverging rapidly. 
     Is this the right direction for them to take?   No decision yet one what they will do when it comes to holding a stock offering.&lt;br/&gt;
     I&amp;#39;ve always felt J n J was a safe long term hold how does this change that now?  More growth potential with the pharmaceutical division but comes with more risk too.  As the WSJ article states the consumer division comes with its own  issues,  as it&amp;#39;s  &amp;quot;Sales are growing more slowly than at the other businesses, and have lower margins too. &amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這有意義嗎？EV討論 ($RIVN) ($LCID) ($TSLA) ($F)]]></title><description><![CDATA[電動汽車初創公司Rivian（RIVN）已經在公開市場上大放異彩，公開募股，市值達1160億美元。
殺手級的公開募股，市值達到1160億美元。這比
通用汽車（GM）的價值，比福特（F）多出47%。裏維安在今年之前從未出售過
輛，直到今年。通用汽車銷售了約700萬輛汽車...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrz8ji/does_this_make_sense_ev_discussion_rivn_lcid_tsla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrz8ji/does_this_make_sense_ev_discussion_rivn_lcid_tsla/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 13:31:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Electric-vehicle startup Rivian (RIVN) has roared into public markets with a killer public offering and a market value of $116 billion. That’s 32% more than General Motors (GM) is worth, and 47% more than Ford (F). Rivian has never sold a vehicle until this year. GM sells around 7 million vehicles per year; Ford, 4 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you add up the market value of Tesla (TSLA), Rivian, and 5 other startups including Lucid (LCID), Nikola (NKLA), Fisker (FSR), Lordstown Motors (RIDE) and Workhorse (WKHS), their combined capitalization is nearly $1.3 trillion. Nine of the world’s biggest automakers—GM, Ford, Stellantis, Toyota, Nissan, Honda, Volkswagen, BMW and Daimler-Benz—are only worth $845 billion. So those 9 giant automakers are worth 34% less than 7 fledgling EV manufacturers. As for sales, the established manufacturers outsell the EV upstarts 100 to 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The market now seems to view &lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rivian-ceo-sees-annual-production-144553789.html&quot;&gt;Rivian&lt;/a&gt; as a Tesla-in-the-making, especially since it already has backing from Amazon and Ford. By focusing on sport pickups and delivery vans, Rivian has one foot in consumer vehicles and the other in commercial applications, a shrewd mix that lets the company spread its bets on a trend that is already a revolution in ground transportation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Growth.&lt;/strong&gt; In market terms, investors consider &lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-is-not-enough-engine-no-1-bets-on-gm-white-paper-details-electric-vehicle-landscape-124811083.html&quot;&gt;EV newcomers&lt;/a&gt; such as Tesla and Rivian to be growth and technology companies with tons of upside potential. Traditional automakers are industrial concerns capable of incremental growth, at best. While virtually every big automaker is developing EV technology, the old ones won’t attain nearly the same rapid growth as the new ones will. That’s because they have massive investments in internal-combustion engines, or ICE—a.k.a. gas-and diesel-powered cars—that will decline as the new EV technology ramps up. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GM, for instance, sold 202,000 EVs in 2020, which was third most of any automaker, behind Tesla and Volkswagen. But for GM the technology of the future represented just 3% of all sales. The other 97% were legacy ICE vehicles likely to decline as a share of the overall market for years to come. At Tesla, 100% of sales were EVs, with no legacy business to manage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new technology is where the growth is. Tesla’s revenue growth rate during the last two years has been 39%, according to S&amp;amp;P Capital IQ. GM’s has been a negative 5%. Pandemic disruptions have been a factor in both company’s performance, but the trend was the same before the pandemic. GM still makes a lot of money selling high-margin pickups and SUVs, but investors view that as a business that could someday dwindle to no profit at all. Electrics, by contrast, will only get more profitable as costs drop, technology advances and more people buy them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capital.&lt;/strong&gt; Traditional carmakers such as GM and Ford argue that the profitability of existing lineups gives them an advantage because they have in-house funding for new EV technology. But startups haven’t needed in-house funding because capital markets have been a ready source of money. “Capital for EV [manufacturers] is widely available and cheap in current market conditions, so we believe momentum/support for many of the stocks will persist,” analyst John Murphy of Bank of America wrote in a recent research note. “As has proven the case for Tesla over the past decade, the higher the upward spiral of stock, the cheaper capital becomes to fund growth.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/its-bizarro-world-in-the-auto-industry-again-203740250.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/its-bizarro-world-in-the-auto-industry-again-203740250.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[槓桿投資 [Ben Felix談槓桿ETF]]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrs6wk/investing_with_leverage_ben_felix_on_leveraged/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrs6wk/investing_with_leverage_ben_felix_on_leveraged/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 12:38:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[無論怎樣，我都會達到目的的！"。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs6dd0/one_way_or_another_im_getting_there/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs6dd0/one_way_or_another_im_getting_there/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 12:38:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特股票和裏維安股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，我完全糊塗了，需要幫助理解。我不可能
我不可能理解，福特汽車公司已經存在了這麼久，並且有一個既定的商業模式。
既定的商業模式，在未來幾年將逐步改變爲電動汽車。
在接下來的幾年裏，福特汽車公司將逐步向電動汽車轉變。自從Rivian進入市場以來，所有...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs3uds/ford_stock_and_rivian_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs3uds/ford_stock_and_rivian_stock/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 11:34:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok, I’m completely confused and need help understanding. I can’t possibly understand how Ford motor company has been around for so long and has an established business model that is progressively going to change here in the next couple of years to electric vehicles. Since Rivian hit the market all kinds of questions have come to mind especially the market cap of these companies and how they’re surpassing other companies that have been around for decades. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can someone explain to me how Ford stock is $19.00 a share at $100B market value and the most sold truck in America…Yet, Rivian sold 156 trucks to date and the stock is $124.00 ish and $120B market. This makes so sense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析師們似乎只是在股票上漲時編造目標價格]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-nvda-stock-price-target-boosts-earnings-51636640350?siteid=yhoof2

"Nvidia股票在盈利前獲得了49%的目標價格提升。爲什麼分析師們會
看漲。
以奧本海默公司的Rick Schafer爲首的分析師重申了他們對Nvidia股票的 "跑贏大盤 "評級，並將其目標價提高了49%。
的評級，並提高了對Nvidia股票...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs5xcq/analysts_seem_to_just_make_up_price_targets_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qs5xcq/analysts_seem_to_just_make_up_price_targets_as/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 11:22:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-nvda-stock-price-target-boosts-earnings-51636640350?siteid=yhoof2&quot;&gt;https://www.barrons.com/articles/nvidia-nvda-stock-price-target-boosts-earnings-51636640350?siteid=yhoof2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Nvidia Stock Gets a 49% Price Target Boost Before Earnings. Why Analysts Are Bullish.&lt;br/&gt;
 Analysts led by Rick Schafer at Oppenheimer reiterated their Outperform rating on Nvidia stock and raised their target price on the shares by 49% to $350 from $235.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Meanwhile, Christopher Rolland at Susquehanna reiterated his Positive rating on Nvidia stock and hiked his target price to $360 from $250. &amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it just me or do these guys just raise their prise targets as the stock soars so their performance on websites like tipranks doesn&amp;#39;t suffer? Nothing about nvidia&amp;#39;s performance has changed this quarter that would suddenly warrant an increase of nvidia&amp;#39;s market cap by 300 billion dollars. I think price targets are an important tool, especially for retail investors, but lately these guys seem to just make it up as they go. At $350b nvidia is a 900b company on 10b of forward net earnings. That&amp;#39;s just bonkers and these guys seem to base their price targets on how far they think the current bull market can inflate the ever increasing sentiment instead of what the stock is fundamentally worth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1月1日要做的事情]]></title><description><![CDATA[我所在的州對捐給529賬戶的錢有稅收減免，所以我打算
在1月1日（之後的第一個交易日）將其全部投資。有什麼事情是我
應該在今年年初做什麼？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrxckw/things_to_do_on_january_1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrxckw/things_to_do_on_january_1/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 07:56:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My state has tax deductions on money contributed to a 529 account so I plan to invest it all on (the first trading day after) January 1. Are there any things I should be doing at the start of the year?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希爾不支付股息的實際邏輯原因是什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，"巴菲特比你更擅長投資 "的老藉口根本沒有
有意義（了）。

 1. 巴菲特把他的現金囤積在儲蓄裏，甚至沒有投資它
 2. 公司已經達到了規模經濟，很難再有增長，所以
    實事求是地說，即使你沒有更好的發展...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs1a74/what_is_an_actual_logical_reason_that_berkshire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs1a74/what_is_an_actual_logical_reason_that_berkshire/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 07:43:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So the old excuse &amp;quot;Buffett is better at investing it than you&amp;quot; simply doesn&amp;#39;t make sense (anymore)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Buffett is stockpiling his cash in savings and not even investing it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The company has reached economies of scale and has a hard time growing so realistically, even if you aren&amp;#39;t better off investing it, it makes more sense for the cash to be distributed to shareholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It really makes no sense. Can someone explain it to me?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[需要一個好的經紀賬戶，儘快]]></title><description><![CDATA[今天想通過Vanguard設立我的Roth IRA賬戶，但由於某些原因
網站不允許我進行設置--不管怎樣。決定打電話給
Vanguard，在等待了30分鐘後，我終於和一位同事通了電話。
同事。結果發現他們的網站已經有兩個問題了。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs2q71/need_a_good_brokerage_account_asap/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qs2q71/need_a_good_brokerage_account_asap/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 07:30:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tried to set up my Roth IRA account today through Vanguard but for some reason the site wasn&amp;#39;t letting me go through with the setup- whatever. Decided to call Vanguard, and after 30 minutes of waiting I was finally on the phone with an associate. Turns out they&amp;#39;ve been having site issues for 2 months now- how convenient. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The associate created an account for me which I greatly appreciated, and he gave me some paperwork to fill out about taxes, place of work, etc. I was pretty frustrated after my call, so I decided that I&amp;#39;d work on this paperwork later, so I logged out of the site. Tried to log back on just now and it turns out that I can&amp;#39;t even log back, and now I have to recall about getting back in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After the nightmare that was setting up an account in the first place&lt;/strong&gt;, I really don&amp;#39;t want to go through this process again. Is it worth it just to set up an account with Fidelity instead? Even Robinhood seems better than this. What should I do?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿斯瓦特-達莫多蘭的特斯拉估值]]></title><description><![CDATA[無論你對特斯拉有什麼看法，都要尊重我認識的一位最好的金融學老師，他在計算股票風險方面的工作。
他在計算股票風險溢價方面的工作。相當
有趣的閱讀。我對特斯拉沒有硬性的意見，除了我喜歡他們的
他們的汽車，但這是一個更有智慧的誠實和...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs0jf3/aswath_damodorans_tesla_valuation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qs0jf3/aswath_damodorans_tesla_valuation/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 06:32:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever your thoughts on Tesla, gotta respect one of the best teacher&amp;#39;s of finance who I know for his work in calculating the equity risk premium. Pretty interesting read.  I have no hard opinions on Tesla beyond the fact that I like their cars,  but this is one of the more intellectually honest and humble attempts at intrinsically valuing the company. &lt;a href=&quot;https://aswathdamodaran.blogspot.com/2021/11/teslas-trillion-dollar-moment-valuation.html&quot;&gt;https://aswathdamodaran.blogspot.com/2021/11/teslas-trillion-dollar-moment-valuation.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[JPow發現通貨膨脹的鏡頭。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrpp8b/footage_of_jpow_finding_out_about_inflation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrpp8b/footage_of_jpow_finding_out_about_inflation/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 06:32:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這是你的孩子，Bundog。我又回來了，又是一個YOLO。(祝願)]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qruurh/its_ya_boy_bundog_im_back_with_another_yolo_wish/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qruurh/its_ya_boy_bundog_im_back_with_another_yolo_wish/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 06:03:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Q3 2021]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs2sii/q3_2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qs2sii/q3_2021/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 06:03:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NFT市場的興起主要是因爲人們對尚不存在的規範的房產交易有需求。]]></title><description><![CDATA[NFTs並不是新的或創新的。我們將唯一的ID附加到物品上已經有幾千年的歷史了。
幾千年來，我們一直在爲物品附加獨特的ID。我認爲人們很快就會發現，不是所有的東西都需要
需要在區塊鏈上，而且NFT市場將更適合於
在中心化的服務器上，而不是以太坊。當你擁有一個NFT時，你不...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qru4zs/the_rise_of_nft_marketplaces_is_mostly_because/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qru4zs/the_rise_of_nft_marketplaces_is_mostly_because/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 05:49:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NFTs aren&amp;#39;t new or innovative. We&amp;#39;ve been attaching unique IDs to items for thousands of years. I think people will soon figure out that not everything needs to be on the blockchain and that NFT marketplaces would be better suited on a centralized server, not Ethereum.   When you own an NFT, you don&amp;#39;t own the legal rights to the JPEG, nor do you even own a JPEG. You are really just buying a shitcoin that has a link to a JPEG URL. In ten years time all their NFTs will be deleted 404 pages and all you will have is a worthless shitcoin. There&amp;#39;s also a lot of problems with NFTs regarding intellectual property theft, as people can auction off property they have no legal right to sell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is merit to a marketplace of property though. There isn&amp;#39;t a regulated exchange for collectables in America. We have the NYSE for stocks, CME for commodities, but we don&amp;#39;t have one to trade collectable/non fungible items. Because such a thing doesn&amp;#39;t exist, blockchain based marketplaces are filling the void for that niche in the meantime. I think the preferred medium is a regulated exchange where real people are KYC&amp;#39;d and vetted before pushing an auction to sale. The obvious advantage of it is that governments will recognize property rights of the sales. You can still settle all of the transactions digitally, but it will take place on centralized servers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是今天（2021年11月11日，星期四）的市場回顧。請欣賞!]]></title><description><![CDATA[心理市場回顧 - 2021年11月11日，星期四

週四市場收盤時漲跌互現，因爲市場參與者繼續
市場參與者繼續努力應對最新通脹報告和第三季度盈利的影響。
盈利，隨着時間的推移，盈利有放緩的跡象。標準普爾500指數
(SPY)和納斯達克...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrvj62/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_thursday_nov_11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrvj62/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_thursday_nov_11/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 05:00:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Thursday, November 11, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The market finished mixed on Thursday, as market participants continue to grapple with the implication of the latest inflation report and third-quarter earnings, which are showing signs of slowing down as it winds down. The S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) and Nasdaq (QQQ) rose after two consecutive down days, as tech stocks made a comeback, closing 0.04% and 0.28% higher, led by a rebound in technology stocks, while the Dow Jones (DIA) closed 0.44% lower. The Russell 2000 (IWM), which tracks the performance of small-caps, rose 0.8% higher. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a slow news days due to it being Veteran’s Day holiday in the US, market participants continue to digest the Consumer Price Index released tomorrow, which showed prices of consumer good surging 6.2%.  in a year-on-year period, accelerating from September’s 5.4% YoY rate, and higher than the 5.9% expected. This represents that fastest pace of inflationary expansion since 1990, though one has to take into account easy comparisons to last year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The staying power and magnitude of inflationary pressures has, perhaps, become the central question for market participants, with companies across the board reporting rising input costs and price hikes passed on to the consumers to preserve margins. While Q3 earning results have robustly demonstrated that companies in the SPY were largely able to navigate these cost pressures, the possibility remains that if inflation runs hotter than expected for longer than expected, it could begin to hamper consumer demand. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matthew Luzzetti, Chief US Economist at Deutsche Bank, said “This [the CPI report] is certainly telling us, I think, that price pressures are more persistent. They are broader. They are not just narrowly focused on those categories, whether it&amp;#39;s autos and the supply-constrained items. And it&amp;#39;s going to last longer than expected. We do think that the Fed is going to have to raise rates next year. They&amp;#39;ve signaled that they&amp;#39;re going to taper through the middle of the year, and that&amp;#39;s our baseline at this point. But if you continue to see price pressures like this over the coming months and more persistent, it may cause them to have to act earlier than expected.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With roughly 89% of companies in the S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) having already reported earnings, 81% of those have so far posted better than expected earnings per share and 75% of those reported better than expected revenue. FactSet projects that the year-on-year earnings growth rate for the index stands at 40%, though this number has continued creeping higher as earnings season unfolds. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_110521.pdf&quot;&gt;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_110521.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disney (DIS) stock slipped to an 11-month low following disappointing earnings. For the first time ever, Netflix (NFLX) has overtaken Disney’s market cap.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After its blockbuster debut to the market yesterday, shares of EV maker Rivian (RIVN) remained on fire, pushing the company well past a $100b market cap in only two days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elon Musk, CEO of Tesla (TSLA) is carrying thru with his promise to sell Tesla stock and sold about $5 billion worth of stock today&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toyota says large parts of the world are not ready for EVs and committed $240 million to building a hybrid car parts plant in West Virginia. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General Mills Inc is considering the sale of its soup brand Progresso and ready-to-eat meals label Helper for $3 billion, according to a report by Bloomberg&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chinese social media giant Tencent Holdings expects Beijing to allow &amp;#39;metaverse&amp;#39; virtual environment services, now the talk of Silicon Valley, to operate in China - provided they fall in line with Chinese rules. &amp;quot;There&amp;#39;s a lot of technologies that&amp;#39;s related to the development of games as well as for the metaverse,&amp;quot; Tencent president Martin Lau told analysts on a call peppered with questions about the metaverse.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google lost an appeal against a 2.42-billion-euro ($2.8-billion) European antitrust decision on Wednesday&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unity Software (U) buy special effects company Weta Digital for $1.3 billion. The studio, founded by Peter Jackson, was responsible for special effects in Avatar and the Lord of the Rings trilogy. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be.&amp;quot; -&lt;em&gt;Ralph Waldo Emerson&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[低增長時期的紅利]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，Bogles，這只是我腦子裏的一些想法，我想
聰明的人都有圖來對付它。

很多人都在談論低增長時期，比如2000年的科技泡沫後，或者70年代的滯脹。
70年代的滯脹。這經常被說成是一個 "市場仍然...... "的時期。
市場仍然...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrmkqg/dividends_during_periods_of_low_growth/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrmkqg/dividends_during_periods_of_low_growth/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 04:16:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey Bogles, this is just something rattling around in my head and I figure smarter people have graphs to put up against it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of people talk about low growth periods like post tech bubble 2000’s, or stagflation during the 70’s. This is often talked about as a period where “the market remains flat.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But during those periods, aren’t companies (and index funds) still paying dividends? Seems to me that you’ll have growth on the way back up as an existing asset holder. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hence why it’s important to stay the course. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully the question makes sense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[中央銀行實際利率（利率減去通貨膨脹）...
阿根廷: -14.1%
美國：-6.1
波蘭：-5.6
歐元區：-4.6
加拿大: -4.2%
祕魯：-3.8
丹麥: -3.6%
挪威: -3.3%
智利：-3.3
捷克共和國: -3.1%
英國：-3.0
巴西：-2.9
澳大利亞：-2.9
菲律賓：-2.9%。-2.6%
瑞典：-2.5
瑞士：-2.0]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458951280450285576</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458951280450285576</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 02:08:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Paysafe ($PSFE)今天下跌42%，下跌機會？]]></title><description><![CDATA[錯過了一點收益，今年的指引也被降低。

跌落是合理的嗎？大多數人都會同意：當然不是

這只是目前市場的運作方式。錯過收益，你就會被
被殺。

我相信，這些因錯過收益而損失一半估值的公司
盈利而損失一半估值的公司是嚴重的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrr105/paysafe_psfe_down_42_today_dip_opportunity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrr105/paysafe_psfe_down_42_today_dip_opportunity/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 02:08:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Missed earnings by a bit and guidance of the year was reduced. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is the dip justify? Most will agree: heck no&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s just how the current market is operating. Miss earnings and you’ll get killed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe these companies that are losing half their valuation from missed earnings are severely undervalued and will rebound in due time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe $PSFE will rebound much easier than most other beaten down stock because it was previously a spac traded publicly at $10. Institutional buyers got in at this price and now we’re 60% down from there. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s trading at a low $4 penny stock range which could be appealing to retail investors. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am starting to load up massively. Possibly make a in-depth DD post if its worth while. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is everyone thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit : in for 75k shares at 4.22 // planning to make extensive DD over the weekend&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我應該退出嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[一年前，我開始 "投資"。在GME的狂熱之後，我開始交易期權
以獲得更多的槓桿作用。我一度上漲了15%，但現在經過無數次的損失後
我的總賬戶爲-86%。

這讓我非常不爽，我覺得我在股市上的財務狀況很失敗。A
年的壓力...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrx48u/should_i_quit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrx48u/should_i_quit/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 02:08:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;One year ago I began &amp;quot;investing&amp;quot;. After the GME frenzy I started trading options to gain more leverage. At one point I was up 15%, but now after countless losses I have a total account at -86%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This upsets me greatly and I feel I&amp;#39;ve financially failed at the stock market. A year of stressing over positions just to lose over 11K. And this isn&amp;#39;t fun money either, it&amp;#39;s all I have to my name. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My current strategies consists of calls and puts with 1-2 month expiration. Sometimes risky earnings plays. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should I try and keep trading and build my account back up? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR After one year of trading I&amp;#39;ve lost 11K (86%), where do I go from here?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[聲稱瑞特豪斯是無辜的並不是勇敢的表現。他當然是無辜的。如果你認爲他不是，那你就是渣滓。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458933743637475333</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458933743637475333</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 01:14:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[哎呀。我昨天在距離收盤約3分鐘時買入了迪斯尼看跌期權，它們賺了錢。對不起。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrn46w/oops_i_bought_disney_puts_at_about_3_min_to_close/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrn46w/oops_i_bought_disney_puts_at_about_3_min_to_close/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 01:14:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Paysafe公司釋放出的收入]]></title><description><![CDATA[今天Paysafe宣佈了收益。不幸的是，他們並沒有那麼
好。股票下跌了40%。我在Paysafe的投資現在下降了70%。對於你們中那些
持有Paysafe的人，你們打算怎麼做？買入更多，賣出還是持有？我不知道該怎麼辦
做什麼]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qroguj/paysafe_releasing_earning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qroguj/paysafe_releasing_earning/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 01:14:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well today Paysafe announced earnings. Unfortunately they haven’t been that good. Stock down 40%. My investment in Paysafe is down 70% now. For those of you holding Paysafe, what are you gonna do? Buy more, sell or hold? Don’t know what to do&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這個子對在這個市場上買房有什麼看法？]]></title><description><![CDATA[隨着3個基金投資組合的最大化，住房市場對你們意味着什麼？

"在你需要的時候購買"，不管價格如何？(顯然，如果你能負擔得起的話)

謝謝大家的回答!]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrsyt5/what_does_this_sub_think_about_home_buying_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrsyt5/what_does_this_sub_think_about_home_buying_in/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 01:14:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the maxed out 3 fund portfolios, what’s housing market mean to you guys?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Buy when you need” regardless of price? (Obviously if you can afford it)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you all for the responses!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-馬斯克做到了。他以3,880,768,307.13美元出售了3,588,047股。]]></title><description><![CDATA[來自FINTEL。

內幕人士Musk Elon報告說，他賣出了242,006股$TSLA/Tesla Motors, Inc.
總成本爲258,484,236.01美元。

內幕人士Musk Elon報告說，賣出了58,101股$TSLA/Tesla Motors, Inc.
總成本爲59,206,941.35美元

內幕人士Musk Elon報告說，出售199,893股$TSLA...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrcua2/elon_musk_did_it_he_sold_3588047_shares_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qrcua2/elon_musk_did_it_he_sold_3588047_shares_for/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 23:46:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FROM FINTEL:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insider Musk Elon reports selling 242,006 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc. at a total cost of $258,484,236.01&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insider Musk Elon reports selling 58,101 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc. at a total cost of $59,206,941.35&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;insider Musk Elon reports selling 199,893 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc. at a total cost of $209,580,233.67&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insider Musk Elon reports selling 411,476 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc. at a total cost of $478,474,857.65&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insider Musk Elon reports selling 613,316 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc. at a total cost of $669,801,010.71&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insider Musk Elon reports selling 528,687 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc. at a total cost of $601,885,328.77&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insider Musk Elon reports selling 952,211 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc. at a total cost of $1,004,977,896.06&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insider Musk Elon reports selling 582,357 shares of $TSLA / Tesla Motors, Inc. at a total cost of $598,357,802.91&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One source said it was for taxes........&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s see where this lands...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[九位美國州長向美國立法者施壓，要求通過520億的半導體資助法案。臺灣不可靠可能有數萬億的風險。]]></title><description><![CDATA[> https://www.governor.pa.gov/newsroom/governor-wolf-bipartisan-governors-urge-congress-to-pass-chips-act-to-create-american-jobs-boost-semiconductor-production/

到目前爲止，短缺已經造成220萬輛汽車的損失。這可能只是一個很小的
如果臺灣未來有更嚴重的問題，如]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrvyuc/nine_us_governors_press_us_lawmakers_to_pass_52/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrvyuc/nine_us_governors_press_us_lawmakers_to_pass_52/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 23:15:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.governor.pa.gov/newsroom/governor-wolf-bipartisan-governors-urge-congress-to-pass-chips-act-to-create-american-jobs-boost-semiconductor-production/&quot;&gt;https://www.governor.pa.gov/newsroom/governor-wolf-bipartisan-governors-urge-congress-to-pass-chips-act-to-create-american-jobs-boost-semiconductor-production/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far the shortage has cost 2.2 Million vehicles. That could just be a tiny fraction if Taiwan has more serious future issues such as natural disasters or China invasion, which could cost businesses TRILLIONS in damages to companies such as:  Ford (F) , General Motors (GM) , and Toyota (TM), Dell Technologies (DELL),  Apples (AAPL), Google (GOOGL), AMD, NVDA, and many more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The group, which also includes the governors of auto-producing states like Alabama, said the shortage had cost automakers 2.2 million vehicles and affected 575,000 jobs in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The semiconductor funding passed the U.S. Senate earlier this year by 68-32 as part of the broader U.S. Innovation and Competition Act, or USICA. But it has not passed the House of Representatives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/world/us/nine-governors-press-us-lawmakers-pass-semiconductor-funding-bill-2021-11-10/&quot;&gt;https://www.reuters.com/world/us/nine-governors-press-us-lawmakers-pass-semiconductor-funding-bill-2021-11-10/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你爲大/中/小盤股分配了多少資金？]]></title><description><![CDATA[通常情況下，我只是 "VT和Chill"，但我的401K中的基金選擇有限。
我的計劃是這樣的，但我擔心小盤股的配置
看一下目標日期基金作爲參考，有點太高了。

70%的FID 500指數(FXAIX)

20%的FID中型股指數(FSMDX)

10%的FID小型股IDX...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrox4q/how_much_do_you_allocate_for_largemidsmall_caps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qrox4q/how_much_do_you_allocate_for_largemidsmall_caps/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 22:24:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Normally I’d just &lt;em&gt;“VT and Chill”&lt;/em&gt; but I have a limited fund selection in my 401K. The plan then would be something like this, but I worry the Smallcap allocation is a bit too high looking at target date funds for reference:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;70% FID 500 Index (FXAIX)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;20% FID MID CAP IDX (FSMDX)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;10% FID SM CAP IDX (FSSNX)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently I’m just doing a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TRowePrice Target Date Fund&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (TRPLX — it’s the only TDF available to me in the 401K), but the Expense Ratio on that is nearly half a percent (0.46) so I’m weighing just switching it over to the Fidelity SP500 + Fidelity Mid / Fidelity Small cap (significantly lower expense ratios).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly there aren’t any good options for International or Bond Funds in my 401K (options are all actively managed with laughable expense ratios) so I’d have to get those in my Taxable/Roth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I’ve done is look at Target Date Funds and it looks like Schwab for example allocates about 20% to mid cap and about 6% to Small cap. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我分析了$SOFI，所以你不必分析。]]></title><description><![CDATA[SOFI Technologies, Inc.是一家在線個人金融公司。他們提供一個
一系列的貸款和財富管理服務。在發這篇文章時，他們
交易價格約爲23.65美元。他們在11月10日發佈了第三季度的收益。他們
報告稱，第三季度的收入爲2.720億美元。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qru1ch/i_analyzed_sofi_so_you_dont_have_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qru1ch/i_analyzed_sofi_so_you_dont_have_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 22:24:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOFI Technologies, Inc. is an online personal finance company. They provide a range of lending and wealth management services. At the time of this post, they are trading at about $23.65. They released earnings for Q3 on November 10. They reported Revenue of $272.01 million for the 3rd quarter of 2021 which is a 35.5% increase from the same prior-year period. SoFi beat estimates by $16.38M. Furthermore, they added 377,000 new members which is the second-highest quarterly increase in the company&amp;#39;s history. That being said, SoFi looks to be a potential buy. Not convinced yet? Here are some other reasons why I believe SoFi is a good company to buy into. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SoFi’s total members grew 96% Year-over-Year. Part of the reason why this occurred is because the products they offer have doubled Year-over-Year. The company beat Revenue Expectations, Earnings Per Share, almost doubled their member growth Year-over-Year and began offering way more products. Most people can find a product that suits them through SoFi’s financial services. In Quarter 3, they did a great job at  demonstrating their ability to capture market share. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SoFi has increased the amount of marketing they’ve been doing. They’ve been working with influencers across Twitter, Instagram, Youtube, and Tik Tok. Which has driven an additional 400 Million impressions and 775K engagements with SoFi content. SoFi has been investing a lot in their marketing strategy and attempts to acquire customers which has obviously translated into very great results. By the looks of it, SoFi has started to get creative in adopting additional customers. These new strategies could help boost the company by a lot. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In relation to their valuation, SoFi experienced strong growth which was driven by the growth of users they had experienced and the products they offer, especially in the personal loans sector. Right now, the company looks like it’s trading at a decent price in comparison with other companies in this sector. If the company can somehow increase their Earnings before interest, taxes, depreciation, and amortization over the years coming, they could see it’s multiples inflate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve made it this far into this post you’re probably asking yourself, Are there any risks involved with investing in this company? Like any investment, there is always a risk. Despite the fact that SoFi reported a strong quarter, they need to show that they can keep up their strength. The stock continuing to go up will be contingent on continued success and an increase in profitability over the future quarters. That being said, I wouldn’t say this is a strong buy, but a potential one. It could be a great buy if it dips again. However, This company is currently trading at reasonable multiples. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading everyone! If you have any questions let me know in the comments below or feel free to message me! I hope this helped you figure out whether or not to buy into SoFi. Also, feel free to check out my profile and see the analysis I did on Digital Turbine AKA $APPS. You will definitely learn something from it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[瞭解並從我們當前的通貨膨脹環境中獲利]]></title><description><![CDATA[通貨膨脹是COVID封鎖經濟中的一個頑固問題，並且
繼續給散戶投資者的空間造成巨大的混亂。
許多散戶交易者不知道它意味着什麼，也不知道如何應對。更具體地說
具體來說，許多人在調整他們的投資組合時遇到了困難。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrtkox/understanding_and_profiting_from_our_current/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrtkox/understanding_and_profiting_from_our_current/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 22:24:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inflation is a persistent issue coming out of the COVID lockdown economy and continues to create a great amount of confusion for the retail investor space. Many retail traders don&amp;#39;t know what it means or how to respond. More specifically, many are having trouble with tailoring their portfolios to either avoid risk or take advantage of inflationary circumstances. I aim to somewhat remedy this. I hope the pointers below will help you better understand the inflationary environment and identify economically favorable industries/sectors. This is not the end all or be all and I welcome your observations and comments on what I could have missed. Enjoy this and lets make some money taking advantage of these once in a lifetime economic circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inflations is Measured by a Change in Rate:&lt;/strong&gt; Inflation doesn&amp;#39;t usually go down. The RATE of inflation goes up or down, but inflation itself is persistent. This is by design. Could you imagine what would happen to the economy if you knew that your dollar would be worth more tomorrow than it is today? Spending on goods other than necessities would come to a very dramatic reduction (&lt;em&gt;Note: You might be rethinking crypto right now huh?&lt;/em&gt;). So it is important to understand that what we are looking at is the CHANGE IN RATE of inflation. There is no deflation!! Deflation is 1000x worse for the economy than inflation. So do not expect deflation. The Fed simply will not allow it. Nor should they!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Current Inflation is Largely a Result of too Much Demand:&lt;/strong&gt; During the COVID lock downs many businesses were forced to grind their operations to a halt. Remember food, toilet paper, &amp;amp; other essentials flying off the shelves? Indeed many grocery stores were limiting the amount of water you could buy. It only stands to reason that when you force businesses to close down you create a situation where the goods that people demand are not being replaced by a steady supply. So what happens as the economy opens back up? Suddenly those same businesses have reduced inventories, they need to hire back workers, they need to order new supplies, &amp;amp; they need to meet an increased demand as a result of some competitors closing their doors for good. Now the quantity of goods demanded well exceeds the quantity of goods supplied ... on all fronts. Reopening firms are competing against other reopening firms for the same raw materials, supplies, resources, shipping, etc. They are also competing for the same labor pool. Remember that goods &amp;amp; services in times of extreme scarcity go to the highest bidder.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secondary &amp;amp; Tertiary Effects of too Much Demand (Or too Little Supply):&lt;/strong&gt; Below you will find the inflationary issues we find ourselves in as a result of increased demand and limited supply. Below each topic you will also find some examples of how to profit from each. You will also receive some examples of secondary and tertiary effects of each.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Supply Chain Bottlenecks:&lt;/strong&gt; First and foremost in the news are the supply chain bottlenecks. We&amp;#39;ve all seen the ships floating off the Port of Los Angeles, or the very long line of trucks waiting to pick up freight from the ports. The United States &amp;amp; Europe have but a limited number of ports and they&amp;#39;re taking on all the supplies that firms ordered as the economy opened back up. Making things worse ... its holiday shopping season. So cost of shipping dry bulk overseas is not just rising as a result of increased demand, but as a result of the fact that it costs money to have all these carriers waiting weeks to offload their goods. Making matters worse many of the imported goods are perishables which can spoil and reduce the supply of foodstuffs amid an already high demand. As a result many firms are opting for alternative methods of shipping like the much more expensive option of air freight.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: Moderately bullish on sea freight carriers, rail, trucking, logistics, logistics outsourcing, and air freight&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Supply Chain Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; As if the bottlenecks weren&amp;#39;t bad enough, there are but a limited number of domestic shipping firms. Firms that not only transport materials to businesses, or, finished goods to retailers, but also delivering orders to retail shoppers. Here we are once again talking about rail, trucking, mail delivery, air freight, logistics firms, logistics outsourcing, etc. So yet again we have an increased demand for shipping and logistics with but a limited supply. And while this demand will keep up for some time, many firms know it will eventually come back down to normal, and therefore, are very hesitant to expand too fast too quickly for fear that they will one day have too much fleet for future business.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: Moderately bullish on rail, trucking, logistics, logistics outsourcing, and air freight&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Semiconductor Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; Everything these days has a semiconductor. Whether its semiconductors, passive semiconductors, diodes, you name it, chances are if it was an electronic made in the last 5 years, it needs a semiconductor to properly operate. Indeed before the supply chain shortages hit critical mass, we were dealing with semiconductor shortages. Now we will not likely fix the semiconductor issue until we fix the supply chain issue. Once again as the economy opened back up &amp;amp; demand skyrocketed, semiconductors too experienced a complementary spike in demand. Semiconductors alone are preventing the automakers from producing at full capacity. There are not enough semiconductors to make vehicles. And with the holidays on the horizon semiconductors are in higher demand than ever. Even Sony had to reduce the number of PlayStations they could manufacture and ship due to component shortages and logistics issues. So expect the price of any new electronic device that has a semiconductor to increase in price.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: Bullish on electronics &amp;amp; semiconductors&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vehicle Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; As noted with the semiconductors, vehicles are in short supply. As a result the quantity of vehicles demanded exceed the quantity of vehicles supplied. Therefore we not only have a shortage of vehicles but the price o vehicles have skyrocketed. Have you seen the empty lots at your local dealership? There&amp;#39;s nothing to sell! People are ordering direct from factory. As a result people turned toward used vehicles which now are also in short supply. As a result people who could not afford the increased price of used vehicles resulted to maintaining their current vehicles. And as a result of people maintaining their current vehicles, the demand for auto parts &amp;amp; auto mechanics have skyrocketed. And I don&amp;#39;t know many large firms that do not need a frequent supply of vehicles to maintain operations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Note:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Moderately bullish to bullish on used car firms, auto parts, and car repair&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;**)**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Raw Material Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; Raw materials were the first to explode out of COVID. Wood, steel, ore, oil, &amp;amp; minerals ... you name it, its all going up. The quantity of supply demanded exceed the current supply ... and for many reasons.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Note:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Moderately bullish on miners, steel, mining equipment suppliers, and oil/gas producers ... see energy shortage below for more detail on oil/gas&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;**)**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Increased Demand for Housing:&lt;/strong&gt; Largely as a result of low interest rates incentivizing lending, we experienced a housing and construction boom in the middle of a Pandemic. Houses and industrial builds in many areas have skyrocketed in value. But this was not only as a result of low interest rates. When the federal government instituted a ban on evictions from rental properties, many took advantage by simply not paying their rent. The forgone payments to the landlord forced the renter to pass on the costs on to new tenants, which increased the cost of rental properties beyond that just owning a home in many areas. So people bought homes instead. Moreover many people moved out of urban areas to escape burdensome COVID restrictions which furthermore increased the demand of housing. Furthermore lifetime renting millennials saw the low interest rates as a great time to buy their first home. Finally, mortgage forbearance reduced a lot of foreclosures during COVID. Less foreclosures means less supply, less supply amid high demand results in higher prices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Note:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Not very bullish on housing &amp;amp; real estate at this time but still moderately bullish on construction, furniture, paint, fixtures, and infrastructure&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;**).**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Energy Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; As we began to put the COVID economy behind us, more people are travelling to work, to school, and going on vacation. More recently international travel is opening back up.  Moreover firms are expanding rapidly to meet demand and shippers are using more energy than ever. This all of course increases the price of oil, natural gas, jet fuel, and the fuel you pay at the pump. Making matters worse, no matter what your politics are, the current administration in the White House is the most ardently unfriendly domestic coal and fossil fuel administrations we&amp;#39;ve had in 5 years. OPEC, perhaps realizing that such demand will be but temporary for the next 1-2 years, refuses to entertain the Biden administrations request to ramp up oil supply. Oddly enough big oil hasn&amp;#39;t been in this good of a position for the last 4 years where the increase of supply made it seriously hard for oil firms to profit. Energy is used for producing everything. When energy goes up the cost of everything goes up. When energy goes up, people spend more on energy and less on other things. So the increase in energy costs are a result of both increased post COVID demand and politics. Of all the issues we are experiencing with inflated prices, energy is among the easiest to fix.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Note: B&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;ullish on oil, natural gas, oil and natural gas equipment maintainers and suppliers, and perhaps oil exploration if the Biden administration would quit putting up road blocks&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;**)**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Worker Shortages:&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;quot;Worker Shortages&amp;quot; is misleading. When people think of a &amp;quot;worker shortage&amp;quot; they generally think that we don&amp;#39;t have enough workers to meet demand. They would be correct. But we should phrase it as &amp;quot;firms do not have enough workers to meet CURRENT demand.&amp;quot; Lets face it we are rear view looking creatures. Simply because a firm doesn&amp;#39;t have enough workers does not indicate that they cant beat previous profit/revenue, but rather they can not only beat previous revenue projections, but also be in a position where they cannot meet CURRENT demand. And just like anything else, when the quantity of labor demanded exceeds the quantity of labor supplied, we run into increased labor costs ... namely wages. And wages are overwhelmingly the highest cost for most firms. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Note:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bullish on staffing and outsourcing firms&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;**)**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secondary &amp;amp; Tertiary Effects of too Much Demand ... Conclusion:&lt;/strong&gt; Lets keep this simple. You want to buy a car. That car is made from raw materials such as aluminum &amp;amp; steel. The car requires electronics. Those electronics require semiconductors. You need a labor force to put that car together. You need energy to manufacture that car. You need truckers &amp;amp; freighters to ship those cars or bring manufacturers the materials to make cars. You need equipment to make cars. In short 100% of the price of all components of that car, or the components used to make that car, have gone up. Still, you have a high demand market where people and businesses require vehicles, but the manufacturer cant meet that demand due to the lack of supplies available. Nevertheless the vehicle manufacturer still needs to pay for overhead costs to keep the doors open. And as so many people are demanding such a short supply of cars, the manufacturers simply increase the price of that car to meet the demand of the highest paying bidders. And this phenomenon is happening in each step of the chain to make that car from the folks who supply the materials, to the folks who produce the energy, to the folks who ship the finished product. When the quantity of goods demanded exceed the quantity of goods supplied, prices necessarily must go up.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monetary Drivers of Inflation:&lt;/strong&gt;  As a result of the dramatic initial downward shift in demand amid COVID lockdowns, the Federal Reserve made money cheap, essentially lowering interests rates to both incentivize borrowing and make borrowing more affordable. The result? Massive influxes of borrowing and lending which in turn flooded the economy with cash. At first this excess cash was used to make it through the pandemic. Later this cash was used by firms to expand rapidly to meet demand. People also used cheap money via extremely low interest rates to purchase homes, which increased the demand for housing. Eventually the Fed is going to need to raise interest rates to disincentive lending and cool off a hot economy. If allowed to persist for too long the influx of cash will lead to investments by firms looking to to stave off losing the value of money via inflation and thereby creating a massive bubble. There are already indicators of this happening by virtue of equity valuations in the market. (&lt;em&gt;Note: the Fed has also been incentivizing investment in the stock market by buying treasury bonds on the secondary market which resulted in keeping the yields artificially low. As a result people were less inclined to buy treasury bonds and more incentivized to invest in other equity&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Government Drivers of Inflation:&lt;/strong&gt; The rapid inflation we are experiencing has not deterred President Biden for advocating for trillions in spending measures. The U.S. Government is a customer just like anyone else, and the government competes for the same goods and services you and I do. Increased spending will to some extent result in crowding out the private sector that competes for the same goods and services. Remember that an increase in demand with limited supply generally results increased prices. If the government spends too much, it can seriously hurt consumers in the form of increased prices. Moreover the Biden administration isn&amp;#39;t the most friendly administration when it comes to mining for coal, oil, minerals, etc.. This inevitably leads to increased costs of energy and raw materials. (&lt;em&gt;Note: This comment used a political figure as an example of a negative economic consequence. Do me a favor, take the example for what its worth to you, and realize I am not going to entertain heated political discussion. There is a cost and benefit to everything, and I don&amp;#39;t have the time to entertain the talking points you pulled from a political webpage or favorable news site and tell you why you&amp;#39;re wrong, when no matter how much the evidence is stacked against you, you&amp;#39;re not going to change your mind anyway. Ergo a massive waste of time that benefits no one&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inflation is Excellent for Debt!:&lt;/strong&gt; I will keep this one quick. Lets say you took out a 30 year fixed mortgage in 1990. You paid $90,000 for your home and have a mortgage of $400 per month. In the year 2019 your home is now worth $200,000 in market value but you&amp;#39;re still paying $400 per month at a fixed rate. Through inflation your wages have eventually increased while your fixed rate mortgage remained stagnant. In short, you may have been scrimping for pennies when you took out the mortgage, but years later you can make your payment while working at a fast food restaurant. Neat huh? Inflation is excellent for debt ridden companies. As their profit margins increase over time through inflation they will find it much easier to pay off their long term debt. (&lt;em&gt;Note: Perhaps this put some of the companies you were looking at into better perspective, and if debt was a major factor for not investing, then you may or may not want to revisit your decision.&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bullish Sectors You Can Profit From that I did not Mention Above:&lt;/strong&gt; Industrial Chemicals, Industrial Equipment, Fertilizers, Farm Equipment/Construction, and Pesticides. As firms ramp up production they will increase the demand for industrial chemicals. Moreover, as food prices continue to increase the more land farmers will be incentivized to clear for additional farming which requires more farming construction, farming equipment, chemicals/pesticides, and fertilizers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Canary in the Inflation Coal Mine:&lt;/strong&gt; If the change in prices rise beyond the change in incomes to the point where people need to start economizing their necessities and forgoing their wants, we could be looking at a very serious correction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/strong&gt; I hope the pointers above have helped you better understand the inflationary environment and identify economically favorable industries/sectors. Please understand that I will be reading this over and over again to identify typos &amp;amp; unclear sentences. I may even edit it as people bring ideas to my attention. Anyway I hope you enjoyed it and can turn this into long term investment opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[科技股、半導體股是否考慮到了中國可能入侵臺灣？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在很多人不情願的情況下，我以我認爲很便宜的價格買了臺積電。最初的不情願來自於一個簡單的擔心：中國可能會破壞臺積電的發展。
最初的不情願來自於一種簡單的恐懼：中國可能會擾亂中國的經濟。
地區。

現在，我不想談政治。我對地緣政治沒有太大的興趣，而且
我傾向於在購買時忽略這些影響因素。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrlnmy/do_tech_semicondutor_stocks_take_in_consideration/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qrlnmy/do_tech_semicondutor_stocks_take_in_consideration/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 21:59:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a lot of reluctance I bought TSMC for what I consider a bargain price. The initial reluctance comes from a simple fear: China’s possible disruption of the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I don’t wanna get political. I have not much interest over geopolitics, and I tend to ignore such influences when buying a business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eventually I came to a conclusion: If TSMC is under threat, so is Apple, AMD, and many other industries for that matter. In fact, every single company on this planet has some exposure if China invades Taiwan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But at the end of the day we cannot paralyze ourselves and wait for a possible tragedy that may or may not happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the stock market does not compute the macro bc the macro is impossible to be predicated. So What you guys think?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我被邀請加入我公司的401k委員會。有什麼建議，我應該提出什麼問題或建議？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們有一個10人的401k審查委員會，在我們的CFO發現我對投資的熱情後，我被邀請加入。
CFO發現了我對投資的外在熱情。有什麼建議可以告訴我
應該注意什麼？

背景。我們使用富達公司。我在公司已經工作了4年，對
我已經在公司工作了4年，對公司的情況有了相當好的瞭解...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrqced/i_was_invited_to_join_my_companys_401k_committee/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qrqced/i_was_invited_to_join_my_companys_401k_committee/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 21:47:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have a 10-person 401k review committee and I&amp;#39;ve been asked to join after our CFO caught onto my outwardly enthusiasm for investing. Any tips as to what I should be paying attention to? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Background: We use Fidelity. I&amp;#39;ve been at the company for 4 years and have a pretty good understanding of the basics when it comes to retirement accounts. I already contribute the IRS max but am curious about contributing more via mega backdoor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這就是美國 
https://t.co/5hO930dHv0]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458856640598487049</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1458856640598487049</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 21:35:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>