<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[国外股市热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览国外股票社区里的热门讨论]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 15:17:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[亞馬遜將停止接受在英國發行的Visa信用卡]]></title><description><![CDATA[亞馬遜（AMZN）將從明年起停止接受英國發行的Visa（V）信用卡的付款。
據透露，從明年開始，亞馬遜將停止接受英國發行的Visa（V）信用卡付款。

這家在線零售巨頭將這一決定歸咎於Visa收取的高額交易費用。
處理交易。

彭博社稱，這些變化最早將於2022年1月19日生效。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvyppt/amazon_to_stop_accepting_visa_credit_cards_issued/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvyppt/amazon_to_stop_accepting_visa_credit_cards_issued/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:20:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon (AMZN) is to cease accepting payments made by UK-issued Visa (V) credit cards from next year, it has been revealed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The online retail giant blamed the decision on high fees charged by Visa to process transactions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The changes will come into effect as early as 19 January 2022, Bloomberg first reported, citing information that Amazon had shared with its customers this week, after they had purchased items.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$V down approx 3.25% in the pre-market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[維度公司爲美國小型股價值ETF和國際小型股價值ETF提交文件]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是否有可能解決流行的AVUV對小盤股價值傾斜的一些限制（我可能不知道）？
這是否有可能解決流行的AVUV小盤股價值傾斜的一些限制（我可能不知道）？我意識到小盤股的傾斜
並不是博格瑞德最擅長的動作，但是我看到它最近在這個子項目中比較流行，我自己也對它很感興趣。
在這個子裏的受歡迎程度，而且我自己也對它相當感興趣。我很想...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvxzxa/dimensional_files_for_us_small_cap_value_etf_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvxzxa/dimensional_files_for_us_small_cap_value_etf_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:20:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Could this have the potential to solve some limitation (that I may not know about) in the popular AVUV for small cap value tilts? I realize an SCV tilt isn&amp;#39;t the most Boglehead move, however I have seen its relatively recent popularity in this sub and am quite interested in it myself. Would love to hear what you guys think!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://us.dimensional.com/about-us/media-center/dimensional-lists-four-fixed-income-etfs-and-announces-further-expansion-of-etf-offering&quot;&gt;https://us.dimensional.com/about-us/media-center/dimensional-lists-four-fixed-income-etfs-and-announces-further-expansion-of-etf-offering&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆仍有超過50%的特斯拉股份可供出售 從推特上看]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你考慮到他在9月份向美國證券交易委員會提交的近10億美元的股票，可以說接近60%。
在他發推文之前，美國證券交易委員會（SEC）9月份的文件已經規定他要賣掉近10億美元的股票。

https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.marketwatch.com/amp/story/another-day-another-tesla-stock-sale-for-elon-musk-8-8-billion-over-past-7-days...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvxlci/elon_still_has_more_than_50_of_shares_to_sell_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvxlci/elon_still_has_more_than_50_of_shares_to_sell_in/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:20:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arguably closer to 60% if you allow for the near $1 billion stock that he was already due to sell from September SEC filings, that preceded his tweet:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.marketwatch.com/amp/story/another-day-another-tesla-stock-sale-for-elon-musk-8-8-billion-over-past-7-days-11637116058&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.marketwatch.com/amp/story/another-day-another-tesla-stock-sale-for-elon-musk-8-8-billion-over-past-7-days-11637116058&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course if Sanders would just respond to his damned tweets, he could be a great scapegoat for offloading far more shares on the highs.  And who would blame Musk if he did.  He did afterall think Tesla &amp;#39;insanely&amp;#39; over valued at $50 billion:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.vanityfair.com/news/2017/05/even-elon-musk-thinks-teslas-stock-is-insanely-overvalued/amp&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.vanityfair.com/news/2017/05/even-elon-musk-thinks-teslas-stock-is-insanely-overvalued/amp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[塔吉特公司盈利超出預期，但股價下跌，因爲零售商專注於保持客戶價格低廉]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/target-tgt-q3-2021earnings.html

每股收益。調整後爲3.03美元，預期爲2.83美元

收入：256.5億美元 vs. 247.8億美元

塔吉特公司第三財季的收益名列前茅，因爲萬聖節和返校等季節性因素促進了銷售。
萬聖節和返校日等季節性因素促進了銷售。

該零售商...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvydgi/target_tops_earnings_estimates_but_shares_fall_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvydgi/target_tops_earnings_estimates_but_shares_fall_as/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:20:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/target-tgt-q3-2021earnings.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/target-tgt-q3-2021earnings.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earnings per share: $3.03 adjusted vs. $2.83, expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revenue: $25.65 billion vs. $24.78 billion&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Target topped earnings for the fiscal third quarter, as seasonal moments like Halloween and back-to-school boosted sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The retailer raised its forecast, saying that comparable sales could rise at between a high-single digit and low double-digit pace in the holiday period. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CEO Brian Cornell said the company is focused on value as prices of food, gas and more rise and consumers face sticker shock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is another non tech stock that always outperform. The e-commerce operations have been improved and getting competitive advantages against Walmart and Amazon. The management teams are dealing with inflations perfectly and will be able to pass those to customers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[許家印變賣個人資產，向恆大投入超過70億元人民幣的救命資金]]></title><description><![CDATA[中國恆大集團董事局主席許家印承諾
許家印承諾確保投資者的利益，並承諾復工和保證交付建設。
的董事長許家印，正在出售他的個人資產以拯救恆大。
恆大。自7月1日以來，爲了維持恆大的流動資金...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvomsc/xu_jiayin_sold_personal_assets_and_invest_over/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvomsc/xu_jiayin_sold_personal_assets_and_invest_over/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:43:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xu Jiayin, chairman of the board of directors of China Evergrande, who promised to ensure the interests of investors and promise the resumption of work and guarantee the delivery of buildings, &lt;strong&gt;is selling his personal assets to save Evergrande&lt;/strong&gt;. Since July 1st, in order to maintain the liquidity of the group, Xu has raised funds through the &lt;strong&gt;sale of personal assets&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;pledged equity&lt;/strong&gt; and has invested more than &lt;strong&gt;RMB7 billion&lt;/strong&gt; in the group to maintain the basic operations of the huge Evergrande empire. During this period, Evergrande did not have financing and sales suspension, but it must ensure the monthly payment of &lt;strong&gt;10%&lt;/strong&gt;, the salary of headquarters employees, and the payment of interest on domestic and foreign bonds, so as to promote the resumption of work and production of projects across the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you think this action can save Evergrande?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在淘金熱中，出售鐵鍬]]></title><description><![CDATA[在芯片熱潮中（由於電動車、採礦、元數據），相關的芯片供應商有哪些？
供應商公司？

我知道TSM是一個大公司，但他們是一家臺灣公司。我正在尋找一家美國公司。
我知道英特爾和Qorvo有他們自己的內部工廠，作爲一個IC設計師，我的設計是在Qorvo進行的。
我的設計是在Qorvo和Global...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvspcz/during_a_gold_rush_sell_shovels/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvspcz/during_a_gold_rush_sell_shovels/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:30:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;During a chip rush (due to EV, mining, metaverse), what are the relevant chip suppliers companies?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know TSM is a big one but they are a Taiwan company. I&amp;#39;m looking for a US one. I know Intel and Qorvo have their own in house fab and as an IC designer I had my designs fab at Qorvo and Global Foundries too. But which companies are the main suppliers for this chip rush?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特公司在最近的高價位19.79美元，是否仍有上升的空間]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道福特公司在Rivian有很大的投資。如果福特公司持有裏維安公司的股份，那麼他們的收益將是什麼呢？
如果他們持有這項投資或決定將其清算，對福特來說會有什麼好處？我個人認爲
我個人認爲，妹妹的車輛仍有很大的增長潛力，特別是他們的
EV150有巨大的未來訂單。你是否認爲...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvp7du/ford_at_a_recent_high_price_of_1979_does_it_still/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvp7du/ford_at_a_recent_high_price_of_1979_does_it_still/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:30:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know that Ford has a big investment in Rivian.  What will the upside be for Ford if they hold onto that investment or decide to liquidate it. Personally I think there’s still a lot of growth potential sister vehicles especially their EV 150 has a tremendous amount of future orders. Do you think will see a move up towards $30 per share during 2022?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[投資初級礦業股票是否值得？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我從今年年初開始投資，雖然我把一些錢放在了FCX和BHP等大型股票上。
較大的股票，如FCX和BHP，我也計劃投資於一些小型企業。I
但我不打算在這些股票上投入大量資金，因爲我知道投資的風險。
因爲我知道投資這些股票的風險。

我正在研究三隻股票...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvx11z/is_investing_in_junior_mining_stocks_worth_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvx11z/is_investing_in_junior_mining_stocks_worth_it/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:30:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been investing since early this year and while I have placed some money on bigger stocks like FCX and BHP, I am planning to invest in some juniors too. I don’t plan on placing a lot on them though, since I am aware of the risks that come with investing in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am looking into three stocks which includes &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fortitudegold.com/&quot;&gt;Fortitude Gold&lt;/a&gt; (FTCO). They are a small producer but a good thing about them is that they have no debts. They recently increased their dividend by 14%, and reported positive results in their Golden Mile property.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I included &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.threevalleycopper.com/&quot;&gt;Three Valley Copper&lt;/a&gt; (TVC) since they’re showing great potential too. They announced a financing with a deal brought about by investor demand, financing the company with $16 million dollars. They are expected to start mining early 2022 and will potentially produce 13-16 thousand tonnes of copper cathodes in a few years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m still looking into other juniors to add to my bigger mining stocks but some peers have been encouraging me to hold physical metals as well. I’m not really sure about this though. It would help me a lot if you guys share your thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[明天的NVDA...你的想法是什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我現在不在NVDA中，我可能只是從旁觀看
我可能只是從旁觀者的角度看一下收益，但看看NVDA的表現肯定會很有趣。
明天白天的股價表現，然後顯然是盤後的情況。
發生在盤後。

通常情況下，我認爲任何事情，即使是遠程...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvo2a3/nvda_tomorrow_your_thoughts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvo2a3/nvda_tomorrow_your_thoughts/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:03:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not currently in NVDA right now, and I&amp;#39;m probably just going to watch earnings from the sidelines, but it&amp;#39;ll certainly be interesting to see how the stock performs during the day tomorrow, and then obviously what&amp;#39;s going to happen in afterhours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Normally, I&amp;#39;d think that anything even remotely good has already been priced into this stock, so I don&amp;#39;t see how it could possibly explode to the upside after earnings. I&amp;#39;m sure they&amp;#39;re hurting in getting parts from their suppliers like anybody else. So, I&amp;#39;d think the forward guidance would be very cautious. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course anything is possible. The thing could hit $350 in AH or maybe $270&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian的市值目前爲1450億。在未來的幾年裏，有哪些市值低於1500億的好股票是你比較看好的？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直聽說Rivian在過去幾天裏已經超過了幾家公司的市值。
我想知道什麼是最好的進入。

你覺得在未來的幾個月和幾年裏，什麼是最好的？
你覺得在未來的幾個月和幾年裏，哪些是最好的，也是市值在1500億以下的？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjzf7/rivians_market_cap_is_currently_at_145b_what_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjzf7/rivians_market_cap_is_currently_at_145b_what_are/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 12:33:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I keep hearing Rivian has surpassed several companies market caps over the last few days and wondering what would the best ones to go into.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you feel are the best ones over the coming months and years to be holding onto that are also sub 150B market caps?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["我們不會因爲擔心可能出現的通貨膨脹而先發制人地提高利率。我們將等待實際通貨膨脹或其他不平衡的證據。" - J. 鮑威爾

過去一年的通貨膨脹...
出口價格。+18.1%
進口價格。+10.7%
生產者價格指數: +8.6%
消費物價指數: +6.2%
PCE: +4.4%]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460828560797667330</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460828560797667330</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:43:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你們這些人讓我感到噁心，Rivian在這些水平上顯然被低估了，你們沒有看到整個畫面。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我很震驚，人們還不明白這一點。rivian出售的T恤衫
[https://rivian.com/gear-shop]。我買了一件35美元的Rivian T恤。
我買了一件35美元的T恤，它的材料真的很好，這有助於證明+1400億美元的
市值，如果我是誠實的。這艘船纔剛剛開始，它...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvo2v1/you_people_make_me_sick_rivian_is_clearly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvo2v1/you_people_make_me_sick_rivian_is_clearly/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:43:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m shocked that people don&amp;#39;t still understand this yet. &lt;a href=&quot;https://rivian.com/gear-shop&quot;&gt;RIVIAN SELLS T-SHIRTS&lt;/a&gt;. I bought one of those $35 dollar T-shirts Rivian sells, it&amp;#39;s really good material which IMO helps justify the +$140 billion market cap if I&amp;#39;m being honest. This ship has only started &amp;amp; it won&amp;#39;t be long until more people buy these t-shirts. Rivian is not just a car company, it&amp;#39;s a clothing company too.(&lt;del&gt;Tsla is not just a car company, it&amp;#39;s a technology company too&lt;/del&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$RIVN的市值比他媽的大衆汽車還要高。絕對不是泡沫。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvfn8c/rivn_has_a_higher_market_cap_than_fucking/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvfn8c/rivn_has_a_higher_market_cap_than_fucking/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:31:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[電動汽車股票有什麼特別之處？]]></title><description><![CDATA[今天和過去幾個月以及2020年和2021年的大部分時間裏，電動車股票一直是
在股價升值方面的領先行業。

我們有LCID，他今天上漲了23%。

RVN今天上漲了15%，其市值幾乎達到1500億美元。

其他如GOEV、FSR、XPEV、PTRA，他們的表現都很出色......]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvilhs/what_is_so_special_about_ev_stocks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvilhs/what_is_so_special_about_ev_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:31:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today and for the past few months and most of 2020 and 2021, EV stocks have been the leading sectors in terms of stock price appreciation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have LCID who is up 23% today. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RVN who is up 15% today and with a market cap of almost $150B. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Others like GOEV, FSR, XPEV, PTRA who have been outperforming most of the market recently. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shit, TSLA is at $1T valuation and won’t stop there most likely. Yes, yes, I know Tesla is NoT jUsT aN EV cOmPaNy. But still. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Point is, what is the hype with EV stocks? I understand that it is a rapidly growing industry since mandates and adoption will allow EVs to replace ICE vehicles in the coming years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, automaker margins are freaking terrible. I just don’t see the appeal of auto maker stocks going up just because they are going EV. There will be lots of competitors (obviously), beit the new companies like Lucid, Rivian, and Tesla and the legacy makers like Volkswagen, Toyota, etc. Also, it’s not like EV is some niche field where duopolies or monopolies will thrive either. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s also not mention that EVs will cost more to make when compared to ICE. So it’s not like auto makers are going to cut major costs like when Ford introduced the assembly line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just want to start a discussion and hear people’s thoughts. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And no, I’m not shorting or buying puts. Just genuinely surprised that this EV bubble or rally - whatever you want to call it - is still going strong. Especially in times of inflation fears.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[週五鮑威爾的決定會對市場產生多大程度的影響？]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登剛剛宣佈美聯儲將在4天內作出決定......因此，這要麼是週五晚些時候
星期五晚上或星期六。因此，當市場在週末關閉時，這使得
我擔心他正在更換負責人並取代鮑威爾。

比起利率、糖價飆升、通貨膨脹......我最大的擔憂是迄今爲止的變化
在...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qviwx9/how_badly_will_the_market_be_affected_by_powell/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qviwx9/how_badly_will_the_market_be_affected_by_powell/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:18:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Biden just announced fed decision will be in 4 days… so that’s either late Friday night or Saturday. So when the market is closed on a weekend which makes me concerned he is changing the head and replacing Powell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More than rates, covid spike, inflation… my biggest concern was by far a change in Powell because the market hates change and unexpected news. I could totally see this resulting in what should have probably already happened with a correction especially with big market cap stocks. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the new chair would be Brainard who has a major supporter in Senator Warren, who opposes the FAANG stock dominance. I am very concerned and hopefully he just sticks with Powell. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The market is going so well this would really be the biggest negative that would sink things for end of year&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["我兩邊都在玩，這樣我總能出頭。"]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvqhsk/im_playing_both_sides_so_that_i_always_come_out/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvqhsk/im_playing_both_sides_so_that_i_always_come_out/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:18:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[電動汽車初創公司Lucid的市值超過福特，股價暴漲，超過890億美元]]></title><description><![CDATA["我對我們的股票價格感覺很好，"豪斯在聯合採訪中告訴CNBC。
採訪時說。"我們已經有的上升，它今天的位置，以及增長的軌跡，坦率地說，這在我們面前。
坦率地說，在我們面前的是增長的軌跡。我看到我們被認爲是一家擁有平臺的技術公司。
我看到我們被認爲是一家技術公司，它的平臺可以擴展到很多領域。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjuok/ev_startup_lucids_market_value_blows_past_ford_at/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjuok/ev_startup_lucids_market_value_blows_past_ford_at/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 10:44:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;I feel great about our stock price,&amp;quot; House told CNBC during the joint interview. &amp;quot;The runup that we&amp;#39;ve had, where it is today and also the growth trajectory, frankly, that&amp;#39;s in front of us. I see that we&amp;#39;re being regarded as a technology company with a platform that&amp;#39;s extensible across lots of vehicle variants and sustainable tech.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1980年至2021年標準普爾500指數的月度平均回報率：年底前的強勁表現？]]></title><description><![CDATA[以下是自1980年以來的平均回報率（%）。

數據是到2021年9月。資料來源。標準普爾和哈弗分析。

1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 +1.2 -0.1 +0.5 +1.5 -0.1 +0.8
+1.6 +0.7 -1.0 +0.4 +0.9 +1.3

你對2021年12月的賭注是什麼？你是如何準備的？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjvni/average_monthly_sp_500_returns_from_1980_to_2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjvni/average_monthly_sp_500_returns_from_1980_to_2021/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 08:11:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below are the average return in % since 1980.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Data are through September 2021.  Source: Standard &amp;amp; Poor’s and Haver Analytics. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Jan&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Feb&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Mar&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Apr&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;May&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Jun&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Jul&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Aug&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Sep&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Oct&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Nov&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Dec&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+1.2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-0.1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+0.5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+1.5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-0.1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+0.8&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+1.6&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+0.7&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;-1.0&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+0.4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+0.9&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;+1.3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What your bet for Dec 2021? How are you preparing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$PFE https://t.co/fQaigrZgaM]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460766555801886722</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460766555801886722</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 06:49:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登公佈美聯儲新任主席的意外人選]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvm3sv/biden_unveils_surprise_pick_for_new_fed_chair/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvm3sv/biden_unveils_surprise_pick_for_new_fed_chair/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 06:49:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[電動汽車公司Polestar（有銷售）將通過SPAC上市 - $GGPI]]></title><description><![CDATA[被忽視的SPAC交易，Polestar，一家位於瑞典的以電動爲重點的汽車公司正在與GGPI合併。
瑞典的電動汽車公司正在與GGPI美元合併。

他們已經在銷售他們的Polestar 1（一種混合動力車）和Polestar 2。
全電動汽車。他們還發布了Polestar "Precept "的願景。

財務狀況

他們做了6.45億美元的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvmzuu/ev_company_polestar_with_sales_going_public_via/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvmzuu/ev_company_polestar_with_sales_going_public_via/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 05:56:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overlooked SPAC deal, Polestar, an electric-focused automotive company based in Sweden is merging with $GGPI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are already selling their Polestar 1, a hybrid, and the Polestar 2, fully-electric car. They are also released a vision for the Polestar &amp;quot;Precept.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Financials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They did $645M in revenue in 2020, and are projecting $1.6B in 2021. Right now, the SPAC is valued at just $1.55B.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/3jmd9c5ulvz71.png?width=624&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=54caf7be4f0b42872a22d4a633e3f28aa78b836c&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/3jmd9c5ulvz71.png?width=624&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=54caf7be4f0b42872a22d4a633e3f28aa78b836c&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;compared to other EV/automotive companies. $645M* revenue&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are also backed by Volvo, Geely, and Leonardo DiCaprio? IMO most undervalued EV company after GM and F.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[新文章。

股票市場不是經濟...

https://t.co/HTQvTJLLHf https://t.co/mg6NMfQ2NF]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460723942314938372</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460723942314938372</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 05:43:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不是在開玩笑。內衣/內褲公司Naked Brand與電動汽車製造商Cenntro Automotive合併後飆升]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是一個多星期前的事。這些公司並不像Lucid或Rivian那樣非常有名。
Rivian，但我認爲電動車公司的市場佔有率最高。

 *Naked Brands的股票在週二飆升至30%，因爲該公司
   該公司宣佈與Cenntro Automotive合併。
 * 這家內衣製造商正在轉向電動汽車。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvocts/not_kidding_lingerieunderwear_company_naked_brand/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvocts/not_kidding_lingerieunderwear_company_naked_brand/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 05:43:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was over a week ago. The companies are not very well known like Lucid or Rivian but I&amp;#39;m calling market top for EV companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Naked Brands stock soared as much as 30% on Tuesday after the company announced a merger with Cenntro Automotive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The lingerie maker is pivoting to electric vehicles as investors look to find the next Tesla.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cenntro develops electrified commercial vehicles and has sold more than 3,000 units to date.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://africa.businessinsider.com/finance/a-lingerie-makers-stock-is-soaring-on-a-deal-to-merge-with-an-ev-manufacturer/040c5jh&quot;&gt;https://africa.businessinsider.com/finance/a-lingerie-makers-stock-is-soaring-on-a-deal-to-merge-with-an-ev-manufacturer/040c5jh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對迪士尼（DIS）的看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[我已經觀察迪斯尼幾個月了，認爲它是一個很好的股票，適合我長期持有。
我的長期持股。自從它跌到160美元以下，我最近開始增加股票。
大家對這隻股票有什麼看法？對它的評價是否過多地集中在
迪斯尼+而不是整個公司？

它已經有了一個新的增長點。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvk3q2/thoughts_on_disney_dis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvk3q2/thoughts_on_disney_dis/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 05:43:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been watching Disney for a few months now and think it’s a great stock for my long term holdings. I began adding shares recently since it dropped sub $160. What are everyone’s thoughts on the stock? Is it being judged too much on Disney+ and not the company as a whole?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s had an underwhelming year and is now 20% below ATH. Has anyone held throughout this recent slump?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone discourse would be appreciated :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[購買比特幣的Bogleheads？]]></title><description><![CDATA[對於在這個子裏做他們的5%有趣的錢和購買比特幣的Bogleheads，哪個
你是用哪個應用程序或供應商來購買比特幣的？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvh6s9/bogleheads_who_buy_bitcoin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvh6s9/bogleheads_who_buy_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 04:32:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the Bogleheads in this sub who do their 5% fun money and buy Bitcoin, which app or provider are you using to buy Bitcoin?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[裏維安的收入爲0美元，現在是地球上第三大價值的汽車製造商]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvinva/rivian_has_0_in_revenue_and_is_now_the_third_most/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvinva/rivian_has_0_in_revenue_and_is_now_the_third_most/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 03:46:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Metaverse以及爲什麼你應該關注 - 基本分類]]></title><description><![CDATA[介紹和什麼是Metaverse？

你們現在可能都知道，流行的社交媒體公司，即以前稱爲
臉書已將其名稱改爲Meta。這引發了關於
這引發了關於Metaverse及其對社會未來影響的討論，這也是理所當然的。雖然我已經
看到許多帖子...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvc6fr/the_metaverse_and_why_you_should_pay_attention/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvc6fr/the_metaverse_and_why_you_should_pay_attention/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 03:32:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction and what is the Metaverse?:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you all probably know by now the popular social media company formerly known as Facebook has changed its name to Meta. This has sparked discussions about the Metaverse and its future effect on society, and rightfully so. Although I have seen many posts online and especially on Reddit which don’t quite seem to grasp what the Metaverse is and why it&amp;#39;s the future, please note if you are one of these people don’t worry - it’s complicated for sure! This post will explain simply what the Metaverse is and why you should get on board now. I will do my best to explain but if you have any questions please feel free to ask in the comments and I will be sure to reply.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Metaverse put simply is the combination of multiple elements of technology, but put more complexly is where virtual reality, blockchain and web3 meet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best way of explaining web3 is to first understand web1 and web2. Web1 is what many may consider the first stage of the internet, if you look at what the first iterations of the internet were, it was just code on a screen. It was complex to use and only really used for sharing scientific work. Web2 is what we now know as the internet. This includes Youtube, Reddit etc. The main downside of web2 is for the longest time other than a domain name you couldn’t own anything online. You could make a video and post it on Youtube, even though you feel you own the video and control it, Youtube at any point can remove the video and even your channel. At any point in time everything online can be controlled by someone else. This is where web3 comes in. Web3 is the next evolution of the internet. Web3 may as well be called the decentralised internet. It allows users to freely use the internet run on blockchain, so anyone can participate without having your personal data involved or monetized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a big reason crypto based items such as coins and NFT’s have taken off as they are based on web3 technology. For the first time normal everyday people are able to own their own little part of the internet, and no one, including the government, can tell you what to do. It&amp;#39;s the next step for total freedom online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Metaverse isn’t a place, the Metaverse isn’t something you can touch. A big mistake I see is people think that there is going to be some sort of invention or overnight change where suddenly the Metaverse is mainstream and that&amp;#39;s our lives, no. It will be a gradual change which has already started and will continue to the point that our virtual life is worth more to us than our physical lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why is the Metaverse the next big thing?:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the best place to start on why the Metaverse will be the next big thing will be to look back at previous technology. 99% of human attention used to be on our physical environment. TV’s dropped that to 85%. Computers dropped that to 70%. Phones dropped that to 50%. It&amp;#39;s clear that as technology advances it absorbs more and more of our time and energy. At some point something new will drop that to lower and lower numbers to the point where we are using technology 100% of the time, this may take decades but it&amp;#39;s entirely possible. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t have to be something mind-blowing but just imagine some type of augmented reality device which either connects to your brain or you see it through contact lenses, imagine it just helped with basic everyday things like arrows on a road so you don&amp;#39;t have to distract yourself with a GPS, or walking into a McDonalds and being able to see the calories of each food item on the menu. These are just basic examples of what the first iteration of augmented reality can do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Metaverse will be the next big thing because &lt;strong&gt;it will be everything.&lt;/strong&gt; Anything you could imagine will be in the Metaverse. It can range from anything from gaming to concerts to seeing family members from the other side of the world. There is no beginning, middle and end, it&amp;#39;s just infinite code waiting to be filled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real life application and potential benefits:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the potential benefits I want to start with isn’t about what will be good inside the Metaverse but outside it. A comment I’m seeing a lot online is people saying “I want to work on fixing the real world, not create a fake one”. But I think people are missing the point that this will make the real world better. Imagine the millions of cars we can get off the road and reduce pollution if people no longer had to drive to work and school, and instead would stay at home and work in the Metaverse. Of course this may vary depending on the industry but even if we could get 50% of cars off the road it would be a massive achievement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I write this more and more benefits keep popping in my head, I will just briefly write some ideas but it&amp;#39;s really going to be endless. Surgeons can practice their work virtually. Architects can design and walk around buildings before construction. Home buyers can visit a home from their own home. People on lower incomes can travel the world from their living room. Schools can visit any museum. Entrepreneurs and businesses can save money on office space. Lovers of history can travel to any time desired (DINOSAURS!). The list really is endless, so I will stop there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Potential negatives and why it won’t matter:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with any new technology there are always downsides. When the microwave first came out people were terrified of it, same with TV, radio, social media and now the Metaverse. I will note that is a good thing. As a society we should always look to protect ourselves and do what&amp;#39;s best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Metaverse won’t be perfect. Even nowadays cyber bullying is a major issue and it may not be any better in the Metaverse. We will distance ourselves further from the real world. Spending less and less physical time with our friends and family and more virtual time with them. The thing is though, the negatives don’t matter. Whether it&amp;#39;s good or bad technology has always advanced on and those who don’t get on board are left behind. Many said at the birth of the internet that it would be bad but it is undoubtedly the best thing to happen to humanity in the past century, and this will have the same effect. I greatly encourage those to at least have an open mind when it comes to the Metaverse, we are on the dawn of something great and those who capitalise on it will be rewarded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How long until the Metaverse is ready and becomes mainstream?:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this is a very hard question. Actually, I think this is an impossible question. You could try and rephrase it to ‘How long until the internet is ready and becomes mainstream?’ At no point does anyone announce the internet is ready and at no point is it officially called mainstream. At some point it just became what it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Metaverse creation will be gradual, it will most likely take a decade minimum but my guess is as good as yours. I think the point at which we accept as a society that the Metaverse is ready is when our digital selves are worth more than our physical selves. You even start to see it now. Kids care more about how they look on Fortnite than in real life. Teens care more about how many followers they have on Instagram than in real life. The world has and always will be  changing with technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to buy and how to make profit:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could list any number of companies which could make you great gains in the near future, including FB, MSFT, U, RBLX, AMZN, ADSK etc. and I would be completely wrong! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though I and many others may know a lot about the Metaverse, the truth is we won’t be able to predict even 1% of what the final product will be. If you asked a million people before the internet what the most popular websites would be you wouldn’t get a single right answer. No one knows so anyone telling you what to buy don’t actually have a clue. Yes you can make money in the short term but that’s it. Remember the dot com bubble? Watch out for a Metaverse bubble.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final thoughts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My thoughts are to tell people now to worry. This isn’t some doomsday device, it’s better to just see it as an extension of your phone. The truth is we are years off of anything serious and no one is going to be forced to use it. I also don’t see any chance of it being stopped by the government as I see some people online say. Sugar and cigarettes are bad but they are legal too. I would recommend anyone to at least try and allocate a small percentage of their portfolio to one of the bigger stock names linked to the Metaverse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[市場被低估了]]></title><description><![CDATA[還記得你們10年前的生活嗎？是的。你們有比以前更多的狗屎。
你有更多的選擇。更多他媽的技術。

現在更加專業化了。

所以未來10年？這將是一個他媽的彩虹。創新並沒有停止。
創新的速度加快了，這是最高的...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvo3kl/the_market_is_undervalued/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvo3kl/the_market_is_undervalued/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 03:32:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember your lives 10 years ago? Yeah. You have way more shit than ever before. You have way more options. Way more fucking technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is more specialized now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the next 10 years? It&amp;#39;ll be a fucking rainbow. Innovation has not stopped. Innovation picked up the speed that is the highest that it ever has been.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s an amazing ride. Enjoy it. It&amp;#39;s never been better to be alive than now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Metaverse might actually happen. Maybe it&amp;#39;s not if but when?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla is overvalued. Is it though? No idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Facebook and Coinbase are ridiculously undervalued.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$10T market cap? Will we ever see it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn&amp;#39;t matter. Hug people you care about. We are all going to die. It does not matter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在目前的市場條件下，是否有可能出現調整？]]></title><description><![CDATA[真正的問題。在目前的市場條件下，廣泛的、交叉的指數修正是否可能？
的市場條件下，是否有可能出現廣泛的、交叉的指數調整？老實說，我認爲不可能。我認爲由於QE和美聯儲的支持
有如此多的現金到處亂晃，尋找一個家，以至於任何有回報前景的東西都被立即投資。
哪怕是回報前景渺茫的東西，都會被立即投資進去。

聽着...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvgi4h/is_a_correction_even_possible_under_current/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvgi4h/is_a_correction_even_possible_under_current/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 02:51:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Genuine question. Is a broad, cross-index correction possible given the current market conditions? I honestly think not. I think due to QE and Fed bolstering there is so much cash sloshing around looking for a home that anything with an even remote prospect of return is instantly invested in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hear me out. I really think this is a new paradigm, not as in oh market goes up forever and this time is different, and more as in this amount of QE and stimulus mixed with bare bones low interest rate has never been achieved before. We have never had a market with the combination of those 2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here&amp;#39;s how I see things going forward:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dumb money is here to stay. There&amp;#39;s just too damn much of it flooding the market looking for a home. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Retail investor sentiment has changed. No one is risk-adverse on a broad scale anymore. Investors are willing to hold through dips and plunge more cash into them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interest rates are rock bottom, and there&amp;#39;s the possibility they stay that way or go negative due to debt implications if they&amp;#39;re raised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s going to change? Is retail suddenly going to become risk adverse? Is the amount of capital flooding the system going to be reigned in? Are interest rates going to drastically rise, if at all?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t think so. I quite literally think that given market conditions and sentiment a correction is not even possible. Do all the remind me&amp;#39;s you want. The market is unable to correct.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉有價值的唯一原因是超級充電網絡，而Rivian和Lucid沒有這個網絡。]]></title><description><![CDATA[兩年前，我以開玩笑的方式試駕了一輛特斯拉3型車，結果當天就買了一輛。
同一天。它們實際上是非常酷的車，而且快得要命......但你知道爲什麼我和其他有錢的正常人（又不是你們這些沒錢的弱智）都要買。
但你知道爲什麼我和其他有錢的正常人（又稱不是你們這些在RH賬戶裏有500美元的破產弱智）會買這些車。
500美元在你的RH賬戶）買它們？

超級充電器網絡....]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvelvp/the_only_reason_tesla_is_worth_anything_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvelvp/the_only_reason_tesla_is_worth_anything_is/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 02:29:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I test drove a Tesla model 3 two years ago as a joke and ended up buying one that same day. They&amp;#39;re actually really cool cars and fast as shit... but you know why I, and other normal people with money (aka not you broke retards with $500 in your RH accounts) buy them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE SUPER CHARGER NETWORK. This is basically a system of electric gas stations that charge your car in 30-40 minutes, and allows you to drive ANYWHERE in America and Canada. You can drive from San Diego to NYC with this network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know what you can&amp;#39;t do with a Rivian or Lucid? Drive anywhere you don&amp;#39;t normally drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you try to charge your car at a charge port or whatever, it&amp;#39;ll take you 8 hours for a full charge. The only reason Tesla is worth anything is because of their phenomenal super charger network. How the fuck are lucid and rivian going to compete with that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;edit: looks like the truth has triggered some fuckin’ noobs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[財政部長珍妮特-耶倫警告說，拜登的基礎設施法案中的要求可能加速美國的債務違約。]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 財政部長珍妮特-耶倫週二警告國會領導層說
> 如果聯邦政府不採取行動，它可能在下個月出現債務違約。
> 採取行動提高債務上限。
> 
> 耶倫女士在給高層立法者的一封信中預計，在12月15日之後，將有
> 有一些情況在...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvlndx/treasury_secretary_janet_yellen_warns_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvlndx/treasury_secretary_janet_yellen_warns_that/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 02:29:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen warned congressional leadership Tuesday that the federal government could default on its debt next month if they don’t take action to raise the debt ceiling.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a letter to top lawmakers, Ms. Yellen projected that after Dec. 15, there are scenarios in which the Treasury could have “insufficient resources to continue to finance the operation of the U.S. government.”  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ms. Yellen added that she has “a high degree of confidence” in the Treasury’s ability to make debt payments through Dec. 15. That’s two weeks longer than her initial forecast of Dec. 3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More money coming in? More pump?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[還有人討厭新的Vanguard應用程序嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我討厭那些試圖成爲超時尚和極簡主義的應用程序。我不知道什麼是
哪些地方，而且感覺功能都被拿走了。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvj98f/anybody_else_hate_the_new_vanguard_app/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvj98f/anybody_else_hate_the_new_vanguard_app/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 01:53:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I hate apps that try to be ultra sleek and minimalist. I don&amp;#39;t know where anything is, and it feels like features have been taken away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cloudflare緩解了來自15,000臺設備的近2 Tbps DDoS發射]]></title><description><![CDATA["Cloudflare表示，它緩解了一次分佈式拒絕服務（DDoS）攻擊，該攻擊的峯值略低於2 Tbps帶寬。
由於使用了大約1.5萬臺被攻擊的設備，該攻擊的帶寬峯值略低於2 Tbps。
15,000臺被破壞的設備。

該公司表示，這是它迄今爲止所目睹的最大的DDoS攻擊。它
據稱，它使用了一種混合型的 "網絡"。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvhk2a/cloudflare_mitigated_nearly_2_tbps_ddos_launched/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvhk2a/cloudflare_mitigated_nearly_2_tbps_ddos_launched/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:51:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Cloudflare says it mitigated a distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack that peaked at just under 2 Tbps of bandwidth thanks to its use of approximately 15,000 compromised devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company says this was the largest DDoS attack it had witnessed to date. It was said to have used a mix of Mirai-infected Internet of Things devices, which are commonly used to launch massive DDoS attacks, as well as unpatched instances of the GitLab developer tool.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source, PCMag: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pcmag.com/news/cloudflare-mitigates-nearly-2-tbps-ddos-attack&quot;&gt;https://www.pcmag.com/news/cloudflare-mitigates-nearly-2-tbps-ddos-attack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以下是今天（2021年11月16日，星期二）的市場回顧。請欣賞!]]></title><description><![CDATA[心理市場回顧 - 2021年11月16日，星期二

今天股市上漲，市場參與者鬆了一口氣，因爲新的
市場參與者鬆了一口氣，因爲新的經濟數據顯示消費者需求仍然強勁，儘管持續的供應鏈
供應鏈中斷和勞動力短缺的情況下，消費需求仍然強勁，市場參與者鬆了一口氣。此外，沃爾瑪（WMT）等主要零售商。
Target...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjo3j/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_tuesday_nov_16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvjo3j/here_is_a_market_recap_for_today_tuesday_nov_16/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:51:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PsychoMarket Recap - Tuesday, November 16, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stocks gained today, with market participants releasing a sigh of relief as new economic data showed consumer demand remains strong despite ongoing supply-chain disruptions and labor shortages. Moreover, major retailers like Walmart (WMT), Target (TGT), Lowe’s (LOW), and Home Depot (HD) are set to release quarterly earnings this week, giving us more information into the state of consumer spending in the US. As a reminder, consumer spending accounts for roughly 70% of US GDP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Department of Commerce released their monthly Retail Sales Report, which showed better than expected consumer spending trends as the holiday season, by far the busiest in the year, continues to play out. Here are the numbers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retail Sales: 1.7% increase vs 1.4% expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core Retail Sales: +1.6%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manufacturing Production: +1.2%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The solid report suggests that high inflation is not dampening consumer spending. Rising household wealth, thanks to a strong stock market, house prices, and rising wages appear to be cushioning consumers against the highest annual pace of inflation in roughly thirty years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matthew Shay, President of the National Retail Federation, said of the report, “Today’s numbers show that consumers are getting a jump on their holiday shopping. We continue to urge consumers to shop early and shop safely, and we fully expect this holiday season to be one for the record books”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, two of the largest retailers in the US, Walmart (WMT) and Home Depot (HD), reported earnings today, with both companies demolishing earnings (though WMT stock did not react positively). Here are the numbers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Walmart (WMT)&lt;/strong&gt; 

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue: $140.53 billion vs $135.60 billion expected &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earnings per Share (EPS): $1.45 vs $1.40 expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sames Store Sales: +9.2% vs +6.9% expected &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;eCommerce Sales: +8% vs +1.9% expected &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Home Depot (HD)&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue: $36.82 billion vs $35.01 billion expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earnings per Share (EPS): $3.92 vs $3.40 expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Same Store Sales: +6.1% vs 1.9% expected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These reports came at the tail end of what has already been an exceptionally strong earnings season. As of Friday, 92% of S&amp;amp;P 500 companies had reported actual results, and of these, 81% of them had reported better-than-expected earnings results, according to FactSet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_111221.pdf&quot;&gt;https://www.factset.com/hubfs/Website/Resources%20Section/Research%20Desk/Earnings%20Insight/EarningsInsight_111221.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Somehow, someway, shares of Rivian (RIVN) keep rising after its blockbuster IPO, with the company now being the third largest auto manufacturer by market cap at roughly $150 billion despite barely completing any deliveries. This is, by far, the craziest valuation I’ve ever seen. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Commerce Department reported Tuesday that import prices rose 1.2% on a monthly basis in October, coming in well above the 0.4% rise for September. This was also above the 1.0% increase consensus economists expected for October, according to Bloomberg data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shares of Qualcomm (QCOM) are on fire after the company projected that its chipset business will average “midteens” revenue growth through its fiscal year 2024. That’s well above the 8% average contemplated by Wall Street’s current estimates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Netflix (NFLX) is set to release the highly anticipated sequel to Tiger King tomorrow. It seems like Netflix has been on an amazing roll as of late and now has a higher market cap than Disney (DIS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lucid Motors (LCID) has now overtaken Ford Motors (F) in market cap&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple (AAPL) is reportedly working to make its own in-house modem chip that allows wireless connection for iPhones by 2023. Qualcomm (QCOM), which currently supplies modem chips for all Apple devices, estimates Apple will self-supply 80% of modem chips by 2023. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Please note that current stock price was written during the session and may not reflect closing prices*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance Auto Parts (AAP) with four target raises. Stock currently around $235

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Citigroup from $282 to $290 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wedbush from $250 to $270 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Credit Suisse from $250 to $255 at Outperform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bank of America from $256 to $282 at Buy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Datadog (DDOG) target raised by Jefferies Financial from $210 to $230 at Buy. Stock currently around $194&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lucid Motors (LCID) price target raised by Citigroup from $28 to $57 at Buy. Stock currently around $57 after gapping up 25%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lattice Semiconductor (LSCC) target raised by Benchmark from $81 to $96 at Buy. Stock currently around $85&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NVIDIA (NVDA) target raised by Credit Suisse from $225 to $400 at Outperform. Stock currently around $300.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tyson Foods (TSN) with a host of target raises. Average price target $95 at Buy. Stock currently aroun d$84&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UnitedHealth Group (UNH) target raised by Deutsche Bank from $421 to $477 at Buy. Stock currently around $450&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Workday (WDAY) target raised by Jefferies Financial from $320 to $350 at Buy. Stock currently around $299&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Turn your wounds into wisdom.” — Oprah Winfrey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這也是磨練的一部分]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvfd4d/its_part_of_the_grind/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvfd4d/its_part_of_the_grind/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 23:53:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我們是否已經進入了一個新的時代，長期的股票市場崩潰已經成爲過去？]]></title><description><![CDATA[看起來鮑威爾的說法起了作用，股市在2020年3月的暴跌後只用了3個月就恢復了。
個月就恢復了。美聯儲是否已經成功地
從市場上消除了所有真正的風險？如果是這樣，這將是未來幾十年的現狀嗎？
未來幾十年的現狀嗎？]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvcaii/have_we_entered_a_new_era_where_prolonged_stock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvcaii/have_we_entered_a_new_era_where_prolonged_stock/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 23:41:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seems like the Powell put has worked and it only took the stock market 3 months to recover after the crash in March of 2020. Has the fed managed to remove all real risk from the market? If so will this be the status quo for the next few decades?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美聯儲爲什麼不加息？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我聽到很多關於美聯儲只是打開閘門以取悅華爾街並保持經濟增長的論點。
討好華爾街並保持經濟增長，但這種說法在歷史上的任何時候都有可能出現。
但這種說法在歷史上的任何時候都有可能出現；但在過去，美聯儲的行爲是負責任的。

當然，這種不計後果的通貨膨脹推動與...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvi2d8/why_is_the_fed_not_raising_rates/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvi2d8/why_is_the_fed_not_raising_rates/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 22:35:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I hear a lot of arguments about the fed simply opening the floodgates to please Wall St and keep the economy rising, but that argument could have been made at any point in history; yet in the past the fed have acted responsibly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Surely this reckless inflatory push has something to do with competition between the US and China/Russia? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether its the fact China will overtake it quicker now or a potential conflict with either one. Could it be an experiment in whether having the “global currency” can allow a country to buy growth without insane amounts of inflation? Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta使用面部識別 "視頻自拍 "尋找 "可疑賬戶"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[看一下Meta公司的發展方向。

我在我的IG上遇到了問題，因爲現在幾乎每天我都不得不
發送視頻自拍進行 "驗證"。似乎他們希望每個IG
帳戶完全公開，而不僅僅是爲了那些想瀏覽IG的人
匿名的人。

它直接...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv20ol/meta_using_facial_recognition_video_selfies_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv20ol/meta_using_facial_recognition_video_selfies_for/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 22:18:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A look at where Meta is heading as a company. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve bene having issues on my IG because nearly every day now I am having to send in a video selfie for &amp;quot;verification&amp;quot;. It seems like they want every IG account totally public and not simply for people who want to browse IG anonymously. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It directly says: &amp;quot;The video will never be visible on Instagram and will be deleted within 30 days. This won&amp;#39;t use ice recognition or collect biometric data&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Instagram/comments/qt15br/this_is_just_creepy/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/Instagram/comments/qt15br/this_is_just_creepy/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But given the new &amp;quot;Meta&amp;quot; name so focused on the meta verse, it&amp;#39;s extremely difficult to trust they aren&amp;#39;t using biometric data. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Captchas and &amp;quot;image puzzles&amp;quot; have been used for years to confirm human users and reduce bot activity, and are far less intrusive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The level of privacy is getting insane at this point and I just wonder where this is leading to for Meta. They say the data will be deleted within 30 days.. but I just don&amp;#39;t believe that and they are using it for some future Metaverse data. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I frankly wish this was a bigger news story already, because if they actually got backlash I think they would have to at least respond about it. Very interesting that I suddenly started getting these messages too around the same time Meta was announced as the name.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GME的淨累積保費不斷增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[GME的淨累積保費不斷增加，這表明有大量的
大量的催款正在積累。這些設置是擠壓的完美選擇，因爲
這些被MM們持有的看漲期權，可以用長線來對沖...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvbkwn/gme_net_cumulative_premiums_keep_increasing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvbkwn/gme_net_cumulative_premiums_keep_increasing/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 21:42:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The net cumulative premiums on GME keep increasing, suggesting that a large amount of calls is being accumulated. Those setups are perfect for a squeeze, as these calls, held short by MMs, net to be hedged with long shares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/srnqtpergzz71.png?width=1332&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=05053ef1adf33bb2305b4ed9db3ec184adb9d4c4&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/srnqtpergzz71.png?width=1332&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=05053ef1adf33bb2305b4ed9db3ec184adb9d4c4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the past few weeks, it&amp;#39;s obvious that the calls have been leading, as you can see on the chart below. The green and purple bars at the bottom are not volume bars, they represent premiums. As you can see, recent sessions have been overwhelmingly biased towards the call side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/2urndniugzz71.png?width=1522&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=a9ab1581d51afd41c637615aec3b0c6c47ca8846&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/2urndniugzz71.png?width=1522&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=a9ab1581d51afd41c637615aec3b0c6c47ca8846&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The volume has also been skewed to the call side MTD, with the majority of large trades being for calls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/bhq044dchzz71.jpg?width=1605&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=65bdfebff36b78ac9df8c7a69c2689ad1645989b&quot;&gt;stockgrid.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[動視首席執行官鮑比-科蒂克多年來對視頻遊戲巨頭的性行爲指控知情不報]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.wsj.com/articles/activision-videogames-bobby-kotick-sexual-misconduct-allegations-11637075680?st=2l46k41g4se9lc8&amp;amp;reflink=share_mobilewebshare

> 多年來，科蒂克先生本人也被幾位女性指控在工作場所內外有
> 在工作場所內外的虐待行爲，並在...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qve7ya/activision_ceo_bobby_kotick_knew_for_years_about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qve7ya/activision_ceo_bobby_kotick_knew_for_years_about/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 21:28:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/activision-videogames-bobby-kotick-sexual-misconduct-allegations-11637075680?st=2l46k41g4se9lc8&amp;amp;amp;amp;reflink=share_mobilewebshare&quot;&gt;https://www.wsj.com/articles/activision-videogames-bobby-kotick-sexual-misconduct-allegations-11637075680?st=2l46k41g4se9lc8&amp;amp;amp;amp;reflink=share_mobilewebshare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the years, Mr. Kotick himself has been accused by several women of mistreatment both inside and outside the workplace, and in some instances has worked to settle the complaints quickly and quietly, according to people familiar with the incidents and documents reviewed by the Journal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2006, one of his assistants complained that he had harassed her, including by threatening in a voice mail to have her killed, according to people familiar with the matter. He settled the matter out of court, the people said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: &lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.md/2021.11.16-160822/https://www.wsj.com/articles/activision-videogames-bobby-kotick-sexual-misconduct-allegations-11637075680&quot;&gt;Non-paywall link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我的投資組合中有1/3投資於VXUS。]]></title><description><![CDATA[另外2/3是在VTI。我是在一個半月前纔開始這個冒險的。
但我不禁注意到，到目前爲止，VTI的表現要好兩倍。I
在一個有錢的熟人的建議下，我買了VXUS，但我讀到一些東西
表明VXUS多年來一直表現不佳。是否...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv7joe/i_have_13_of_my_portfolio_invested_in_vxus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qv7joe/i_have_13_of_my_portfolio_invested_in_vxus/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 20:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other 2/3 is in VTI.  I just started this adventure about a month and a half ago, but I can&amp;#39;t help but to notice that VTI performs twice as well to date.  I picked up VXUS on advice from a rich acquaintance, but I&amp;#39;ve read some things indicating that VXUS has underperformed for many years now.  Does anyone have experience with this?  I&amp;#39;m contemplating dumping everything into VTI.  This port is worth around 136k for reference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼馬斯克要賣掉任何東西來支付他的稅收？]]></title><description><![CDATA[像他這樣的億萬富翁不是以他們的股票價值爲抵押進行借款嗎？如果他
如果他相信他的股票會升值，那麼很明顯，以1%的利息獲得貸款比出售他的股票更便宜。
以1%的利息獲得貸款比出售他的股票更便宜。

銀行不可能不願意借錢給世界上最富有的人。
最低限度...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv6u5w/why_does_musk_have_to_sell_anything_to_pay_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv6u5w/why_does_musk_have_to_sell_anything_to_pay_for/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 20:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t billionaires like him borrow against the value of their shares? If he believes in the value of his shares to appreciate then obviously it&amp;#39;s cheaper to get a loan at 1% interest than to sell his shares. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s no way banks aren&amp;#39;t willing to lend money to the world&amp;#39;s richest man at a minimal interest rate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[福布斯》。南希-梅斯議員提出了結束聯邦大麻禁令的法案。]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvbyxa/forbes_representative_nancy_mace_introduces_bill/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/wallstreetbets/comments/qvbyxa/forbes_representative_nancy_mace_introduces_bill/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:56:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian公司的IPO讓我思考。很明顯，美國股市被高估了。然而，它卻一直在走高。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在698家價值超過100億美元的美國企業中，你有25%的企業以10倍的價格銷售。
銷售額。因此，如果你只有10億美元的銷售額，你的價值是100億美元。

在接下來的13年裏，你的銷售額必須每年增長20%才能達到1倍的銷售額。

在價值超過100億美元的公司中，只有約4%的公司的銷售額增長達到或超過了1倍。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvacjm/the_rivian_ipo_got_me_thinking_clearly_the_us/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qvacjm/the_rivian_ipo_got_me_thinking_clearly_the_us/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:56:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Out of 698 US businesses worth over $10b, you&amp;#39;ve got 25% of those selling at 10x sales. So, if you have only $1b in sales, you&amp;#39;re worth $10b.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#39;d have to grow sales 20% per year for the next 13 years to get to 1x sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only about 4% of companies worth over $10b have grown sales at, or above, 20% over the last 10 years. This figure drops to 2% if you include all US SEC reporting businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That means, roughly, about 20% of your stock market valuations are insanely overpriced. Rivian being one of them. That paired with the Shiller P/E being close to all-time highs, and inflation spiking well above expectation, signals potential disaster on the horizon. Be careful out there peeps. If the FED starts talking rate hikes, expect a sell-off. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/pressreleases/monetary20211103a.htm&quot;&gt;https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/pressreleases/monetary20211103a.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rivian（收入0美元，淨收入-16億美元）現在的市值高於星巴克（收入290億美元，淨收入42億美元）和Target（收入1000億美元，淨收入63億美元）。

$rivn $sbux $tgt

數據來自@ycharts https://t.co/hv4gEyxqDt]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460622351582773250</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460622351582773250</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:43:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[您對伯恩斯坦有什麼經驗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我剛剛和我妻子的家人通了電話......我不知道該怎麼稱呼他們。
他們......財富管理人？伯恩斯坦。聽起來他們是一家巨大的公司，對客戶的最低要求很高。
他們與我交談的唯一原因是我岳父的身份。
因爲我的岳父是誰。我想知道是否有一個...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvc66l/what_is_your_experience_with_bernstein/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/investing/comments/qvc66l/what_is_your_experience_with_bernstein/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:18:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just got off the phone with my wife&amp;#39;s family&amp;#39;s...I don&amp;#39;t know what to call them...Wealth management people? Bernstein. Sounds like they&amp;#39;re a huge firm with high minimums for clients, and the only reason they&amp;#39;re talking to me is because of who my father in law is. I&amp;#39;m wondering whether there&amp;#39;s an advantage to going with a group like this and what sort of benefit I&amp;#39;d see over SPY all the way. They told me in their sales pitch they determine asset allocation and they have great research blah blah etc, then have what sound like their own mini funds and at a higher level REITs available only to high net worth clients. No crypto exposure, no nft&amp;#39;s. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This all seems extremely old school and outdated. Am I missing something? They have my wife 30% bonds in her early 30&amp;#39;s, which seems...short sighted. They couldn&amp;#39;t give me a straight answer on how they do compared with a passive index fund&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[誰能給我解釋一下，爲什麼伯克希爾公司的市值仍然比裏維安公司大？]]></title><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460668037032562703</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/tweet/1460668037032562703</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 18:45:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[請告訴我，不要理會所有的噪音，堅持走下去。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想把錢投到特斯拉、加密貨幣或其他一些我的朋友們都很喜歡的熱門股票上。
我的朋友們都在大肆宣傳。請勸說我不要這樣做，並告訴我堅持到底。
並告訴我繼續投資於VTI。謝謝你的服務。]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvb5wx/please_tell_me_to_ignore_all_the_noise_and_stay/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvb5wx/please_tell_me_to_ignore_all_the_noise_and_stay/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 18:25:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to throw money into Tesla, crypto, or some of the other hot stocks all my friends are raving about. Please talk me out of this, and tell me to stay the course and just invest in VTI instead. Thank you for your service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[家得寶收益高於預期，因消費者修繕房屋，銷售量猛增9.8%。]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/16/home-depot-hd-q3-2021-earnings.html

每股收益。3.92美元，預期3.40美元

收入：368.2億美元，預期350.1億美元

家得寶第三季度的盈利和收入超過了華爾街的預期。
收入。

該季度的同店銷售攀升了6.1%，...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv7hil/home_depot_earnings_top_estimates_fueled_by_98/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/stocks/comments/qv7hil/home_depot_earnings_top_estimates_fueled_by_98/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 17:59:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/16/home-depot-hd-q3-2021-earnings.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/16/home-depot-hd-q3-2021-earnings.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earnings per share: $3.92 vs. $3.40 expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revenue: $36.82 billion vs. $35.01 billion expected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Home Depot topped Wall Street’s estimates for its third-quarter earnings and revenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Same-store sales climbed 6.1% in the quarter, beating StreetAccount estimates of 2.2%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consumers were spending more when they visited, raising the average ticket by 12.9% to $82.38.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Home Depot is one of the non tech stock that keep outperform. This is one of the portfolio must have stock due to the loyalty of the customers. Every time you visit there you will see a never ending long line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天達到了巨大的個人里程碑! 下一步是什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我已經正式達到我的個人儲蓄目標，即5萬現金。我今年29歲，爲了達到這個目標
爲了達到這個目標，我犧牲了很多，花了近十年時間才達到這個目標。

稅前和扣除前的工資是6萬。

學生貸款還剩2萬，2022年1月開始還款。

401(a)爲16,230 - Vanguard Target...]]></description><link>https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvbw93/big_personal_milestone_reached_today_what_next/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://stocks.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bogleheads/comments/qvbw93/big_personal_milestone_reached_today_what_next/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 17:47:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have officially reached my personal savings goal of 50k cash. I&amp;#39;m 29 and have sacrificed a lot to meet this goal, it&amp;#39;s taken me almost a decade to get here. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salary is 60k before taxes and deductions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;20k left on student loans, payments start up again Jan 2022. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;401(a) at 16,230 - Vanguard Target Retire 2055 11.1% Vanguard Target Retire 2060 88.9%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;457(b) at 8,340 - Vanguard Target Retire 2055 11.1% Vanguard Target Retire 2060 88.9%&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: I did not select these Target funds or allocations. It was selected automatically through my employers retirement servicer.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taxable Ally brokerage account worth: $642.52. Crypto account worth about: $600 ($400 btc). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personal note: my family is poor/working class so I pay the lion&amp;#39;s share of my family&amp;#39;s bills (mom and brother). Mom is overcoming cancer and will likely be out of work till 2022, had surgery to remove cancer and will be going through radiation sessions soon (hopefully no chemo). Fortunately (or unfortunately) she makes so little money that she&amp;#39;s always qualified for medicaid and all her treatments have been covered. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;#39;t crunched the numbers but I think all the bills (personal, communal, her personal) will likely run between 4-5k till February 2022... fingers crossed she can get back to work sooner. Brother makes about 30-35k but does not routinely contribute to communal bills, mom doesn&amp;#39;t force him and that&amp;#39;s just the way it is, it&amp;#39;s fruitless to argue about it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any advice on what my next move should be?  I feel like I stalk this sub enough to know the basics: open a Roth and split funds between an US index, international index, and bond right? I guess I need that echo chamber to confirm. I&amp;#39;m very much a serial saver. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to make this money work in my favor. Growing up in poverty I&amp;#39;ve gained a serious emergency mindset. I&amp;#39;m obsessed with preparing for the worst because bad news is the only consant. That&amp;#39;s how my family existed; constantly stressed about money, the next bill, and next big financial disaster etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry for the long post, ANY advice is GREATLY appreciated!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>